<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>GNews Health</title><link>https://news.google.com/</link><description></description><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>波士顿报告2例与流感相关的儿童死亡，使马萨诸塞州总数达到4例-波士顿环</title><link>https://www.bostonglobe.com/2026/01/06/metro/boston-flu-related-child-deaths/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="body | gutter_16--desktop gutter_16--tablet paywalled_content
              "&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;From Dec. 14-27, Boston saw a 126 percent increase in confirmed flu cases. During the same timeframe, hospitalizations tripled and flu-related emergency department visits increased by 135 percent, Boston public health officials said Tuesday.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Most of the people hospitalized are adults 65 and older. However, hospitalizations among children younger than 5 increased 150 percent in the last two weeks.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;“We are very concerned about the severity of illness that we’ve noted amongst children this season,” said Dr. Bisola Ojikutu, Boston’s commissioner of public health, at a Tuesday news conference.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Compared to last year, twice as many children were hospitalized for flu this year, Ojikutu said. This season’s hospitalizations for children younger than 5 have already exceeded last season’s peak hospitalizations.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;In total, 29 &lt;a href="https://www.mass.gov/info-details/influenza-reporting" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://www.mass.gov/info-details/influenza-reporting"&gt;adults&lt;/a&gt; have died from the flu this season, according to state data last updated Dec. 31.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;The Boston Public Health Commission urged parents to get their children older than six months vaccinated as soon as possible. The city also announced it was opening six additional vaccination clinics starting with one from 10 a.m. to noon Wednesday at City Hall. No appointments are needed, officials said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;“It is safe to vaccinate children as soon as they are eligible,” Ojikutu said. “The flu vaccine is safe, effective, and it saves lives.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;The vaccination rate among Boston residents is lagging behind the state — a 32.5 percent rate of vaccination in Boston compared to 34 percent statewide, she said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;“Vaccination rates for the flu are low, and this is a problem, and it’s something that we’re working on,” Ojikutu said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Ojikutu urged families not to listen to misinformation about the safety of vaccines.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;This year’s vaccine is potentially mismatched with the flu strain that is circulating most widely: a variant of influenza A H3N2, known as “subclade K.” But Ojikutu said the shot can still decrease the severity of illness and risk of hospitalization.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Ojikutu urged parents to watch for symptoms such as trouble breathing, persistent fever lasting for several days, extreme weakness or tiredness, confusion, or decreased urination. If they observe those symptoms, she advised parents bring their child into the emergency department for medical attention. Children 2 and younger, and those with underlying illnesses like asthma, lung disease, or obesity, are at a higher risk of complications from the flu.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;“Usually the flu presents as a mild illness in children,” Ojikutu said. “However, it can be very dangerous and severe as it was in these two cases.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;As of Dec. 27, nine pediatric flu-related deaths have been reported to the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention across the country. The CDC &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/fluview/surveillance/2025-week-52.html" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://www.cdc.gov/fluview/surveillance/2025-week-52.html"&gt;estimates&lt;/a&gt; there have been at least 5,000 deaths from flu this season nationwide, as well as at least 11,000,000 illness and 120,000 hospitalizations. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Last season, there were 470 flu-related deaths in Massachusetts, up from 251 during the 2023-2024 season, according to &lt;a href="https://www.mass.gov/doc/archived-influenza-dashboard-data-2024-2025/download" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://www.mass.gov/doc/archived-influenza-dashboard-data-2024-2025/download"&gt;DPH&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;In addition to getting vaccinated, avoiding congregated areas when sick and masking can help prevent the spread of flu, she said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Individuals at higher risk of complications, including people 2 and younger, and 65 and older, pregnant people, immunocompromised individuals and people with chronic illnesses should seek medical care if they develop flu-like symptoms or are exposed to a person with flu. Certain antiviral treatments can be prescribed to help prevent severe illness.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;On Monday, the federal Department of Health and Human Services dropped the number of vaccines it recommends for every child from 17 to 11.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;“There is no new data that was presented that led to the changes that that the federal administration and HHS made, or any of the decisions that they’ve made,” Ojikutu said. “This is political. It doesn’t feel responsible.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Ojikutu said parents should instead turn to organizations like the American Academy of Pediatrics or the Boston Public Health Commission for guidance.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr class="tagline_hr | border_foreground border_half gutter_20_28--mobile
               margin_none text_align_left width_100px"&gt;&lt;p class="tagline | font_primary inline_block  margin_top_32"&gt;Katie Muchnick can be reached at &lt;a href="mailto:katie.muchnick@globe.com" class="" target="_blank"&gt;katie.muchnick@globe.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Boston Globe</author><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 19:52:30 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigwFBVV95cUxQMU1tYmRPdVh0bEEzV2NRYmRQR3FVamJCNXdiUmZGTHNYb0xHX196aEw3bUtQa0hwbHB5cDUzREd1MlVHcm8zWGwzaWJjWV9FM3pXTFByT2hVWWREenBQTWtxQno2eFZ5VkVacFRsWjZBUVo3d3dpblU2dnNtM2t5TGxoQQ</guid></item><item><title>疾病预防控制中心顶级流行病学家表示，美国的流感活动可能持续数周- ABC新闻</title><link>https://abcnews.go.com/Health/flu-activity-us-continue-rise-weeks-top-cdc/story?id=128950754</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="xvlfx ZRifP TKoO eaKKC EcdEg bOdfO qXhdi NFNeu UyHES " data-testid="prism-article-body"&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao MvWXB TjIXL aGjvy ebVHC "&gt;Flu activity could continue to increase in the U.S. over the next few weeks, according to a top flu epidemiologist at the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;"There's a lot of influenza out there right now," Dr. Carrie Reed, chief of the epidemiology and prevention branch of the CDC's influenza division, told ABC News.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;"We often see activity continue into the spring ... I think the reality is that it's going to continue to be elevated for a little bit longer," she continued.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;The CDC's &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://www.cdc.gov/fluview/surveillance/2025-week-52.html" target="_blank" dir="ltr"&gt;latest estimates&lt;/a&gt; indicate that there have been at least 11 million illnesses, 120,000 hospitalizations and 5,000 deaths from flu so far this season.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;"That's likely a low estimate based on the data that we're seeing so far," Reed said, adding that the federal health agency typically publishes the lower range of the estimates. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;A new variant that first emerged in the summer, known as subclade K, has become the dominant strain, CDC data shows. Subclade K is a variant of the H3N2 virus, which is itself a subtype of influenza A.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Of the 994 flu samples tested since Sept. 30, nearly all were influenza A. Of those samples that underwent further testing roughly ​90% were H3N2, CDC data shows.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;"Subclade K has acquired some mutations in the virus that make it a little bit different than what's in the vaccine and what was circulating over the last couple years," Reed said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Public health experts currently recommend that everyone ages 6 months and older, with rare exceptions, get an annual flu vaccine.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Although the current flu vaccine is not a perfect match to subclade K, it is still expected to offer some protection against the new variant and lower the risk of serious disease, hospitalization and death.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Reed added that the new variant does not appear to be driving more severe illness yet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;"There are still benefits to vaccine, even if the virus [has] somewhat drifted from what's in the vaccine," she said. "We haven't seen increases in hospitalization and mortality yet in the ways that we have with [doctors' visits], although that's something that we continue to watch for as well."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;For those who have gotten sick, there are medicines available, known as antivirals, that may help reduce the severity and length of illness. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Reed said for those who contract the flu and have a higher risk of severe disease, they should seek care early and speak with their doctor about receiving a prescription for flu antivirals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;She explained that flu antivirals have been found to reduce the duration of illness as well as lower the risk for severe disease, hospitalization and death.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Health officials have stressed that it is not too late for people get a flu shot if they haven't received one yet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC eTIW sUzSN "&gt;"There's still time to get a flu vaccine," Reed said. "It does take a couple weeks for your immune response to pick up after vaccination, but that does mean there's many more weeks of flu activity to benefit from the protection of an influenza vaccine."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ABC News</author><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 18:09:05 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilwFBVV95cUxPd29QZWoza2dPWFl2ajFHQktQaHVDQ0xPRFdWUUFteTJHUVFfMEVKVWI5SXBnWmU1VXlwYU5VT0FkNFNaM29XRU0wSUJhMktvakJsX0RaZUFsNHRqU3JQUGZJRHhOVlh1S3hEY2NJaG9iRE84QzFkUTFJQ0hKZFl0OHVKY3gxMlVwS1BaSnl5UlNVMXRHTnV30gGcAUFVX3lxTE5pVmhCRWt3WWJwZ3V4emd4b1ByQi1jbkFjZDNBQjlUYV9lV0Q2c1hjNzlGdDlZOThSQ0Q3aHJILVJOVDhWblM5ZmhjYk12b3N6NWxrNFMycHFKVjlqYnBVYURGdm1jZTZaWVQ2d0hRMVd1NklHSXJvWUZfdnVKSzVYd1dKTm04TUVpVWxja0MydkpiSkkwalgxRjl0Yw</guid></item><item><title>我经常流鼻血。是什么原因导致的，它是否正常？ -《卫报》</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/wellness/2026/jan/06/nosebleeds-what-to-know</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body-commercial-selector article-body-viewer-selector dcr-hdpgoq"&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;If you frequently experience nosebleeds, you might come to regard them as nothing more than a messy inconvenience.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Yet, even though most nosebleeds are mild and benign, they shouldn’t happen “if everything inside the nose is healthy”, says Dr Patricia Loftus, an otolaryngologist at the University of California, San Francisco.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="sign-in-gate"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Here’s what experts say about nosebleeds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="what-is-a-nosebleed" class="dcr-n4qeq9"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What is a nosebleed?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;A nosebleed, known medically as epistaxis, comes in two forms: anterior and posterior.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;About 90% of nosebleeds are anterior, and start in the area between your two nostrils, called Kiesselbach’s plexus, says Loftus. This area contains a lot of blood vessels – little capillaries that keep the nostrils well supplied with blood, to warm the air you inhale. These can break open, creating a bleed that mostly pours from the nostril, though some blood may trickle into the mouth or throat, especially if you lean your head back.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="38f6c6ba-dc34-4082-a870-9e78838a62af" data-spacefinder-role="richLink" data-spacefinder-type="model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.RichLinkBlockElement" class="dcr-47fhrn"&gt;&lt;gu-island name="RichLinkComponent" priority="feature" deferuntil="idle" props='{"richLinkIndex":6,"element":{"_type":"model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.RichLinkBlockElement","prefix":"Related: ","text":"‘Let them’, creatine and fibermaxxing: the biggest wellness trends of 2025","elementId":"38f6c6ba-dc34-4082-a870-9e78838a62af","role":"richLink","url":"https://www.theguardian.com/wellness/2025/jul/31/creatine-fibermaxxing-biggest-wellness-trends"},"ajaxUrl":"https://api.nextgen.guardianapps.co.uk","format":{"design":10,"display":2,"theme":4}}'&gt;&lt;/gu-island&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Posterior nosebleeds are rarer and bigger. These are triggered when larger blood vessels deeper in the nasal passage burst. If there is significantly more blood flowing down the back of your throat, potentially causing you to choke, that’s a posterior nosebleed, explains Dr Amin Javer, an ENT surgeon and research director at the University of British Columbia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Posterior nosebleeds are more serious than anterior ones, and require prompt medical attention. They’re most often seen in older adults, especially those taking anticoagulants, which increase the risk of hemorrhage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="what-should-you-do-when-your-nose-is-bleeding" class="dcr-n4qeq9"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What should you do when your nose is bleeding?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;When a nosebleed starts, many people instinctively tip their head back.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“That’s the worst thing you could do,” says Javer. “You’re going to just start drinking the blood.” Blood in the stomach causes nausea, so it’s best to avoid this.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Instead, you should put your head forward and very gently pinch your nose, he says. A cold compress on the neck or nose can help constrict blood vessels and slow the bleed, as can a spritz of a nasal decongestant like oxymetazoline.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;If you see thick clots come out of your nose, it can be unsettling. But it’s not necessarily a bad sign, nor is it uncommon. “It’s actually just showing that your blood is clotting effectively,” says Dr Peter Manes, an ENT surgeon and residency director at Yale School of Medicine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;If your nosebleeds are occurring multiple times a week, interfering with your daily life, and/or lasting longer than &lt;a href="https://www.mayoclinic.org/first-aid/first-aid-nosebleeds/basics/art-20056683" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;30 minutes&lt;/a&gt;, they warrant seeing a doctor for a clinical evaluation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="what-causes-nosebleeds" class="dcr-n4qeq9"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What causes nosebleeds?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“One of the most common reasons for [anterior] nosebleeds is when the area dries out,” explains Loftus.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Dry air is especially to blame in winter. “It doesn’t matter how much rain there is outside – our heaters turn on, the humidity in our bedrooms goes down,” says Javer. He recommends cracking a window while you sleep or getting a humidifier to keep humidity levels between 40% and 50%. You can also moisturize your nasal lining with saline spray or a very thin layer of Vaseline just inside the nostrils.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Another common reason for nosebleeds is “digital manipulation, which is a nice way of saying nose picking or scratching your nose”, says Loftus. The nose is delicate, and even a light bump or scratch can pop a capillary and cause bleeding.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;aside data-spacefinder-role="inline" data-gu-name="pullquote" class="dcr-nyoej5"&gt;&lt;svg viewbox="0 0 22 14" class="dcr-scql1j"&gt;&lt;path d="M5.255 0h4.75c-.572 4.53-1.077 8.972-1.297 13.941H0C.792 9.104 2.44 4.53 5.255 0Zm11.061 0H21c-.506 4.53-1.077 8.972-1.297 13.941h-8.686c.902-4.837 2.485-9.411 5.3-13.941Z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;blockquote class="dcr-zzndwp"&gt;Ginseng, garlic, ginkgo – some of those herbal medications can thin your blood&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Inflammation from &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/wellness/2025/may/13/how-to-treat-manage-seasonal-allergies" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;allergies&lt;/a&gt; or viral infections can make the lining more fragile and prone to cracking. Physical exertion sometimes plays a role too. Exercises, especially those that combine effort with positions where your head dips below your heart, like downward dog pose, can increase pressure in the face and prompt a bleed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Medications and supplements add another layer of risk. Prescription blood thinners and aspirin make bleeding more likely, and some herbal supplements have similar effects. “Ginseng, garlic, ginkgo – some of those herbal medications can thin your blood,” says Manes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure data-spacefinder-role="inline" data-spacefinder-type="model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.NewsletterSignupBlockElement" class="dcr-173mewl"&gt;&lt;gu-island name="EmailSignUpWrapper" priority="feature" deferuntil="visible" props='{"index":22,"listId":6039,"identityName":"well-actually","description":"Practical advice, expert insights and answers to your questions about how to live a good life","name":"Well Actually","frequency":"Weekly","successDescription":"You are subscribed","theme":"lifestyle","idApiUrl":"https://idapi.theguardian.com","hideNewsletterSignupComponentForSubscribers":true}'&gt;&lt;/gu-island&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;h2 id="why-am-i-having-frequent-nosebleeds" class="dcr-n4qeq9"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why am I having frequent nosebleeds?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“If you’re having a nosebleed every day and you don’t know what’s causing it, you need evaluation,” says Loftus. “Even if it’s not bothering you that much, that’s alarming enough to come see a doctor.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Manes agrees that nosebleeds can become “normalized”, and easy to dismiss as minor, but they do occasionally signal more serious issues.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Abundant nosebleeds can indicate that your blood is not clotting correctly, Loftus says. A doctor may ask about alcohol use or other factors to discern if a liver issue is involved.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Hormonal changes in pregnancy can play a role. Loftus says pregnancy-induced surges in hormones like estrogen and progesterone are linked to a higher likelihood of lobular capillary hemangioma, a “usually pretty small lesion in the nose” that can cause nosebleeds. These growths are not inherently dangerous, but should be evaluated by a doctor.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;If you’re in your 20s and suddenly having frequent, heavy nosebleeds, you could be among the roughly one in 5,000 people with “hereditary hemorrhagic telangectasia” (HHT), a genetic vascular abnormality that often presents in young adulthood and requires treatment. Without medical attention, patients with HHT may “succumb to death from nosebleed,” says Javer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;gu-island name="InteractiveBlockComponent" priority="critical" deferuntil="idle" props='{"url":"https://interactive.guim.co.uk/uploader/embed/2023/10/archive-zip/giv-13425WMrLo2pc9VIk/","scriptUrl":"https://interactive.guim.co.uk/embed/iframe-wrapper/0.1/boot.js","alt":"Graphic with three lines of text that say, in bold, ‘Well Actually’, then ‘Read more on living a good life in a complex world,’ then a pinkish-lavender pill-shaped button with white letters that say ‘More from this section’ ","format":{"design":10,"display":2,"theme":4},"elementId":"8123c371-b43f-4f74-b9b7-7faefc0f5289","isMainMedia":false}'&gt;&lt;figure id="8123c371-b43f-4f74-b9b7-7faefc0f5289" class="element element-interactive element--inline element-inline dcr-w422y2" data-alt="Graphic with three lines of text that say, in bold, ‘Well Actually’, then ‘Read more on living a good life in a complex world,’ then a pinkish-lavender pill-shaped button with white letters that say ‘More from this section’ " data-testid="interactive-element-Graphic%20with%20three%20lines%20of%20text%20that%20say,%20in%20bold,%20%E2%80%98Well%20Actually%E2%80%99,%20then%20%E2%80%98Read%20more%20on%20living%20a%20good%20life%20in%20a%20complex%20world,%E2%80%99%20then%20a%20pinkish-lavender%20pill-shaped%20button%20with%20white%20letters%20that%20say%20%E2%80%98More%20from%20this%20section%E2%80%99%C2%A0" data-spacefinder-role="inline"&gt;&lt;a data-name="placeholder" href="https://interactive.guim.co.uk/uploader/embed/2023/10/archive-zip/giv-13425WMrLo2pc9VIk/" class="dcr-1eupayo"&gt;Graphic with three lines of text that say, in bold, ‘Well Actually’, then ‘Read more on living a good life in a complex world,’ then a pinkish-lavender pill-shaped button with white letters that say ‘More from this section’ &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/gu-island&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Frequent unilateral nosebleeds – bleeding from only one nostril – are a significant red flag for doctors. That pattern can signal a tumor or polyp, especially if accompanied by symptoms on the same side of the face, like not being able to breathe through the nose; facial pain or pressure; or unilateral ear pain, numbness or vision changes, says Loftus. “That should get checked out,” she says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="how-do-doctors-treat-a-nosebleed" class="dcr-n4qeq9"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How do doctors treat a nosebleed?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Many nosebleeds can be taken care of at home. But if you have persistent, frequent or high-volume nosebleeds that disrupt your daily life, or if you think you’re having a posterior bleed, seek medical attention.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;If you arrive in the emergency room or a doctor’s office with an active nosebleed, there are a few things you can expect.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;First is “a thorough examination of your nasal cavity, trying to identify a source of the bleed,” says Manes. Most bleeds can be controlled with packing – the insertion of a nasal tampon (which is different to the menstrual product).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;A doctor may cauterize the area that is bleeding, says Manes. The procedure stings, but a numbing cream can ease the pain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;You may have your vitals checked and blood drawn to look for issues such as anemia or clotting abnormalities. If symptoms suggest a mass in the sinuses, a CT scan or MRI may be recommended. And if you’ve lost a significant amount of blood, you could require a transfusion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Guardian</author><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:02:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMifEFVX3lxTFA0N2xKdE9XSkhSS3B5RGdKMVgzVDB2MUFhLVJpREFDM2lFclBJZmdOMWtjcC02ZXotVFVEQ0JxVTJOZnBNRFVrTW9sLXRVTXNPUU9lT2NlNTRlaW5FWkY3WXRqampHbGJZREFaZEF1TzE0TllobTdDRlIwVGg</guid></item><item><title>富兰克林县的后院羊群禽流感检测呈阳性- WRAL</title><link>https://www.wral.com/news/local/avian-flu-franklin-county-january-2026/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body"&gt;
					&lt;p id="font-resize" class="font-resize-container"&gt;
						&lt;button id="small-font-button"&gt;
							&lt;svg aria-hidden="true" focusable="false" data-prefix="fas" data-icon="text-height" class="fa-text-height fa-w-18 svg-inline--fa small-buttom-font-svg" role="img" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 576 512"&gt;
								&lt;use href="#i-text-height"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;
							&lt;/svg&gt;
						&lt;/button&gt;
						&lt;button id="medium-font-button"&gt;
							&lt;svg aria-hidden="true" focusable="false" data-prefix="fas" data-icon="text-height" class="fa-text-height fa-w-18 svg-inline--fa" role="img" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 576 512"&gt;
								&lt;use href="#i-text-height"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;
							&lt;/svg&gt;
						&lt;/button&gt;
						&lt;button id="large-font-button"&gt;
							&lt;svg aria-hidden="true" focusable="false" data-prefix="fas" data-icon="text-height" class="fa-text-height fa-w-18 svg-inline--fa" role="img" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 576 512"&gt;
								&lt;use href="#i-text-height"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;
							&lt;/svg&gt;
						&lt;/button&gt;
						
					&lt;/p&gt;

					
						&lt;p&gt;The state reports a case of bird flu has been discovered in Franklin County.&lt;/p&gt;
						
							
							
							
						
					
						&lt;p&gt;The North Carolina Department of Agriculture &amp;amp; Consumer Services said a 'backyard flock' tested positive for High Path Avian Influenza (HPAI) in a release distributed on Tuesday. The strain of virus is considered low-risk, according to the U.S. Centers for Disease Control. The virus is considered highly contagious to other birds.&lt;/p&gt;
						
							
								
							
							
							
						
					
						&lt;p&gt;A backyard flock generally refers to animals not intended for commercial use.&lt;/p&gt;
						
							
							
							
						
					
						&lt;p&gt;The development is the first confirmed positive case in Franklin County and the ninth confirmed positive case in North Carolina since Oct. 1, 2025.&lt;/p&gt;
						
							
							
							
						
					
						&lt;p&gt;“HPAI has been found in wild birds throughout the state so
reports of positive backyard flocks will likely happen on occasion,” said state veterinarian Dr.
Mike Martin. “I encourage our commercial and backyard flock
owners to continue to follow strict biosecurity measures and if your flock is
experiencing a sudden higher-than-normal mortality rate, report it right away
to your local veterinarian or to the NCDA&amp;amp;CS’ Veterinary Division at
919-707-3250.” &lt;/p&gt;
						
							
							
							
						
					
						&lt;p&gt;A list of domestic bird cases of HPAI is &lt;a href="https://www.ncagr.gov/divisions/veterinary/AvianInfluenza"&gt;available online&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
						
							
							
							
						
					
					
				&lt;/div&gt;


				&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>WRAL</author><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 16:18:56 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMie0FVX3lxTE9tVlI5eXVmWkpDNFhaX1BqbjF6WkR0MnJvSlFSSHZkbmdGUTlmUXhTM1pkYjlKMzZkU3drUnVydzFkZ1RIa3N4MEl5RWVQOWZxbXBIby1zRjRiOTRVUEZPa1ZKMXNNaXlpd0xJaHNmWVVhMVVUcm5XTy1Eaw</guid></item><item><title>消除关于女性健康的9个误区-《纽约时报》</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2026/01/06/well/womens-health-myths.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The New York Times</author><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 16:00:04 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMickFVX3lxTE9QMThDVGlpajF3ck96RzQ3bHlzLXl0T2xucTVPRGx3TU5oUzRfd2hIeVN1Zy05MDBkOTYzcFFTQzZweFRYOUVqUFRpaUtQVm1Qc3BfZkFVNVhMRktNcnljYmhiS0o0VVU1RGRtVmNjTzl3QQ</guid></item><item><title>随着医生就诊达到1997年以来的最高水平，美国各地的流感激增- CBS新闻</title><link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/flu-season-cases-rise-cdc-data-doctors-visits/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article id="article-0" data-index="0" data-path="/news/flu-season-cases-rise-cdc-data-doctors-visits/" class="content content-article lazyload"&gt;
  
      &lt;span class="content__observer-marker content__observer-marker--fixed lazyload"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    
        

&lt;p class="content__promo-image-wrapper" data-sort-time="1767716942000" data-update-time="1767716942000"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="content__high-wrapper content__high-wrapper--is-show" id="article-header" data-sort-time="1767716942000" data-update-time="1767716942000"&gt;
    
  &lt;/p&gt;


  &lt;section class="content__body"&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Flu cases are continuing to spike in the United States. New data from the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention show that at least 5,000 people have died of the illness this year and that doctor's visits for flu have reached their highest level in decades. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The CDC estimated there have been at least 11 million flu cases &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/fluview/surveillance/2025-week-52.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"&gt;as of December 27&lt;/a&gt;, as well as at least 120,000 hospitalizations and 5,000 deaths. There have been nine flu-related pediatric deaths, the CDC said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At the same time, 8.2% of outpatient doctor's visits nationwide were for flu-like illnesses, the CDC said. That's the highest level recorded since 1997, &lt;a href="https://gis.cdc.gov/grasp/fluview/fluportaldashboard.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"&gt;according to CDC data&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Forty-eight jurisdictions are showing "high" or "very high" levels of flu, the agency said. Last week, 32 jurisdictions met that description. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Only four jurisdictions had low or minimal flu levels. Nevada has "insufficient data," the CDC said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="embed embed--type-image is-image embed--float-none embed--size-medium"&gt;
    
                                    
      &lt;span class="img embed__content"&gt;&lt;img src="https://assets1.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2026/01/06/fa045b20-96c7-40c3-91d9-6c98315b5c2d/thumbnail/620x347/afa07d7dc1eed4a46be3c733b118a3d1/screenshot-2026-01-06-at-9-49-40-am.png#" alt="screenshot-2026-01-06-at-9-49-40-am.png " class=" lazyload" srcset="https://assets1.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2026/01/06/fa045b20-96c7-40c3-91d9-6c98315b5c2d/thumbnail/620x347/afa07d7dc1eed4a46be3c733b118a3d1/screenshot-2026-01-06-at-9-49-40-am.png 1x" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;

      
          &lt;figcaption class="embed__caption-container"&gt;
        
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__caption"&gt;A CDC map uses the proportion of outpatient visits to health care providers for influenza-like illnesses that include a fever plus a cough or sore throat to measure flu activity levels in the jurisdiction.&lt;/span&gt;
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__credit"&gt;
            
                Centers for Disease Control and Prevention

                          &lt;/span&gt;
              &lt;/figcaption&gt;
      &lt;/figure&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;A new subtype of influenza A called H3N2 is spreading quickly and fueling this year's cases, &lt;span class="link"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/news/flu-season-2025-experts-pretty-worried/" target="_blank" data-invalid-url-rewritten-http=""&gt;experts told CBS News&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;. The CDC reported that of the 994 influenza viruses that tested positive for flu between Dec. 20 and Dec. 27, 971 of them had influenza A. When 600 of those specimens were subtyped, 91.2% of them were found to be H3N2. The strain is known to cause tough flu seasons, especially for seniors, and is harder for the immune system to recognize. &lt;/p&gt;

    
    &lt;p id="mpu-plus-outstream-middle" data-ad="mpu-plus-outstream-middle" class="ad-mpu-plus-outstream-middle ad-wrapper " data-ad-unit='"mpu-plus-outstream-middle"'&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At the same time, fewer people have received the flu vaccine. The CDC estimated that about 130 million doses of the flu vaccine had been given this year. On Monday, the CDC announced updates to its &lt;span class="link"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/news/cdc-announces-new-childhood-vaccine-recommendations/" target="_blank" data-invalid-url-rewritten-http=""&gt;recommended childhood vaccine schedule&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;. The changes included saying that children who are not high-risk should engage in "shared clinical decision-making" with their doctor about whether to get the flu vaccine. The American Academy of Pediatrics called the changes "dangerous" and said they would continue to share their own recommendations. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Making these changes amid ongoing outbreaks of vaccine-preventable diseases shows a disregard for the real confusion families already face," said Dr. Ronald G. Nahass, president of the Infectious Diseases Society of America, in a statement. &lt;/p&gt;

    

                  
        
    
  
          
  
  



  
    
    
  &lt;/section&gt;

  

  
    
&lt;/article&gt;
            

                                                                                            &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>CBS News</author><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 15:22:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigAFBVV95cUxPSUw1TjBHa1RSaFFld08xMnlQSTFjSXFVbldhMFdGVUZ2el9iYzV5QmdTYU02a3BFVnQ0M04xM0hhaE1UQVF5RXU4YU54YlFod2x5Yjg1LUhSU245ejVjS2N1UDBGSlRBVjJCeVNqOWFxOGs1MTQ4UFJvZHI5Y1c3dtIBhgFBVV95cUxNN2tsdkswQXJNZERXRTN6enNjMXhsazFxbzBYU0NtdHJqWnNKUG85cy1Hd0NYQWY1ZkNrU2xNcmNQSGdjTWxrNURPbTBrclFiRVhycjFZNUFlN3VOa2FfUERLd1MxbXhLQ25tcG9UQWU2OUphVnAydlNvcDlFVjk1N3hDcmxkUQ</guid></item><item><title>密歇根州流感激增：该州在疾病预防控制中心规模上达到最差水平- MLive.com</title><link>https://www.mlive.com/news/2026/01/flu-surge-in-michigan-state-reaches-worst-tier-on-cdc-scale.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content   "&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="H26XK7IMLBC43ONZEENKNVM33I"&gt;Influenza is surging in Michigan and throughout the country.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-1" data-gaid="inarticle-1"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="ZICCX6I7SFBZRKTCAVBX54CSZA"&gt;The state’s level of flu-like illness activity for the week ending Dec. 27 earned it “very high” status, or the worst tier of the 13-level assessment reported weekly by the U.S. Centers for Disease Control and Prevention (CDC). &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-2" data-gaid="inarticle-2"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="CSM3LWATJVCE7CJ5DLNUWBVGS4"&gt;Eighteen states earned the top activity level at the end of 2025 while 11 others fell into the second or third levels, including Ohio, Indiana, Missouri and Minnesota in the Midwest. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-3" data-gaid="inarticle-3"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="QFYZ4LY4YVH2JAK6T6CBAXFZIE"&gt;“We’ve been seeing quite a bit of viral illness,” said Dr. Jason Vieder, an emergency department physician and vice chairman of emergency medicine for Henry Ford Health. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-4" data-gaid="inarticle-4"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="L37BLK7NGRD5VLFAEXKX64LKJI"&gt;Vieder noted “record-setting” days around Christmas in terms of patients seen throughout the system. Sick visitors weren’t limited to any particular demographics, though there were plenty of children, he recalled. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-5" data-gaid="inarticle-5"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="ACAO6RZCDJF2HLT7WAOC4SH2FA"&gt;Last year’s flu season was &lt;a href="https://www.mlive.com/public-interest/2025/03/flu-season-has-michigan-kids-sicker-with-many-many-needing-ventilation.html" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://www.mlive.com/public-interest/2025/03/flu-season-has-michigan-kids-sicker-with-many-many-needing-ventilation.html"&gt;among the worst&lt;/a&gt; in the last 15 years, highlighted by high hospitalization rates and the most pediatric flu deaths in a season since at least 2004. Trends from other countries around the globe suggested a &lt;a href="https://www.mlive.com/news/2025/12/michigans-flu-season-could-start-early-and-be-more-intense.html" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://www.mlive.com/news/2025/12/michigans-flu-season-could-start-early-and-be-more-intense.html"&gt;potentially early and more intense&lt;/a&gt; 2025-26 flu season as well. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-6" data-gaid="inarticle-6"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="Q7ZXITHGBVGZ3EQAUAWVQLXWHY"&gt;Those projections have begun to take shape. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-7" data-gaid="inarticle-7"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="PKAOTWPWTNBWZP33KDTM6G5MJQ"&gt;About 11.3% of Michigan’s outpatient health care visits in late December were for influenza-like illness. That outpaced the national average (8.2%) and was an increase from 4.4% and 7.5% the two weeks prior. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-8" data-gaid="inarticle-8"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="U3NSUJHIYNHZ7KRPREVEWOQ3PA"&gt;Test positivity is another key measurement health officials track during cold and flu season. At Henry Ford Health, positivity exceeded 25% for the past three weeks, including a peak of 33% for the week ending Dec. 27. For context, the system’s positivity rate peaked at 31.7% last year, and almost 16.5% during the 2023-24 flu season. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-9" data-gaid="inarticle-9"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="3VC7BE7ZYBHLFJH36Q6KOGDYZI"&gt;“Last week went down a little but it’s still pretty robust in terms of flu activity and people feeling ill in general,” Vieder said. “We’re going to see folks not feeling well for a while still.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-10" class="middleParagraph" data-gaid="inarticle-10"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="LF3AYCKGGZHIHBMUGLJ5IQ4LWE"&gt;Elsewhere around the state, Corewell Health noted week-over-week increases across all of its regions, including a more rapid increase in southeast Michigan. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-11" data-gaid="inarticle-11"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="OWOB6TM6IRCUTHV4TPPSORFKFI"&gt;Nationally, hospital admissions are on a steep upward trajectory, led by adults age 65 and older and children younger than 5. Influenza A accounts for about 97% of hospitalizations, with the majority of sampled specimens being of the H3N2 subtype, according to the CDC. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-12" data-gaid="inarticle-12"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="6QHZCU3WCFATFOJ7ZWRCYDWKKI"&gt;Federal officials estimate the current flu season has caused at least 11 million illnesses, 120,000 hospitalizations, and 5,000 deaths, including nine children. No pediatric flu deaths have been reported yet in Michigan. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-13" data-gaid="inarticle-13"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="3XNUDICVFFB7RLKIIYGDKIRCAY"&gt;Beyond the flu, Michigan hospitals have noted lesser increases in COVID-19, RSV and other seasonal viruses. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-14" data-gaid="inarticle-14"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="NGGYHKOWZZGETAZLYN73B46IHI"&gt;Most of the state’s large health systems hadn’t yet implemented any visitor restrictions as of Monday, though they’re monitoring flu activity and may limit visitors down the road. Detroit Medical Center was an exception; officials said they proactively updated their visitation guidelines Dec. 8 to limit patients to two visitors at a time and turn away visitors younger than 13. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-15" data-gaid="inarticle-15"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="A2TOCEHRVRE3FFPWH4BVG42AVA"&gt;While emergency rooms are seeing more patients with respiratory illnesses, hospital representatives said their capacity remains stable. Doctors encourage residents to get a flu shot if they haven’t already, and to be more cautious. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-16" data-gaid="inarticle-16"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="U4IFKNXB3RB2BHCBCKZSZZFSAU"&gt;“We really need to be vigilant about handwashing,” Vieder said. “Cough or sneeze into your sleeve, not your closed hand. And we encourage you to stay home or keep your kids home if they don’t feel good.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-17" data-gaid="inarticle-17"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="G5WGLRTO4BBTXKRZA2YYUN67II"&gt;As of Dec. 27, about 24% of Michiganders had received this year’s flu shot and 8.3% had received the latest COVID-19 booster. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-18" data-gaid="inarticle-18"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-enter:YD3VSZSNJFBK5JCBXBEHYRZ3UY" data-fusion-component="YD3VSZSNJFBK5JCBXBEHYRZ3UY"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-exit:YD3VSZSNJFBK5JCBXBEHYRZ3UY" data-fusion-component="YD3VSZSNJFBK5JCBXBEHYRZ3UY"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-19" data-gaid="inarticle-19"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>MLive.com</author><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 15:01:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMioAFBVV95cUxOZVJhUHBQaFVpRnZTeEM4ZVI1Rlkyc2ZlMjVQaFFOWkZwTjU0SlYwV2xRY2RIWlcxSGRVM2JDUjgxQ0ZmMjM1ajd3ZzdMSW8wRlJlNUhIS3ozWmlJbTFtVjYzd3NuNWNBd0Z4Znh6UnM4Rkg4Y1ZwQ0NFVWRoY1dSTGI2THBRQjhOQ3o2Nkx2U2p6SXl6V3l2RHRSSjgzSUk20gG0AUFVX3lxTE1QMEVNVnF2Sm16dkczX3FuZU83eUdPTmdoQVd5ZWItVTBoZUoya1k2YjMtbnNHSmxLZ3BzWTctbDZwck1iS1d3UC1SaVB2QTNkckxDZmNwSzRlQzJxaXgybWJTZ1c5MF95V2Y2WWJ2T3lSVTh3a2pGaWZuN1Y2STVhOTktNlNlcFZnWFpvTi1DT1V2Y1plbGhPMExyVUZxcjdnMXVVdTJXVHBYUUZ3dXNMMlBBZw</guid></item><item><title>随着感染的增加，美国建立了保持麻疹消除状态的案例-路透社</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/legal/litigation/us-builds-case-retain-measles-elimination-status-infections-mount-2026-01-06/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Reuters</author><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 14:37:28 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiugFBVV95cUxNdjFmUGMzYXVURVMxOGQzWTNiZU1wdkRzWGFxQk9SbjhzMm1pM1h3M2tDc3dxNlJES0g4a0R6S0RnbnhJenh1T0phOF9vamJmZFdFU3otMl9BYk0td1NKNk1vQjQ4ei1BdGEyX19OcTRpakltRmd1cjB3bjBiVHlGbXRXNjAzUTRRaWpXS1o5d0xSS2x5NG9XOGxTM2l1aUFjQUp4eDNzVXNYeUxjVDdBOWVsa1dxNG5vUUE</guid></item><item><title>阿灵顿的流感病例激增，促使人们呼吁接种更多疫苗- ARLnow</title><link>https://www.arlnow.com/2026/01/06/flu-cases-jump-in-arlington-prompting-calls-for-more-vaccinations/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content pt-6 px-4 content-post"&gt;
		&lt;p&gt;As flu cases surge in Arlington, health leaders are encouraging residents to get vaccinated and practice healthy habits.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hospitalizations for the flu surged by more than 50% in Arlington during the last week of 2025, according to Arlington Public Health. About 14% of all patients visiting emergency departments and urgent care clinics were diagnosed with the virus.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“While last year was one of the worst flu seasons we had seen in many years, this year may surpass it,” Taryn Overman, VHC Health’s associate chief nursing officer, told ARLnow.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Emergency department visits for the flu are trending up &lt;a href="https://www.vdh.virginia.gov/epidemiology/respiratory-diseases-in-virginia/data/#Weekly-Summary"&gt;across Virginia&lt;/a&gt;, making up 9.8% of all visits as of the last week of December. Meanwhile, almost a quarter of all emergency visits statewide — 24.3% — were for respiratory illnesses, a 6.1-point increase from the previous week.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By age group, the largest proportion of patients were from 0-4 years old and 5-17 years old.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Arlington Public Health offered the following advice to help prevent the spread of illness.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Get vaccinated:&lt;/b&gt; It’s not too late to get your flu shot. Arlington Public Health strongly recommends flu vaccination to reduce illness and hospitalization. COVID-19 vaccination is also advised, and both vaccines can be given at the same time. Vaccines are widely available through primary care providers and local pharmacies such as CVS and Walgreens. To find a location, visit &lt;a href="http://vaccinefinder.org/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=http://vaccinefinder.org&amp;amp;source=gmail&amp;amp;ust=1767733207566000&amp;amp;usg=AOvVaw3ENXxveCSPmr_hX5MJXPRo"&gt;vaccinefinder.org&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Practice good hygiene:&lt;/b&gt; Wash your hands often or use hand sanitizer to kill germs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Stay home if you’re sick:&lt;/b&gt; This helps prevent spreading illness to others.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Consider wearing a mask:&lt;/b&gt; Masks provide an added layer of protection against respiratory viruses.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Additionally, Overman advised members of the public to support a healthy immune system by staying hydrated, getting plenty of sleep, eating a balanced diet, exercising regularly and managing stress.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It is recommended that you stay home until you are fever-free for at least 24 hours,” she said. “If you must be around others, wearing a mask can help prevent the spread of flu.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;During the last full week of 2025, seven Arlington residents visited emergency rooms for Covid and 12 were hospitalized for RSV, according to the county’s &lt;a href="https://www.arlingtonva.us/Government/Programs/Health/Respiratory-Illness/Data"&gt;respiratory illness dashboard&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.vdh.virginia.gov/epidemiology/respiratory-diseases-in-virginia/data/vaccines/"&gt;About 17.3%&lt;/a&gt; of Arlington’s population has received the 2025-26 Covid vaccine, significantly above the statewide average of 9.2%.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Statewide, Covid-19 and RSV cases are relatively stable, making up 0.7% and 0.6% of all emergency department visits, respectively.&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;
				&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ARLnow</author><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 14:15:45 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiogFBVV95cUxOaVkyQ19kVldmUWxUMnIxdEdvSHAyZEM4cF9jOWZ4YU1CZlJWYm5EbHJzTnUtNzRWRDhMVFVwZUpCUi1DcXBjc1JoWXdCNzhvZWVkdFFLeHpacGRCV3VLYkFFc2pXMXFHRmhhOFpBM2RBakVDelY2SzMwMVRiY1dneHBXTXNxM1A0UlM1aHNhT05oTmFDajMtV2xDYWdpdWlydEE</guid></item><item><title>健身专家说，这就是在行走时锻炼肌肉的方法-预防</title><link>https://www.prevention.com/fitness/fitness-tips/a69921141/how-does-walking-build-muscle/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div data-journey-body="standard-article" class="article-body-content article-body standard-body-content css-n3hm4j et2g3wt7"&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="1" class="css-6wxqfj emevuu60"&gt;&lt;br data-node-id="1.0"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="2" class="body-dropcap css-1k0tyz7 emevuu60"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.prevention.com/health/a63024078/walking-adds-11-years-to-life-study/" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.prevention.com/health/a63024078/walking-adds-11-years-to-life-study/" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="Walking" data-node-id="2.0" class="body-link css-inlxvj emevuu60"&gt;Walking&lt;/a&gt; is a powerful form of exercise that offers numerous benefits, many of which help promote &lt;a href="https://www.prevention.com/food-nutrition/a69854690/quality-carbohydrates-health-aging-longevity-study/" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.prevention.com/food-nutrition/a69854690/quality-carbohydrates-health-aging-longevity-study/" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="healthy aging" data-node-id="2.2" class="body-link css-inlxvj emevuu60"&gt;healthy aging&lt;/a&gt;. But while &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC8926180/" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC8926180/" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="studies have shown" data-node-id="2.4" class="body-link css-inlxvj emevuu60"&gt;studies have shown&lt;/a&gt; that walking can help build bone to improve bone density, building muscle via a simple stroll is not quite as effortless. Fortunately, there are plenty of ways to walk to build muscle that can make walking an effective part of your &lt;a href="https://www.prevention.com/fitness/workouts/g69656476/strength-training-exercises-women-over-50/" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.prevention.com/fitness/workouts/g69656476/strength-training-exercises-women-over-50/" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="strength-training regimen" data-node-id="2.6" class="body-link css-inlxvj emevuu60"&gt;strength-training regimen&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="3" class="body-tip css-txvov emevuu60"&gt;Meet the Experts: Justin Kraft, C.P.T., founder and trainer at &lt;a href="https://www.aspire2morefitness.com/about-me" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.aspire2morefitness.com/about-me" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="Aspire 2 More Fitness" data-node-id="3.1" class="body-link css-inlxvj emevuu60"&gt;Aspire 2 More Fitness&lt;/a&gt;, Cara D’Orazio, C.P.T., group fitness instructor and owner of &lt;a href="https://cgmfit.com/" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://cgmfit.com/" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="C.G.M. Fitness" data-node-id="3.3" class="body-link css-inlxvj emevuu60"&gt;C.G.M. Fitness&lt;/a&gt;, and Joy Puleo, N.P.C.P., A.C.S.M., director of education at &lt;a href="https://www.pilates.com/" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.pilates.com/" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="Balanced Body" data-node-id="3.5" class="body-link css-inlxvj emevuu60"&gt;Balanced Body&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="4" class="css-6wxqfj emevuu60"&gt;Here, personal trainers and fitness experts explain how to build muscle through walking, plus the small adjustments you can make to your strolls that may help you get stronger even faster.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;section data-node-id="6" data-lazy-id="P0-15"&gt;&lt;h2 title="How walking supports muscle-building" data-anchor-id="how-walking-supports-muscle-building" class="body-h2 css-ne8qws emt9r7s1"&gt;How walking supports muscle-building&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="7" class="css-6wxqfj emevuu60"&gt;Muscle growth isn’t just about lifting weights, explained Justin Kraft, C.P.T., founder and trainer at &lt;a href="https://www.aspire2morefitness.com/about-me" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.aspire2morefitness.com/about-me" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="Aspire 2 More Fitness" data-node-id="7.1" class="body-link css-inlxvj emevuu60"&gt;Aspire 2 More Fitness&lt;/a&gt;. “It has three major contributors: strength training, proper nutrition, and recovery,” he continued. “Strength training stimulates muscles, causing micro-tears that your body repairs, making them stronger. Nutrition fuels the process with adequate protein, carbs, and healthy fats that ensure optimal muscle development. Rest is where growth happens—neglecting recovery can stall progress.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="8" class="css-6wxqfj emevuu60"&gt;How does walking fit into that process? “When we walk, we engage multiple muscle groups simultaneously, which can help improve muscle endurance and strength,” said Cara D’Orazio, C.P.T., group fitness instructor and owner of &lt;a href="https://cgmfit.com/" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://cgmfit.com/" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="C.G.M. Fitness" data-node-id="8.1" class="body-link css-inlxvj emevuu60"&gt;C.G.M. Fitness&lt;/a&gt;. “While walking alone may not be enough to build significant muscle mass, it can certainly contribute to overall muscle development. The key is to incorporate walking into a comprehensive exercise routine that includes strength training and other forms of physical activity.” Kraft said it’s also ideal for injury recovery and weight management.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;section data-node-id="9" data-lazy-id="P0-16"&gt;&lt;h2 title="What muscles are working when you walk?" data-anchor-id="what-muscles-are-working-when-you-walk" class="body-h2 css-ne8qws emt9r7s1"&gt;What muscles are working when you walk?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="10" class="css-6wxqfj emevuu60"&gt;Walking activates multiple muscle groups with a primary focus on legs, glutes, and core, Kraft said. Over time, that engagement enriches stability, posture, and overall mobility, he added. The more specific heavy hitter muscles walking engages, according to D’Orazio, are: &lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-node-id="11" class="css-kw9lqy emevuu60"&gt;&lt;li data-node-id="11.0"&gt;&lt;strong data-node-id="11.0.0"&gt;Quadriceps: &lt;/strong&gt;These muscles in the front of the thigh help straighten the knee and extend the leg.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-node-id="11.1"&gt;&lt;strong data-node-id="11.1.0"&gt;Hamstrings: &lt;/strong&gt;The hamstring muscles in the back of the thigh help bend the knee and flex the leg.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-node-id="11.2"&gt;&lt;strong data-node-id="11.2.0"&gt;Glutes:&lt;/strong&gt; The gluteal muscles in the buttocks help extend the hip and stabilize the pelvis.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-node-id="11.3"&gt;&lt;strong data-node-id="11.3.0"&gt;Calves:&lt;/strong&gt; The calf muscles in the lower leg help flex the foot and stabilize the ankle.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;section data-node-id="12" data-lazy-id="P0-17"&gt;&lt;h2 title="Ways to boost your walks to build muscle" data-anchor-id="ways-to-boost-your-walks-to-build-muscle" class="body-h2 css-ne8qws emt9r7s1"&gt;Ways to boost your walks to build muscle&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="13" class="css-6wxqfj emevuu60"&gt;There are lots of ways to enhance your walks with strength training. It’s all about incorporating resistance and variety. Below, D’Orazio and Joy Puleo, N.P.C.P., A.C.S.M., director of education at &lt;a href="https://www.pilates.com/" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.pilates.com/" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="Balanced Body" data-node-id="13.1" class="body-link css-inlxvj emevuu60"&gt;Balanced Body&lt;/a&gt;, suggest adding one or two of the following variations to each of your walks to increase the challenge for your muscles.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-node-id="14" class="css-kw9lqy emevuu60"&gt;&lt;li data-node-id="14.0"&gt;&lt;strong data-node-id="14.0.0"&gt;Intervals:&lt;/strong&gt; Vary your speed by walking at a relaxed pace followed by short, faster paced intervals. This will challenge your cardio threshold and increase general cardiovascular health—plus, &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC10565117/" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC10565117/" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="studies show" data-node-id="14.0.2" class="body-link css-inlxvj emevuu60"&gt;studies show&lt;/a&gt; that interval training may also help build muscle mass. Even adding short intervals of light jogging will do the trick. As little as 20 to 30 seconds for every two minutes of walking can reap excellent results. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-node-id="14.1"&gt;&lt;strong data-node-id="14.1.0"&gt;Incline/Decline:&lt;/strong&gt; Walking inclines, declines, and generally uneven terrain (safely!) will increase challenge, engage new muscles, and elevate your heart rate. “Incline walking and decline walking will also challenge different muscle groups, creating strength and the development of power,” Puleo added. “Walking stairs is another way to add inclines and declines to your routine.”&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-node-id="14.2"&gt;&lt;strong data-node-id="14.2.0"&gt;Fitness moments:&lt;/strong&gt; Throwing in squats, lunges, or other fitness-based calisthenics are a great way to mix up your walking routine, Puleo said. “For every 15 minutes of walking, stop, do a set of 10 to 15 squats and/or lunges, then continue,” she suggested. “Adding some lower body fitness moments will go a long way in developing strength while you also increase your cardio capacity.”&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-node-id="14.3"&gt;&lt;strong data-node-id="14.3.0"&gt;Use weights or resistance bands: &lt;/strong&gt;“Wearing a weighted vest or using resistance bands can help increase the resistance and challenge your muscles,” D’Orazio said.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-node-id="14.4"&gt;&lt;strong data-node-id="14.4.0"&gt;Focus on proper form and technique:&lt;/strong&gt; Maintaining proper form and technique can help ensure that you’re targeting the correct muscle groups, plus reducing your risk of injury.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="15" class="css-6wxqfj emevuu60"&gt;It’s important to remember that while walking is a wonderful exercise, if you have goals of significant muscle building, you’ll want to walk, strength train, and eat nutritiously. Below, D’Orazio shared an example workout for muscle building that includes walking.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ol data-node-id="16" class="css-kw9lqy emevuu60"&gt;&lt;li data-node-id="16.0"&gt;&lt;strong data-node-id="16.0.0"&gt;Do a dynamic warm-up:&lt;/strong&gt; Begin with a five to 10 minute walk, jog, or jumping jacks to prepare your muscles for exercise.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-node-id="16.1"&gt;&lt;strong data-node-id="16.1.0"&gt;Incorporate strength-training exercises:&lt;/strong&gt; Do squats, lunges, and/or leg presses to target specific muscles and build overall muscle strength.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-node-id="16.2"&gt;&lt;strong data-node-id="16.2.0"&gt;Add high-intensity interval training (HIIT)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong data-node-id="16.2.1"&gt;:&lt;/strong&gt; Try some fast-paced, challenging bursts, such as sprint intervals or burpees, to improve cardiovascular endurance and increase muscle strength.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-node-id="16.3"&gt;&lt;strong data-node-id="16.3.0"&gt;Finish with a static cool-down:&lt;/strong&gt; Finish your workout with a five to 10 minute static cool-down such as stretching or foam rolling to help your muscles recover and reduce your risk of injury.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;section data-node-id="17" data-lazy-id="P0-18"&gt;&lt;h2 title="Other health benefits of walking" data-anchor-id="other-health-benefits-of-walking" class="body-h2 css-ne8qws emt9r7s1"&gt;Other health benefits of walking&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="18" class="css-6wxqfj emevuu60"&gt;In addition to the fitness perks mentioned above, our experts said walking is associated with &lt;a href="https://www.prevention.com/fitness/a20485587/benefits-from-walking-every-day/" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.prevention.com/fitness/a20485587/benefits-from-walking-every-day/" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="tons of other benefits" data-node-id="18.1" class="body-link css-inlxvj emevuu60"&gt;tons of other benefits&lt;/a&gt; for your overall health and wellness, including:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-node-id="19" class="css-kw9lqy emevuu60"&gt;&lt;li data-node-id="19.0"&gt;Increased bone density and reduced osteoporosis risk&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-node-id="19.1"&gt;Breath regulation &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-node-id="19.2"&gt;Decreased anxiety and depression&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-node-id="19.3"&gt;Greater longevity&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-node-id="19.4"&gt;Diabetes management&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-node-id="19.5"&gt;Lower blood pressure&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-node-id="19.6"&gt;Improved circulation  &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-node-id="19.7"&gt;Weight management&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-node-id="19.8"&gt;Reduced chronic disease risk &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p data-ad-exclude="true" id="journey-inline" class="css-ciejky e1ye6jr30"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Prevention</author><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 13:30:21 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikgFBVV95cUxPaDhJWlZUM1Jkb0o5RG1TNVNwYTVTZWQ3d0ZwSHBEajNmV1haSlRvVUlzZFFrbm1lS2ZnMXZyTEJELWZ5SGlyZURpUDRWU0YybWV4SUxmOWNBTnNiak5pMEd1T3JXVTBhYS1teVpOZVgybXMyN1hLYUtVQW1sa1k3S2hQa0F3LWZHQTFmQWpSQ1Z3dw</guid></item><item><title>专栏|礼仪小姐：一月婴儿的哀悼-《华盛顿邮报》</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/advice/2026/01/06/miss-manners-unfair-january-birthday/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="T4NFZGV4XFE2JJ2SWBV3SPXM5I" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dear Miss Manners:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i&gt; My birthday is a few days after the new year. It’s a very easy date to miss altogether in the shadow of December and New Year’s celebrations. Growing up, I often received “combo” holiday and birthday presents. I was taught to thank relatives and friends and not complain that it “wasn’t fair.”&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijwFBVV95cUxQdmZjNVFDYkp6ZU45am9VdDR3Rnl3MjVubFpXTXdqSEJVV1ZvM0ptSXkyTml2eUF6ZTNlaEFQWWItSnpGQW9vOGRJTXJVMnFGS0U5VVNOc0h6VnJFNWh1MngyT3Nud3VZdm9ZRVpjYmY2VlU5aW1Dbms0UkxTMVVENEdMeElOTnl5VEVsdnFvTQ</guid></item><item><title>被忽视的蔬菜，实际上是世界上最有营养的蔬菜-外卖</title><link>https://www.thetakeout.com/2064979/most-nutritious-vegetable-overlooked-watercress/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="content" class="article"&gt;
            

            &lt;article class="news-post"&gt;
    
    
    
                &lt;p class="news-article"&gt;
                &lt;h1 class="title-gallery" data-post-id="2064979" id="title-gallery" data-has-pixel-tags="1" data-pixel-tag="thetakeout" data-author="Haley McNamara" data-category="ingredients" data-content_type="Short Article" data-mod_date="2026-01-06" data-layout="Infinite" data-post_id="2064979" data-pub_date="2026-01-06" data-day="Tuesday" data-dayhour="Tuesday-8AM" data-pubhour="8AM" data-num_slides="2" data-num_words="500" data-pitcher="Shawna Schofield" data-trello_board="News" data-intent="evergreen" data-ideation="oo-hits"&gt;The Overlooked Vegetable That's Actually The Most Nutritious In The World&lt;/h1&gt;
            &lt;/p&gt;

    
                &lt;div class="news-article"&gt;
                
                                
                                &lt;div class="slide-key image-holder gallery-image-holder credit-image-wrap lead-image-holder" data-post-url="https://www.thetakeout.com/2064979/most-nutritious-vegetable-overlooked-watercress/" data-post-title="The Overlooked Vegetable That's Actually The Most Nutritious In The World" data-slide-num="0" data-post-id="2064979"&gt;
                                             &lt;picture id="p2c2aa4ca0a7159b92ea2d34fab3c4ea9"&gt;
                                                    &lt;source media="(min-width: 429px)" srcset="https://www.thetakeout.com/img/gallery/the-overlooked-vegetable-thats-actually-the-most-nutritious-in-the-world/intro-1764610674.webp" type="image/webp"&gt;
                            &lt;source media="(max-width: 428px)" srcset="https://www.thetakeout.com/img/gallery/the-overlooked-vegetable-thats-actually-the-most-nutritious-in-the-world/intro-1764610674.sm.webp" type="image/webp"&gt;
                        &lt;img class="gallery-image " src="https://www.thetakeout.com/img/gallery/the-overlooked-vegetable-thats-actually-the-most-nutritious-in-the-world/intro-1764610674.jpg" data-slide-url="https://www.thetakeout.com/2064979/most-nutritious-vegetable-overlooked-watercress/" data-post-id="2064979" data-slide-num="0" data-slide-title="The Overlooked Vegetable That's Actually The Most Nutritious In The World: " alt="Angled shot of groceries in produce section"&gt;
                    &lt;/source&gt;&lt;/source&gt;&lt;/picture&gt;
                    &lt;span class="gallery-image-credit"&gt;Alvarez/Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;
                    &lt;/div&gt;
				            &lt;div class="columns-holder "&gt;
                
                
                &lt;p&gt;What if the healthiest vegetable on the planet isn't kale, spinach, or &lt;a href="https://www.thetakeout.com/broccoli-is-america-s-favorite-vegetable-1847101896/" target="_blank"&gt;broccoli (America's favorite vegetable)&lt;/a&gt;, but something you've probably walked past in the grocery store without a second glance? It's tiny, peppery, and misused and abused as garnish — it's watercress! Most people aren't familiar with watercress — maybe because for some absurd reason grocery stores tend to stock it in obscure places or because it never got the same PR push as kale or cauliflower. Unfortunately, watercress is barely making headlines six years after it topped the &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/pcd/issues/2014/13_0390.htm" target="_blank"&gt;Centers for Disease Control and Prevention's list of Powerhouse Fruits and Vegetables&lt;/a&gt;, with a perfect nutrient density score of 100.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While many fruits and vegetables are known for their nutrients, the CDC used a stricter standard in the study. To qualify as a "powerhouse" food, an item had to deliver at least 10% of the daily value of 17 key nutrients per 100 calories. The nutrient amounts were pulled from USDA data measured per 100 grams of raw food, then converted into nutrients per calorie to determine the score (now that's some pretty particular criteria!). Those 17 nutrients were chosen for their public health importance: potassium, protein, calcium, iron, thiamin, riboflavin, niacin, and vitamin A, plus nutrients linked to chronic-disease protection, including fiber, folate, zinc, and vitamins B6, B12, C, D, E, and K.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Although watercress may not have the vitamin A of sweet potatoes, the potassium of beet greens, or the protein of Brussels sprouts, what makes it special is that it still delivers at least 10% of every qualifying nutrient — all while staying vastly below 100 calories.&lt;/p&gt;

            &lt;/div&gt;
            &lt;/div&gt;

            &lt;div class="news-article"&gt;
                
                &lt;h2 class=""&gt;Watercress is full of nutrients&lt;/h2&gt;
                                &lt;div class="slide-key image-holder gallery-image-holder credit-image-wrap " data-post-url="https://www.thetakeout.com/2064979/most-nutritious-vegetable-overlooked-watercress/" data-post-title="The Overlooked Vegetable That's Actually The Most Nutritious In The World" data-slide-num="1" data-post-id="2064979"&gt;
                                             &lt;picture id="p927437e4e87f7ecb86635dc338fe8c4f"&gt;
                                                    &lt;source media="(min-width: 429px)" srcset="https://www.thetakeout.com/img/gallery/the-overlooked-vegetable-thats-actually-the-most-nutritious-in-the-world/from-garnish-to-bodyguard-1764610678.webp" type="image/webp"&gt;
                            &lt;source media="(max-width: 428px)" srcset="https://www.thetakeout.com/img/gallery/the-overlooked-vegetable-thats-actually-the-most-nutritious-in-the-world/from-garnish-to-bodyguard-1764610678.sm.webp" type="image/webp"&gt;
                        &lt;img class="gallery-image " src="https://www.thetakeout.com/img/gallery/the-overlooked-vegetable-thats-actually-the-most-nutritious-in-the-world/from-garnish-to-bodyguard-1764610678.jpg" data-slide-url="https://www.thetakeout.com/2064979/most-nutritious-vegetable-overlooked-watercress/" data-post-id="2064979" data-slide-num="1" data-slide-title="The Overlooked Vegetable That's Actually The Most Nutritious In The World: Watercress is full of nutrients" alt="A bunch of watercress sitting on a round wooden cutting board with handle"&gt;
                    &lt;/source&gt;&lt;/source&gt;&lt;/picture&gt;
                    &lt;span class="gallery-image-credit"&gt;Bhofack2/Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;
                    &lt;/div&gt;
				            &lt;div class="columns-holder "&gt;
                &lt;p&gt;Watercress is also one of the richest sources of phytochemicals — natural compounds found in plant foods that not only give them their color, but also help protect the body from inflammation and cell damage linked to chronic illnesses, especially cancer. When watercress is cut or chewed, it releases compounds called isothiocyanates, which help neutralize carcinogens and stop tumors from spreading. Studies show the isothiocyanates in watercress may help prevent colon cancer as well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some phytochemicals within watercress contain a high amount of antioxidants called carotenoids, which protect cardiovascular health and reduce the risk of a heart attack and stroke. Watercress also contains dietary nitrates — plant compounds known to improve blood flow, support healthy blood vessels, reduce blood pressure, and may even enhance athletic performance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And the list of benefits goes on. Next time you're at the grocery store, add watercress to your cart — and if you can't find it, ask a grocer where it's hiding. Watercress is most nutrient-dense when it's raw since many of its vitamins are heat-sensitive, so you'll want to add it as a peppery bite to salads, replace &lt;a href="https://www.thetakeout.com/1880682/salad-green-iceberg-lettuce-lack-nutrients/" target="_blank"&gt;the classic greens that are lacking in the nutrient department&lt;/a&gt; on cold sandwiches, top on eggs and roasted meats, or blend into pesto, green goddess dressing, or even &lt;a href="https://www.thetakeout.com/1897648/easy-green-sauce-pasta-blender/" target="_blank"&gt;a quick green pasta sauce&lt;/a&gt;. Your body — and your taste buds — will thank you.&lt;/p&gt;

            &lt;/div&gt;
            &lt;/div&gt;

    
&lt;/article&gt;                        
            
                            
                           &lt;p id="div-ad-1x1a" class="google-ad-placeholder clear placeholder placeholder-1-1" data-ad-height="any" data-ad-width="any" data-ad-pos="1x1"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

        &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Takeout</author><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiwFBVV95cUxNYzNKRVFZTDk2R19veEtoX1ZWQ3FUT1M2VDJFQUZlRE4zSHJmU0JNdjBhcHlUYVVtQUZvTGxDT2x5ZVd0bVdEN3BTMWNsUlNlOHgxZ1JXSnY3bGNQWWFDOTJ0d1hmcUZUNGNtdW9JVzNHcnBaVFJveUVRaUtkbjhndTc4alJGZmxHTkM0</guid></item><item><title>夫妇在核磁共振扫描机中发生性行为，以揭示性行为中身体发生了什么- UNILAD Tech</title><link>https://www.uniladtech.com/news/tech-news/couple-intercourse-mri-machine-what-happens-to-your-body-554743-20260106</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;header class="article-header_header__gD613"&gt;&lt;div class="article-header_meta__N4zeN"&gt;&lt;p class="article-timestamps_times__qZyED"&gt;&lt;time datetime="2026-01-06T10:58:33.621Z" class="article-timestamps_time__KUAGt"&gt;Published 10:58 6 Jan 2026 GMT&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h1 class="article-header_heading__7ivKD"&gt;Couple had sex in MRI scan machine to reveal what happens to your body during sex&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;h2 class="summary_summary__q_VAA"&gt;We hope they took our their piercings&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/header&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>UNILAD Tech</author><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 12:59:42 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMitAFBVV95cUxPVzJSdW93NzM0QzNSaDhCRW12WG1GTGt3dlRIWjFVb0hFRWdRcHlZQWJzb0Npa0Rnc2lnLUxXeU5xOW5jbndZZWRWeDAzNzJHNGlnLXpoTGFETmk1OUd0SnBzTklYODRqaEJTVnl0MkxVdnVPMklVQ1REeWw1NVhCeXpVV0RKVEJoRDhDdGxBTmk2bVNGT1lpUlNTdUU1b2VnVTNvZDFvTFNXRnMzSXBTWFVieFA</guid></item><item><title>疫苗对老年人的帮助比我们想象的要大-《西雅图时报》</title><link>https://www.seattletimes.com/nation-world/vaccines-are-helping-older-people-more-than-we-knew/</link><description>&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMimgFBVV95cUxNUkpiRlJBS2l3MzJHNGU1ZTB6MkZxblcxS21XekJGU1U5QjVReVc2RlBEZmFpdFFha0tWdFY1TDE0NHVBeHdseXhfTzBBN2xjZnFJTXdRZUdYc0l6Wkp2bUtXN0lmdFZQSFN1X01HOGROUFp1enRpeWR2SThYQkF4UFZDSTZsWW0wRE5Db1JTcHpVSkVkaHVySlRB?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;Vaccines are helping older people more than we knew&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Seattle Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/stories/CAAqNggKIjBDQklTSGpvSmMzUnZjbmt0TXpZd1NoRUtEd2lQb1ltbkVCRWZxMG85Y0twaEhpZ0FQAQ?hl=en-US&amp;amp;gl=US&amp;amp;ceid=US:en&amp;amp;oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;View Full Coverage on Google News&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;</description><author>The Seattle Times</author><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 12:38:02 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimgFBVV95cUxNUkpiRlJBS2l3MzJHNGU1ZTB6MkZxblcxS21XekJGU1U5QjVReVc2RlBEZmFpdFFha0tWdFY1TDE0NHVBeHdseXhfTzBBN2xjZnFJTXdRZUdYc0l6Wkp2bUtXN0lmdFZQSFN1X01HOGROUFp1enRpeWR2SThYQkF4UFZDSTZsWW0wRE5Db1JTcHpVSkVkaHVySlRB</guid></item><item><title>医生警告高传染性疾病在美国蔓延-预防</title><link>https://www.prevention.com/health/health-conditions/a69918178/measles-spreading-exposure-protection/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div data-journey-body="standard-article" class="article-body-content article-body standard-body-content css-n3hm4j et2g3wt7"&gt;&lt;ul data-node-id="0" class="css-kw9lqy emevuu60"&gt;&lt;li data-node-id="0.0"&gt;&lt;em data-node-id="0.0.0"&gt;Measles cases are spreading across the country.&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-node-id="0.1"&gt;&lt;em data-node-id="0.1.0"&gt;Doctors share what to do if you’ve been exposed to the virus. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-node-id="0.2"&gt;&lt;em data-node-id="0.2.0"&gt;Plus, what infectious disease doctors want you to know about the disease.&lt;br data-node-id="0.2.0.1"&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;hr data-node-id="1" class="css-18pb4rg emevuu60"&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="2" class="css-6wxqfj emevuu60"&gt;Public health officials in &lt;a href="https://www.nj.gov/health/news/2025/approved/20251226a.shtml" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.nj.gov/health/news/2025/approved/20251226a.shtml" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="New Jersey" data-node-id="2.1" class="body-link css-inlxvj emevuu60"&gt;New Jersey&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.mass.gov/news/state-public-health-officials-alert-residents-about-potential-exposure-to-measles-in-multiple-locations-0" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.mass.gov/news/state-public-health-officials-alert-residents-about-potential-exposure-to-measles-in-multiple-locations-0" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="Massachusetts" data-node-id="2.3" class="body-link css-inlxvj emevuu60"&gt;Massachusetts&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href="https://cdphe.colorado.gov/press-release/health-officials-alert-public-of-potential-measles-exposure-at-denver-international-0" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://cdphe.colorado.gov/press-release/health-officials-alert-public-of-potential-measles-exposure-at-denver-international-0" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="Colorado" data-node-id="2.5" class="body-link css-inlxvj emevuu60"&gt;Colorado&lt;/a&gt; have recently sent out warnings of travelers infected with measles passing through busy airports and other areas. Couple that with measles’ ability to spread rapidly, and it’s understandable to have concerns about the disease. &lt;br data-node-id="2.7"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="3" class="css-6wxqfj emevuu60"&gt;“Measles is extraordinarily infectious—if you’re susceptible,” says &lt;a href="https://medicine.buffalo.edu/faculty/profile.html?ubit=trusso" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://medicine.buffalo.edu/faculty/profile.html?ubit=trusso" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="Thomas Russo, M.D.," data-node-id="3.1" class="body-link css-inlxvj emevuu60"&gt;Thomas Russo, M.D.,&lt;/a&gt; a professor and chief of infectious diseases at the University at Buffalo in New York.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="4" class="css-6wxqfj emevuu60"&gt;Each year, a small number of measles cases pop up in select areas around the country. But the past 12 months have been different. Nearly 2,100 people across 44 states were impacted by measles in 2025, according to data shared by the &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/measles/data-research/index.html" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.cdc.gov/measles/data-research/index.html" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="Centers for Disease Control and Prevention" data-node-id="4.1" class="body-link css-inlxvj emevuu60"&gt;Centers for Disease Control and Prevention&lt;/a&gt; (CDC). That’s the highest number of cases in &lt;a href="https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jama/article-abstract/2837030" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jama/article-abstract/2837030" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="25 years" data-node-id="4.3" class="body-link css-inlxvj emevuu60"&gt;25 years&lt;/a&gt;. Unfortunately, cases continue to surface.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="6" class="body-tip css-txvov emevuu60"&gt;&lt;strong data-node-id="6.0"&gt;Meet the experts&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;a href="http://medicine.buffalo.edu/content/medicine/faculty/profile.html?ubit=jsellick" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="http://medicine.buffalo.edu/content/medicine/faculty/profile.html?ubit=jsellick" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="John Sellick, D.O." data-node-id="6.2" class="body-link css-inlxvj emevuu60"&gt;John Sellick, D.O.&lt;/a&gt;, an infectious disease expert and professor of medicine at the State University of New York at Buffalo; &lt;a href="https://www.jhsph.edu/faculty/directory/profile/3528/amesh-adalja" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.jhsph.edu/faculty/directory/profile/3528/amesh-adalja" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="Amesh A. Adalja, M.D." data-node-id="6.4" class="body-link css-inlxvj emevuu60"&gt;Amesh A. Adalja, M.D.&lt;/a&gt;, an infectious disease expert and senior scholar at the Johns Hopkins Center for Health Security; &lt;a href="https://medicine.buffalo.edu/faculty/profile.html?ubit=trusso" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://medicine.buffalo.edu/faculty/profile.html?ubit=trusso" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="Thomas Russo, M.D.," data-node-id="6.6" class="body-link css-inlxvj emevuu60"&gt;Thomas Russo, M.D.,&lt;/a&gt; a professor and chief of infectious diseases at the University at Buffalo in New York.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="7" class="css-6wxqfj emevuu60"&gt;These warnings about exposures keep coming, making it fair to wonder what this means for you. Here, infectious disease doctors break down some of the most pressing questions people have about measles, plus what to do if you are exposed. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="why-is-measles-so-contagious" data-node-id="8" class="body-h2 css-ne8qws emevuu60"&gt;&lt;strong data-node-id="8.0"&gt;Why is measles so contagious?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="9" class="css-6wxqfj emevuu60"&gt;While there are outbreaks across the country each year, most people aren’t overly familiar with measles. Also known as rubeola, measles is a highly contagious respiratory virus, according to the &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/measles/about/index.html" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.cdc.gov/measles/about/index.html" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="CDC" data-node-id="9.1" class="body-link css-inlxvj emevuu60"&gt;CDC&lt;/a&gt;. It may cause symptoms like a cough, runny nose, red and watery eyes, high fever, and spots inside the mouth. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="10" class="css-6wxqfj emevuu60"&gt;But measles may also cause serious health complications, including pneumonia and encephalitis (inflammation in the brain), per the CDC. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="11" class="css-6wxqfj emevuu60"&gt;Measles is considered one of the most contagious diseases in the world, according to the &lt;a href="https://www.who.int/news-room/fact-sheets/detail/measles" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-node-id="11.1" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.who.int/news-room/fact-sheets/detail/measles" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="World Health Organization" class="body-link css-inlxvj emevuu60"&gt;World Health Organization&lt;/a&gt; (WHO). The virus can stay active and contagious in the air or on infected surfaces for up to two hours. The WHO also notes that one person who is infected with measles may infect up to 18 other people. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="12" class="css-6wxqfj emevuu60"&gt;The virus spreads when an infected person coughs or sneezes, Dr. Russo explains. From there, people breathe in infectious particles or touch surfaces that those particles land on and then touch their eyes, nose, or mouth, which may lead to infection.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="13" class="css-6wxqfj emevuu60"&gt;The infectious period with measles is long—people who are infected may spread the virus to others four days before they develop the classic measles rash and four days after it appears, per the WHO. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="the-vaccine-is-very-effective-at-preventing-measles" data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="14" class="body-h2 css-1udqo6z emevuu60"&gt;&lt;strong data-node-id="14.0"&gt;How can I prevent getting measles?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="15" class="css-6wxqfj emevuu60"&gt;There is a vaccine to prevent measles, called the measles, mumps, and rubella (MMR) vaccine. It’s part of the childhood vaccination series and is given in two doses. One dose is 93% effective at preventing measles, while two doses is 97% effective, per the &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/measles/vaccines/index.html" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.cdc.gov/measles/vaccines/index.html" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="CDC" data-node-id="15.1" class="body-link css-inlxvj emevuu60"&gt;CDC&lt;/a&gt;. (Despite new changes to the CDC's childhood vaccination schedule, the MMR vaccine is &lt;a href="https://www.hhs.gov/press-room/cdc-acts-presidential-memorandum-update-childhood-immunization-schedule.html" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.hhs.gov/press-room/cdc-acts-presidential-memorandum-update-childhood-immunization-schedule.html" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="still recommended" data-node-id="15.3" class="body-link css-inlxvj emevuu60"&gt;still recommended&lt;/a&gt; for all children.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="16" class="css-6wxqfj emevuu60"&gt;The first dose is usually given between 12 and 15 months, and the second dose is given between ages four and six, or whenever children start school, according to the &lt;a href="https://www.aap.org/en/patient-care/measles/measles-vaccine/" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-node-id="16.1" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.aap.org/en/patient-care/measles/measles-vaccine/" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="American Academy of Pediatrics" class="body-link css-inlxvj emevuu60"&gt;American Academy of Pediatrics&lt;/a&gt; (AAP). It’s still possible to get the MMR vaccine as an adult or beyond that age range, but the doses need to be spread out by 28 days, per the AAP. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="17" class="css-6wxqfj emevuu60"&gt;The MMR vaccine is a live attenuated vaccine, which means that it contains a weakened form of the measles virus, explains &lt;a href="http://medicine.buffalo.edu/content/medicine/faculty/profile.html?ubit=jsellick" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="http://medicine.buffalo.edu/content/medicine/faculty/profile.html?ubit=jsellick" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="John Sellick, D.O." data-node-id="17.1" class="body-link css-inlxvj emevuu60"&gt;John Sellick, D.O.&lt;/a&gt;, an infectious disease expert and professor of medicine at the State University of New York at Buffalo. That trains the immune system to react if you’re exposed to measles down the road. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="18" class="css-6wxqfj emevuu60"&gt;“The vaccine is not perfect, but it’s really pretty good,” Dr. Russo says. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="19" class="css-6wxqfj emevuu60"&gt;&lt;em data-node-id="19.0"&gt;(Just be aware that people born between 1963 and 1967 received a measles vaccine during childhood that isn’t considered effective, according to the CDC. If this describes you, the CDC &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/vaccines/vpd/mmr/hcp/recommendations.html" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.cdc.gov/vaccines/vpd/mmr/hcp/recommendations.html" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="recommends" data-node-id="19.0.1" class="body-link css-inlxvj emevuu60"&gt;recommends&lt;/a&gt; getting vaccinated again.)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="20" class="css-6wxqfj emevuu60"&gt;Ultimately, you &lt;a href="https://www.prevention.com/health/a64016549/can-you-get-measles-if-you-are-vaccinated/" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.prevention.com/health/a64016549/can-you-get-measles-if-you-are-vaccinated/" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="can get measles if you’re fully vaccinated" data-node-id="20.1" class="body-link css-inlxvj emevuu60"&gt;can get measles if you’re fully vaccinated&lt;/a&gt;, but it’s unlikely. (Again, the vaccine is 97% effective, so &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/measles/about/questions.html" target="_blank" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.cdc.gov/measles/about/questions.html%23:~:text%3DVery%2520few%2520people%25E2%2580%2594about%25203,or%2520have%2520weakened%2520immune%2520systems.&amp;amp;source=gmail&amp;amp;ust=1767734909627000&amp;amp;usg=AOvVaw3oqc3TQbEQFAVHSKFWgInP" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.cdc.gov/measles/about/questions.html" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="three out of 100 vaccinated people" data-node-id="20.3" class="body-link css-inlxvj emevuu60"&gt;three out of 100 vaccinated people&lt;/a&gt; may get it.) “There were a few individuals who received a shot in the most recent measles outbreak and got infected,” Dr. Russo says. “But if you have some protection, you’re less likely to get severe disease as well.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="what-to-do-if-youve-been-exposed-to-measles" data-node-id="21" class="body-h2 css-ne8qws emevuu60"&gt;&lt;strong data-node-id="21.0"&gt;What to do if you’ve been exposed to measles&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="22" class="css-6wxqfj emevuu60"&gt;If you discover that you crossed paths with someone who has measles, don’t panic. If you were born before 1957, doctors consider you to have “&lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/measles/about/questions.html" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.cdc.gov/measles/about/questions.html" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="presumptive immunity" data-node-id="22.1" class="body-link css-inlxvj emevuu60"&gt;presumptive immunity&lt;/a&gt;,” which means that you were likely exposed to the virus as a child and therefore should have immunity to it, Dr. Russo says. “If you have presumptive immunity or if you’ve been vaccinated, you don’t have to worry about a measles exposure,” he says. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="23" class="css-6wxqfj emevuu60"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.jhsph.edu/faculty/directory/profile/3528/amesh-adalja" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.jhsph.edu/faculty/directory/profile/3528/amesh-adalja" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="Amesh A. Adalja, M.D." data-node-id="23.0" class="body-link css-inlxvj emevuu60"&gt;Amesh A. Adalja, M.D.&lt;/a&gt;, an infectious disease expert and senior scholar at the Johns Hopkins Center for Health Security, agrees. “There is no action to take,” he says. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="24" class="css-6wxqfj emevuu60"&gt;If you were born after 1957 and you haven’t been vaccinated or are partially vaccinated, you still have options. While there is no treatment for measles, you can get vaccinated after an exposure or receive an injection of antibodies called immune serum globulin to help provide protection against severe disease, Dr. Adalja says. (The immune serum globulin treatment is the only option for pregnant women, infants, and people who are immunocompromised because the vaccine is a live virus and not recommended for those groups, Dr. Russo explains.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="25" class="css-6wxqfj emevuu60"&gt;But if you know you’ve been exposed and you’re not sure if you have immunity, “the safest thing is to get vaccinated,” Dr. Russo says. Dr. Sellick agrees. “It’s safe to get another dose, even if you were fully vaccinated or already immune to the virus,” he says. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="what-to-do-if-you-get-measles" data-node-id="26" class="body-h2 css-ne8qws emevuu60"&gt;What to do if you get measles&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="27" class="css-6wxqfj emevuu60"&gt;If you develop symptoms of measles, call your doctor (don’t go into the office—you’ll risk exposing others). Again, there is no treatment for measles, but your doctor may suggest immune serum globulin and supportive care, like acetaminophen for fever and plenty of fluids, along with monitoring yourself for serious complications of the virus. Ultimately, it’s best to contact a healthcare provider. They can provide the next steps from there. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-ad-exclude="true" id="journey-inline" class="css-ciejky e1ye6jr30"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Prevention</author><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 12:34:37 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiogFBVV95cUxOUDRpUzVWMV9rTlBHU0d0LWxWeU1kMHJhTnZDX0E4aGtON0xmVWYydEJoTEt5YXJ0SjdaUU9ZN1N0TzI1RUpmbTA5Tk1pZmZTa1Q5RGVfQ0ZHZ1N4TTZnR1FTWmdURkt5NF90bzdpNXZ1Z00yZUsxUVI4SWpyaExwUGh6eEFXM3BqVjlTQm9qbWlWTDJsUEhBbV90OFVpQzNub2c</guid></item><item><title>如果您因为走上楼梯而被缠住，这意味着什么- HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffpost.com/entry/winded-walking-up-stairs-normal-health_l_695bd707e4b0c1bd90c46bc7</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;section class="entry__content-list js-entry-content js-cet-subunit"&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you’ve ascended a flight or two of stairs, you likely know the feeling of being out of breath once you reach the top.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s a common occurrence among folks of all ages and fitness abilities. But is it something to worry about?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Experts told HuffPost there are a few points to keep in mind when it comes to this phenomenon. While it can be normal, it can also be cause for concern or even a fitness challenge to try and improve. Here’s what to know:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;It &lt;em&gt;can&lt;/em&gt; be perfectly normal — going up stairs is harder on your body than walking on a flat surface.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Feeling out of breath after walking up a flight of stairs is “what we call a normal physiological response,” said &lt;a href="https://uoflhealth.org/provider/katherine-pohlgeers/" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Dr. Katherine Pohlgeers" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="695bd707e4b0c1bd90c46bc7" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://uoflhealth.org/provider/katherine-pohlgeers/" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="0"&gt;Dr. Katherine Pohlgeers&lt;/a&gt;, a family medicine and sports medicine doctor at University of Louisville Health. “Because you’ve got this increased demand on your body, you’ve got increased work — you’ve got increased oxygen demand and ventilatory requirements.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you’re winded for a minute or so but can easily catch your breath, it’s no cause for concern, said &lt;a href="https://sportsmedicine.mayoclinic.org/expert/karl-erickson/" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Karl Erickson" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="695bd707e4b0c1bd90c46bc7" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://sportsmedicine.mayoclinic.org/expert/karl-erickson/" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="1"&gt;Karl Erickson&lt;/a&gt;, a performance specialist at Mayo Clinic Sports Medicine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“It’s quite normal ... you’re essentially lifting your body. You’re doing a squat or a lunge when you go up the stairs,” said Erickson, “so, definitely more effortful than just walking.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Just how winded you are will vary; you’ll be more out of breath if you run up the stairs or walk up with a heavy suitcase than if you leisurely walked up the stairs. Some folks may not even notice the breathlessness as much as others.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“If you’ve got an elite athlete ― like, I doubt Caitlin Clark gets winded going up a flight of stairs ― but for the average middle-aged person, and, unfortunately, especially here in the United States, we tend to live a little bit more sedentary lifestyle, so it can be very normal to get winded just going up one flight of stairs,” Pohlgeers said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;If it’s a new change or you’re noticing prolonged breathlessness, you should let your doctor know.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;While it can be perfectly normal to feel winded after climbing the stairs, there are a few red flags that may signal a concern. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Is your breathlessness a new issue that’s never happened before? Or is it getting worse? If the answer to either of those questions is yes, you should talk to a doctor about potential underlying issues, according to Pohlgeers. “The biggest thing is for people not to necessarily think, ‘Oh, my gosh, I’m dying,’ but also, don’t always just simply dismiss it as, ‘Well, I’m out of shape.’”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Those are things that we really take seriously,” Pohlgeers added. “If there is a change in the exercise capacity, just making sure that we as doctors are able to do our due diligence and rule out any underlying conditions, so that we can maximize people’s lifestyles and help them be as healthy as they possibly can.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Underlying conditions such as heart failure, obesity, chronic lung disease, being a smoker, COPD and even being &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/entry/iron-deficiency-anemia-fatigue-brain-fog_l_68b1a883e4b07a70c7bc5b14" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-internal-link" data-vars-item-name="anemic" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="695bd707e4b0c1bd90c46bc7" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="68b1a883e4b07a70c7bc5b14" data-vars-target-content-type="buzz" data-vars-type="web_internal_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="2"&gt;anemic&lt;/a&gt; can all make the breathlessness you feel after &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/topic/walking" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-internal-link" data-vars-item-name="walking" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="695bd707e4b0c1bd90c46bc7" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="/topic/walking" data-vars-target-content-type="feed" data-vars-type="web_internal_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="3"&gt;walking&lt;/a&gt; up stairs worse.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“How long it takes you to recover is always a good indicator, too,” Erickson said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s normal for your breathing to be faster for a minute or two after walking up a bunch of stairs, Erickson explained. “But if it’s staying elevated past three minutes or a prolonged period of time, that’s when it becomes more concerning.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you notice chest pain, headache or vision changes along with the breathlessness, that’s worrisome and worth chatting with your doctor about too, Pohlgeers added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure class="cli cli-image js-no-inject"&gt;&lt;p class="cli-image__spacer"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="cli-image__source-wrapper"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="cli-image__caption caption-cli"&gt;"If you get up three or four flights of stairs as an average person carrying groceries, you're good. That's a very good sign."&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Here’s how you can build your stair-climbing endurance:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you want to be less winded after climbing the stairs, start doing it more often (as long as you don’t have any underlying conditions that can put your health at risk). If you have issues such as heart failure or COPD that make climbing stairs a challenge, get those treated first, Pohlgeers stressed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Your body adapts to imposed demands on it. So, if you’re practicing going up the stairs, you become more efficient,” Erickson said. The muscles needed to climb the stairs will strengthen the more you use them, he added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“We’ll ask patients, actually, that are getting ready to go into surgery, it’s like a pre-op clearance: ‘Could you carry groceries up three to four flights of stairs?’” Pohlgeers explained.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s OK if you’re out of breath by the top of the three or four flights of stairs. The concern is can you physically do it without having symptoms like chest pain, vision changes or a headache, she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“If you get up three or four flights of stairs as an average person carrying groceries, you’re good. That’s a very good sign,” Pohlgeers noted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Developing your base strength levels — doing &lt;a href="https://www.mayoclinic.org/healthy-lifestyle/fitness/multimedia/lunge/vid-20084662" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="lunges" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="695bd707e4b0c1bd90c46bc7" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.mayoclinic.org/healthy-lifestyle/fitness/multimedia/lunge/vid-20084662" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="4"&gt;lunges&lt;/a&gt;, doing &lt;a href="https://www.mayoclinic.org/healthy-lifestyle/fitness/multimedia/squat/vid-20084663" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="squats" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="695bd707e4b0c1bd90c46bc7" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.mayoclinic.org/healthy-lifestyle/fitness/multimedia/squat/vid-20084663" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="5"&gt;squats&lt;/a&gt;, that’s going to give you more power, more strength to go up [stairs],” Erickson added. Improving your cardiovascular fitness can also help decrease the fatigue you feel at the top of the stairs. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;When working on building up your endurance, do so gradually, Pohlgeers suggested. You don’t need to go up and down the stairs five times in a row. Instead, slowly build up your fitness ability in a sustainable and even enjoyable way, whether that’s by doing more yard work, going on walks with your neighbor or taking up gardening.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;As you work on your strength and cardiovascular fitness, your stair-climbing endurance should also improve, according to Erickson. You’ll be easily climbing back-to-back flights of stairs in no time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>HuffPost</author><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 12:00:17 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMinAFBVV95cUxQNml0UUNmQmFUTGE3Rm94ZmZabHlETDVjcnB2bExrTlpnZ211RDJ4WmNicmUxd2hoenNSTGZVUF81VHJjZXFVYUJqWnA3NWxHUng3M0RCSEt1NEZld1hNT3BLQnpzLVJuYjFId1pKZXkyYXJRa0xwRXMxbmNMSjNxc1g0X1R0djVBSXp6bHFpdE1nSU9uYXVlLXIzX2fSAaIBQVVfeXFMUEpBdEhqQUw5bXpJcHJpeGVGYmF2WnVQTmh3ejV6VkNoR0xjVGRsQVVNSkFRSWZVcXhpcU5YR1lEVENDbEI2TElKcHl0RmJ3NGJQXzVwN19TdlNSOVlQRnRQQ1FmZXRoYmNqWWRvN0tjQVA1TEZrNHVIbGhxckNDY3Ytb3dVbDFVVkU2MXZpYTNkY0FOanQ3UUFzZTNIb0NVWDJ3</guid></item><item><title>多动症药物起作用，但不是专家认为的那样-《华盛顿邮报》</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/health/2026/01/06/adhd-ritalin-sleep-children/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="LUIFNLOHENCR7KGR7QXN2SAHCE" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;The stimulants Ritalin and Adderall have been used to treat attention-deficit/hyperactivity disorder (ADHD) for decades, but research shows they don’t act on the brain’s attention circuitry as had long been assumed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:32:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigwFBVV95cUxNTGNwSU5MakYwNzZyVDd1bVI3WWJVZTNaVGg2Ui1NaGxPRjN1RVVUOFVyczQtTnNJYkx5NUJOSTRvajdZdnQxNDRFZVZLNEpRaERaRjlOR0FwM3I2WEo2c3RiczZyWUxJa1hQMG9yOE9uT2U3N3lJY3FmNjVnbnlzVENIMA</guid></item><item><title>特朗普政府引发中期疫苗战争- Axios</title><link>https://www.axios.com/2026/01/06/trump-administration-rfk-midterms-vaccines-kids</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Axios</author><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:07:17 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihwFBVV95cUxQQnJfYWphZzY2YkJfUTUzNzlYTmNaZVB0NE5sLWUtSTY0QVA0Vms5Z05wTGpWWnpTOVBuR0pnTnZiX1JyaFFOQS12VDlWVDdWU1F3WThiLTFJd1ZIUFRsWGhHOUV6eGFLOEtCVDhQbWEtTjZGa28yZnhuRm5IcDROd0RRcnBCcVU</guid></item><item><title>为什么癌症可以在几年后复发—以及如何阻止它-自然</title><link>https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-025-04149-3</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article__teaser" data-test="access-teaser"&gt; &lt;p&gt;When Lisa Dutton was declared free of &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-025-00265-2" data-track="click" data-label="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-025-00265-2" data-track-category="body text link"&gt;breast cancer&lt;/a&gt; in 2017, she took a moment to celebrate with family and friends, even though she knew her cancer journey might not be over. As many as one-third of people whose breast tumours are cleared see &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-024-01717-x" data-track="click" data-label="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-024-01717-x" data-track-category="body text link"&gt;the disease come back&lt;/a&gt;, sometimes decades later. Many other cancers are known to recur in the years following an initial treatment, some at much higher rates.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“It’s always in the back of your mind, and that can be stressful,” says Dutton, a retired health-care management consultant living in Philadelphia, Pennsylvania.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;article class="recommended pull pull--left u-sans-serif" data-label="Related"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-025-01570-6" class="u-link-inherit" data-track="click" data-track-label="recommended article"&gt;&lt;img class="recommended__image" alt="" src="//media.nature.com/w400/magazine-assets/d41586-025-04149-3/d41586-025-04149-3_51849280.jpg"&gt;&lt;p class="recommended__title u-serif"&gt;Cancer-fighting immune cells could soon be engineered inside our bodies&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As part of her treatment, Dutton had enrolled in a clinical trial called SURMOUNT. This would monitor her for sleeping cancer cells, which many researchers now think might explain at least some cancer recurrence&lt;sup&gt;&lt;a href="#ref-CR1" data-track="click" data-action="anchor-link" data-track-label="go to reference" data-track-category="references"&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;. These dormant tumour cells evade initial treatment and move to other parts of the body. Instead of multiplying to form tumours right away — as is typical for &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-024-02555-7" data-track="click" data-label="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-024-02555-7" data-track-category="body text link"&gt;metastatic cancer&lt;/a&gt;, in which cells spread from the main tumour — the dormant cells remain asleep. They are hidden from &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-025-00126-y" data-track="click" data-label="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-025-00126-y" data-track-category="body text link"&gt;the immune system&lt;/a&gt; and not actively dividing. But later, they can reawaken and give rise to tumours.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even though Dutton understood that her treatment might not have removed all signs of cancer, she says she was floored in 2020 when dormant cells were found in her bone marrow for the first time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Researchers are discovering dormant tumour cells, also known as disseminated cancer cells, in association with breast, prostate, lung, colon&lt;sup&gt;&lt;a href="#ref-CR2" data-track="click" data-action="anchor-link" data-track-label="go to reference" data-track-category="references"&gt;2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; and other cancers, and these cells are increasingly implicated in some metastatic cancers. An estimated 30% of people who have been successfully treated for cancer might harbour these cells, although unpublished work suggests they could be even more common.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Over the past decade, a flurry of efforts have attempted to identify and understand dormant cells, with the ultimate goal of treating them. A handful of clinical trials are now under way to test potential therapies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Although the first trial Dutton enrolled in only monitored the cells, she has since enrolled in a second, called CLEVER, that aims to eliminate them&lt;sup&gt;&lt;a href="#ref-CR3" data-track="click" data-action="anchor-link" data-track-label="go to reference" data-track-category="references"&gt;3&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;. As such trials move ahead, open questions about the sleeper cells, including what induces dormancy and how to fight it, are drawing more researchers into the field.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“We’re starting to see multiple groups converging on some of the same ideas, which is always very affirming,” says Cyrus Ghajar, a cancer biologist at the Fred Hutchinson Cancer Center in Seattle, Washington. The trials under way are “a testament to just how much progress has been made”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;A silent threat&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The existence of dormant tumour cells was proposed as early as the 1930s, when Australian pathologist Rupert Willis attributed some secondary cancer growths to such cells&lt;sup&gt;&lt;a href="#ref-CR4" data-track="click" data-action="anchor-link" data-track-label="go to reference" data-track-category="references"&gt;4&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;. As people who had been treated for cancer began to live longer, he and others noticed that the disease sometimes returned much later, and was often even more aggressive. Despite this early proposal, the idea of dormancy didn’t catch on for decades.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lewis Chodosh, a physician-scientist at the University of Pennsylvania in Philadelphia, recalls facing resistance when he began discussing the idea with colleagues more than 20 years ago. No one wanted to believe that cancer-killing drugs might be leaving something behind, he says, and drug companies weren’t interested in developing therapies for people who seemed to have been cured. Many scientists at the time said that recurrent cancers must instead be new, not linked to any past diagnoses.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“It’s only when enough evidence accumulates that you get pushed out of this way of thinking,” says Chodosh, who is a co-investigator on the SURMOUNT and CLEVER studies alongside Angela DeMichele, a medical oncologist at the University of Pennsylvania’s Perelman School of Medicine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="figure"&gt;&lt;picture class="embed intensity--high"&gt;&lt;source type="image/webp" srcset="//media.nature.com/lw767/magazine-assets/d41586-025-04149-3/d41586-025-04149-3_51843414.jpg?as=webp 767w, //media.nature.com/lw319/magazine-assets/d41586-025-04149-3/d41586-025-04149-3_51843414.jpg?as=webp 319w" sizes="(max-width: 319px) 319px, (min-width: 1023px) 100vw,  767px"&gt;&lt;/source&gt;&lt;img class="figure__image" alt="Researchers Angela DeMichele and Lewis Chodosh stand at the interior window of a large medical building." loading="lazy" src="//media.nature.com/lw767/magazine-assets/d41586-025-04149-3/d41586-025-04149-3_51843414.jpg"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;p class="figure__caption u-sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span class="mr10"&gt;Angela DeMichele (left) and Lewis Chodosh are investigating ways to target dormant tumour cells.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Credit: Peggy Peterson for Penn Medicine&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/picture&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Using a handful of cellular markers, researchers have now identified dormant tumour cells in many parts of the body&lt;sup&gt;&lt;a href="#ref-CR5" data-track="click" data-action="anchor-link" data-track-label="go to reference" data-track-category="references"&gt;5&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;. These markers can tell scientists not only whether the cells are growing and dividing, but also where the cells originated and therefore &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-024-01110-8" data-track="click" data-label="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-024-01110-8" data-track-category="body text link"&gt;which type of cancer&lt;/a&gt; they’re associated with. The methods aren’t perfect, however, and researchers are still trying to determine whether certain cells are more likely to go dormant than others, and which features define these cells.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ghajar and others have found that dormant cells leave the primary tumour early in a cancer’s progression, often before the disease has been diagnosed&lt;sup&gt;&lt;a href="#ref-CR6" data-track="click" data-action="anchor-link" data-track-label="go to reference" data-track-category="references"&gt;6&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;. How and why these cells break away isn’t entirely clear, but after spending just minutes in circulation, they exit the bloodstream and concentrate in certain parts of the body, such as the bone marrow and lymph nodes. Even in these niches, dormant cells are extremely rare, amounting to just a handful among millions of healthy cells, he says. Their state of suspended animation shields them from conventional treatments, such as chemotherapy, that target rapidly dividing cells.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Petros Tsantoulis, a medical oncologist at the University of Geneva in Switzerland, says that dormancy differs from &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-024-01370-4" data-track="click" data-label="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-024-01370-4" data-track-category="body text link"&gt;other known states such as senescence&lt;/a&gt;, in which old cells stop dividing as they prepare to die. Given the right conditions, dormant cells can begin dividing anew. Once reawakened, dormant cells multiply into tumours that replicate the full complexity of the original tumour.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This has led some researchers to suggest that dormant tumour cells might be cancer stem cells, a type of cell that through renewal and differentiation might give rise to the tumour — or that, at least, they might be cancer cells with stem-like features.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;article class="recommended pull pull--left u-sans-serif" data-label="Related"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-024-00216-3" class="u-link-inherit" data-track="click" data-track-label="recommended article"&gt;&lt;img class="recommended__image" alt="" src="//media.nature.com/w400/magazine-assets/d41586-025-04149-3/d41586-025-04149-3_26701508.jpg"&gt;&lt;p class="recommended__title u-serif"&gt;Forget lung, breast or prostate cancer: why tumour naming needs to change&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dormant tumour cells have some characteristics that are commonly associated with stem cells, such as the overexpression of certain genes. Cancer biologist Joan Massagué, director of the Sloan Kettering Institute in New York City, says that stem cells spend most of their time dormant, waking only after an injury or illness — making them obvious candidates. Still, the existence of cancer stem cells is a contentious idea.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Scientists seem poised to resolve some of these open questions soon. With advanced laboratory techniques that give researchers the ability to &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-025-03768-0" data-track="click" data-label="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-025-03768-0" data-track-category="body text link"&gt;study individual cells&lt;/a&gt; more closely, it’s now possible to identify, isolate and enrich dormant tumour cells for further study. Chodosh and DeMichele’s team, for example, is developing an assay to identify dormant cells. Chodosh says it is much more sensitive than existing approaches, and might ultimately improve estimates of how many people harbour dormant cells.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ghajar, meanwhile, is settling on a different way of thinking about these cells. If a dormant cell from a breast tumour ends up in the bone marrow, for example, it might be expected to retain many features of a breast cancer cell that would enable its identification. “But what we’re finding is that these expectations don’t hold up,” Ghajar says, noting that once a cancer cell spreads, it often changes its shape, size and behaviour. “We’re going to have to go beyond a definition based on unifying features, and instead map the mutations in these cells to mutations in the originating tumour — to define a disseminated cell not by what we think it should look like, but what its genome tells us it is.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Sleep–wake signals&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Beyond defining dormancy, researchers want to understand how and why cells go dormant, and what sorts of triggers reawaken them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to Judith Agudo, an immunologist at the Dana-Farber Cancer Institute in Boston, Massachusetts, cells probably enter dormancy as a protective measure. As part of a tumour, individual cells might be insulated from attack by the immune system, but once on their own, “they can easily be picked off without taking steps to hide themselves”, she says. In addition, the journey through the body to a new niche is a stressful one that kills the vast majority of cells that break away. Dormancy is one way of persisting in a harsh environment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Research has shown that while cells are asleep, they continue to engage in crosstalk with their microenvironment&lt;sup&gt;&lt;a href="#ref-CR7" data-track="click" data-action="anchor-link" data-track-label="go to reference" data-track-category="references"&gt;7&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; and modify themselves to actively maintain dormancy. For example, dormant cells seem to alter the expression patterns of genes involved in cell survival, including a central regulator of cell metabolism and growth called the mTOR pathway&lt;sup&gt;&lt;a href="#ref-CR8" data-track="click" data-action="anchor-link" data-track-label="go to reference" data-track-category="references"&gt;8&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;. The cells also exploit a form of self-recycling called autophagy — literally ‘self-eating’ — that allows dormant cells to repurpose internal resources and survive with little input from their surroundings&lt;sup&gt;&lt;a href="#ref-CR9" data-track="click" data-action="anchor-link" data-track-label="go to reference" data-track-category="references"&gt;9&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The cells seem to have a complex relationship with their external environment, too, including the immune system. Julio Aguirre-Ghiso, founding director of the Cancer Dormancy Institute at the Montefiore Einstein Comprehensive Cancer Center in New York City, says that the immune response is implicated not only in inducing dormancy, but also in maintaining and ending it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He and his team have shown that macrophages in the lungs produce a particular protein that binds to dormant breast cancer cells and reinforces dormancy&lt;sup&gt;&lt;a href="#ref-CR10" data-track="click" data-action="anchor-link" data-track-label="go to reference" data-track-category="references"&gt;10&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;. Other research has demonstrated how dormant cells can evade surveillance by immune-system cells, including T cells&lt;sup&gt;&lt;a href="#ref-CR11" data-track="click" data-action="anchor-link" data-track-label="go to reference" data-track-category="references"&gt;11&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; and natural killer cells&lt;sup&gt;&lt;a href="#ref-CR12" data-track="click" data-action="anchor-link" data-track-label="go to reference" data-track-category="references"&gt;12&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Taken together, the research suggests that cells most often remain dormant until the immune landscape is disrupted in some way, shifting the balance enough for cells to reawaken safely. These shifts might involve injury or illness, with studies in the past few years linking cellular damage&lt;sup&gt;&lt;a href="#ref-CR13" data-track="click" data-action="anchor-link" data-track-label="go to reference" data-track-category="references"&gt;13&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; and COVID-19 and influenza infections&lt;sup&gt;&lt;a href="#ref-CR14" data-track="click" data-action="anchor-link" data-track-label="go to reference" data-track-category="references"&gt;14&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; to an escape from dormancy. Ageing, fibrosis&lt;sup&gt;&lt;a href="#ref-CR15" data-track="click" data-action="anchor-link" data-track-label="go to reference" data-track-category="references"&gt;15&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-025-02066-z" data-track="click" data-label="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-025-02066-z" data-track-category="body text link"&gt;chronic stress&lt;/a&gt; or lifestyle choices might also contribute to reawakening.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="figure"&gt;&lt;picture class="embed intensity--high"&gt;&lt;source type="image/webp" srcset="//media.nature.com/lw767/magazine-assets/d41586-025-04149-3/d41586-025-04149-3_51843412.jpg?as=webp 767w, //media.nature.com/lw319/magazine-assets/d41586-025-04149-3/d41586-025-04149-3_51843412.jpg?as=webp 319w" sizes="(max-width: 319px) 319px, (min-width: 1023px) 100vw,  767px"&gt;&lt;/source&gt;&lt;img class="figure__image" alt="Flourescent image of mouse lung with influenza virus that shows blue and pink cells, some of them rimmed with green." loading="lazy" src="//media.nature.com/lw767/magazine-assets/d41586-025-04149-3/d41586-025-04149-3_51843412.jpg"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;p class="figure__caption u-sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span class="mr10"&gt;Flu infections can force dormant tumour cells to start growing and dividing (green).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Credit: Bryan Johnson&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/picture&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;For the cells, “it’s an odds game”, says Shelly Peyton, a biomedical engineer at Tufts University in Medford, Massachusetts. Cells are constantly attempting to exit dormancy after small perturbations, only to be killed. “But in moments when the balance is disrupted, that’s when we often see metastasis taking off,” she says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Peyton’s work focuses on fibrosis, the build-up of fibrous connective tissue at a damaged site. This is often associated with cancer, because stiffness helps the tumour to grow and aids in signalling between cells. But the bone marrow, where dormant cells often reside, is soft, and Peyton is interested in whether that soft environment might be one feature reinforcing dormancy. She says it’s possible that natural, age-related loss of bone density (osteoporosis) or hormonal changes in women who previously had breast cancer could trigger fibrosis, and potentially a reawakening of their cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
                        &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Nature</author><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:03:45 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiX0FVX3lxTE1hOXU3aHVPQXh2MUNIZUdIU3VVaktjOG9abjZOSzIwRFhITFBNVG9vNGxLWkF2X2JsRTIyeks5OTRMdGlJYUNYbENndl9CQy0wNkZYZTBhT1ZwYnJSOXlJ</guid></item><item><title>研究提出了关于间歇性禁食益处的严重问题- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/study-raises-serious-questions-about-the-benefits-of-intermittent-fasting</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;The notion behind &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/intermittent-fasting-does-work-for-weight-loss-but-only-if-you-follow-this-rule"&gt;intermittent fasting&lt;/a&gt; is simple: eat less for a time, improve your metabolism. The reality is more complex, and a new study finds that some forms of intermittent fasting do not alter markers of metabolic or cardiovascular health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Researchers, led by a team from the German Institute of Human Nutrition Potsdam-Rehbruecke (DIfE), put 31 women &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/fat-cells-seem-to-cling-to-the-memory-of-being-obese-study-finds"&gt;who were overweight&lt;/a&gt; or obese on two different intermittent fasting schedules for two weeks each. The schedules were 8 am to 4 pm or 1 pm to 9 pm, a particular kind of intermittent fasting known as time-restricted eating (TRE).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While the timing of the schedules differed, the diet parameters were the same: participants could eat &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/high-fat-diets-may-break-the-brains-ability-to-regulate-calories"&gt;like they normally did&lt;/a&gt;, and therefore take in the same amount of total calories (making this what's known as an isocaloric study).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/a-fasting-style-diet-seems-to-result-in-dynamic-changes-to-human-brains"&gt;A Fasting-Style Diet Seems to Result in Dynamic Changes to Human Brains&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Although the women lost some weight, other benefits that might be expected based on &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.cmet.2018.04.010"&gt;previous research&lt;/a&gt; – including lower blood sugar levels, lower blood pressure, and &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/experts-reveal-how-to-actually-lower-your-cholesterol"&gt;lower cholesterol&lt;/a&gt; – didn't show up in the data, raising questions about just how effective these timed fasting routines are.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The beneficial cardiometabolic effects described previously might be induced by TRE-mediated calorie restriction and not by the shortening of the eating window itself," &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1126/scitranslmed.adv6787"&gt;write&lt;/a&gt; the researchers in their published paper.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"In this nearly isocaloric trial, no improvements in metabolic parameters were observed after two weeks of TRE."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_187651" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-187651" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2026/01/GlucoseProfile.jpg" alt="Glucose level chart" class="wp-image-187651 size-full" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2026/01/GlucoseProfile.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2026/01/GlucoseProfile-600x393.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-187651" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;The researchers looked at health indicators like glucose levels. (Peters et al., &lt;em&gt;Sci. Transl. Med.&lt;/em&gt;, 2025)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;The findings suggest it may be &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/weight-loss-involves-more-than-calories-in-calories-out-heres-how"&gt;calorie reduction&lt;/a&gt; rather than time-restricted eating itself that boosts key indicators of health inside the body, although it's important to bear in mind this was a relatively small-scale, short-term study.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In addition to the study's modest reductions in body weight, researchers observed changes in participants' body clocks. The timing of their &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/scientists-explain-why-you-wake-up-minutes-before-your-alarm"&gt;circadian rhythms&lt;/a&gt;, including those that nudge the body towards sleep, was shifted based on the TRE schedule.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It's more evidence that our internal clocks can be partially controlled by when we drink and eat, as well as through other triggers (such as when &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/stunning-sunset-images-on-the-moon-could-help-solve-enduring-mystery"&gt;the Sun goes down&lt;/a&gt;). This could play into health problems associated with eating late at night, for example.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Those who want to lose weight or improve their metabolism should pay attention not only to the clock, but also to their energy balance," &lt;a href="https://www.dzd-ev.de/en/article/intervallfasten-ohne-kalorienreduktion-verbessert-nicht-die-stoffwechselgesundheit-verschiebt-aber-die-innere-uhr"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; biologist and nutritionist Olga Ramich, from the DIfE.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Improving metabolic health is particularly important when tackling insulin resistance and  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/diabetes" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73018" data-postid="187648" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;diabetes&lt;/a&gt;. Future findings like these may change how diets are structured for people with conditions like these or who are &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/caffeine-in-your-blood-could-affect-body-fat-and-diabetes-risk-study-reveals"&gt;at risk of developing&lt;/a&gt; them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/newsletter?utm_source=promo_generic_health"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-642x273.jpg" alt="Subscribe to ScienceAlert's free fact-checked newsletter" class="alignnone wp-image-182810 size-medium" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-642x273.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-768x326.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-600x255.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final.jpg 850w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers are keen to continue investigating the relationship between calorie consumption and calorie timing. It's possible that in hypocaloric scenarios (when calories are restricted), timing may have some influence on biological markers of health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Various types of intermittent fasting continue to be analyzed by researchers, but studies &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/study-reveals-intermittent-fasting-has-2-key-benefits-for-people-with-obesity"&gt;can differ substantially&lt;/a&gt; in terms of the diets that are allowed, the participants, study duration, and the health benefits measured.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Our findings suggest the importance of calorie restriction for metabolic improvements in TRE," &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1126/scitranslmed.adv6787"&gt;write&lt;/a&gt; the researchers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Whether the timing of eating under the hypocaloric conditions can additionally contribute to metabolic changes and whether the optimal eating timing differs between individuals warrants investigation in future studies."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The research has been published in &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1126/scitranslmed.adv6787"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Science Translational Medicine&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:02:09 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipAFBVV95cUxNNU8wakhzM1dUWlFBNnV6TWxvZEh1b1VHODhlMURKdnpCY2RqeDRBczdONU9uZnNaNUxXUFFQUmFNcFhHUHlreEVCQ1IxdVJtdlFCOTNJUWZ0eXo3aEF2eWNVVlhoU2N3MEV0WmFQMGxMT0dlTXFiUmkxcURhRTlXNGI0dnBwbGt2QzkxNnRENDQ5dXRydjhlMDBRX0xlNkszOFp4MQ</guid></item><item><title>马萨诸塞州的医生看到了流感病例的爆炸性增长。“原因如下。-《波士顿环球报》</title><link>https://www.bostonglobe.com/2026/01/06/metro/massachusetts-influenza-flu-subclade-k-surge-2026/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="body | gutter_16--desktop gutter_16--tablet paywalled_content
              "&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Local doctors say a perfect storm has developed, a rapidly spreading strain of influenza A compounded by a drop in vaccination rates and an increase in holiday travel, which could elongate the flu surge into spring.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;“This is one of those seasons where everything is lining up in the wrong direction,” said Dr. Vandana Madhavan, clinical director of infectious disease at Mass General Brigham for Children. “It’s hard to say when our peak is going to be, and in some years, we see a second peak.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;At the end of December, the number of visits to health care providers for flu-like illness jumped to 11.8 percent, up from 7.6 percent the week before, according to the &lt;a href="https://www.mass.gov/info-details/influenza-reporting" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://www.mass.gov/info-details/influenza-reporting"&gt;Massachusetts Department of Public Health&lt;/a&gt;. The share of emergency room visits that resulted in a hospitalization for influenza rose to 9 percent — nearly double from the previous week and triple the rate from the same time last year.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Each day last week, there were nearly 9,000 emergency department visits statewide, with about one-quarter of those related to acute respiratory illness, including flu, COVID-19, and RSV, or respiratory syncytial virus. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Last year, flu hospitalizations in Massachusetts peaked in early February, when about 10.5 percent of hospital admissions were attributed to influenza. This year’s trajectory suggests the state could meet or surpass that mark, said Dr. Larry Madoff, of the Massachusetts Department of Public Health.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;“The flu season is likely to continue well into the spring. Typically, it doesn’t peak until late January or February,” said Madoff, medical director of the department’s Bureau of Infectious Disease and Laboratory Sciences.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Starting Tuesday, Brown University Health will require surgical masks or N95s for all patients, visitors, and staff at all times across its locations in Massachusetts and Rhode Island due to high rates of hospital infections.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Nationally, the picture is similarly grim. Through Dec. 27, the &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/fluview/surveillance/2025-week-52.html" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://www.cdc.gov/fluview/surveillance/2025-week-52.html"&gt;Centers for Disease Control and Prevention&lt;/a&gt; reported “very high” flu activity in more than half the states. The agency estimates there have been at least 11 million illnesses, 120,000 hospitalizations, and 5,000 deaths so far this season, including at least nine children nationwide. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;In the state, 32 influenza-related deaths have been reported this season — 29 adults and three children, including &lt;a href="https://www.bostonglobe.com/2026/01/05/metro/massachusetts-pediatric-death-influenza/?p1=Article_Inline_Text_Link" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://www.bostonglobe.com/2026/01/05/metro/massachusetts-pediatric-death-influenza/?p1=Article_Inline_Text_Link"&gt;one child who died during Christmas week&lt;/a&gt;. Last season, which ran from fall to summer, there were 470 influenza-related deaths. The state is also reviewing two possible COVID-19-associated deaths and one RSV-associated death in individuals younger than 18 years.&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Influenza is a contagious viral illness that attacks the respiratory system, including the nose, throat, and lungs. Typical symptoms include high fever, cough, sore throat, body aches, and extreme fatigue, sometimes accompanied by nausea, vomiting, or diarrhea. This season, clinicians are reporting fevers as high as 104 or 105 degrees in some patients.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Doctors say the intensity of this year’s outbreak is driven by a dominant strain of influenza A H3N2 — specifically, a genetic variant known as &lt;a href="https://www.bostonglobe.com/2025/11/18/metro/new-flu-strain-massachusetts-subclade-k/" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://www.bostonglobe.com/2025/11/18/metro/new-flu-strain-massachusetts-subclade-k/"&gt;subclade K&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Among influenza A H3N2 viruses that have undergone further genetic analysis at the CDC, about 90 percent belong to subclade K. While experts are still studying whether it causes more severe disease, early evidence suggests it spreads more quickly and may be better at evading existing community immunity.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Internationally, subclade K has already raised alarms. Health leaders in the United Kingdom warned in November of a “&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/society/2025/nov/14/flu-mutated-strain-uk-hospitals-winter-surge" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://www.theguardian.com/society/2025/nov/14/flu-mutated-strain-uk-hospitals-winter-surge"&gt;once-in-a-decade&lt;/a&gt;” winter flu surge as infections rose sharply among young people. The strain has also been detected in Canada and Japan, where authorities declared a &lt;a href="https://www.cidrap.umn.edu/influenza-general/japan-sees-early-flu-activity-school-closures#:~:text=Japan%20is%20seeing%20early%20and,Smederevac%20/%20iStock" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://www.cidrap.umn.edu/influenza-general/japan-sees-early-flu-activity-school-closures#:~:text=Japan%20is%20seeing%20early%20and,Smederevac%20/%20iStock"&gt;flu epidemic as early as October&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;“It really did feel like a switch flipped,” said Dr. Zachary Binder, an associate professor of pediatrics at UMass Chan Medical School and a pediatric emergency medicine physician at UMass Memorial Medical Center in Worcester. “We went from seeing hardly any flu to over half the patients in the emergency department being flu positive.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Binder said more than half the patients he treated in recent weeks had influenza A, and many children experienced febrile seizures triggered by dangerously high fevers.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;“We are seeing an absolute explosion in flu cases over the last few weeks,” Binder said. “When we see kind of severe cases, even death, it’s most often in children with underlying health conditions like asthma, other respiratory illnesses, or cardiac illnesses.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Another major factor is the lack of vaccination. Only about 34 percent of Massachusetts residents have received a flu shot so far this season, according to the &lt;a href="https://www.mass.gov/info-details/immunizations-for-respiratory-diseases" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://www.mass.gov/info-details/immunizations-for-respiratory-diseases"&gt;state’s tracker&lt;/a&gt;. That’s a drop from last year, when roughly 40 percent of residents were vaccinated.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Complicating matters further, the &lt;a href="https://www.gavi.org/vaccineswork/everything-you-need-know-about-subclade-k-flu-and-vaccine-protection-against-it" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;newly mutated strain&lt;/a&gt;, which was surging earlier in the UK, appears to be only a partial match to &lt;a href="https://www.bostonglobe.com/2025/09/03/metro/healey-covid-booster-massachusetts-trump-kennedy-vaccine-2/?p1=StaffPage&amp;amp;p1=Article_Inline_Text_Link&amp;amp;p1=Article_Inline_Text_Link" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;this year’s vaccine&lt;/a&gt;. Each year, scientists must predict which flu strains are most likely to circulate months in advance, and this year’s prediction missed the mark.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Madoff, of the state’s Department of Public Health, said even though the circulating strain “is not a perfect match for the vaccine, a vaccine is far better than no vaccine.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;He said it’s unfortunate that more people are choosing not to vaccinate in the state, and combats the federal health officials’ &lt;a href="https://www.bostonglobe.com/2026/01/05/nation/childhood-vaccine-cdc-schedule-overhaul/" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://www.bostonglobe.com/2026/01/05/nation/childhood-vaccine-cdc-schedule-overhaul/"&gt;decision Monday&lt;/a&gt; to slash recommended childhood vaccinations under President Trump’s directive.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;“I think it’s the wrong move at the wrong time,” Madoff said. “It flies in the face of what doctors recommend and what our professional organizations recommend. This guidance seems to backtrack on important protections for our children, and backing off on those recommendations, weakening those recommendations in any way, is exactly the wrong thing to be doing.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;The reasons for declining flu vaccination rates are complex. Some experts point to pandemic fatigue such as&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;reduced routine care visits, and lingering skepticism about vaccines following COVID-19. Others note that people may underestimate the severity of influenza compared with other respiratory viruses.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Still, physicians in Massachusetts stress that the vaccine significantly reduces the risk of severe illness, hospitalization, and death.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;“It does take a couple of weeks to get full protection from vaccination,” Madhavan said. “Now is the time, if you haven’t gotten vaccinated, to get vaccinated, to get some protection on board. And I would say that for COVID as well.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Pediatric specialists say they are seeing more &lt;a href="https://www.bostonglobe.com/2025/12/22/metro/super-flu-virus-children-kids/" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://www.bostonglobe.com/2025/12/22/metro/super-flu-virus-children-kids/"&gt;severe complications in children&lt;/a&gt; than usual. Madhavan, with Mass General Brigham for Children, said she has treated patients with acute necrotizing encephalopathy, a rare but serious complication of influenza that can cause sudden changes in mental status, difficulty speaking or eating, problems with movement, and, in severe cases, trouble breathing.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Severe flu cases are more common in children with underlying health conditions, but even otherwise healthy children can become critically ill, doctors warn. Parents are urged to watch for signs of dehydration, difficulty breathing, persistent high fever, or lethargy.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;For home care, Madhavan recommends aggressive hydration, including popsicles and electrolyte solutions like Pedialyte, along with controlling fever using ibuprofen or acetaminophen. Honey can help soothe coughs in children older than 1, she recommends.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;COVID-19 activity in Massachusetts remains relatively low compared with influenza, though health officials caution that seasonal waves can overlap.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;For now, doctors and public health officials are urging residents to get vaccinated, stay home when sick, wash hands frequently, and seek medical care early if symptoms worsen.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Madoff recommends residents seek care as soon as symptoms onset.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;“There are treatments available, and the earlier those treatments are started, the more beneficial they are,” he said. “For the vulnerable populations like young children, older adults, those with underlying medical conditions, those with respiratory issues or cardiovascular issues, Tamiflu and other treatments can be lifesaving.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr class="tagline_hr | border_foreground border_half gutter_20_28--mobile
               margin_none text_align_left width_100px"&gt;&lt;p class="tagline | font_primary inline_block  margin_top_32"&gt;Sarah Rahal can be reached at &lt;a href="mailto:sarah.rahal@globe.com" class="" target="_blank"&gt;sarah.rahal@globe.com&lt;/a&gt;. Follow her on X &lt;a href="https://www.twitter.com/SarahRahal_" class="" target="_blank"&gt;@SarahRahal_&lt;/a&gt; or Instagram &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/sarah.rahal" class="" target="_blank"&gt;@sarah.rahal&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Boston Globe</author><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:01:46 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimwFBVV95cUxOZTZqc0g4VWx3cU5oTUdCb2hjcmFvcVowSHU3elYzbDg5WEZ1dGNpUVRGWGY1N2lpdzJpT2xuNVZGaG1NZkxpT1B5V3VnRUFRWVczbGNfYVByYk5fcHY2VDd5c1duRlktTnJwbnF6QXRPbGxaVmRsLVFmSzdjV29hb2hYZ1JiNElERGQwX1hCNVpoZUMzbWVHS1NSVQ</guid></item><item><title>什么是迷走神经刺激，我需要这样做吗？ -金融时报</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/47eaf3fb-d5ec-499b-9d60-281d2d45206d</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article__content-sign-up"&gt;&lt;p class="article__content-sign-up-topic-title"&gt;Unlock the Editor’s Digest for free&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__content-sign-up-topic-description o3-type-body-base"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Roula Khalaf, Editor of the FT, selects her favourite stories in this weekly newsletter.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;article id="article-body" class="n-content-body js-article__content-body o3-type-body-content-base" data-attribute="article-content-body" data-component="article-content-body"&gt;&lt;h2 id="eawwvrdh" class="n-content-heading-2 o3-editorial-typography-chapter"&gt;Yes&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Vagus” is a Latin word meaning “wandering”, and the nerves with that name (one on the right, one on the left) meander around the body, connecting the brain to the heart, the lungs, the gut and beyond. They’re known to play a significant role in putting us in a state of rest and digest (as opposed to fight or flight), and studies have shown that vagus nerve stimulation (VNS) can calm and regulate some bodily functions. (The potential cardiac side effects of stimulating the right means that VNS concentrates almost exclusively on the left.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote class="n-content-pullquote o3-editorial-typography-pullquote n-content-pullquote--no-image" aria-hidden="true"&gt;&lt;p&gt;I started to feel I had more energy just after the first week&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most notably, VNS implants have long been used by doctors to treat epilepsy. But the vagus nerve can also be stimulated via the skin, usually in or around the left ear, using small electrical pulses that give a tingling sensation. A number of devices on the market claim to do this safely, and some have been shown to have positive effects for specific conditions. One, &lt;a href="https://gammacore.co.uk/" title="" data-trackable="link"&gt;GammaCore&lt;/a&gt;, is available on the NHS to treat cluster headaches via neck-based VNS. Another, made by German firm tVNS Technologies, is being used in a £2mn study (&lt;a href="https://sheffield.ac.uk/ctru/current-trials/triceps" title="" data-trackable="link"&gt;Triceps&lt;/a&gt;) at Sheffield University into treating arm weakness following a stroke, funded by the NIHR Efficacy and Mechanism Evaluation board, the Association of British Neurologists and the Stroke Association. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="mdnrlywm" class="n-content-image n-content-image--full" data-component="image-set"&gt;&lt;picture&gt;&lt;source media="(min-width: 700px)" srcset="https://images.ft.com/v3/image/raw/ftcms%3Ad1c0c20a-1fc2-48c3-8b00-c094481fefc8?source=next-article&amp;amp;fit=scale-down&amp;amp;quality=highest&amp;amp;width=700&amp;amp;dpr=1 1x,https://images.ft.com/v3/image/raw/ftcms%3Ad1c0c20a-1fc2-48c3-8b00-c094481fefc8?source=next-article&amp;amp;fit=scale-down&amp;amp;quality=highest&amp;amp;width=700&amp;amp;dpr=2 2x,https://images.ft.com/v3/image/raw/ftcms%3Ad1c0c20a-1fc2-48c3-8b00-c094481fefc8?source=next-article&amp;amp;fit=scale-down&amp;amp;quality=highest&amp;amp;width=700&amp;amp;dpr=3 3x"&gt;&lt;/source&gt;&lt;img src="https://images.ft.com/v3/image/raw/https%3A%2F%2Fd1e00ek4ebabms.cloudfront.net%2Fproduction%2Fd1c0c20a-1fc2-48c3-8b00-c094481fefc8.jpg?source=next-article&amp;amp;fit=scale-down&amp;amp;quality=highest&amp;amp;width=700&amp;amp;dpr=1" alt="Yōjō vagus stimulation device and subscription, £399 per year" data-image-type="image" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/picture&gt;&lt;figcaption class="n-content-picture__caption o3-editorial-typography-caption"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Yōjō vagus stimulation device and subscription, £399 per year&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Manufacturers indicate that the nerve’s size means that stimulating it could have wider beneficial effects relating to fatigue, digestive disorders and more. Parasym, makers of a device called &lt;a href="https://nurosym.com/en-gb" title="" data-trackable="link"&gt;Nurosym&lt;/a&gt;, has published more than 50 clinical studies including one showing a 32 per cent improvement in memory. Anecdotal evidence, meanwhile, is rich. “My energy levels have been such an obvious difference,” says Andrea, COO of a medical education company, who uses a device called &lt;a href="https://www.yojo.health/" title="" data-trackable="link"&gt;Yōjō&lt;/a&gt; to treat chronic migraines. “I started to feel like I had more energy just after the first week.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="xwluzhqk" class="n-content-heading-2 o3-editorial-typography-chapter"&gt;No&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The word “vague” comes from the same Latin word, and could be used to describe some of the feelgood claims made for VNS devices. While users have credited them with improving sleep patterns, symptoms of IBS and much else, the reasons are not properly understood. “It might improve someone’s mental health, and if it works for them then who am I to argue, but as a doctor I can’t prescribe it,” says Professor Arshad Majid, chief investigator of the Triceps trial. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="n-content-layout" data-layout-name="card" data-layout-width="full-width"&gt;&lt;div class="n-content-layout__container"&gt;&lt;div class="n-content-layout__slot"&gt;&lt;figure class="n-content-image n-content-image--full" data-component="image-set"&gt;&lt;picture&gt;&lt;source media="(min-width: 700px)" srcset="https://images.ft.com/v3/image/raw/ftcms%3A96e0d359-753a-4895-b618-fb4547ae8fa7?source=next-article&amp;amp;fit=scale-down&amp;amp;quality=highest&amp;amp;width=700&amp;amp;dpr=1 1x,https://images.ft.com/v3/image/raw/ftcms%3A96e0d359-753a-4895-b618-fb4547ae8fa7?source=next-article&amp;amp;fit=scale-down&amp;amp;quality=highest&amp;amp;width=700&amp;amp;dpr=2 2x"&gt;&lt;/source&gt;&lt;img src="https://images.ft.com/v3/image/raw/https%3A%2F%2Fd1e00ek4ebabms.cloudfront.net%2Fproduction%2F96e0d359-753a-4895-b618-fb4547ae8fa7.png?source=next-article&amp;amp;fit=scale-down&amp;amp;quality=highest&amp;amp;width=700&amp;amp;dpr=1" alt="TVNS E with Legacy Electrode, €3,500" data-image-type="image" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/picture&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;TVNS E with Legacy Electrode&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Price:&lt;/strong&gt; €3,500&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://shop.t-vns.com/en/" title="" data-trackable="link"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;BUY&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="n-content-layout__slot"&gt;&lt;figure class="n-content-image n-content-image--full" data-component="image-set"&gt;&lt;picture&gt;&lt;source media="(min-width: 700px)" srcset="https://images.ft.com/v3/image/raw/ftcms%3A29a79fe6-b45d-4e6c-bd3e-23617966c0ad?source=next-article&amp;amp;fit=scale-down&amp;amp;quality=highest&amp;amp;width=700&amp;amp;dpr=1 1x,https://images.ft.com/v3/image/raw/ftcms%3A29a79fe6-b45d-4e6c-bd3e-23617966c0ad?source=next-article&amp;amp;fit=scale-down&amp;amp;quality=highest&amp;amp;width=700&amp;amp;dpr=2 2x"&gt;&lt;/source&gt;&lt;img src="https://images.ft.com/v3/image/raw/https%3A%2F%2Fd1e00ek4ebabms.cloudfront.net%2Fproduction%2F29a79fe6-b45d-4e6c-bd3e-23617966c0ad.png?source=next-article&amp;amp;fit=scale-down&amp;amp;quality=highest&amp;amp;width=700&amp;amp;dpr=1" alt="Nurosym, €700" data-image-type="image" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/picture&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nurosym&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Price: &lt;/strong&gt;£599&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://nurosym.com/en-gb/products/nurosym-v2" title="" data-trackable="link"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;BUY&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;“To be able to understand which device is better, we would need some sort of signal of efficacy to measure,” he continues. For its part, Yōjō pairs with an app that does a face scan via your phone’s camera to estimate blood pressure, HRV and pulse, with the aim of building up a picture of said efficacy – but in my own tests its estimation of my blood pressure was rather different to readings from a cuff. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Stimulating the vagus nerve pathway via the ear is biologically plausible, but there are many questions left to answer – which stimulation settings? When? For how long?” says Tiago da Silva Costa, senior research fellow in Psychiatry at Newcastle University. His colleague, Hamish McAllister-Williams, professor of affective disorders at the same institution, agrees. “I think that the main benefit that people get from some devices may be more of a placebo response. But they are probably safe, probably do not harm and may at least get people to relax for periods of the day.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Financial Times</author><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:00:07 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMicEFVX3lxTFByM2VFR3NoVk85WHVORW5leTZPYUxMMC1FN2dKVzljVHd3Z1lPQ2dVRi10UTRWVGlvclEwOFU1U19vMWs2NWVfX1dseWxfNk1iWUZnRV9mVG9KZHVoYWZtLVpzcy1XTkFFeDZZeVlJUVc</guid></item><item><title>如何帮助身体排毒- BBC</title><link>https://www.bbc.com/future/article/20260105-how-to-help-your-body-detox-itself</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="sc-85f9acf9-0 kfxpiP"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Fibre also helps &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC5105045/" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;protect the kidneys and liver&lt;/a&gt; – both crucial for removing toxins from the body – by protecting them from harmful bacteria and helping beneficial bacteria to grow. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;To &lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.bbc.com/food/articles/fibremaxxing" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;increase your fibre intake&lt;/a&gt;, plant-based foods are your best bet. Dried fruits like apricots, leafy vegetables like spinach and legumes like a chickpeas, lentils and beans are all high in fibre, as are porridge oats and wholewheat bread and pasta. Snack on &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.cancer.gov/about-cancer/treatment/side-effects/nutrition/high-fiber-foods" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;apples, berries, nuts, seeds, popcorn&lt;/a&gt; or roasted pulses. Lots of variety is key, since there are &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0963996925001802#b0645" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;lots of different fibres with different properties&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 gXmhTb"&gt;&lt;span id="drink-more-water" class="sc-d16436d-0 gCPVhV"&gt;&lt;b id="drink-more-water" class="sc-d16436d-0 gnUCoQ"&gt;Drink more water&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span id="" class="sc-d16436d-0 gCPVhV"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Water helps to remove toxins from the body by helping the kidneys and liver to excrete waste. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The kidneys, for instance, use water to flush out toxins such as &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.kidney.org.uk/kidneys-the-basics" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;sodium and urea&lt;/a&gt;. Dehydration can cause waste to build up. Over time, even mild dehydration can &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.kidney.org/news-stories/can-dehydration-affect-your-kidneys" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;increase the risk of kidney damage&lt;/a&gt; and make their waste clearance less effective. Drinking enough water can also help protect your kidneys in the long run – one review of 18 randomised controlled trials found that drinking more water could &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jamanetworkopen/fullarticle/2827021" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;help reduce the risk of kidney stones&lt;/a&gt;, among other benefits.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;So how much water is enough to help your body perform these essential functions? The widespread advice of eight glasses of water (around two litres) is outdated, stemming from &lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.bbc.com/future/article/20190403-how-much-water-should-you-drink-a-day" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;advice in 1945&lt;/a&gt; which included food as a source of water. Instead, &lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.bbc.com/news/uk-scotland-north-east-orkney-shetland-63755475" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;around 1.5 to 1.8 litres per day&lt;/a&gt; (six to seven-and-a-half glasses) is enough for most people.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BBC</author><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihAFBVV95cUxQYUtLMDFmYVJnY1pGNGdXd1VNNFk4bDJ3bV9WVnoxRWRJQ3I3d0J6OGhiSS1LaE5sbEtrYVQtZlNPMUNLRUVhN2RTVmpwRHB2anpHUmltS0c3eTZOcHNBa2FOYnZ0WDl0Ny1qSThUMUttT1NXbDZuMk41Qkl6NHA1ZVh4S2E</guid></item><item><title>全面的痛苦：我对抗集群头痛的神秘痛苦的战斗-卫报</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/society/2026/jan/06/cluster-headaches-full-blown-agony-battle-mysterious-pain</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body-commercial-selector article-body-viewer-selector dcr-hdpgoq"&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-15rw6c2"&gt;I&lt;/span&gt;t was a dreary Monday morning in September 2016, and I was working as a teacher, trying to settle a new year 7 class, when a sharp pain bloomed behind my right eye. It was followed by quick jolts, like electric shocks. As each class came and went, the pain eased and then returned with greater intensity. Four times that day I left a teaching assistant with worksheets and ran to the school bathroom to douse my face with cold water. I took ibuprofen, paracetamol, aspirin, but the pain remained unbearable.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The headaches appeared repeatedly that autumn, and again in spring, and soon formed an annual pattern. September and October were the worst, then February and March. I could predict the routine: aura in the shower, early twinges on the train, full-blown agony in class by 9.30am. In late 2019, a GP finally referred me to a neurologist and I was diagnosed with cluster headaches.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="sign-in-gate"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;aside data-spacefinder-role="showcase" data-gu-name="pullquote" class="dcr-v6upx6"&gt;&lt;svg viewbox="0 0 22 14" class="dcr-scql1j"&gt;&lt;path d="M5.255 0h4.75c-.572 4.53-1.077 8.972-1.297 13.941H0C.792 9.104 2.44 4.53 5.255 0Zm11.061 0H21c-.506 4.53-1.077 8.972-1.297 13.941h-8.686c.902-4.837 2.485-9.411 5.3-13.941Z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;blockquote class="dcr-zzndwp"&gt;Cluster headaches typically begin with severe pain around one eye that lasts up to three hours &lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;About one in 1,000 &lt;a href="https://www.brainresearchuk.org.uk/neurological-conditions/cluster-headache" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;people are affected&lt;/a&gt; by the condition, and men are more frequently diagnosed. Cluster headaches typically begin with sudden, severe pain around one eye that peaks within minutes and lasts up to three hours. Attacks come in clusters, daily or multiple times a day, and are accompanied by red or watery eyes, drooping eyelids or facial sweating. I have &lt;a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/books/NBK544241/#:~:text=Episodic:%2085%20to%2090%25%20of,15%20to%2020%25%20of%20patients." data-link-name="in body link"&gt;the episodic form&lt;/a&gt;, which arrives in seasonal bouts; others have chronic cluster headaches, defined by the absence of long pain-free periods.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;What unites sufferers is the intensity. One &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC7898696/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;study rated the pain&lt;/a&gt; at 9.7 out of 10, higher than bone fractures or pancreatitis. Another &lt;a href="https://journals.sagepub.com/doi/full/10.1177/0333102419845660?journalCode=cepa" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;found 64% of cluster headache patients&lt;/a&gt; experienced suicidal thoughts during bouts; the number dropped to 4% when they were not in pain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="f774e231-08c1-43bf-b825-95f2f93de50c" data-spacefinder-role="supporting" data-spacefinder-type="model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.ImageBlockElement" class="dcr-a2pvoh"&gt;&lt;figcaption data-spacefinder-role="inline" class="dcr-9ktzqp"&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-1inf02i"&gt;&lt;svg viewbox="0 0 18 13"&gt;&lt;path d="M18 3.5v8l-1.5 1.5h-15l-1.5-1.5v-8l1.5-1.5h3.5l2-2h4l2 2h3.5l1.5 1.5zm-9 7.5c1.9 0 3.5-1.6 3.5-3.5s-1.6-3.5-3.5-3.5-3.5 1.6-3.5 3.5 1.6 3.5 3.5 3.5z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-1qvd3m6"&gt;‘Greater occipital nerve blocks became my main preventive tool’ … Morgan Ofori.&lt;/span&gt; Photograph: Ethan Parker/The Guardian&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Val Hobbs, 74, a chronic sufferer from Pembrokeshire, isn’t surprised. Her attacks began when she was two. “I would throw myself on the floor and bang my head. That was put down to being spoiled,” she says. Her symptoms worsened through childhood. Alcohol in her teens, &lt;a href="https://headachejournal.onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1111/j.1526-4610.2008.01317.x" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;like many triggers&lt;/a&gt;, made things worse. After drinking sherry at her school leaving party, she recalls barely being able to see on the bus home.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Her family often interpreted her attacks as drunken episodes. Support eventually came from her father and then from her husband, Rod, who was diagnosed with epilepsy in early adulthood. “I was very lucky to find such an exceptional person,” she says. “We were meant to meet.” Hobbs took clerical work after moving to Wales in 1981, but often hid her condition. She was fired from one job, partly due to absences during attacks. Her breakthrough diagnosis came in 2002 at the &lt;a href="https://www.uclh.nhs.uk/our-services/our-hospitals/national-hospital-neurology-and-neurosurgery" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;National Hospital for Neurology and Neurosurgery&lt;/a&gt; in London.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Still, the inability to plan life around unpredictable attacks took its toll. She especially hated being unable to plan social events, being seen as unreliable as a colleague, and even having to be looked after by her children (at home and in public) in the midst of the paralysis caused by the worst episodes. “It robs you of the small freedoms we don’t appreciate until they’re gone,” she says. She remembers winning tickets for the queen’s golden jubilee concert, only to have an attack inside a portable toilet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr class="dcr-z9ge1j"&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-15rw6c2"&gt;H&lt;/span&gt;eadaches have been described throughout history. “The first description of headache comes by&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;way of the Mesopotamians in 4000BC,” write Seymour Diamond and Mary Franklin in their 2005 book, Headache Through the Ages. They attributed the disease to Tiu, an evil spirit who attacked his victims’ heads.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1353/bhm.2018.0030" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;The Ebers Papyrus&lt;/a&gt;, a record of ancient Egyptian medical knowledge dating from 1550BC, suggests crocodiles should be wrapped around the head to combat what some modern-day observers would describe as a migraine. In the middle ages, migraine was recognised as a distinct disorder, with treatments ranging from bloodletting and herbal concoctions to other, more superstitious remedies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;It was the Dutch physician Nicolaes Tulp who provided the first detailed description of a cluster headache. In his Observationes Medicae, published in 1641, Tulp speaks of a patient “afflicted with a very severe headache occurring and disappearing daily at fixed hours”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Cluster headaches were only officially recognised by the Headache Classification Committee of the International Headache Society in 1988. From the 1960s to the late 1990s, they were thought to be caused by a problem with the carotid artery, which supplies blood to the brain, says Prof Peter Goadsby, a leading specialist in diagnosing and treating the condition.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;In 1998, Goadsby and the neuroscientist Arne May published the results of a study for which they had triggered cluster headaches in patients and &lt;a href="https://www.thelancet.com/journals/lancet/article/PIIS0140-6736(98)02470-2/abstract" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;monitored the attacks in a brain scanner&lt;/a&gt;. The results, published in the Lancet, showed activation of the hypothalamus, which is responsible for human circadian rhythm, when patients were in pain, and a deactivation when they recovered.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="39a021b3-9aca-491f-8889-de01d30b7492" data-spacefinder-role="supporting" data-spacefinder-type="model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.ImageBlockElement" class="dcr-a2pvoh"&gt;&lt;figcaption data-spacefinder-role="inline" class="dcr-9ktzqp"&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-1inf02i"&gt;&lt;svg viewbox="0 0 18 13"&gt;&lt;path d="M18 3.5v8l-1.5 1.5h-15l-1.5-1.5v-8l1.5-1.5h3.5l2-2h4l2 2h3.5l1.5 1.5zm-9 7.5c1.9 0 3.5-1.6 3.5-3.5s-1.6-3.5-3.5-3.5-3.5 1.6-3.5 3.5 1.6 3.5 3.5 3.5z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-1qvd3m6"&gt;Jamie Charteris’s cluster headaches were misdiagnosed as sinus problems.&lt;/span&gt; Photograph: Handout&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Despite such advances, diagnosis remains slow. Jamie Charteris’s attacks began in 1986 and felt like “a modelling balloon being inflated behind my left eye”. GPs thought he had sinus problems; he underwent four surgeries before finally being diagnosed in 2014, after a doctor Googled his symptoms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Dr Nicholas Silver, a neurologist at the Walton Centre in Liverpool, says delays in diagnosis and treatment happen because patients are rarely seen mid-attack. “You’re tired and depressed, but not in agony,” he says. He proceeds by ruling out other primary headache disorders, such as migraine, tension-type, &lt;em&gt;hemicrania continua&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;paroxysmal hemicrania&lt;/em&gt; and SUNCT (short-lasting unilateral neuralgiformheadache), before diagnosing cluster headaches. A detailed history is essential: on which side do symptoms appear? For how long? What time of year? Are there triggers, such as alcohol? Do symptoms change with touch? Certain features such as redness, tearing, drooping eyelids and nasal congestion help confirm cluster headaches. Once diagnosed, patients may be referred to specialist centres including the Walton, or rapid-access clinics such as the one I attend at St Thomas’ hospital in London. But many first arrive in A&amp;amp;E or are given inadequate treatments.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Dorothy Chapman, 78, is a trustee of the UK charity Ouch (&lt;a href="https://ouchuk.org/home" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;Organisation for the Understanding of Cluster Headache&lt;/a&gt;). She has experienced cluster headaches for most of her life, although she hasn’t had an attack since 2016. When she was in her 20s, she had her teeth pulled because dentists misinterpreted her pain. She believes dentists still need much more awareness. When Charteris sought help from Ouch, it was Chapman who replied to his email. I remember calling the Ouch helpline during an attack in early 2021; a calm volunteer talked me through oxygen treatment and medication until the episode eased.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The National Institute for Health and Care Excellence (Nice) &lt;a href="https://www.nice.org.uk/guidance/cg150/ifp/chapter/Treatments-for-cluster-headache" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;guidance on treatment&lt;/a&gt; recommends sufferers are offered high-flow oxygen and/or the anti-migraine drug triptan delivered by injection or nasal spray. No tablets, painkillers or opioids should be used. Preventive options include verapamil, a blood pressure medication, which apparently soothes &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/film/2014/aug/17/-sp-daniel-radcliffe-speculating-sexuality-harry-potter" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;Harry Potter actor Daniel Radcliffe’s&lt;/a&gt; bouts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;But Dr Giorgio Lambru, the consultant neurologist who diagnosed me, believes the Nice guidance needs updating to reflect a clearer treatment pathway and help GPs avoid misprescribing. For episodic patients, he says, timing is everything: “The duration of the bout dictates the treatment.” Short bouts with infrequent attacks are handled with abortive therapy alone: triptan injections or nasal sprays, plus oxygen. Longer or more intense bouts require preventives such as verapamil, sometimes paired with steroids, which act quickly before wearing off. Many patients also receive a &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/24313966/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;greater occipital nerve block&lt;/a&gt; during a bout – an injection into the side of the head where the pain is that reduces nerve activity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;aside data-spacefinder-role="showcase" data-gu-name="pullquote" class="dcr-v6upx6"&gt;&lt;svg viewbox="0 0 22 14" class="dcr-scql1j"&gt;&lt;path d="M5.255 0h4.75c-.572 4.53-1.077 8.972-1.297 13.941H0C.792 9.104 2.44 4.53 5.255 0Zm11.061 0H21c-.506 4.53-1.077 8.972-1.297 13.941h-8.686c.902-4.837 2.485-9.411 5.3-13.941Z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;blockquote class="dcr-zzndwp"&gt;The Nice guidance needs updating to reflect a clearer treatment pathway and help GPs avoid misprescribing&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;If these fail, Lambru may consider topiramate, an anti-epilepsy medication, or vagus nerve stimulation devices. Chronic patients sometimes require multiple nerve blocks, radio-frequency treatment or, in rare cases, neuromodulation through occipital nerve stimulation, in which a battery-operated device is implanted and zaps the nerve to calm it down. Lambru stresses that, unlike in migraines, frequent use of triptans to treat cluster headache rarely causes medication-overuse headaches – an important point missing from many GP guidelines.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Patients also experiment with other approaches: cold air, cold showers, intense exercise, caffeine, vitamin D and &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/science/ng-interactive/2025/apr/23/cluster-headaches-magic-mushrooms-psilocybin" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;in some cases psychedelics&lt;/a&gt;, though evidence remains largely anecdotal, according to Lambru. One promising emerging option is CGRP (calcitonin gene-related peptide) targeting medication, used in migraine. Injectables such as galcanezumab, which aim to slow the potent inflammatory protein, &lt;a href="https://www.nejm.org/doi/full/10.1056/NEJMoa1813440" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;show potential for episodic&lt;/a&gt; cluster headache treatment &lt;a href="https://www.nice.org.uk/guidance/discontinued/gid-ta10425#:~:text=16%20November%202022-,Following%20on%20from%20information%20provided%20to%20NICE%20by%20the%20company,appraisal%20on%20its%20work%20programme." data-link-name="in body link"&gt;but are unavailable&lt;/a&gt; on the NHS.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;My own treatment journey has involved preventives and acute options when bouts strike. I briefly tried verapamil, but Covid restrictions made the required ECG monitoring (because of risks to the conduction of the heart) difficult. Oral steroids helped me temporarily but couldn’t be used long-term because of the increased risk of harm, such as weakened bones, eyesight problems and diabetes. Greater occipital nerve blocks became my main preventive tool. The moment I sense patterns emerging, I call the headache clinic at St Thomas’, and the nurses fit me in as soon as possible.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="684642a1-00ea-47a6-bf79-d716bf41661e" data-spacefinder-role="showcase" data-spacefinder-type="model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.ImageBlockElement" class="dcr-5h0uf4"&gt;&lt;figcaption data-spacefinder-role="inline" class="dcr-9ktzqp"&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-1inf02i"&gt;&lt;svg viewbox="0 0 18 13"&gt;&lt;path d="M18 3.5v8l-1.5 1.5h-15l-1.5-1.5v-8l1.5-1.5h3.5l2-2h4l2 2h3.5l1.5 1.5zm-9 7.5c1.9 0 3.5-1.6 3.5-3.5s-1.6-3.5-3.5-3.5-3.5 1.6-3.5 3.5 1.6 3.5 3.5 3.5z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-1qvd3m6"&gt;‘Oxygen therapy constricts dilated blood vessels, reducing the pressure and pain’ … Morgan Ofori.&lt;/span&gt; Photograph: Ethan Parker/The Guardian&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;When attacks hit, I use high-flow medical oxygen delivered to my home in tall industrial cylinders. The relief is extraordinary. Prof Goadsby and Dr Anna Cohen’s 2009 &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/19996400/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;study showed oxygen&lt;/a&gt; could make patients pain-free within 15 minutes, leading to its approval by Nice. During a cluster attack, blood flow in the brain increases. Oxygen therapy constricts the dilated blood vessels, reducing the pressure and pain while calming down overactive nerves. The drug sumatriptan, which reduces the release of pain-causing chemicals and blocks pain signals from being transmitted to the brain, never worked for me, despite trying several forms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Hobbs also relies heavily on oxygen, though she believes demand-valve masks, which deliver big bursts of oxygen quickly, could improve outcomes. Ouch has campaigned for wider access to these masks, though Lambru notes evidence is still emerging. The challenge is that only about one in 10 UK patients use or have access to oxygen – a stark shortfall, considering its effectiveness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr class="dcr-z9ge1j"&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-15rw6c2"&gt;A&lt;/span&gt;t Ouch’s annual conference in Newcastle last summer, about 100 sufferers gathered with neurologists. There were quiet rooms, oxygen stations and sessions on new research and coping strategies. A recurring theme was the need for better data. Headache diaries help clinicians recognise patterns, but until recently most were kept by hand.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Inspired by his own struggles, 37-year-old web developer Darshan Ramanagoudra created MyClusters, a free app for tracking attacks, triggers and treatment effectiveness. Within its first month, users from more than a dozen countries logged thousands of attacks. Ramanagoudra hopes better data will reduce misdiagnosis and strengthen research.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“By the summer of 2023, I was getting multiple daily attacks. By the winter, it was about six a day, and that’s when I started reading a lot of medical papers,” says Ramanagoudra, who is based in the Netherlands. He consulted doctors and researchers to see what the online community in the Netherlands was saying, then started tracking it all on a spreadsheet. “It got a bit complicated, and I realised I could do pivot tables and things, but I figured someone else would want additional information. How were they going to do it?” The idea for MyClusters was born.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="469ffe48-c9f8-4f90-9ce5-4532f557ec09" data-spacefinder-role="richLink" data-spacefinder-type="model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.RichLinkBlockElement" class="dcr-47fhrn"&gt;&lt;gu-island name="RichLinkComponent" priority="feature" deferuntil="idle" props='{"richLinkIndex":32,"element":{"_type":"model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.RichLinkBlockElement","prefix":"Related: ","text":"Cluster headaches are ‘the most painful condition on the planet’. Sufferers are going to extreme – and secretive – measures for relief","elementId":"469ffe48-c9f8-4f90-9ce5-4532f557ec09","role":"richLink","url":"https://www.theguardian.com/science/ng-interactive/2025/apr/23/cluster-headaches-magic-mushrooms-psilocybin"},"ajaxUrl":"https://api.nextgen.guardianapps.co.uk","format":{"design":10,"display":2,"theme":0}}'&gt;&lt;/gu-island&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The percentage of cluster headache sufferers, diagnosed or undiagnosed, in each country is estimated to be about 6.5%, says Tom Zeller Jr, the author of the 2025 book The Headache: The Science of a Most Confounding Condition – and a Search for Relief. However, in terms of funding and research, “cluster headaches are given short shrift compared with the impact it has on our economies and on people’s individual lives”, he says. He believes this is a mistake. “It’s not a terminal disease, it’s a lifelong disease. But if you add up all the time a person spends being disabled by these bouts of head pain and other neurological symptoms, it adds up to a lot.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;I’ve just emerged from my latest autumn bout. This time the pain struck on the left side, a first for me, and I received my first multi-cranial block to treat it. I was injected four times in the side of my head, plus another shot at the back. I’m not needle-phobic; I imagine I’m giving blood from my skull. The approach seems to have worked. Using MyClusters to track patterns, I’ve been headache-free for nearly six weeks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Winter brings respite, and is a time of calm. But sometime in this new year, I know the cycle will begin again. Cluster headaches are my own recurring, disabling season, never too far around the corner.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Guardian</author><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiqAFBVV95cUxQaHMtcE9Ha09kMzBPY3lId0lGcEQ2cXIzU0FYZHRtd3pOOTE2Vjlya2hEOU1VVl9leDhpRUlhTWtxMXFEeFpIRy1UWGZDUXpWQk1kbkN6U1ZSb1FhOHlOTzItdFJxOW5OZ1ItMTk4cGR4amRDenk0Q0dCUGNiUU53LVhwUF9YQ2htdmh2NUk5VDlMbHZ2cW1FcVdxbjdoSlNtLUdpQ2llSHA</guid></item><item><title>凯霍加县的主要过量杀手现在是可卡因。我们如何对待它？ - Cleveland.com</title><link>https://www.cleveland.com/news/2026/01/cuyahoga-countys-leading-overdose-killer-is-now-cocaine-how-do-we-treat-it.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content   "&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="TBSDUL54HVFZBJZXS7TTQPTZAQ"&gt;CLEVELAND, Ohio — For the first time in decades, cocaine is killing more people in Cuyahoga County than opioids – including fentanyl – and the drug is going to require a different type of treatment and prevention strategy to combat it. But what could that look like?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-1" data-gaid="inarticle-1"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="MSRCJKHCTNHNNN54BMMEILLALU"&gt;Medical Examiner Dr. Thomas Gilson started to notice a shift in overdose deaths early last year. As opioid overdoses continued to fall, &lt;a href="https://www.cleveland.com/news/2025/09/enemy-number-one-cocaine-now-deadlier-than-fentanyl-in-cuyahoga-county.html" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://www.cleveland.com/news/2025/09/enemy-number-one-cocaine-now-deadlier-than-fentanyl-in-cuyahoga-county.html"&gt;cocaine-related deaths were rising&lt;/a&gt;, accounting for 63% of cases, compared with 46% involving opioids, including some overlap from drug mixtures. At the time, he predicted cocaine would kill 399 Cuyahogans by the end of the year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-2" data-gaid="inarticle-2"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="JUN2X57XUBA7LP3A5IYKINAJM4"&gt;During recent budget talks before County Council, Gilson noted cocaine deaths will drop slightly as toxicology screenings are completed, but the drug still remains the top killer. Its victims: primarily older Black residents, echoing patterns from the 1980s and 1990s crack-cocaine crisis. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-3" data-gaid="inarticle-3"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="AVC3RQINONAH5JP6AH3NDHSANA"&gt;Gilson said it marks a new phase of the overdose crisis, one that will require a new kind of response than what the county developed during the opioid epidemic. That means different prevention strategies to target Black communities – which have historically had a mistrust of medical systems and limited access to addiction treatment – and a greater focus on stimulant treatments. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-4" data-gaid="inarticle-4"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="URFR45BOLNEJJM7FJE32NDKLE4"&gt;“It doesn’t mean the opioid crisis is over and the interventions that we have put forth are ineffective anymore, but we’re going to start to see stimulants, specifically cocaine and to a lesser extent methamphetamine, account for more and more overdose deaths, and we should be thinking now, how do we pivot to respond to that?” Gilson argued to County Council. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-5" data-gaid="inarticle-5"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="TNRARQDE5FES7CJL4ZEPFI7GKQ"&gt;Addiction treatment experts say that shift could be tricky. Dr. Megan Testa, medical director of psychiatric services at the county’s Diversion Center, and Sarah Tkac, clinical manager at Oriana House, noted that the two drugs affect the body differently, requiring different treatment strategies, which just aren’t as developed for stimulants. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-6" data-gaid="inarticle-6"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="OBPOKNCLCFF5BMODMNGXASVVTY"&gt;For opioid use, there’s methadone, buprenorphine, naltrexone, Suboxone and Vivitrol to ease withdrawal symptoms or block the receptors that drive compulsive use, and there’s Naloxone to reverse the effects of an overdose – allowing users another chance, perhaps, to get sober. For cocaine, though, there is no overdose-reversal drug or medications to help people taper off it. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-7" data-gaid="inarticle-7"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="KACYVQ5QYBAR7BVSANR2U2EASA"&gt;“We really have a lot of meds in our toolbox for opiate use disorder, which is probably because of the money and the research that’s gone into it,” Testa said. “But cocaine use disorder is not the same. We just don’t have those tools.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-8" data-gaid="inarticle-8"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="article-heading"&gt;‘There’s no pill for this’ &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-9" data-gaid="inarticle-9"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="Y62O5WRR4JBCDAQQ5YHCG5KWQY"&gt;While both drugs flood the brain with the feel-good hormone dopamine, they affect the body in opposite ways. Opioids suppress the nervous system, leading to slowed breathing and overdose that can be reversed with naloxone. Cocaine and other stimulants overstimulate the heart and brain, often triggering fatal arrhythmias or strokes that come on too fast for emergency intervention. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-10" data-gaid="inarticle-10"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="LICY7RPBI5GYTJBEUTTUQKBQ54"&gt;The biology shapes treatment. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-11" data-gaid="inarticle-11"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="M3S5VVV4JFFS5H6X6UJCFDHP5Q"&gt;Opioid withdrawal, sometimes called “dope sickness,” can be excruciating. Users get extremely sick, experiencing muscle aches, nausea, vomiting, diarrhea, sweating, agitation and severe cravings that often drive them to seek out more of the drug to stop the pain. That’s why opioid addiction is typically managed through medication that curbs cravings and stabilizes the brain to reduce the risk of relapse. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-12" data-gaid="inarticle-12"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="R74FW7N3HNELPO4PCC3347GWFM"&gt;Cocaine withdrawal, by contrast, is marked by psychological symptoms, such as fatigue, depression and increased appetite. Users “crash” and “just want to eat everything and sleep,” Testa said, but they don’t experience the type of physical symptoms seen with opioids. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-13" data-gaid="inarticle-13"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="XP3CN3Z5AND53JSULZLG7THGYU"&gt;For stimulants, treatment relies almost entirely on behavioral therapies: cognitive behavioral therapy, motivational interviewing and contingency management, a reward-based approach that pays or recognizes patients for milestones like negative drug screens. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-14" data-gaid="inarticle-14"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="55RG5LGZRZAH7APAG57JXXWCMU"&gt;“There’s no pill for this,” as Tkac puts it; which can also make it harder to treat – and to access treatment. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-15" data-gaid="inarticle-15"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="7IVH4CRI3NDGHJTMQBIO2JRIQQ"&gt;Most detox centers won’t admit patients experiencing cocaine or methamphetamine withdrawal because there are no meds to manage or to bill for, the pair agree. That means people seeking help are often left to manage the symptoms and stay sober on their own. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-16" class="middleParagraph" data-gaid="inarticle-16"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="EBET22OSXZCNZL2VFHQMRTK63A"&gt;“Right now, you can walk in anywhere and get some kind of detox treatment for opioids, but if you go with a cocaine disorder, you could be shown the door,” Tkac said. “So maybe that’s where we need to pivot in this community to be more open to whatever substance people present with.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-17" data-gaid="inarticle-17"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="article-heading"&gt;Ideas for more effective treatment &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-18" data-gaid="inarticle-18"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="L2YBCP5ZYBDZZHZWDM45BY56RQ"&gt;Some researchers have been exploring vaccines to prevent cocaine highs or other methods that might help people metabolize stimulants faster, which may mitigate the potential for overdoses. Others have been testing the effects of mood-stabilizers on treating cocaine to replace the dopamine hit they crave. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-19" data-gaid="inarticle-19"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="6BTYOXOH6RBJLAD3CVLTATWPNY"&gt;Testa said they even prescribe some of those medications at the Diversion Center, the county-owned treatment center, but they’re not FDA-approved for cocaine treatment. They’re “off-label” uses, until the research catches up, she said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-20" data-gaid="inarticle-20"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="WT2P6NWNSNDQZPRMP3V75GJKFQ"&gt;To truly close the gap, the experts say treatment centers will need to view stimulant use disorder as seriously as opioid addiction and beef up behavioral health care to address it, rather than relying on medication management. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-21" data-gaid="inarticle-21"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="YGAX5775HJEDFINEWEYYASXBXE"&gt;Because “drugs are never the problem,” Tkac stressed, they’re just the solution people use to deal with whatever problem they’re seeking to avoid, often rooted in some kind of trauma. She noted that over 90% of the clients they see at Oriana House have been diagnosed with PTSD. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-22" data-gaid="inarticle-22"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="34NAYOH2HJDLNA24BP5OSPVEEE"&gt;In those cases, the majority of people are using drugs as a coping mechanism to avoid feeling pain. Removing the drug doesn’t address the underlying cause, they said, it just sends people searching for another filler. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-23" data-gaid="inarticle-23"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="MN56ZMFEO5B6RARUGBPYRV26II"&gt;“If we’re not treating the problem, it doesn’t matter what substance you use,” Tkac said. “So, really getting good trauma therapy is one of the most essential things you can do for recovery, because that’s the problem.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-24" data-gaid="inarticle-24"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="XGARJCPY4VBAXAT2FW4M7RWE7E"&gt;That starts with reducing the mental health stigma so people are more open to treatment options. It also means beefing up recovery coaching for stimulant users, so they have peer support while they address their addiction. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-25" data-gaid="inarticle-25"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="VR4DDUSK3BFZNPQU223ODQQCNI"&gt;But above all, it means “meeting people where they’re at,” Testa argued. That means providing harm reduction tools in the meantime, like safer-smoking kits with supplies to prevent exposure to other toxins and communicable diseases, and fentanyl test strips to avoid contamination that may increase the likelihood of an overdose. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-26" data-gaid="inarticle-26"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="5ZP27TQUT5GLLONJD7PAZEVA6Y"&gt;She equated it to the needle exchange programs that became more popular during the heroin and opioid epidemics and reduced the spread of HIV. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-27" data-gaid="inarticle-27"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="5SI2QXEQCZDOZEDAJQSJDTLVLM"&gt;“It brought people into treatment,” Testa said. “It didn’t just help people use more, those people were going to use anyways, but...it helped people use more safely and get into treatment.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-28" data-gaid="inarticle-28"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="NJ4AJJJZTRA67L7J6NPAQUIJUA"&gt;Without these shifts, the experts say the system can only keep playing catch-up. It was the same fear Gilson expressed when urging the county to act now to address cocaine overdoses – before more lives are lost. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-29" data-gaid="inarticle-29"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="6GYJBGSWVBGCHE35I4H7G3VU4M"&gt;“This is a population who paid with their life to teach us a lesson,” Gilson said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-30" data-gaid="inarticle-30"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-enter:BN5TBABJ6ZHCXAOPNOU4DHSUE4" data-fusion-component="BN5TBABJ6ZHCXAOPNOU4DHSUE4"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-exit:BN5TBABJ6ZHCXAOPNOU4DHSUE4" data-fusion-component="BN5TBABJ6ZHCXAOPNOU4DHSUE4"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-31" data-gaid="inarticle-31"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Cleveland.com</author><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiugFBVV95cUxOaVRjcEY3bk5ySS1PeFBxNDA0M1kybTZDSlhKcHFWVl83Sm5YTGx3d2JzUVg4dW5LbDJlR1R3RkVObzQ0TVNSWkxCNDVHRVJibVljQ3poOXkwX0RxOGJGZ3liV3FLRm5TSlRJSkZNRmdPU0ROYWFJeWJwZDNRTDRoUDVUNjRKSzhHbTZjRE1BVVVwZ2lNZ21ObWMwbTJuZXd3ZEtyZmhuT3IwS1FvSWs0aHhmUU9LOTItZVHSAc4BQVVfeXFMTkllWm52RTVOeXRSSXEzSVZ2d2Q3WU1XdUlSa3FSN3F3RHl3WXRhUURpUC03V09mUl9UQlNlT0RmVXFqNFBPb1dJbVdRQ21ydGRMWERHM3VKQUhZZlZINEVUTDBjcXRiS1RJTHFMcmdiUTRvYmp1M0swQzdpcGdUdVJBVE1rakdFdmZzeFlrX3dQeklIN2d5VEJjejhnQjdHek81Q2tBZS1nazJXX3Q0M0RYUGtUdnNlQkRwQlZialpINHNHU2EzTkZUM2tGNmc</guid></item><item><title>特朗普， RFK大幅调整儿童疫苗接种时间表- Axios</title><link>https://www.axios.com/2026/01/05/trump-rfk-kennedy-vaccine-schedule-children</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Axios</author><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 09:26:18 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiggFBVV95cUxNcV9NZ2Q3NEdEWGVLdDlwbXhnWVJibGNNbUtiTkc4cGd3aU9TTmRGQzlzWUlzaDhxX1JmME1rMnRIQ1JnNWRNZWtfM2lCcElKdm1VRXdERXJ0cTZKT19GQnFFdkZkakVpcEV0Q2R6cnNtejg1MjZEQmV3bGk0ci1OeHRn</guid></item><item><title>我每周不做饭就吃30棵植物，养成4种节省时间的习惯- Business Insider</title><link>https://www.businessinsider.com/eat-30-plants-week-fiber-gut-health-time-saving-habits-2025-12</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;section class="post-body-content post-story-body-content" data-component-type="post-body-content" data-load-strategy="exclude" data-track-content="" data-post-type="story" data-track-marfeel="post-body-content"&gt;
            
                &lt;p&gt;I try to eat &lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.businessinsider.com/eating-30-plants-a-week-gut-health-easier-2024-6" data-track-click='{"element_name":"body_link","event":"tout_click","index":"bi_value_unassigned","product_field":"bi_value_unassigned"}' rel=""&gt;30 different types of plant&lt;/a&gt; foods a week for a healthy gut microbiome.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It might sound like a lot, but I manage it as a recovering picky eater who doesn't meal prep (I'd rather spend my precious Sunday afternoons lying down).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As a child (read: young adult), I recoiled at the sight of greenery on my plate. I looked at a raspberry and saw only unappealing little hairs. Even a slice of buttered whole wheat toast had me running for the door because it tasted too healthy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Around five years ago, I realized that I needed to expand my culinary horizons, if not for the enjoyment then for my health. Fruits, vegetables, as well as wholegrains, legumes, nuts, and seeds, not only contain micronutrients and vitamins crucial for bodily processes and general health, they're also high in gut-friendly fiber.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://journals.asm.org/doi/10.1128/msystems.00031-18" data-track-click='{"click_type":"other","element_name":"body_link","event":"outbound_click"}' rel=" nofollow"&gt;2018 study&lt;/a&gt; called The American Gut Project found that people who ate 30 plant foods a week had more "good" bacteria and less "bad" bacteria in their guts than those who ate 10. It gave me an easy framework to follow for eating healthily.&lt;/p&gt;
              
            
              
            &lt;p&gt;Gut health has strong links to overall health. As well as digestion, &lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.businessinsider.com/gut-health-boost-overall-digestion-better-moods-2024-7" data-track-click='{"element_name":"body_link","event":"tout_click","index":"bi_value_unassigned","product_field":"bi_value_unassigned"}' rel=""&gt;the gut microbiome&lt;/a&gt;, the trillions of microbes that live in the colon lining, is thought to influence our mood, skin, hormones, immune system, weight, and possibly even cancer risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Research suggests that a &lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.businessinsider.com/plant-based-shopping-list-dietitian-no-meal-prep-2024-3" data-track-click='{"element_name":"body_link","event":"tout_click","index":"bi_value_unassigned","product_field":"bi_value_unassigned"}' rel=""&gt;diverse gut microbiome&lt;/a&gt; is a healthy one, and that eating a wide range of fiber-rich foods, i.e., plants, boosts diversity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Here are the four time-saving habits I've built in the past five years&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;that help me eat 30 plant foods a week.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="1d1c3aea-4d55-405c-9cc8-6a31e0782020" data-toc-id="1d1c3aea-4d55-405c-9cc8-6a31e0782020"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Keeping leafy greens in the freezer&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
              &lt;figure class="figure image-figure-image   " data-type="img" data-e2e-name="image-figure-image" data-media-container="image" itemscope="" itemtype="https://schema.org/ImageObject"&gt;
              
              
                
              
              &lt;span class="image-source-caption "&gt;
                    &lt;figcaption class="image-caption headline-semibold" data-e2e-name="image-caption"&gt;
                      A typical dinner of grilled fish with canned chickpeas, grilled with zucchini, cherry tomatoes, onion, and garlic.
                      
              &lt;span class="image-source headline-regular" data-e2e-name="image-source" itemprop="creditText"&gt;
              
              Kim Schewitz
              
              &lt;/span&gt;
                    &lt;/figcaption&gt;
                  &lt;/span&gt;
              &lt;/figure&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;I always keep a bag of spinach and a bag of kale in my freezer and add them to any meal lacking veggies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.businessinsider.com/why-salad-greens-are-good-for-brain-health-aging-2024-7" data-track-click='{"element_name":"body_link","event":"tout_click","index":"bi_value_unassigned","product_field":"bi_value_unassigned"}' rel=""&gt;Dark leafy greens&lt;/a&gt; not only contain fiber, but are high in chlorophyll, the molecule that gives them their rich color. Chlorophyll is densely packed with essential nutrients, including iron, magnesium, and nitrogen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It takes seconds to reach for a handful of frozen leaves, and I can add them to almost anything I'm cooking, from pasta sauce or curry, to scrambled eggs. It involves no preparation or additional steps, and instantly makes any meal more nutritious.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="4200054b-7a25-4029-a183-d633283a6897" data-toc-id="4200054b-7a25-4029-a183-d633283a6897"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Always have pre-cooked grains to hand&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
              &lt;figure class="figure image-figure-image   " data-type="img" data-e2e-name="image-figure-image" data-media-container="image" itemscope="" itemtype="https://schema.org/ImageObject"&gt;
              
              
                
              
              &lt;span class="image-source-caption "&gt;
                    &lt;figcaption class="image-caption headline-semibold" data-e2e-name="image-caption"&gt;
                      Schewitz used tinned lentils to make a stew with tomatoes, zucchini, and mozzarella.
                      
              &lt;span class="image-source headline-regular" data-e2e-name="image-source" itemprop="creditText"&gt;
              
              Kim Schewitz
              
              &lt;/span&gt;
                    &lt;/figcaption&gt;
                  &lt;/span&gt;
              &lt;/figure&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;While I can quickly whip up &lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.businessinsider.com/how-to-eat-enough-protein-without-skimping-on-fiber-2025-11" data-track-click='{"element_name":"body_link","event":"tout_click","index":"bi_value_unassigned","product_field":"bi_value_unassigned"}' rel=""&gt;vegetables and protein&lt;/a&gt;, I often find it's the carb element of my meals that takes the most time to prepare.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When I cook whole grains like brown rice or quinoa, I make extra to put in a sandwich bag and freeze. I also buy bags of pre-cooked grains, which I love to add to salads or eat with fish and veggies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Keeping my kitchen stocked with pre-cooked whole grains, dry whole wheat pasta, and frozen whole wheat sourdough speeds up cooking and are great sources of fiber.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="2dec175e-30e5-4c34-aae8-4701093f3d62" data-toc-id="2dec175e-30e5-4c34-aae8-4701093f3d62"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fibermaxxing at breakfast&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
              &lt;figure class="figure image-figure-image   " data-type="img" data-e2e-name="image-figure-image" data-media-container="image" itemscope="" itemtype="https://schema.org/ImageObject"&gt;
              
              
                
              
              &lt;span class="image-source-caption "&gt;
                    &lt;figcaption class="image-caption headline-semibold" data-e2e-name="image-caption"&gt;
                      Schewitz's gut-friendly breakfast comes together in minutes.
                      
              &lt;span class="image-source headline-regular" data-e2e-name="image-source" itemprop="creditText"&gt;
              
              Kim Schewitz
              
              &lt;/span&gt;
                    &lt;/figcaption&gt;
                  &lt;/span&gt;
              &lt;/figure&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;I've previously written about the &lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.businessinsider.com/quick-easy-high-protein-high-fiber-breakfast-every-morning-2025-11" data-track-click='{"element_name":"body_link","event":"tout_click","index":"bi_value_unassigned","product_field":"bi_value_unassigned"}' rel=""&gt;high-fiber breakfast&lt;/a&gt; I eat every day, which consists of Greek Yogurt, berries, peanut butter, and a selection of nuts and seeds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I switch up the ingredients depending on what I have in the cupboard, but typically it provides me with around seven different plant foods and around 7 grams of fiber.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It's so quick to put together and helps me start my day with a big hit of fiber.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="db9af5d0-bf77-4c94-b700-b9f78fa77d00" data-toc-id="db9af5d0-bf77-4c94-b700-b9f78fa77d00"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Gamifying eating vegetables&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
              &lt;figure class="figure image-figure-image   " data-type="img" data-e2e-name="image-figure-image" data-media-container="image" itemscope="" itemtype="https://schema.org/ImageObject"&gt;
              
              
                
              
              &lt;span class="image-source-caption "&gt;
                    &lt;figcaption class="image-caption headline-semibold" data-e2e-name="image-caption"&gt;
                      Schewitz always tries to add an extra vegetable to her meals.
                      
              &lt;span class="image-source headline-regular" data-e2e-name="image-source" itemprop="creditText"&gt;
              
              Kim Schewitz
              
              &lt;/span&gt;
                    &lt;/figcaption&gt;
                  &lt;/span&gt;
              &lt;/figure&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;I set myself a goal of buying at least three types of vegetables a week, and making sure I eat them before they spoil.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If they don't pair well with my meals, I eat them as a snack. For example, I recently chopped up a whole cabbage, cooked it down on the stovetop with garlic, ginger, soy sauce, and rice vinegar, and warmed up little portions throughout the week whenever I felt like it. It took about 15 minutes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I find this helpful little challenge gets me in the habit of &lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.businessinsider.com/how-to-eat-more-fiber-without-feeling-gassy-2025-11" data-track-click='{"element_name":"body_link","event":"tout_click","index":"bi_value_unassigned","product_field":"bi_value_unassigned"}' rel=""&gt;adding more plants&lt;/a&gt; to my diet because I get dopamine from "winning" the game.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Now that I've developed these habits, I don't worry too much about hitting my plant count because I know I'm consistently eating fiber-filled, nutritious foods.&lt;/p&gt;
            
            
            &lt;/section&gt;
            
            
            
            
            
            
    
    
    
    
      &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Business Insider</author><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 08:56:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimgFBVV95cUxPWG45bjhlZlM2S3gzUUc1Tlpvem5ObjN4SmhTYUhtd1JkZHRoVE9kVjU5YmNpVW5DRzVsVzJnemJZTDRybXlXamZ6bVNNVldRQkxiR0NVQnJoanlYX3E2cktJUzhlSmoyUDhGelpGZWlpYkVXYURFNlJHY2U1c1NPNVl2VFZLV3RoTW56R25RbF9ZOEp4Q21ySWhn</guid></item><item><title>斯坦福大学神经科学家安德鲁·休伯曼（ Andrew Huberman ）说，一个早晨的习惯为他的一天定下了基调-商业内幕</title><link>https://www.businessinsider.com/andrew-huberman-podcast-morning-routine-health-daylight-2026-1</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;section class="post-body-content post-story-body-content" data-component-type="post-body-content" data-load-strategy="exclude" data-track-content="" data-post-type="story" data-track-marfeel="post-body-content"&gt;
            
                &lt;p&gt;Stanford neuroscientist Andrew Huberman says one &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="https://www.businessinsider.com/daily-routines-successful-business-people-share-power-hours-2026-1" data-track-click='{"element_name":"body_link","event":"tout_click","index":"bi_value_unassigned","product_field":"bi_value_unassigned"}' rel=""&gt;morning habit&lt;/a&gt; plays a key role in his overall health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In an interview &lt;a target="_blank" class="" href="https://www.gq.com/story/andrew-huberman-diet-advice" data-track-click='{"click_type":"other","element_name":"body_link","event":"outbound_click"}' rel=" nofollow"&gt;with GQ&lt;/a&gt; published on Monday, the host of the popular "Huberman Lab" podcast shared the routines he's relying on to stay healthy in 2026.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Getting your physical health right — which puts your mental health in the best possible place — is all about intentionally high cortisol in the morning and intentionally low cortisol at night," Huberman told GQ.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Although cortisol has a bad reputation as a &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="https://www.businessinsider.com/reference/how-to-lower-cortisol" data-track-click='{"element_name":"body_link","event":"tout_click","index":"bi_value_unassigned","product_field":"bi_value_unassigned"}' rel=""&gt;stress hormone&lt;/a&gt;, Huberman says it plays an important role in how the body transitions from sleep to wakefulness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"No, you wake up in the morning because of a rise in cortisol. You want a big, massive spike of cortisol in the morning. If you don't spike your morning cortisol, your cortisol spikes in the afternoon or evening, and then everything goes awry, OK? You want your morning cortisol at least 30x higher than your nighttime cortisol," he said.&lt;/p&gt;
              
            
              &lt;div class="dynamic-module" data-component-type="dynamic-module" data-load-strategy="disable-lazy"&gt;
            
                  &lt;div class="dynamic-module-components" data-component-name="follow-author-inline-signup" data-component-segment="anonymous-fly-by"&gt;
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    &lt;div data-component-type="follow-author-inline-signup" data-author='{"name":"Amanda Goh","id":"amanda-goh","shortenedName":"Amanda","image":{"type":"image","id":"68ddccd81c1f80efbec4c095","attributes":{"caption":"Amanda Goh","contentType":"image/jpeg","description":"Amanda Goh","height":2617,"source":"Mount Studio","width":2617},"links":{"self":"https://i.insider.com/68ddccd81c1f80efbec4c095"}},"links":{"self":"https://cda.businessinsider.com/author/amanda-goh","site":"https://www.businessinsider.com/author/amanda-goh","twitter":{"href":"https://twitter.com/agohjourno","meta":{"username":"agohjourno"}}}}' data-load-strategy="exclude" class="follow-author-inline-signup" data-track-view='{"subscription_experience":"bi_value_unassigned","product_field":"inline","element_name":"follow_author","event":"module_in_view"}'&gt;
                        
                      &lt;div class="content-wrapper"&gt;
                        
                        &lt;p class="body-sm-subtle body"&gt;
                          Every time Amanda publishes a story, you’ll get an alert straight to your inbox!
                        &lt;/p&gt;
                        &lt;p class="body-sm-subtle body-sm"&gt;
                          Stay connected to Amanda and get more of their work as it publishes.
                        &lt;/p&gt;
                        
                      &lt;/div&gt;
                    &lt;/div&gt;
                  &lt;/div&gt;
                  
            
            
              &lt;/div&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;One way to keep that rhythm on track would be to send the body a signal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The best way to spike your morning cortisol is to &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="https://www.businessinsider.com/kate-hudson-morning-routine-phone-free-sunlight-outdoors-meditation-2025-10" data-track-click='{"element_name":"body_link","event":"tout_click","index":"bi_value_unassigned","product_field":"bi_value_unassigned"}' rel=""&gt;get bright light&lt;/a&gt; — ideally from sunlight — in your eyes in the first hour after waking. If you can't do that, maybe invest in a 10,000 Lux artificial light," Huberman said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If that's not possible, he suggests flipping on "as many artificial lights as you can."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I've made a mistake in the past — a tactical mistake, a strategic mistake — by calling it sunlight&lt;em&gt;.&lt;/em&gt; People say, 'It's overcast.' What we should say is, 'Get daylight in your eyes,'" he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Having dim mornings and bright nights is "the worst way to go," he added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Light exposure isn't the only thing Huberman says matters in the morning. He also encourages people to &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="https://www.businessinsider.com/helen-mirren-aging-wellness-fitness-routine-exercise-military-workout-longevity-2025-4" data-track-click='{"element_name":"body_link","event":"tout_click","index":"bi_value_unassigned","product_field":"bi_value_unassigned"}' rel=""&gt;fit in a workout&lt;/a&gt; if they can.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"If you don't have time to exercise first thing in the morning, you need bodily movement. Even some knee bends, some arm swings, some jumping jacks. Movement generates cortisol and adrenaline," he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When it comes to winding down at night, people should take the opposite approach, Huberman said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"If you want to wear BluBlockers, you can. But dim the lights down, avoid caffeine. If you're going to exercise, don't make it terribly intense," he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The benefits of getting light in the mornings are supported by broader research in the field.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mariana Figueiro, professor and director of the Light and Health Research Center at the Icahn School of Medicine at Mount Sinai, told Business Insider in 2023 that &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="https://www.businessinsider.com/andrew-huberman-swears-by-morning-sunlight-healthy-circadian-clock-2023-11" data-track-click='{"element_name":"body_link","event":"tout_click","index":"bi_value_unassigned","product_field":"bi_value_unassigned"}' rel=""&gt;getting daylight&lt;/a&gt; is "just as important as diet and exercise."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Light in the built environment is not always strong enough to synchronize the biological clock," Figueiro said. "The beauty of daylight is that daylight is the right amount, it's the right color, it's on at the right time."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Moreover, getting enough darkness at night is just as crucial, since circadian disruption has been linked to poor cognitive performance and a weakened immune system, Figueiro said.&lt;/p&gt;
            
            
            &lt;/section&gt;
            
            
            
            
            
            
    
    
    
    
      &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Business Insider</author><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 05:03:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimgFBVV95cUxOVVdjRzFiUmJEOTBXamtRd01uT3IxUGhuYVFvMjdzTVRtQ0QzZzdTbmhFN3dOMXd4T01hczB6N0gwdklWY0hkcDhKT2wtUVpfdnZlRmpvR284U3R5RHh2TmRZVWd5UDU5R0p5c1BHOUtkemExeWx3bnp3NXA5TDFFZTJ4M3B0VGl0Q2dSTE9rUjliRkdRMGpYcUln</guid></item><item><title>所以你今年想减肥... - Escape Collective</title><link>https://escapecollective.com/so-you-want-to-lose-weight-this-year/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article__top"&gt;
                
                &lt;div class="article__top-right"&gt;
                        &lt;a class="article__category" href="https://escapecollective.com/tag/nutrition/"&gt;nutrition&lt;/a&gt;
                    &lt;h1 class="article__title"&gt;So you want to lose weight this year ...&lt;/h1&gt;
                        &lt;p class="article__sub-title"&gt;In part one of this two-part series, dietitian Dr Alan McCubbin takes aim at weight-loss-related new year's resolutions.&lt;/p&gt;
                    &lt;p class="article__thumbnail-caption"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Image: &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://unsplash.com/@foodistika"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Elena Leya&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;/Unsplash&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
                &lt;/div&gt;
            &lt;/div&gt;
        &lt;article class="article"&gt;
                


            

&lt;p class="photo-by"&gt;Elena Leya&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As 2025 drew to a close, you were no doubt flooded with social media posts from your family, friends, work colleagues, and those randoms that somehow show up in your feed ‘cause the algorithm said so’. They were probably full of reflections on the year just gone, and full of hope for the year ahead. This time, they said, things will be different. A fresh start. A new them (funnily enough, that’s what last year’s posts said too). You may have made a similar post yourself. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The most common of all new year’s resolutions is a commitment to improving physical and mental health. Working less. Sleeping more. Getting out on the bike more often. And of course, eating better. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But the thing with new year’s resolutions, like most overly optimistic plans, is that they rarely survive contact with the real world. Those couple of weeks of blue-sky thinking in late December quickly make way for the sad realities of February; realities that were so obvious in hindsight yet completely overlooked at the time. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In this piece, we’re going to take a different look at nutrition-related new year’s resolutions, and leave you with some ideas that might help make dietary changes that survive to see the start of March.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="kg-card kg-image-card kg-card-hascaption"&gt;&lt;img src="https://escapecollective.com/content/images/2026/01/carson-arias-7zZLoemCauo-unsplash.jpg" class="kg-image" alt="" loading="lazy" srcset="https://escapecollective.com/content/images/size/w600/2026/01/carson-arias-7zZLoemCauo-unsplash.jpg 600w, https://escapecollective.com/content/images/size/w1000/2026/01/carson-arias-7zZLoemCauo-unsplash.jpg 1000w, https://escapecollective.com/content/images/size/w1600/2026/01/carson-arias-7zZLoemCauo-unsplash.jpg 1600w, https://escapecollective.com/content/images/2026/01/carson-arias-7zZLoemCauo-unsplash.jpg 1920w" sizes="(min-width: 720px) 720px"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;span&gt;New year, new you? Best to make sure your goals are realistic, and worthwhile. (Image: &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://unsplash.com/@carsonarias?ref=escapecollective.com"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Carson Arias&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; / Unsplash)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;h2 id="what%E2%80%99s-the-goal"&gt;What’s the goal?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is often where new year’s resolutions go to die. We’ve all set lofty, overly ambitious goals for our eating (or other lifestyle) habits, that in hindsight we never had a chance in hell of achieving. But it’s bigger than that. The number-one nutrition-related new year’s resolution that most people have, cyclist or not, is weight loss. Some people set modest, realistic expectations for what they might achieve. Others have goals of being leaner than they were in high school (20+ years ago, before kids and that sedentary desk job).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Regardless of the level of ambition, I’m going to suggest that setting a weight loss goal is not the smartest approach to making dietary changes, for several reasons:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Being leaner, and becoming leaner, are two very different things.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;p&gt;There are those who are naturally on the leaner side, seemingly no matter what they do. Then there’s everyone else. And the concern here is not necessarily about being leaner, but about the process required for many of us to get there and stay there.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Being in a caloric deficit can have many physiological and psychological consequences and the more aggressive and prolonged the deficit, the more significant these become. They can range from poor performance on the bike due to inadequate fueling for the training you’re doing, through to health effects, in both male and female athletes, summarised by the term &lt;a href="https://bjsm.bmj.com/content/57/17/1073?ref=escapecollective.com"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Relative Energy Deficiency in Sport (REDs)&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. This can include loss of bone density, loss of menstrual cycle in females, suppressed testosterone in males, and much more. There’s been plenty written on REDs and cyclists in recent years so I won’t rehash it all here, but if you’re not so familiar with the term then &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/goodweekendmag/reel/DQ8tgiziXua/?hl=id&amp;amp;ref=escapecollective.com"&gt;&lt;u&gt;this short reel&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; featuring &lt;em&gt;Escape Collective’s&lt;/em&gt; own Georgie Howe provides a bit of insight.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Note though that this is not an issue unique to elite or professional athletes. Any large mismatch between training load and calorie intake can potentially have these consequences, and I’ve seen variations of this in riders of all ages, sexes, and abilities.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;aside class="gh-post-upgrade-cta"&gt;
    &lt;div class="gh-post-upgrade-cta-content"&gt;
            &lt;h2&gt;This post is for paying subscribers only&lt;/h2&gt;
            &lt;a class="gh-btn" data-portal="signup" href="#/portal/signup"&gt;Subscribe now&lt;/a&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;Already have an account? &lt;a data-portal="signin" href="#/portal/signin"&gt;Sign in&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/aside&gt;


            &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

            &lt;p class="single-subscribe-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

                &lt;h2 class="reactions-title"&gt;Did we do a good job with this story?&lt;/h2&gt;

                &lt;p class="reactions" data-post-id="695b0715898a82a86c84ab52"&gt;
                    &lt;button class="reaction" data-type="2"&gt;&lt;span&gt;👍&lt;/span&gt;Yep&lt;/button&gt;
                    &lt;button class="reaction" data-type="0"&gt;&lt;span&gt;👎&lt;/span&gt;Nope&lt;/button&gt;
                &lt;/p&gt;

                

                &lt;p class="tags"&gt;
                        &lt;a href="/tag/nutrition/" title="nutrition" class="tag tag-67a677ae0c7ad49bf4f293cb nutrition" rel="tag"&gt;nutrition&lt;/a&gt;
                        &lt;a href="/tag/science/" title="Science" class="tag tag-67a677ae0c7ad49bf4f294dc science" rel="tag"&gt;Science&lt;/a&gt;
                &lt;/p&gt;

        &lt;/article&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Escape Collective</author><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 02:18:32 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMidEFVX3lxTE1yNzhxbzJkeEh2Z2hHOUtXYU9DbU81dXcyZ2ZsU1VLR1lnY2ZsZllSSDlFVG1hRUdCNzFVUDBBQ3lIN19hOHlqVlNQU0ttQjNjMHFNNkN6YUtycGtXV09YTFZMWEplYWV1cFVtb3BUSDZMR0l1</guid></item><item><title>生病和疲惫：查塔努加附近的县现在报告田纳西州的流感发病率最高- WTVC</title><link>https://newschannel9.com/news/local/chattanoogas-flu-season-intensifies-as-nearby-counties-report-highest-rates-in-tennessee</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="dateline"&gt;CHATTANOOGA, Tenn — &lt;/span&gt;Tennessee health officials say flu activity is rising sharply in around Chattanooga, with counties surrounding Hamilton showing some of the highest rates in the state.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="ImageEmbed_imageEmbed__5mYLo"&gt;&lt;img alt="Marion, Grundy, Sequatchie, Bradley, Meigs, Rhea, Bledsoe, McMinn and Polk counties are currently the only areas in Tennessee rated “very high” for influenza activity by the Tennessee Dept. of Health. Photo via the Tennessee Health Dept." class="ImageEmbed_image__qZBo_" src="/resources/media2/16x9/928/986/12x0/90/cebbe8c7-109c-4c81-ad20-0904b3ac85bc-tnfludata1526.png"&gt;&lt;div class="ImageEmbed_caption__gAtoE"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Marion, Grundy, Sequatchie, Bradley, Meigs, Rhea, Bledsoe, McMinn and Polk counties are currently the only areas in Tennessee rated “very high” for influenza activity by the Tennessee Dept. of Health. Photo via the Tennessee Health Dept.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Marion, Grundy, Sequatchie, Bradley, Meigs, Rhea, Bledsoe, McMinn and Polk counties are currently the only areas in Tennessee rated “very high” for influenza activity by the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These counties have flu positivity rates greater than 10 percent. By comparison, the statewide average is 6.5 percent, and Hamilton County itself is at 6.9 percent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The illness can cause symptoms like fever, body aches, coughing and fatigue.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mark Harrison, a Hamilton County resident, told us those are the same symptoms he felt when he says he was diagnosed with the flu in December.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;"I began to lose my ability to focus and continue engaged in the conversation," Harrison said.&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;"The fact that I got it at all, makes it seem worse than usual."&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;State and federal health experts say the surge comes as influenza A(H3N2) continues to circulate widely.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr. Chirag Patel, a pharmacist at Max Discount Pharmacy on Highway 58, told us local pharmacies and clinics are witnessing a surge in cases firsthand.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;"We did not see that many flu cases last year and the previous year," said Patel. "This year, we already started early, around October, November, and now it's still going on. That's little bit red flag right there."&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;Patel says detecting symptoms of the flu early can make a big difference in recovery.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;"The first 48 hours after you having a first symptoms is really critical, Patel said."&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;The CDC reports at least 11 million flu illnesses, 120,000 hospitalizations, and 5,000 deaths nationwide so far this season. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One pediatric death was reported this week in Tennessee, bringing the season total to nine nationwide.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="ImageEmbed_imageEmbed__5mYLo"&gt;&lt;img alt="File photo: Getty Images." class="ImageEmbed_image__qZBo_" src="/resources/media2/16x9/612/986/0x32/90/07914280-83d3-4e02-8d02-9ee7be6c56ef-flushots2.jpg"&gt;&lt;div class="ImageEmbed_caption__gAtoE"&gt;&lt;p&gt;File photo: Getty Images.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Georgia officials are also reporting higher-than-average flu activity, signaling that the region is experiencing a particularly active season. Health authorities encourage residents six months and older to get vaccinated if they have not already and to take precautions such as frequent handwashing and staying home when sick.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Flu activity is expected to remain elevated in Tennessee and across the U.S. for several more weeks, according to the CDC. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Local hospitals and clinics are urging families to monitor symptoms and seek care early, especially for children, older adults, and those with chronic health conditions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For the latest guidance on influenza vaccination and antiviral treatments, visit the Tennessee Department of Health or the CDC at cdc.gov.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Depend on us to keep you informed as we learn more.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>WTVC</author><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 01:37:13 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiwgFBVV95cUxQbVVXSVhxYjM1aEp6UXVoeTY5cmRka2pvV3FpRExpTExXZ2pQTWszMXpTY1Q5UnhLX3l2SFNVdmlreXotZ2k2bHdSc05vMElvMWdSbDMwM0VVMGdEZGcwZTFPMS1LcFlYd1lOT2h0U28zUE9wUmRrWGt5NUYxeFBsTkdHOVAxcXBZZmJqOWVFaWtjVkdRRUE4Y0JWRFJKUUszb05qQkhLMUZyQm1KbUEySXY0OGxpeE0xN2hROUNFdVd2QQ</guid></item><item><title>新的NHS在线医院将专注于九种健康状况- BBC</title><link>https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/c62w3wr92npo</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article&gt;&lt;p data-component="headline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 hNbOGD"&gt;&lt;h1 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 idLnWK"&gt;New NHS online hospital to focus on eyes, menopause and prostates &lt;/h1&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="byline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="byline" class="sc-573fa0e8-0 bWRWzH"&gt;&lt;span data-testid="byline-contributors" class="sc-573fa0e8-11 cOQNNv"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="byline-contributors-contributor-0" class="sc-573fa0e8-5 gXJgDY"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="sc-573fa0e8-7 gqeTMs"&gt;Nick Triggle&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-testid="byline-contributors-contributor-0-role-location" class="sc-573fa0e8-8 bIfajQ"&gt;Health correspondent&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 eRlINq"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="hero-image" class="sc-5340b511-1 cMIbKV"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20251210-151139-37baf2dfdd-web-2.36.1-1/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 gUePlo hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/430f/live/27d30630-ea5b-11f0-b5f7-49f0357294ff.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/430f/live/27d30630-ea5b-11f0-b5f7-49f0357294ff.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/430f/live/27d30630-ea5b-11f0-b5f7-49f0357294ff.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/430f/live/27d30630-ea5b-11f0-b5f7-49f0357294ff.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/430f/live/27d30630-ea5b-11f0-b5f7-49f0357294ff.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/430f/live/27d30630-ea5b-11f0-b5f7-49f0357294ff.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/430f/live/27d30630-ea5b-11f0-b5f7-49f0357294ff.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/430f/live/27d30630-ea5b-11f0-b5f7-49f0357294ff.jpg.webp" loading="eager" alt="Getty Images Patient using phone for remote consultation" class="sc-5340b511-0 hLdNfA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 jVqbAn"&gt;Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The new NHS online hospital service being launched in England next year will initially focus on menopause, prostate and eye conditions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The NHS has selected nine different conditions in total for the service which will be available through the NHS app in 2027.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The service, &lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/articles/c9317k58xkjo" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;which was first announced &lt;/a&gt;&lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/articles/c9317k58xkjo" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;in September&lt;/a&gt;, will allow patients to have assessments, check-ups and follow-up appointments online and will have its own dedicated team of doctors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The aim is to carry out 8.5 million appointments in the first three years – four times more than the average NHS trust.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;But experts have questioned how it will be staffed and paid for.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The nine conditions that will be prioritised initially are:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class="sc-6f869981-0 diUlgm"&gt;&lt;li class="sc-734a601e-0 cRgahm"&gt;glaucoma&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="sc-734a601e-0 cRgahm"&gt;conditions affecting the retina at the back of the eye (including age-related macular degeneration)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="sc-734a601e-0 cRgahm"&gt;cataracts&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="sc-734a601e-0 cRgahm"&gt;inflammatory bowel disease&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="sc-734a601e-0 cRgahm"&gt;iron deficiency anaemia&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="sc-734a601e-0 cRgahm"&gt;prostate enlargement&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="sc-734a601e-0 cRgahm"&gt;raised PSA levels (not  cancer diagnoses)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="sc-734a601e-0 cRgahm"&gt;menopause&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="sc-734a601e-0 cRgahm"&gt;menstrual problems which may be a sign of endometriosis&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The expectation is more conditions will be added to this list in the future.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;No patient will be forced down this route though, NHS England said, as they can still choose face-to-face appointments.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Patients will have the option of using NHS Online when a GP makes a referral for specialist care. Instead of having a physical site, patients will be able to receive care from doctors around the country, directly through the NHS App.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Tests, scans or procedures that are needed will take place at healthcare sites close to patients' homes, while doctors review and assess their notes remotely.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The government and NHS England believe the service will provide quicker access to care for patients and help relieve the pressure on in-person appointments, helping to cut waiting lists in the process.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Health Secretary Wes Streeting insisted that "everyone will benefit" from using the online service, even if not using it directly. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;He told BBC Breakfast that those choosing to go online may be seen more quickly, freeing up space for those who want a face-to-face appointment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Professor Stella Vig, head of elective care at NHS England, said: "The NHS's new online hospital will see a huge shift in the way we deliver care, giving patients the option to have an online appointment with a specialist anywhere in England.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Regarding the nine conditions being prioritised, she said: "We know that these conditions can be painful and difficult to cope with so providing faster, more convenient access to diagnosis and treatments will have a real and positive impact on people's lives."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 hNbOGD"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 gXmhTb"&gt;Questions remain&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Patients can already get test results on the NHS app and have online appointments.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;But this service builds on that by essentially offering a start-to-finish service digitally, building on some initiatives that have already been piloted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;For example, University Hospital Southampton developed a virtual follow-up service for low-risk inflammatory bowel disease, enabling patients to access care and support remotely when they had flare-ups.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;It meant the NHS trust could cut back on routine follow-up appointments. Three quarters of patients were managed virtually and the initiative was credited in reducing waiting times by 58%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Meanwhile, Moorfields Eye Hospital in London has introduced a virtual system for managing non-emergency eye referrals. More than half ended up being treated in routine clinics without the need for specialist treatment at Moorfields.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Moorfields Eye Hospital consultant Peter Thomas said: "The impact is clear – patients are being seen more quickly in more appropriate settings, and the pressure on NHS services is being reduced."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Dr Becks Fisher said, of the Nuffield Trust think tank, said the service will be helpful for some and focussing on menopause and menstrual health "makes sense" given the long waits for gynaecology services.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;But she added "tricky questions remain", including how the service will be staffed and paid for.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;She also said: "NHS IT infrastructure could also pose a problem, as it will need to enable relevant information – like scan results – to be seen across different NHS organisations, something that is infamously difficult at the moment."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Get our flagship newsletter with all the headlines you need to start the day. &lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.bbc.co.uk/newsletters/zhp28xs" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;Sign up here.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BBC</author><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 01:30:53 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiWkFVX3lxTFA1LVhvSHRDVlgwbDU1MzZ1Rlh0aG01cmtUWnY2QUh3MVpQbUFlNWtvMXFHUktqVVFwaGdvS245MUNLZTRTeHF3U0NkRjI5VTkzRXhfUVBOTk9DZ9IBX0FVX3lxTE92T2M1NUpTTUdKVlZvRE0zLXE1RWdlN2FwX2lPX0ZfeFFTQ1Fsem5LMmJ3bnBMTEN2WmdrU3FMNjZZSHRITUdERmk3TnJPdmJ2dzRKTzRYbm5TbE1QUHJN</guid></item><item><title>数以百万计的母亲细胞持续存在于您的体内，现在我们知道了方法- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/millions-of-your-mothers-cells-persist-inside-you-and-now-we-know-how</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Every human born on this planet is not entirely themselves.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A tiny fraction of our cells – around one in a million – is actually not our own, but comes from our mothers. That means each of us has millions of cells that our immune systems would normally recognize as foreign; yet somehow, in most of us, they hang around peacefully without causing any immune problems.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Now, immunologists have figured out why. A small number of maternal immune cells that cross the placenta during pregnancy actively train the fetus's immune system to tolerate the mother's cells for their entire life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Related: &lt;/b&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/humans-actually-have-secret-stripes-and-other-strange-markings"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Humans Actually Have Secret Stripes And Other Strange Markings&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The exchange of cells between a mother and a fetus is a well-documented phenomenon that scientists have known about for &lt;a href="http://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-025-04102-4"&gt;more than 50 years&lt;/a&gt;. It's called &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Microchimerism"&gt;microchimerism&lt;/a&gt;, and it goes both ways: every human who has ever been pregnant retains cells from their fetus, and every human retains cells from their mother.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These lingering cells pose a puzzle for immunology, which is built around the idea that the immune system should mount an attack against foreign cells.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A team led by pediatric infectious disease specialist Sing Sing Way of Cincinnati Children's Hospital Medical Center wanted to understand more about how these foreign maternal cells keep the immune system in check, and what role they play in shaping the fetus' immune system.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To find out, the researchers studied maternal microchimerism in mice. Building on their &lt;a href="https://doi.org/https://doi.org/10.1126/science.adf9325"&gt;previous studies&lt;/a&gt;, the researchers bred mice with immune cells engineered to express specific cell surface markers. This allowed researchers to selectively deplete those cells and see whether or not immune tolerance was maintained.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Here's where it got fascinating. A small subset of the maternal immune cells, with properties similar to bone marrow myeloid cells and dendritic cells, persisted long after birth. They were also strongly associated with both immune activity and the expansion of regulatory T cells – the cells that tell the immune system that everything is copacetic.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To confirm, the researchers next selectively edited out those specific maternal cells in offspring mice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The results were dramatic. The regulatory T cells disappeared, and the immune tolerance of maternal cells disappeared.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/newsletter?utm_source=promo_generic_health"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-642x273.jpg" alt="Subscribe to ScienceAlert's free fact-checked newsletter" class="alignnone wp-image-182810 size-medium" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-642x273.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-768x326.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-600x255.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final.jpg 850w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The implication is that lifelong tolerance to maternal microchimeric cells is probably dependent on just a tiny subset of maternal cells. Take those away, and immune chaos likely ensues. That also means that immune tolerance needs to be continuously and actively maintained; it's not a one-and-done process during pregnancy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That's interesting and exciting in its own right, but the research also offers a way to gain a greater understanding of the broad swath of diseases and conditions to which microchimerism may contribute.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The new tools we developed to study these cells will help scientists pinpoint exactly what these cells do and how they work in a variety of contexts including autoimmune disease,  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/cancer" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73077" data-postid="187604" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;cancer&lt;/a&gt; and neurological disorders," &lt;a href="https://scienceblog.cincinnatichildrens.org/deeper-microchimerism-study-sheds-new-light-on-a-mothers-cellular-gift/"&gt;Way says&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Microchimerism is increasingly linked with so many health disorders. This study provides an adaptable platform for scientists to investigate whether these rare cells are the cause of disease, or alternatively, found in diseased tissue at increased levels as part of the natural healing process."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The research has been published in &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.immuni.2025.08.005"&gt;&lt;i&gt;Immunity&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 01:23:18 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMinwFBVV95cUxNTWpJa2h4YnJ2MDFsWGVIRE5xYXI5RlJPN291Y0VySnlsV3N2X19KMC11OEJMc1dxeWJ1UkE5Y1pHeXloY3YyUXZXTHhYVG9lOHpOc2t0YmFaMzU2R01fRk1hbXJYZU1LLXZMMk9qZ0dSQWVrenRKZDh4c3hIdEdaTmxXbnEwN2hCaFZuUUpUNEFMbF8xSWdCa2E0bjFWMFk</guid></item><item><title>大脑健康挑战：尝试MIND饮食-《纽约时报》</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2026/well/brain-health-mind-diet-recipes.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;section class="g-main svelte-19neaxa"&gt;&lt;p class="g-text  svelte-19nwvmi"&gt;Welcome to Day 2 of the Brain Health Challenge. Today, we’re talking about food.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="g-wrapper  svelte-19s2qxj"&gt;   &lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="g-text  svelte-19nwvmi"&gt;Your brain is an energy hog. Despite comprising about 2 percent of the average person’s body mass, it consumes roughly 20 percent of the body’s energy. In other words, what you use to fuel yourself matters for brain health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="g-text  svelte-19nwvmi"&gt;So what foods are best for your brain?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="g-text  svelte-19nwvmi"&gt;In a &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC4581900/"&gt;nine-year study&lt;/a&gt; of nearly 1,000 older adults, researchers at Rush University in Chicago found that people who ate more of nine particular types of food — berries, leafy greens, other vegetables, whole grains, beans, nuts, fish, poultry and olive oil — and who ate less red meat, butter and margarine, cheese, sweet treats and fried food had slower cognitive decline.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="g-text  svelte-19nwvmi"&gt;Based on these findings, the researchers developed the &lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2023/08/31/well/eat/mind-diet-dementia.html"&gt;MIND diet&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="g-text  svelte-19nwvmi"&gt;Large studies encompassing thousands of people have since shown that following the MIND diet corresponds with &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/37105521/"&gt;better cognitive functioning&lt;/a&gt;, a &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/37133875/"&gt;lower risk of dementia&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41598-025-17055-5"&gt;slower disease progression&lt;/a&gt; in people with Alzheimer’s. People benefit from the diet regardless of whether they start it &lt;a href="https://cdn.nutrition.org/article/S2475-2991(25)01953-5/fulltext"&gt;in midlife or late life&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="g-text  svelte-19nwvmi"&gt;Experts think the foods included in the MIND diet are especially good for the brain because they contain certain macro and micronutrients.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="g-text  svelte-19nwvmi"&gt;Berries and leafy greens, for example, are rich in polyphenols and other antioxidants, said Jennifer Ventrelle, a dietitian at Rush and a co-author of “The Official Mind Diet.” Many of these compounds can cross the blood-brain barrier and help to fight inflammation and oxidative stress, both of which can damage cells and are linked to dementia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="g-text  svelte-19nwvmi"&gt;Nuts and fatty fishes, like salmon and sardines, contain omega-3 fatty acids, which are important for building the insulating sheaths that surround the nerve fibers that carry information from one brain cell to another.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="g-text  svelte-19nwvmi"&gt;Whole grains and beans both contain a hefty dose of fiber, which feeds the good microbes in the gut. Those microbes produce byproducts called short-chain fatty acids that experts think can influence brain health via the gut-brain axis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="g-text  svelte-19nwvmi"&gt;You don’t have to revamp your whole diet to get these nutrients. Instead, think about “MIND-ifying” whatever you already tend to eat, said Dr. Joel Salinas, a neurologist at NYU Langone Health and the founder and chief medical officer of the telehealth platform Isaac Health. For instance, add a handful of nuts or berries to your breakfast.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="g-text  svelte-19nwvmi"&gt;Today’s activity will help you MIND-ify your own meals. Share your choices with your accountability partner and in the comments, and I’ll discuss the ways I’m adjusting my diet, too. For added inspiration, check out these &lt;a href="https://cooking.nytimes.com/68861692-nyt-cooking/131990666-brain-health-recipes"&gt;MIND-approved recipes&lt;/a&gt; from New York Times Cooking.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/section&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The New York Times</author><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 01:03:37 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiAFBVV95cUxNQXBuWFlEbE1rOS1tM1lxWlZOd2pTQnlpdC1LYW9wSmQxYXVyZkI0VjlXdFcwWTJ5b0pCQ0J0eHdTOFJkc05xclpvRlhoTl9UcDMyQjBJd0YyRC0zLXIwcVJPZ2k5R3cwc2RwWGgyc19VUE9CTVVobXM3WTdCY0F4QTFoX2l4X1cx</guid></item><item><title>马萨诸塞州报告本季首例与流感相关的儿童死亡病例激增- WBUR</title><link>https://www.wbur.org/news/2026/01/05/massachusetts-flu-spike-child-death</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;header class="article-section--title article-section--island"&gt;&lt;nav aria-label="Breadcrumb" class="Breadcrumbs_bcrm__47hhd"&gt;&lt;ol&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;/nav&gt;&lt;p class="article-action"&gt;&lt;h1 class="article-hdr"&gt;Mass. reports first flu-related deaths of children this season as cases spike&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/header&gt;&lt;section class="article-section--content hang-punctuation article-section--first article-section--centered article-sections"&gt;&lt;p class=""&gt;At least 30 people, including three children, in Massachusetts have died from flu-related illness this season as the state reports "very high and rising" levels of flu activity across the state.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=""&gt;One child died during the week that ended on Dec. 27, according to &lt;a href="https://www.mass.gov/info-details/influenza-reporting"&gt;data from the Department of Public Health&lt;/a&gt;. It is not clear when the other two children died and no other information about the children is publicly available.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="indent-medium"&gt;"These viruses are serious, dangerous, and life-threatening," said Massachusetts Public Health Commissioner Dr. Robbie Goldstein.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=""&gt;The percent of hospitalizations associated with the flu has spiked in the last couple of weeks — a full month before last year's surge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=""&gt;Hospitalizations during last winter's harsh flu season peaked at 10.5% at the beginning of February. In total, 470 people died.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Flourish_flourish__XgVxY  flourish-embed" data-src="visualisation/27077245"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=""&gt;State data shows only about 34% of Massachusetts residents have been vaccinated against the flu so far this year. The vaccination rate was around 45% in the winter of 2022-2023, and has been decreasing in the years since.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=""&gt;On Monday, the state's public health commissioner encouraged residents to get vaccinated if they have not done so already.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="indent-medium"&gt;“This is a moment for clarity, urgency, and action,” Goldstein said in a statement. "There is a simple, effective, and available way to address these concerns: vaccines. They can prevent serious illness and hospitalization. And they save lives."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=""&gt;Boston Public Health Commissioner Dr. Bisola Ojikutu reminded residents it's not too late to get vaccinated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="indent-medium"&gt;"The flu vaccine actually takes about two weeks after getting the shot to be fully protected," she said. "And that's really the time that it takes your body to fully develop protective antibodies."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=""&gt;In Boston, she noted infection is increasing most rapidly in children. Children under 5 are seeing an 83% jump, and older children are seeing a 217% spike.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=""&gt;Beth Israel Lahey Health and &lt;a href="https://www.boston.com/news/health/2026/01/02/mass-general-brigham-strongly-encouraging-masking-for-visitors-respiratory-infections/"&gt;Mass General Brigham&lt;/a&gt; are requiring masks for health care providers. Masks are not required, though encouraged, for patients and visitors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=""&gt;The other two respiratory viruses known to spike over the winter — COVID-19 and respiratory syncytial virus (or RSV) — are not widely circulating right now, but cases of both are beginning to rise, the state's health department said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;section class="article-section--story-group article-section--centered"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This article was originally published on January 05, 2026.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>WBUR</author><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 01:01:07 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMifEFVX3lxTE9kYzNZWU5aY3dkOHJTTEFmd3ZwYS1YRUxBRW1SdGRuQnFEYU50elJzVWxNV2tSNWIwdThyRkFfV2JCd25yakd3X0hfM2k0SDMwMmo5QTRLbHVmVjZsT01MbHFrXy1aZEhHZTYwbjhZVk0wWFotMTRmaEl4WXU</guid></item><item><title>三城地区“非常高”的流感病例- WCYB</title><link>https://wcyb.com/news/local/flu-cases-at-very-high-level-in-tri-cities-region</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="StoryText_storyText__C3hWI StoryText_storyText__C3hWI"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="dateline"&gt;(WCYB) — &lt;/span&gt;The CDC’s latest weekly flu surveillance report shows very high influenza activity across the Tri-Cities area.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to the 2025 Week 52 flu map, Tennessee is now at the highest flu activity level nationwide, while Virginia is one step lower but still classified as Very High.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Locally, the Tri-Cities region falls into the Very High category, indicating a large share of doctor visits are tied to flu-like illness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>WCYB</author><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 00:22:30 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigwFBVV95cUxOelVoY2RHalg1S1ViMWdHTE16aFRwVnFyUzNUdTVVSDVzLUpxRlVXbl9BUmlfZ2JVYmZkV2ZCQmVtMUdlTEFsTl8wd3VSSHBERWQwWWtyZmt5MUU4VFBwZ3VxU0hiZktWWmtYeTM2RV9aVHJPcndXY2xHdHp4QVZHaVdYMA</guid></item><item><title>扩大宫颈癌筛查范围，由大多数私人保险承保-《华盛顿邮报》</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/health/2026/01/05/cervical-cancer-screening-self-collection-insurance/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="7JUGJRPDKFBFTL3HQ54BFS5DII" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;The Department of Health and Human Services is endorsing self-collected vaginal samples for cervical cancer screening and requiring most private insurance plans to cover testing without cost sharing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="PSGFU3UTXBEVFMH3AWWJ3H5AJ4" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;The Health Resources and Services Administration, an agency within HHS, announced &lt;a href="https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jama/fullarticle/2843501" target="_blank"&gt;updated cervical cancer screening guidelines&lt;/a&gt; Monday that expand screening options to include self-collection to test for human papillomavirus, or HPV, a sexually transmitted infection that causes nearly all cervical cancer cases. The new guidelines also aim to lower out-of-pocket costs for screening that could deter people from getting care.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 00:16:26 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiowFBVV95cUxNYnhjSzdXTkliY0hVNG0zRU1FRHNpN1JqSzF4SlNHTlFOSkM0ZzdrdDZIcnhwcFMxRG1UOXF3OUtlTGFMVUpMLXRIaW5TOEQ3cjB6SFhLQWlqLTU2QUZLX0hDTU81TnFKTF9IREF3dUdPWWV3S3dBQVo3LUs5amgtbV9Qdm5QTzRWM3MyVnQ2ZTU0S1ZLMWZxTkg2YzN5TTlKX1pZ</guid></item><item><title>耐药性念珠菌在康涅狄格州兴起- fox61.com</title><link>https://www.fox61.com/article/news/health/drug-resistant-candida-auris-connecticut/520-2b106257-538f-4291-9000-ed66a0970687</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="article__summary"&gt;Candida auris, a multi-drug resistant yeast-like fungus, is emerging across the state, posing significant health challenges, especially in nursing homes.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;div class="article__body"&gt;
                    &lt;div class="article__section article__section_type_text utility__text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;NEW HAVEN, Conn — A fungus that grows as yeast, Candida Auris is popping up more in our state and across the nation. Health experts said the fungus can cause severe infections.&lt;/p&gt;                    &lt;/div&gt;
                    &lt;div class="article__section article__section_type_text utility__text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One of the biggest problems with the fungus is that it's multi-drug resistant, which makes infections difficult to treat. &lt;/p&gt;                    &lt;/div&gt;
                    &lt;div class="article__section article__section_type_text utility__text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are several strains of Candida, but what many medical centers are dealing with right now is a newer form. It was identified in 2009, the first case was found in 2016, and cases have been sharply increasing in recent years, according to the &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/candida-auris/tracking-c-auris/index.html"&gt;Centers for Disease Control and Prevention&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;                    &lt;/div&gt;
                        
                    &lt;div class="article__section article__section_type_text utility__text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dr. Scott Roberts, the associate medical director for infection prevention at Yale-New Haven Health, said this strain being newer, complicates treatment. &lt;/p&gt;                    &lt;/div&gt;
                    &lt;div class="article__section article__section_type_text utility__text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“A lot of labs don’t yet have the mechanisms or capability to actually identify it,” said Roberts.&lt;/p&gt;                    &lt;/div&gt;
                    
                    &lt;div class="article__section article__section_type_text utility__text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Although research and treatment methods are limited, he said the fungus is known to cause outbreaks. &lt;/p&gt;                    &lt;/div&gt;
                    &lt;div class="article__section article__section_type_text utility__text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“There’s been a handful of reports that there have been outbreaks in nursing homes and congregate care settings where a lot of people live in the same setting and there’s a lot of mixing between patients and between patients,” said Roberts.&lt;/p&gt;                    &lt;/div&gt;
                    &lt;div class="article__section article__section_type_text utility__text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The people at highest risk for infection are those with weakened immune systems, people who use invasive medical devices like catheters or are in long term care facilities. &lt;/p&gt;                    &lt;/div&gt;
                    &lt;div class="article__section article__section_type_text utility__text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Someone infected by the fungus may experience symptoms like fevers, low blood pressure, or a high heart rate. &lt;/p&gt;                    &lt;/div&gt;
                    &lt;div class="article__section article__section_type_text utility__text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dr. Roberts said proper hygiene is the best way to prevent spreading the fungus. &lt;/p&gt;                    &lt;/div&gt;
                    &lt;div class="article__section article__section_type_text utility__text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“ Hand washing is the biggest thing. So just washing your hands with soap and water is going to kill this. The other thing is disinfecting the environment so if somebody does have it you can disinfect it with bleach is what we recommend," explained Roberts.&lt;/p&gt;                    &lt;/div&gt;
                    &lt;div class="article__section article__section_type_text utility__text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He wants to make it clear that not everyone who encounters the fungus will become sick or ever show symptoms, but it is certainly something to monitor for high risk patients. If you believe you’re infected, you’re encouraged to contact your primary care physician.&lt;/p&gt;                    &lt;/div&gt;
                    &lt;div class="article__section article__section_type_text utility__text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Alyshia Hercules is a Multi-skilled Journalist at FOX61 News. She can be reached at &lt;a href="mailto:ahercules@fox61.com" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" id="isPasted"&gt;ahercules@fox61.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;                    &lt;/div&gt;
                    &lt;div class="article__section article__section_type_text utility__text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Do you have a story idea or something on your mind you want to share? We want to hear from you! Email us at &lt;a href="mailto:newstips@fox61.com" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;newstips@fox61.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;                    &lt;/div&gt;
                                
                    &lt;div class="article__section article__section_type_text utility__text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;HERE ARE MORE WAYS TO GET FOX61 NEWS  &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;                    &lt;/div&gt;
                    &lt;div class="article__section article__section_type_text utility__text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Download the FOX61 News APP  &lt;/p&gt;                    &lt;/div&gt;
                    &lt;div class="article__section article__section_type_text utility__text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;iOS:&lt;/strong&gt; Click &lt;a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/fox61-ct-news-from-wtic/id1491063786?ls=1" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; to download  &lt;/p&gt;                    &lt;/div&gt;
                    &lt;div class="article__section article__section_type_text utility__text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Android: &lt;/strong&gt;Click &lt;a href="https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.tribtv.wtic" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; to download  &lt;/p&gt;                    &lt;/div&gt;
                    &lt;div class="article__section article__section_type_text utility__text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Stream Live on &lt;strong&gt;ROKU: &lt;/strong&gt;Add the channel from the &lt;a href="https://channelstore.roku.com/details/7e2fb7c097662263741d062e390d1c22/fox61-ct-news-from-wtic" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;ROKU store&lt;/a&gt; or by searching FOX61.  &lt;/p&gt;                    &lt;/div&gt;
                    &lt;div class="article__section article__section_type_text utility__text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Stream Live on&lt;strong&gt; FIRE TV: &lt;/strong&gt;Search ‘FOX61’ and click ‘Get’ to download.  &lt;/p&gt;                    &lt;/div&gt;
                    &lt;div class="article__section article__section_type_text utility__text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;FOLLOW US ON &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/FOX61News" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;X&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/FOX61News/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;FACEBOOK&lt;/a&gt; &amp;amp; &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/fox61news/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;INSTAGRAM&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;                    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>fox61.com</author><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 23:34:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiwAFBVV95cUxOcDFoM3cyb21uWE9nMnlsTWs4dzVMNXNzdS1meHdJcHpfODdmTFlWcGZHWjVCT3NPZ1U4SGU0NWxidVFoc3ItQnNwSEdtZmFOVHZPTnJSajdJSzU3V1lqTENyc1hPR1BPaG5XQnI5RHdGNk1veE1BYzNuQVQ3Wm9CR1pGRGxEb2lsQ0pucm5tZjEwMGNXbUZORnBkWEkwTjcyeEhpZkotSW8tSnRac2VBQ0dIQktEd2FTdGVEZ29sakc</guid></item></channel></rss>