<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>GNews Health</title><link>https://news.google.com/</link><description></description><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>科学家揭示了如何在不哭的情况下切洋葱，他们的方法非常简单。- Farmingdale Observer | Scientists reveal how to cut onions without crying, and their method is incredibly simple. - Farmingdale Observer</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMizgFBVV95cUxQZWJoblpqaU8wVjFUcWVSZUJCUWIxcmIxdE15Ml82T2FudVpTVDVvSTExRVVUbjdkLXJqNklGTUhPSTNlb3BEcUlvSVZ0OTdqb2o1aWZxRGtGbzB1akhhcFJ2YWdpZWUtWGFCNnFrZjBuOHdmdE5UREVnOThyTXRMWWp6VG83Tk5WNGduQzkzbHg2RlNVRjloT252cDhxTzdzbVI5RGx2R1JiNU45RUN0bGdhdEx0dFN3SXBkRlhWWmh0ZmJRLWYxeFc2WjBJZw?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content" itemprop="text"&gt;
			
&lt;p&gt;Cutting onions ranks among the most dreaded kitchen tasks for many &lt;a href="https://farmingdale-observer.com/tag/home/" class="st_tag internal_tag " rel="tag" title="Posts tagged with home"&gt;home&lt;/a&gt; cooks. The inevitable tears and burning sensation can turn a simple &lt;a href="https://farmingdale-observer.com/tag/cooking/" class="st_tag internal_tag " rel="tag" title="Posts tagged with cooking"&gt;cooking&lt;/a&gt; preparation into an uncomfortable experience. However, recent scientific research has uncovered a surprisingly straightforward method to chop onions without the waterworks. This technique could revolutionize how we approach this essential culinary ingredient that features in countless dishes worldwide.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Scientific insights into why onions make us cry&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Understanding why onions trigger tears helps explain the scientific solution. When you cut into an onion, you damage its cells, releasing enzymes that convert sulfur compounds into syn-propanethial-S-oxide. This volatile chemical rises through the air and irritates the sensitive membranes in your eyes, prompting them to produce tears as a protective response.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="farmi-in-text-1" id="farmi-1297554083"&gt;

&lt;ins class="adsbygoogle" data-ad-client="ca-pub-7994036760405448" data-ad-slot="3843226833" data-ad-format="auto" data-full-width-responsive="true"&gt;&lt;/ins&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;This chemical reaction occurs naturally as a defense mechanism for the onion plant. Research conducted at Cornell University has delved deeper into this process, examining exactly how these irritating compounds become airborne during cutting. Their findings reveal that the method of cutting significantly impacts how much of this tear-inducing substance reaches your eyes.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Traditional remedies like chilling onions or cutting them underwater offer limited effectiveness against this chemical reaction. However, the Cornell research team discovered that the primary factors affecting tear production relate to knife technique rather than external interventions. This revelation provides a practical solution that doesn’t require special equipment or preparation steps.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="farmi-display-adsense-3" id="farmi-2526234600"&gt;

&lt;ins class="adsbygoogle" data-ad-client="ca-pub-7994036760405448" data-ad-slot="9294255259" data-ad-format="auto" data-full-width-responsive="true"&gt;&lt;/ins&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="farmi-display-adsense" id="farmi-1037479000"&gt;

&lt;ins class="adsbygoogle" data-ad-client="ca-pub-7994036760405448" data-ad-slot="4875636047" data-ad-format="auto" data-full-width-responsive="true"&gt;&lt;/ins&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Just as &lt;a href="https://farmingdale-observer.com/2025/02/14/french-pastry-chefs-know-it-this-type-of-butter-makes-the-best-pie-crusts/"&gt;French pastry chefs know which butter creates superior pie crusts&lt;/a&gt;, professional chefs have long understood that proper knife skills make a difference when cutting onions – now &lt;a href="https://farmingdale-observer.com/tag/science/" class="st_tag internal_tag " rel="tag" title="Posts tagged with science"&gt;science&lt;/a&gt; confirms why.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;The simple technique for tear-free onion cutting&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The groundbreaking research from Cornell University reveals that two key factors determine how much eye-irritating spray gets released when cutting onions: knife sharpness and cutting speed. Contrary to what many might assume, the solution doesn’t involve fancy gadgets or unusual preparation methods.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Scientists created a specialized guillotine apparatus that allowed them to test different blade types and cutting speeds while filming the resulting spray patterns. Their experiments conclusively demonstrated that using a sharp knife and cutting slowly dramatically reduces the amount of irritating compounds released into the air.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;When using dull knives, the researchers observed that the blade pushed down on the onion layers, causing them to bend inward before springing back and forcefully ejecting juice into the air. Sharp knives, by contrast, cleanly slice through the onion cells without compressing them, minimizing juice spray.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The cutting speed proved equally important. Fast chopping motions, while seemingly efficient, actually generated more airborne mist. The researchers found that slowing down your cutting motion allows for more precise slicing and significantly less tear-inducing spray. This patient approach yields better results than rushing through the task.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;This technique also carries additional benefits beyond preventing tears. The same approach that prevents &lt;a href="https://farmingdale-observer.com/2025/02/16/italians-add-this-ingredient-to-their-cakes-making-them-incredibly-moist-and-soft/"&gt;moisture loss when adding secret ingredients to cakes&lt;/a&gt; helps preserve the onion’s flavor compounds when cut properly.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Practical applications beyond kitchen comfort&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The implications of this research extend beyond simply making onion preparation more comfortable. The scientists noted that minimizing airborne food particles has broader hygiene benefits in the kitchen. Reducing the spray from cutting vegetables with tough outer layers helps limit the spread of potential pathogens during food preparation.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;This finding proves particularly relevant for professional kitchens where large quantities of onions are processed daily. The cumulative effect of reducing airborne particles creates a healthier environment for food preparation. Commercial kitchens can benefit from implementing these techniques as standard practice.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;For home cooks, adopting this method eliminates the need for quirky workarounds that many have tried over the years. No more swimming goggles, bread in the mouth, or freezing onions before cutting. The solution lies simply in using proper equipment and technique – a sharp knife and a patient cutting motion.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Maintaining sharp kitchen knives represents a wise investment for any &lt;a href="https://farmingdale-observer.com/tag/cook/" class="st_tag internal_tag " rel="tag" title="Posts tagged with cook"&gt;cook&lt;/a&gt;. While many focus on &lt;a href="https://farmingdale-observer.com/2025/02/21/this-is-the-household-appliance-that-consumes-the-most-electricity-after-heating/"&gt;reducing energy consumption of major kitchen appliances&lt;/a&gt;, proper knife maintenance requires minimal resources while delivering significant benefits.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;This discovery reminds us that sometimes the most effective solutions come from understanding the science behind everyday problems. Just as &lt;a href="https://farmingdale-observer.com/2025/03/14/more-and-more-gardeners-are-burying-bananas-in-their-gardens-and-once-you-know-why-it-makes-perfect-sense/"&gt;gardeners apply scientific principles when using natural fertilizers&lt;/a&gt;, home cooks can apply these findings to improve their culinary experience through better understanding of the chemistry happening in their kitchens&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="farmi-display-adsense-end" id="farmi-1619915483"&gt;

&lt;ins class="adsbygoogle" data-ad-client="ca-pub-7994036760405448" data-ad-slot="4701254182" data-ad-format="auto" data-full-width-responsive="true"&gt;&lt;/ins&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;		&lt;/div&gt;

				&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Farmingdale Observer</author><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 15:31:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMizgFBVV95cUxQZWJoblpqaU8wVjFUcWVSZUJCUWIxcmIxdE15Ml82T2FudVpTVDVvSTExRVVUbjdkLXJqNklGTUhPSTNlb3BEcUlvSVZ0OTdqb2o1aWZxRGtGbzB1akhhcFJ2YWdpZWUtWGFCNnFrZjBuOHdmdE5UREVnOThyTXRMWWp6VG83Tk5WNGduQzkzbHg2RlNVRjloT252cDhxTzdzbVI5RGx2R1JiNU45RUN0bGdhdEx0dFN3SXBkRlhWWmh0ZmJRLWYxeFc2WjBJZw</guid></item><item><title>3个孩子的父亲感觉很健康。然后，常规筛查发现了一种罕见的致命疾病。-哥伦比亚广播公司新闻 | A father of 3 felt healthy. Then a routine screening found a rare, deadly illness. - CBS News</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMirgFBVV95cUxPZncxZGNQNWtFUzEzUHo2dTNlUUZXa1hPOHB4Tk5VZXdfODNLYTdWUUVXTFhGc1VmQndzYzNzem0tNkpiYklmZVRBRVNuZW55amswYWlpeGJGem9EQ3lRckZ0SHNXYmpLSGk4UUlzeFQ5Yl8wMWZOSno1NmxmdkZKTTRaZ2RsY211U0o0MUt1Z2tuVURZSC1aOGJFUXYydmVESnBGeVFXZTNJdkJZZHfSAbMBQVVfeXFMUGpoNGZvR2RVQjhLWHc0TzZhejl3SEpFM0dVdEc0Qm5QRGdIdTllWkZocUc3Vm5jdGo0ZnhpZ21NVlJOQnhtR25oalZxTjY5NDlNaTVLMTdtSmIyMEtHM0FrU1N5cHZXY1RyWUV3MHpTSW1WcDItc1RpUW90YVZwRFFQdXBLeHNDdUlGWk1OZ2hjYmdrYVo4bXdGRWw5NUxyM1kzZlAyem9CT0xuUGhka0FmS0E?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;section class="content__body"&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Curtis Jackson was feeling fit and healthy in late 2020 when he decided to update his life insurance policy: He was in better shape than he'd been in a while, but he wanted to make sure his wife and three kids were taken care of if anything happened to him. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jackson, now 46, underwent an intensive physical, and everything seemed to be going well until he received a strange phone call. The call was focused on a questionnaire he had filled out. Jackson had truthfully marked that he did not drink alcohol. But his liver numbers were those of "a functioning alcoholic," he was told. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It set off alarm bells. Jackson went to his primary care physician for another round of bloodwork. That doctor thought he had a problem with his gallbladder. Jackson went to have his gallbladder removed. During that operation, doctors found he had an unusual condition called primary sclerosing cholangitis, or PSC. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The chronic, progressive disease affects the liver and inflames the bile ducts, causing liver damage. Patients eventually need a liver transplant. There's also a small but real chance of a deadly diagnosis: a dangerous cancer called cholangiocarcinoma.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Early treatment and diagnosis can make a difference, so Jackson started undergoing two MRIs a year at the Mayo Clinic in Arizona to make sure he was cancer-free. He also had a regular test to check the progress of his PSC. In October 2024, Jackson had a nerve-wracking appointment where the technician scoping him seemed "very concerned." He felt healthy, but was worried by the appointment. &lt;/p&gt;

    
&lt;p id="mpu-plus-outstream-middle" data-ad="mpu-plus-outstream-middle" class="ad-mpu-plus-outstream-middle ad-wrapper " data-ad-unit='"mpu-plus-outstream-middle"'&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"She didn't say that it was cancer, but she was hinting towards it," Jackson said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="embed embed--type-image is-image embed--float-none embed--size-medium"&gt;
    
                                    
      &lt;span class="img embed__content"&gt;&lt;img src="https://assets3.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/06/13/aac23374-cd38-4e62-96b9-dd69f28874c5/thumbnail/620x827/0b26fe16954a1c41fe2b54729f82acb7/curtis-jackson-4-7-25-1-mos-post-op.jpg?v=d2f497bd9339ad99d2e0559414346698#" alt="curtis-jackson-4-7-25-1-mos-post-op.jpg " srcset="https://assets3.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/06/13/aac23374-cd38-4e62-96b9-dd69f28874c5/thumbnail/620x827/0b26fe16954a1c41fe2b54729f82acb7/curtis-jackson-4-7-25-1-mos-post-op.jpg?v=d2f497bd9339ad99d2e0559414346698 1x, https://assets1.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/06/13/aac23374-cd38-4e62-96b9-dd69f28874c5/thumbnail/1240x1654/0148cd4d734935cedb4235eb53c91753/curtis-jackson-4-7-25-1-mos-post-op.jpg?v=d2f497bd9339ad99d2e0559414346698 2x" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;

      
          &lt;figcaption class="embed__caption-container"&gt;
        
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__caption"&gt;Curtis Jackson at home in April 2025.&lt;/span&gt;
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__credit"&gt;
            
                Mayo Clinic

                          &lt;/span&gt;
              &lt;/figcaption&gt;
      &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Three weeks later, Jackson and his wife received the news he had been dreading: The tests had diagnosed him with the deadly cancer. He would need to undergo intensive treatment to try to fight the illness. It felt like a repeat of when he had had the initial PSC diagnosis. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I was feeling fine ... and both times netted a result of something pretty serious," Jackson said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What is cholangiocarcinoma? &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cholangiocarcinoma, or bile duct cancer, is considered a silent killer, according to Dr. Tanios Bekaii-Saab, the chairman of the division of hematology and medical oncology at the Mayo Clinic in Phoenix, Arizona. Bekaii-Saab was Jackson's oncologist. It tends to spread to other organs before symptoms appear, so most patients are diagnosed "too late to cure," Bekaii-Saab said. &lt;/p&gt;

    
    
&lt;p id="leader-plus-inc3" data-ad="leader-plus-inc" class="ad-leader-plus-inc ad-wrapper " data-ad-unit='["leader-plus-inc",3]'&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;About 20% of people with PSC are diagnosed with cholangiocarcinoma, said Dr. Aqel Bashar, the director of the Mayo Clinic's Transplant Center in Phoenix, Arizona, who also treated Jackson. It's a rare disease, affecting about 1 in 100,000 people in the U.S., Bashar said. Not all cases are associated with PCS. Like many other cancers, it is on the rise, Bekaii-Saab said, with diagnoses of cholangiocarcinoma increasing more than 50% in the past decade. Fewer than 10% of the people diagnosed with cholangiocarcinoma live more than five years, Bashar said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The best way to treat cholangiocarcinoma is with a liver transplant, Bekaii-Saab said. But it can only be done if the disease is caught early, before the cancer spreads. Many cholangiocarcinoma patients are not eligible for a liver transplant. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thankfully, Jackson's case was caught early. He underwent three weeks of chemotherapy and radiation to kill as many cancer cells as possible. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Basically, I lived at Mayo Clinic. I would literally do work out of the parking lot, and then go and do radiation," Jackson said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;During treatment, he lost about 30 pounds. But despite the odds, he remained optimistic that everything would work out. He even encouraged his wife to start a long-anticipated kitchen renovation. In the middle of the process, the family was told a liver was available.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On March 6, he was wheeled into surgery. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="embed embed--type-image is-image embed--float-none embed--size-medium"&gt;
    
                                    
      &lt;span class="img embed__content"&gt;&lt;img src="https://assets1.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/06/13/b748edc0-b06e-4210-bee1-421bb1c5e0c6/thumbnail/620x465g2/28690e52890a37fb3e572ac3410c5fc5/curtis-jackson-family-4-7-25-aprox-1-mo-post-op.jpg?v=d2f497bd9339ad99d2e0559414346698#" alt="curtis-jackson-family-4-7-25-aprox-1-mo-post-op.jpg " class=" lazyload" srcset="https://assets1.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/06/13/b748edc0-b06e-4210-bee1-421bb1c5e0c6/thumbnail/620x465g2/28690e52890a37fb3e572ac3410c5fc5/curtis-jackson-family-4-7-25-aprox-1-mo-post-op.jpg?v=d2f497bd9339ad99d2e0559414346698 1x, https://assets2.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/06/13/b748edc0-b06e-4210-bee1-421bb1c5e0c6/thumbnail/1240x930g2/108ac8e727377944edd4b49c12544429/curtis-jackson-family-4-7-25-aprox-1-mo-post-op.jpg?v=d2f497bd9339ad99d2e0559414346698 2x" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;

      
          &lt;figcaption class="embed__caption-container"&gt;
        
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__caption"&gt;The Jackson family and their dog Lucy at home in April 2025. From left: Stetson Jackson, Gwyn Jackson, Rooney Jackson, Curtis Jackson and Kim Jackson. &lt;/span&gt;
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__credit"&gt;
            
                Mayo Clinic

                          &lt;/span&gt;
              &lt;/figcaption&gt;
      &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Surgery and recovery &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The surgery took about four hours. Six days later, Jackson was released from the hospital. Testing showed that he was cancer-free. For the next year, he will undergo weekly blood tests and have monthly check-ups. He will need close monitoring for the rest of his life, Bashar said, since his transplant needs to be monitored and doctors need to make sure his cholangiocarcinoma does not return.&lt;/p&gt;

    
    
&lt;p id="leader-plus-inc4" data-ad="leader-plus-inc" class="ad-leader-plus-inc ad-wrapper " data-ad-unit='["leader-plus-inc",4]'&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For now, Jackson is trying to focus on his home and family, he said. His routine is "pretty close to normal," though he still can't lift more than 10 pounds, and climbing stairs can be draining. He gained back much of the weight he lost in treatment, and his energy levels are close to where they were before the cancer diagnosis. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Things are definitely getting back to normal, which is really exciting. I wasn't expecting that so fast," Jackson said. "We might call it either lucky, or blessed, or whatever. I am just so thankful that I was able to bounce back so quickly." &lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="embed embed--type-image is-image embed--float-none embed--size-medium"&gt;
    
                                    
      &lt;span class="img embed__content"&gt;&lt;img src="https://assets2.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/06/13/e098f644-b5ae-46fd-b2b6-c2c658a73b0d/thumbnail/620x827/24b7575afb49284ea5b5f62d60fee9d1/curtis-jackson-stetson-rooney-gwyn-3-6-25-6-hrs-post-op.jpg?v=d2f497bd9339ad99d2e0559414346698#" alt="curtis-jackson-stetson-rooney-gwyn-3-6-25-6-hrs-post-op.jpg " srcset="https://assets2.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/06/13/e098f644-b5ae-46fd-b2b6-c2c658a73b0d/thumbnail/620x827/24b7575afb49284ea5b5f62d60fee9d1/curtis-jackson-stetson-rooney-gwyn-3-6-25-6-hrs-post-op.jpg?v=d2f497bd9339ad99d2e0559414346698 1x, https://assets3.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/06/13/e098f644-b5ae-46fd-b2b6-c2c658a73b0d/thumbnail/1240x1654/902cc53388ff4d0c638157f3b3168635/curtis-jackson-stetson-rooney-gwyn-3-6-25-6-hrs-post-op.jpg?v=d2f497bd9339ad99d2e0559414346698 2x" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;

      
          &lt;figcaption class="embed__caption-container"&gt;
        
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__caption"&gt;Curtis Jackson and his children hours after his transplant surgery. &lt;/span&gt;
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__credit"&gt;
            
                Jackson family

                          &lt;/span&gt;
              &lt;/figcaption&gt;
      &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Jacksons are putting the finishing touches on the kitchen renovation, and planning to travel to North Carolina for vacation this summer. He also wants to plan family trips outside the country once he needs less frequent check-ups. His other priority is turning his story into something that can help others, and advocating for organ transplant and donation. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I have a new passion now," Jackson said. "I'm here because of these things. I would like to help this going forward and make sure people are learning the importance of donation." &lt;/p&gt;

      

                    
        
      
                  
    

    


    
      
    
  

          
  
        
      &lt;div class="content-author"&gt;
      &lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/team/kerry-breen/" class="content-author__name" data-invalid-url-rewritten-http=""&gt;Kerry  Breen&lt;/a&gt;

      &lt;div class="content-author__bio"&gt;
        &lt;div class="content-author__full-information"&gt;
          &lt;p class="content-author__text"&gt;Kerry Breen is a news editor at CBSNews.com. A graduate of New York University's Arthur L. Carter School of Journalism, she previously worked at NBC News' TODAY Digital. She covers current events, breaking news and issues including substance use.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
        &lt;/section&gt;

  
  

  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>CBS News</author><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMirgFBVV95cUxPZncxZGNQNWtFUzEzUHo2dTNlUUZXa1hPOHB4Tk5VZXdfODNLYTdWUUVXTFhGc1VmQndzYzNzem0tNkpiYklmZVRBRVNuZW55amswYWlpeGJGem9EQ3lRckZ0SHNXYmpLSGk4UUlzeFQ5Yl8wMWZOSno1NmxmdkZKTTRaZ2RsY211U0o0MUt1Z2tuVURZSC1aOGJFUXYydmVESnBGeVFXZTNJdkJZZHfSAbMBQVVfeXFMUGpoNGZvR2RVQjhLWHc0TzZhejl3SEpFM0dVdEc0Qm5QRGdIdTllWkZocUc3Vm5jdGo0ZnhpZ21NVlJOQnhtR25oalZxTjY5NDlNaTVLMTdtSmIyMEtHM0FrU1N5cHZXY1RyWUV3MHpTSW1WcDItc1RpUW90YVZwRFFQdXBLeHNDdUlGWk1OZ2hjYmdrYVo4bXdGRWw5NUxyM1kzZlAyem9CT0xuUGhka0FmS0E</guid></item><item><title>许多老年人接种疫苗。研究证明了他们是对的。-《纽约时报》 | Many Older People Embrace Vaccines. Research Is Proving Them Right. - The New York Times</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMifEFVX3lxTE1kSldSWVJWbEpPaWh5Z3VKc3NrVnQ4cTdnbjFYcVpjeWNLNDE1cUktd1BGU0ZwWXEzdG55X3duOC1ZRDZJN3hyU3BPZkpOWkRIMjVnZ0ZUX1BuRngtMXBRd01iLTBHekE5V0dnSWZUN1RvblFIN0lfc1ZJcHY?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The New York Times</author><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 11:21:08 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMifEFVX3lxTE1kSldSWVJWbEpPaWh5Z3VKc3NrVnQ4cTdnbjFYcVpjeWNLNDE1cUktd1BGU0ZwWXEzdG55X3duOC1ZRDZJN3hyU3BPZkpOWkRIMjVnZ0ZUX1BuRngtMXBRd01iLTBHekE5V0dnSWZUN1RvblFIN0lfc1ZJcHY</guid></item><item><title>研究发现，每天花五分钟来做这件事可以提高幸福感-旧金山纪事报 | Taking five minutes a day to do this can improve happiness, study finds - San Francisco Chronicle</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiggFBVV95cUxOXzI1WGFuWjhrZW03UWo0cXYzNzh5bVNNVGRNa2U5YWQwaHlwNTMtUmhVb2RVNlYtZUc4ejFvVnFFTEpUVEZXaDBEUmJ3WXpicVRBTkhBMUh2M3N4Rmg5bE5YMU5xdlZZMEVzNVpuemZJR3RHWnFGTmh1bzNwckpQTzVn?oc=5</link><description>&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;
    
        
&lt;/body&gt;
</description><author>San Francisco Chronicle</author><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 11:11:58 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiggFBVV95cUxOXzI1WGFuWjhrZW03UWo0cXYzNzh5bVNNVGRNa2U5YWQwaHlwNTMtUmhVb2RVNlYtZUc4ejFvVnFFTEpUVEZXaDBEUmJ3WXpicVRBTkhBMUh2M3N4Rmg5bE5YMU5xdlZZMEVzNVpuemZJR3RHWnFGTmh1bzNwckpQTzVn</guid></item><item><title>在吃袋装生菜之前，您可能需要三思而后行- HuffPost | You May Want To Think Twice Before You Eat Bagged Lettuce - HuffPost</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMivAFBVV95cUxPb3lfcUU5Y3gxdHQtWlZwaWRZb2xxTlVJNF9zQ2lzc0tNQjAtOGljcW5RdHI3OVpNd0dfYnJJSzVVTE5LS1lJQXBINDI1dWxuZ2JuenN2b2pLWXVCTXBUaWtaT2VvSmk0RXo4bTBobDIxYmt0RnM2aGgySGNYVkFHTkczWjJIUTF5cExkeEhtU1QyOHNNNDZweDZKMk1ZcVNPdFhWWTB4WmVIOVFTeXZBUnhXTFZRLThQUkVYQdIBwgFBVV95cUxPMU9kQmd1NmhZSTVscndiUThWWl9Sa0VMRktjN1BUQUQyVlNZaFYzcy1kVVp0OFY2eWw1eVgwUDdsVjF5Snk5bVh4Zk53MzVXMk4tZkk4ZDNaTUREcVJ5OGFRSVl6S1VQYktRYW5pVENNV2dHNEFVcEIteVNldlVtRlNRYzdiT3JCYVJ2TFBzMlZTWjBMSzNqa3poTEN0LUZRZnU0Tlo0cmhLRi1sR1MzM1VjeU5RMkI1OHVNRjZhQjl0UQ?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;section class="entry__content-list js-entry-content js-cet-subunit"&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;You likely buy some &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/topic/grocery-shopping" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-internal-link" data-vars-item-name="grocery" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68499306e4b03de6beaf7ff0" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="/topic/grocery-shopping" data-vars-target-content-type="feed" data-vars-type="web_internal_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="0"&gt;grocery&lt;/a&gt; items for convenience, to save a couple of steps when it’s time to prepare a meal. Prewashed bagged greens, such as lettuce or spinach, seem like a no-brainer if you’re trying to eat nutritiously. But not so fast ...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to food safety experts, prewashed bagged greens aren’t the safest choice. Bacteria and contamination are more common than you may suspect in this particular grocery item.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“While consumers expect convenience and safety, the reality is that prewashed bagged greens remain one of the riskiest items in the grocery store due to contamination risks throughout the supply chain,” says &lt;a href="https://cps.northeastern.edu/faculty/darin-detwiler/" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Darin Detwiler" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68499306e4b03de6beaf7ff0" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://cps.northeastern.edu/faculty/darin-detwiler/" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="1"&gt;Darin Detwiler&lt;/a&gt;, a professor of food policy at Northeastern University and author of “&lt;a href="https://r.bttn.io?btn_ref=org-677cb81987ed72f9&amp;amp;btn_url=https://r.bttn.io/?tag=thehuffingtop-20%26ascsubtag%3D68499306e4b03de6beaf7ff0%252C-1%252C-1%252Cd%252C0%252C0%252Chp-fil-am%253D0%252C0%253A0%252C0%252C0%252C0" role="link" data-amazon-link="true" data-aps-asin="null" data-aps-asc-tag="null" data-aps-asc-subtag="null" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Food Safety: Past, Present, and Predictions" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68499306e4b03de6beaf7ff0" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://r.bttn.io?btn_ref=org-677cb81987ed72f9&amp;amp;btn_url=https://r.bttn.io/?tag=thehuffingtop-20%26ascsubtag%3D68499306e4b03de6beaf7ff0%252C-1%252C-1%252Cd%252C0%252C0%252Chp-fil-am%253D0%252C0%253A0%252C0%252C0%252C0" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="2"&gt;Food Safety: Past, Present, and Predictions&lt;/a&gt;.” He avoids buying bagged greens because of the risk of deadly E. coli contamination. “When you look at past outbreaks, bagged salads have been a leading cause of foodborne illness, with some outbreaks resulting in hospitalizations, kidney failure (hemolytic uremic syndrome), and even death,” Detwiler said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You’re not imagining it — there are a lot of outbreaks.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many factors in the supply chain can contaminate the greens with pathogens — such as E. coli, listeria or salmonella — that can leave people sick, hospitalized or worse. “Bagged greens are washed and processed in large batches, which is an effective way to spread pathogens,” said &lt;a href="https://www.ice.edu/about/faculty-profiles/olivia-roszkowski" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Olivia Roszkowski" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68499306e4b03de6beaf7ff0" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.ice.edu/about/faculty-profiles/olivia-roszkowski" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="3"&gt;Olivia Roszkowski&lt;/a&gt;, chef-instructor of plant-based culinary arts and food safety certification at the Institute of Culinary Education’s New York City campus. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Leafy green outbreaks happen more than you’d expect, and the FDA created a &lt;a href="https://www.fda.gov/food/foodborne-pathogens/leafy-greens-stec-action-plan" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Leafy Greens STEC Action Plan" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68499306e4b03de6beaf7ff0" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.fda.gov/food/foodborne-pathogens/leafy-greens-stec-action-plan" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="4"&gt;Leafy Greens STEC Action Plan&lt;/a&gt; in 2020 to reduce different strains of E. coli in leafy greens and updated the plan in 2023. (For example, shiga toxin-producing Escherichia coli O157:H7 is the pathogenic strain that is often associated with &lt;a href="https://www.ars.usda.gov/oc/utm/keeping-bagged-leafy-greens-safe-and-nutritious-for-human-consumption/" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="lettuce and leafy green outbreaks" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68499306e4b03de6beaf7ff0" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.ars.usda.gov/oc/utm/keeping-bagged-leafy-greens-safe-and-nutritious-for-human-consumption/" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="5"&gt;lettuce and leafy green outbreaks&lt;/a&gt;, and Detwiler says it “is particularly dangerous because it takes a very small amount to cause severe illness. ... The risk isn’t theoretical — it’s been repeatedly proven in outbreak after outbreak.” )&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure class="cli cli-image js-no-inject"&gt;&lt;p class="cli-image__spacer"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="cli-image__source-wrapper"&gt;&lt;div class="cli-image__credit" aria-label="Image Credit: Stefano Oppo via Getty Images"&gt;&lt;p class="credit-container"&gt;&lt;span class="credit"&gt;Stefano Oppo via Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption class="cli-image__caption caption-cli"&gt;The greens that end up in a bag can come from multiple different farms and locations.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;And despite the efforts to reduce leafy green-related outbreaks, they continue to occur. Leafy greens are attributed to “up to 9.2% of known pathogen-caused foodborne illnesses” in the U.S., according to a report in the &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0362028X24000590" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Journal of Foodborne Illness" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68499306e4b03de6beaf7ff0" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0362028X24000590" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="6"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Journal of Foodborne Illness&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; published in April 2024. The report estimates over 2.3 million illnesses every year are related to contaminated leafy greens. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How the food supply chain becomes contaminated&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;On the farm&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Contamination can occur at different stages before bagged salad greens reach the refrigerated produce section and eventually your plate. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“In the field, produce can become contaminated with pathogens from sources such as contaminated irrigation water, wild or domesticated animals, soil, or air,” said &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.clemson.edu/cafls/faculty_staff/profiles/kabaker" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Kimberly Baker," data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68499306e4b03de6beaf7ff0" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.clemson.edu/cafls/faculty_staff/profiles/kabaker" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="7"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Kimberly Baker,&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;span&gt;a food systems and safety program team director at Clemson University. It’s more common to have contaminated greens “when the field is in close proximity to livestock farms or feedlots where animals are being held in densely populated conditions,” Roszkowski explained. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Arizona and California are big producers of leafy greens in the United States and are often near large cattle operations, according to Detwiler. E. coli, salmonella, or listeria can be introduced to the crops through contaminated irrigation water from nearby cattle farms, he said. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“Runoff from manure lagoons can seep into irrigation canals and contaminate fields with deadly bacteria like E. coli O157:H7,” Detwiler continued. Manure lagoons are large pits where livestock waste is stored, per &lt;a href="https://environmentamerica.org/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/AccidentsFactsheet-ManureLagoons-1.pdf" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Environmental" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68499306e4b03de6beaf7ff0" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://environmentamerica.org/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/AccidentsFactsheet-ManureLagoons-1.pdf" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="8"&gt;Environmental&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://environmentamerica.org/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/AccidentsFactsheet-ManureLagoons-1.pdf" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name=" America" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68499306e4b03de6beaf7ff0" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://environmentamerica.org/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/AccidentsFactsheet-ManureLagoons-1.pdf" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="9"&gt;&lt;span&gt; America&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;. And it’s not only contaminated water that can be a problem. Some farms use unregulated water sources to irrigate the fields. “Some farms use untreated or minimally treated surface water from rivers, lakes or canals, increasing the risk of contamination,” Detwiler said. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;When it’s time to harvest, there are added risks for pathogens and bacteria to come in contact with lettuce. “Contamination can occur through human handling, contaminated equipment or water used in post-harvest processes to transport, produce or remove soil,” Baker said. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;In the processing plant&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;There are opportunities for pathogens to come in contact with leafy greens once they reach a processing plant. The greens you get in a bag don’t typically come from one field but from multiple farms, complicating traceability and increasing contamination. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Greens are processed in a centralized area and distributed — which is convenient for all the companies involved in the process— but not ideal from a food safety standpoint. “Greens from different farms are mixed, washed and packaged together, so one contaminated leaf can impact thousands of bags across multiple states,” Detwiler explained. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Lettuce is washed in large vats, added &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://drexel.edu/cnhp/faculty/profiles/TroutRosemary/" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Rosemary Trout," data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68499306e4b03de6beaf7ff0" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://drexel.edu/cnhp/faculty/profiles/TroutRosemary/" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="10"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Rosemary Trout,&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; associate professor and program director of Culinary Arts &amp;amp; Food Science at Drexel University. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;What you may not suspect, according to Trout, is that “plant foods are usually more often associated with foodborne illness than animal products.” &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;On the journey to store shelves&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Keeping the greens cold is necessary to prevent any pathogens from growing and spreading. According to &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Roszkowski&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;, “Not keeping the greens consistently cold throughout the process of harvesting, processing and transporting can cause bacterial growth to occur.” &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;However, refrigeration doesn’t eliminate the chance of pathogens; it can help slow them down. “Refrigeration slows bacterial growth but does not kill bacteria, meaning contaminated greens can still cause illness, even if stored properly,” Detwiler said. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Will washing prewashed salad greens help?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;If you’re thinking, “W&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;ell, I’ll wash my prewashed greens for extra safety measures&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;,” don’t. Washing greens at home doesn’t make them safer because water won’t remove the pathogens, Detwiler said. Rinsing prewashed greens can introduce pathogens that may be lurking on your counter or sink. “Prewashed greens should not be rewashed at home, as doing so can introduce contamination if the sink, utensils, equipment or hands of the preparer are not properly cleaned or sanitized,” Baker said. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure class="cli cli-image js-no-inject"&gt;&lt;p class="cli-image__spacer"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="cli-image__source-wrapper"&gt;&lt;div class="cli-image__credit" aria-label="Image Credit: Westend61 via Getty Images"&gt;&lt;p class="credit-container"&gt;&lt;span class="credit"&gt;Westend61 via Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption class="cli-image__caption caption-cli"&gt;Washing greens can remove pesticides, but it's not been proven to be effective in removing pathogens.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Bacteria or pathogens aren’t obvious and can’t be seen. “If greens are contaminated with pathogens, they cannot be detected by sight, smell or taste … and can’t be removed by washing,” Baker explained. According to Detwiler, “Bacteria like &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;E. coli&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt; and &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;salmonella&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt; can form biofilms that help them stick to the surface of the leaves [and] once attached, these bacteria do not simply rinse off.” &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Harmful pathogens need to be cooked to be eliminated, as heat kills them, said Detwiler. A big issue with lettuce is it’s usually eaten raw, not cooked, “making it challenging to reduce the risk of foodborne illness,” Baker said. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Recommendations for buying bagged greens&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;If you still prefer buying bagged greens for the convenience, there are several precautions to take. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Check for recalls &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Before you purchase any salad greens, check if there are any recalls, advised &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Detwiler and &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Roszkowski&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;. “Stay updated on recalls via the FDA and CDC websites,” Detwiler said. “If your greens are part of an outbreak, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;throw them away immediately.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Check expiration dates&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Experts say you should look at the expiration dates before purchasing. Trout advises to only buy what you will eat within a day or two. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Look for freshness&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Avoid bags with excess moisture that look wet, as damp environments are a haven for bacteria to thrive, Detwiler said. “Inspect the package to ensure the lettuce looks fresh, without wilting or discoloration, as these signs may indicate improper storage or reduced freshness,” Baker said. You also want to stay away from any bags that have slimy leaves, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Roszkowski added&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Minimize temperature changes&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Once you’ve purchased greens, don’t let them sit in a hot car or garage or out on the counter. “Avoid drastic changes in temperature when transporting them from the store and when preparing a meal,” &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Roszkowski said&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;. “This leads to condensation and creates a moist and warm environment that can encourage both spoilage and bacterial growth.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.ice.edu/about/faculty-profiles/olivia-roszkowski" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68499306e4b03de6beaf7ff0" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.ice.edu/about/faculty-profiles/olivia-roszkowski" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="11"&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Store properly&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Greens should be kept refrigerated at or below 40 degrees Fahrenheit, say Detwiler and Trout. &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Buy heads of lettuce &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Purchasing a head of lettuce or a bunch of spinach may have the extra step of rinsing and drying before tossing in a salad bowl or stir-frying, but you could be minimizing the risk of lurking pathogens. “Whole heads of lettuce or spinach have less surface area for contamination compared to pre-cut, mixed bagged greens,” Detwiler said. He suggests rinsing them under cold water — not soaking — to remove dirt, debris, any insects and surface-level bacteria. “Wash them at home before eating.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>HuffPost</author><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 11:00:17 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMivAFBVV95cUxPb3lfcUU5Y3gxdHQtWlZwaWRZb2xxTlVJNF9zQ2lzc0tNQjAtOGljcW5RdHI3OVpNd0dfYnJJSzVVTE5LS1lJQXBINDI1dWxuZ2JuenN2b2pLWXVCTXBUaWtaT2VvSmk0RXo4bTBobDIxYmt0RnM2aGgySGNYVkFHTkczWjJIUTF5cExkeEhtU1QyOHNNNDZweDZKMk1ZcVNPdFhWWTB4WmVIOVFTeXZBUnhXTFZRLThQUkVYQdIBwgFBVV95cUxPMU9kQmd1NmhZSTVscndiUThWWl9Sa0VMRktjN1BUQUQyVlNZaFYzcy1kVVp0OFY2eWw1eVgwUDdsVjF5Snk5bVh4Zk53MzVXMk4tZkk4ZDNaTUREcVJ5OGFRSVl6S1VQYktRYW5pVENNV2dHNEFVcEIteVNldlVtRlNRYzdiT3JCYVJ2TFBzMlZTWjBMSzNqa3poTEN0LUZRZnU0Tlo0cmhLRi1sR1MzM1VjeU5RMkI1OHVNRjZhQjl0UQ</guid></item><item><title>Ossett前列腺癌患者敦促男性进行检查- BBC | Ossett prostate cancer patient urges men to have checks - BBC</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiWkFVX3lxTE5rb1hRWFJLbW5DNjh3bml6bV9zOTF1NV9SaUhBWEJiNmR3NVNhUWhyaGQzNHhPUF9yN2pTQ3FqTmd0NUNrY01SdjZyNksxRktkanBBSEtLZTc3QdIBX0FVX3lxTE5ULWtYOGVsZjVjQXJuYzRCNDdpN01EOXpMV1hKbHN0dzZaWXRNZE52dmJ6STI2eTRjb25IVVMwYm1URUxuQVFDYWQxajRUdE5WYmtkTi1Nd1d2LWVaMkI4?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article&gt;&lt;p data-component="headline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 fDtfvH"&gt;&lt;h1 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 dfvxux"&gt;'Prostate cancer diagnosis felt like a black hole'&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 gyQxwn"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="hero-image" class="sc-d1200759-1 kycbVO"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20250611-093910-fc500e843d-web-2.23.1-1/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-d1200759-0 dkIvM hide-when-no-script"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/bf7d/live/63effdd0-479f-11f0-852d-2b00931dcf75.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/bf7d/live/63effdd0-479f-11f0-852d-2b00931dcf75.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/bf7d/live/63effdd0-479f-11f0-852d-2b00931dcf75.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/bf7d/live/63effdd0-479f-11f0-852d-2b00931dcf75.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/bf7d/live/63effdd0-479f-11f0-852d-2b00931dcf75.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/bf7d/live/63effdd0-479f-11f0-852d-2b00931dcf75.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/bf7d/live/63effdd0-479f-11f0-852d-2b00931dcf75.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/bf7d/live/63effdd0-479f-11f0-852d-2b00931dcf75.jpg.webp" loading="eager" alt="PCUK A man in a black polo shirt sits in a white armchair. He has grey hair and wears a Prostate Cancer UK badge." class="sc-d1200759-0 dvfjxj"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-d1200759-2 gwFzuU"&gt;PCUK&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jvncPH"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 FPsqq"&gt;Danny Burkey was diagnosed with prostate cancer in 2021&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;A man diagnosed with incurable prostate cancer said the news felt like falling into a "black hole", as he urged others to check for signs of the disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Danny Burkey, from Ossett, was diagnosed in 2021, and was told his condition was incurable after a bone scan.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;The 59-year-old spoke as Prostate Cancer UK launched a campaign urging men to visit their GP with prostate concerns, in the hope of an early diagnosis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Mr Burkey told BBC Radio Leeds: "You think it is always going to happen to somebody else; you just cannot believe it is you."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Mr Burkey sought a diagnosis after experiencing symptoms related to prostate cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;According to the NHS, symptoms can include:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class="sc-6f869981-0 fusmZA"&gt;&lt;li class="sc-734a601e-0 huNRXw"&gt;Having a sudden urge to urinate &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="sc-734a601e-0 huNRXw"&gt;Getting up often in the night to urinate&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="sc-734a601e-0 huNRXw"&gt;Blood in your urine&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="sc-734a601e-0 huNRXw"&gt;Erectile dysfunction.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;"I had a blood test, an MRI and a biopsy," Mr Burkey said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Recalling being told his illness was incurable, he said: "You are almost standing next to yourself thinking, I do not know what to do with this.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;"You just cannot process it."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 hoQmHM"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-d1200759-1 kycbVO"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20250611-093910-fc500e843d-web-2.23.1-1/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-d1200759-0 dkIvM hide-when-no-script"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/bd5d/live/92acd730-485b-11f0-83bd-e5b5d0a69992.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/bd5d/live/92acd730-485b-11f0-83bd-e5b5d0a69992.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/bd5d/live/92acd730-485b-11f0-83bd-e5b5d0a69992.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/bd5d/live/92acd730-485b-11f0-83bd-e5b5d0a69992.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/bd5d/live/92acd730-485b-11f0-83bd-e5b5d0a69992.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/bd5d/live/92acd730-485b-11f0-83bd-e5b5d0a69992.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/bd5d/live/92acd730-485b-11f0-83bd-e5b5d0a69992.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/bd5d/live/92acd730-485b-11f0-83bd-e5b5d0a69992.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="PA Media A medic looks through a microscope at prostate cancer testing measures." class="sc-d1200759-0 dvfjxj"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-d1200759-2 gwFzuU"&gt;PA Media&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jvncPH"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 FPsqq"&gt;Prostate cancer is now England's most common cancer, affecting one in eight men&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;According to Prostate Cancer UK, one in eight men will get prostate cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;It is now England's most common cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Despite the prevalence, the charity's research suggests six in 10 men are concerned about having a Digital Rectal Exam (DRE).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Of those, over a third would not speak to a GP about prostate worries because they feared the DRE exam.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Mr Burkey urged men to seek a diagnosis despite barriers, saying: "You do not need to have a DRE now.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;"You can ask your GP for a simple blood test and that gets the ball rolling, it is as simple as that."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 hoQmHM"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-d1200759-1 kycbVO"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20250611-093910-fc500e843d-web-2.23.1-1/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-d1200759-0 dkIvM hide-when-no-script"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/7443/live/fafc9ee0-4862-11f0-83bd-e5b5d0a69992.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/7443/live/fafc9ee0-4862-11f0-83bd-e5b5d0a69992.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/7443/live/fafc9ee0-4862-11f0-83bd-e5b5d0a69992.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/7443/live/fafc9ee0-4862-11f0-83bd-e5b5d0a69992.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/7443/live/fafc9ee0-4862-11f0-83bd-e5b5d0a69992.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/7443/live/fafc9ee0-4862-11f0-83bd-e5b5d0a69992.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/7443/live/fafc9ee0-4862-11f0-83bd-e5b5d0a69992.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/7443/live/fafc9ee0-4862-11f0-83bd-e5b5d0a69992.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt='PCUK A man with grey hair and a beard stands in a garden. He wears a black polo shirt and a Prostate Cancer UK badge. He holds a card which reads: "The first test is a simple blood test you can ask your GP for."' class="sc-d1200759-0 dvfjxj"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-d1200759-2 gwFzuU"&gt;PCUK&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jvncPH"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 FPsqq"&gt;Doctors determined Danny Burkey's prostate cancer was incurable after a bone scan&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Earlier this week, the &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.baus.org.uk/professionals/baus_business/news/289/rectal_exam_a_poor_test_for_prostate_cancer_surgeons_and_charity_agree" class="sc-f9178328-0 bGFWdi"&gt;British Association of Urological Surgeons&lt;/a&gt; urged GPs to stop using the "outdated" and "inaccurate" DRE as a standard test.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;They labelled it a "poor test" that deterred men from coming forward.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Men are encouraged to use Prostate Cancer UK's 30-second online risk checker and to talk to their GP about the prostate-specific antigen (PSA) blood test.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;A high level of PSA in the blood can indicate prostate cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Research led by Prostate Cancer UK shows that the way prostate cancer is diagnosed - with a PSA blood test followed by an MRI scan - reduces potential harms to men by 79%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Among those to catch the disease early was actor Colin McFarlane.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;McFarlane, who has appeared in The Dark Knight and Doctor Who, announced he had prostate cancer on the BBC Breakfast sofa in June 2023.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;He said: "I'm really lucky I caught it early, so I thought if I'm lucky and I know so much about this, I need to try and share this knowledge."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jvncPH"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 FPsqq"&gt;Actor Colin McFarlane announced he had prostate cancer on the BBC Breakfast sofa in June 2023&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;McFarlane's friend, theatre director Femi Elufowoju Jr said hearing his story encouraged him to get checked, which led him to also being diagnosed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;He &lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/articles/cqxenrxy3n7o" class="sc-f9178328-0 bGFWdi"&gt;thanked McFarlane&lt;/a&gt; for saving his life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Despite treatment, including chemotherapy and radiotherapy, Mr Burkey's body has stopped responding to advanced hormone therapy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;He said: "Inevitably your body becomes resistant, the cancer becomes resistant to them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;"You are constantly having your PSA levels monitored to see how treatments are working.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;"You are constantly sort of on your toes thinking where am I up to now?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;"What have I still got left that can be used?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;"It is a very anxious time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;"I do not want another man to be in the position I am in."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="embed-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dHQIrb"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BBC</author><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 10:12:28 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiWkFVX3lxTE5rb1hRWFJLbW5DNjh3bml6bV9zOTF1NV9SaUhBWEJiNmR3NVNhUWhyaGQzNHhPUF9yN2pTQ3FqTmd0NUNrY01SdjZyNksxRktkanBBSEtLZTc3QdIBX0FVX3lxTE5ULWtYOGVsZjVjQXJuYzRCNDdpN01EOXpMV1hKbHN0dzZaWXRNZE52dmJ6STI2eTRjb25IVVMwYm1URUxuQVFDYWQxajRUdE5WYmtkTi1Nd1d2LWVaMkI4</guid></item><item><title>“我们不了解大量精子” ：为什么精子仍然如此神秘-英国广播公司 | 'There's a huge amount that we don't understand': Why sperm is still so mysterious - BBC</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiowFBVV95cUxPektuVkZrZTRMWnRMSHF0UGdvNGRrUXF6OWpjeXRtNHZwUHdBMTlwVk0wY3ZfZGNDRFFZQ2RpeWlLRk1POVQtZXl0ZTdLODc5clVfWHg4N0lzcmpLRVJuZVVwbjVYbXpFME1WQzYwczd3VXJOc29SeXVKWklNUjFSQjNndldoV1pfZnhTWGhpNUpIeEw5NG5vcWduWDdTLVBfZVBz?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article&gt;&lt;p data-component="headline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 fDtfvH"&gt;&lt;h1 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 dfvxux"&gt;'There's a huge amount that we don't understand': Why sperm is still so mysterious&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;&lt;b id="how-do-sperm-swim?-how-do-they-navigate?-what-is-sperm-made-of?-what-does-a-world-war-two-codebreaker-have-to-do-with-it-all?-the-bbc-untangles-why-we-know-so-little-about-this-mysterious-cell." class="sc-d16436d-0 jpoiOL"&gt;How do sperm swim? How do they navigate? What is sperm made of? What does a World War Two codebreaker have to do with it all? The BBC untangles why we know so little about this mysterious cell.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;But much about this epic journey – and the microscopic explorers themselves – remains a mystery to science. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Using newly developed methods, scientists are now following sperm on their migration – from their genesis in the testes all the way to the fertilisation of the egg in the female body. The results are leading to groundbreaking new discoveries, from how sperm really swim to the surprisingly big changes that occur to them when they reach the female body.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="quote-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;div class="sc-2b8ea91d-0 bgzaEJ"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-2b8ea91d-2 dYxeIv"&gt;No other cell within the body changes its structure, its shape, in such a unique way – Adam Watkins&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;"Sperm – or spermatozoa – are 'very, very different' from all other cells on Earth," says Martins da Silva. "They don't &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/35680646/%2525252523:~:text=The%252525252520two%252525252520main%252525252520ATP-producing,-called%252525252520sperm%252525252520energy%252525252520debate)." class="sc-f9178328-0 bGFWdi"&gt;handle energy&lt;/a&gt; in the same way. They don't have the same sort of cellular metabolism and mechanisms that we would expect to find in all other cells."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Sperm are also the only human cells which can survive outside the body, Martins da Silva adds. "For that reason, they are extraordinarily specialised." However, due to their size these tiny cells are very difficult to study, she says. "There's a lot we know about reproduction – but there's a huge amount that we don't understand."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 hoQmHM"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-d1200759-1 kycbVO"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20250611-093910-fc500e843d-web-2.23.1-1/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-d1200759-0 dkIvM hide-when-no-script"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/160xn/p0lj3f37.jpg.webp 160w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/240xn/p0lj3f37.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/320xn/p0lj3f37.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/480xn/p0lj3f37.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/640xn/p0lj3f37.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/800xn/p0lj3f37.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/1024xn/p0lj3f37.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/1376xn/p0lj3f37.jpg.webp 1376w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/1920xn/p0lj3f37.jpg.webp 1920w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/480xn/p0lj3f37.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Alamy Despite being the smallest cell in the human body, sperm are extraordinarily specialised (Credit: Alamy)" class="sc-d1200759-0 dvfjxj"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-d1200759-2 gwFzuU"&gt;Alamy&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jvncPH"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 FPsqq"&gt;Despite being the smallest cell in the human body, sperm are extraordinarily specialised (Credit: Alamy)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;One fundamental question that remained unanswered over almost 350 years of research: what exactly are sperm?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;"The sperm is incredibly well-packaged," says Adam Watkins, associate professor in reproductive and developmental physiology at Nottingham University in the UK. "We typically thought of the sperm as a bag of DNA on a tail. But as we've started to realise, it's quite a complex cell – there's a lot of &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC3015006/" class="sc-f9178328-0 bGFWdi"&gt;[other] genetic information in there&lt;/a&gt;."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Almost 200 years later, in 1869, Johannes Friedrich Miescher, a Swiss physician and biologist, was studying human white blood cells collected from pus left on soiled hospital bandages when he &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC7268995/" class="sc-f9178328-0 bGFWdi"&gt;discovered what he called "nuclein"&lt;/a&gt; inside the nuclei. The term "nuclein" was later changed to "nucleic acid" and eventually became "deoxyribonucleic acid" – or "DNA". &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Since then, our understanding of sperm has moved on leaps and bounds. But &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://journals.plos.org/plosbiology/article?id=10.1371/journal.pbio.3000953" class="sc-f9178328-0 bGFWdi"&gt;much still remains a mystery&lt;/a&gt;, says Watkins. As scientists have started to better understand early embryonic development, he adds, they are realising that sperm doesn't just pass the father's chromosomes on, but also &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://clinicalepigeneticsjournal.biomedcentral.com/articles/10.1186/s13148-025-01815-1" class="sc-f9178328-0 bGFWdi"&gt;epigenetic information&lt;/a&gt;, an extra layer of information that affects how and when the genes should be used. "It can really influence how the embryo develops and potentially the lifelong trajectory of the offspring that those sperm generate," says Watkins.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="quote-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;div class="sc-2b8ea91d-0 bgzaEJ"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-2b8ea91d-2 dYxeIv"&gt;It turns out that what's driving the system is female evolution – and males are just trying to keep up – Scott Pitnick&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Sperm cells begin to form from puberty onwards, made in vessels within the testicles called seminiferous tubules.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;"If you look inside the testes where the sperm are made, it starts as just a round cell that looks pretty much like anything else," says Watkins. "Then it undergoes this dramatic change where it becomes a sperm head with a tail. No other cell within the body changes its structure, its shape, in such a unique way."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;After ejaculation, each of these tiny cells must propel themselves forward (alongside their 50 million competitors) using their tail-like appendages to swim for the egg. And while you may have seen plenty of videos of tadpole-like sperm swimming around, in fact scientists are only just beginning to understand how sperm really swim.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 hoQmHM"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-d1200759-1 kycbVO"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20250611-093910-fc500e843d-web-2.23.1-1/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-d1200759-0 dkIvM hide-when-no-script"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/160xn/p0lj3gcj.jpg.webp 160w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/240xn/p0lj3gcj.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/320xn/p0lj3gcj.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/480xn/p0lj3gcj.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/640xn/p0lj3gcj.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/800xn/p0lj3gcj.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/1024xn/p0lj3gcj.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/1376xn/p0lj3gcj.jpg.webp 1376w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/1920xn/p0lj3gcj.jpg.webp 1920w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/480xn/p0lj3gcj.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Alamy 17th-Century Dutch microbiologist Antoni van Leeuwenhoek believed a tiny but complete human existed within spermatozoa (Credit: Alamy)" class="sc-d1200759-0 dvfjxj"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-d1200759-2 gwFzuU"&gt;Alamy&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jvncPH"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 FPsqq"&gt;17th-Century Dutch microbiologist Antoni van Leeuwenhoek believed a tiny but complete human existed within spermatozoa (Credit: Alamy)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="quote-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;div class="sc-2b8ea91d-0 bgzaEJ"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-2b8ea91d-2 dYxeIv"&gt;Some fruit fly species produce sperm cells 20 times their own body length. That would be like a man producing sperm the length of a 40m (130ft) python&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Spermatozoa which are healthy and take the right route are rare. &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.open.edu/openlearn/nature-environment/natural-history/sperm-counts" class="sc-f9178328-0 bGFWdi"&gt;Many take a wrong turn&lt;/a&gt; in the maze that is the female body – and never even make it near the goal line. For the ones that do find their way to the fallopian tubes, scientists think that they may be &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/16272225/%2525252523:~:text=A%252525252520few%252525252520thousand%252525252520sperm%252525252520swim,with%252525252520endosalpingeal%252525252520(oviductal)%252525252520epithelium." class="sc-f9178328-0 bGFWdi"&gt;guided by chemical signals&lt;/a&gt; emitted by the egg. One recent theory is that sperm may use taste receptors to "&lt;a target="_blank" href="http://mdpi.com/1422-0067/20/4/967" class="sc-f9178328-0 bGFWdi"&gt;taste&lt;/a&gt;" their way to the egg.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Once the sperm find the egg, the challenge is not over. The egg is surrounded by a &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/16272225/%2525252523:~:text=A%252525252520few%252525252520thousand%252525252520sperm%252525252520swim,with%252525252520endosalpingeal%252525252520(oviductal)%252525252520epithelium." class="sc-f9178328-0 bGFWdi"&gt;triplicate coat of armour&lt;/a&gt;: the &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.britannica.com/science/fertilization-reproduction%23ref606596" class="sc-f9178328-0 bGFWdi"&gt;corona radiata&lt;/a&gt;, an array of cells; the &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC8789258/" class="sc-f9178328-0 bGFWdi"&gt;zona pellucida&lt;/a&gt;, a jelly-like cushion made of protein; and finally the &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://link.springer.com/article/10.1007/s13669-013-0059-2%23:~:text=When%2520the%2520first%2520sperm%2520enters%2520the%2520egg,,has%2520not%2520been%2520well%2520studied%2520in%2520humans." class="sc-f9178328-0 bGFWdi"&gt;egg plasma membrane&lt;/a&gt;. The sperm cells have to fight their way through all the layers, using chemicals contained in their &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC3271650/%2525252523:~:text=The%252525252520acrosome%252525252520is%252525252520a%252525252520unique,sperm%252525252520penetrate%252525252520the%252525252520egg's%252525252520coats." class="sc-f9178328-0 bGFWdi"&gt;acrosome&lt;/a&gt;, a cap-like structure on the head of a sperm cell containing enzymes that digest the egg cell coating. However, what prompts the release of these enzymes &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.frontiersin.org/journals/endocrinology/articles/10.3389/fendo.2023.1273878/epub" class="sc-f9178328-0 bGFWdi"&gt;remains a mystery&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;&lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.genome.gov/genetics-glossary/Diploid" class="sc-f9178328-0 bGFWdi"&gt;Human cells are diploid&lt;/a&gt;. This means they contain two complete sets of chromosomes, one from each parent. If more than one sperm were to fuse with the egg, a condition called &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/books/NBK26843/" class="sc-f9178328-0 bGFWdi"&gt;polyspermy&lt;/a&gt; would arise. Nondiploid cells – ones with the incorrect number of chromosomes – would develop, a condition lethal to a growing embryo.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;To prevent this from happening, once a sperm cell has made contact with it, the egg quickly employs two mechanisms. First, its plasma membrane rapidly depolarises – meaning it creates &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.carlsonscience.com/fast-block" class="sc-f9178328-0 bGFWdi"&gt;an electrical barrier&lt;/a&gt; that further sperm cannot cross. However, this only lasts a short time before returning to normal. This is where the &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/books/NBK26843/" class="sc-f9178328-0 bGFWdi"&gt;cortical reaction&lt;/a&gt; comes in. A sudden release of calcium causes the zona pellucida – the egg's "&lt;a target="_blank" href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC2528931/" class="sc-f9178328-0 bGFWdi"&gt;extracellular coat&lt;/a&gt;" – to become hardened, creating an impenetrable barrier.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jvncPH"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 FPsqq"&gt;What external factors affect male fertility and why.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;One way researchers are hoping to shed light on sperm is by &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.nature.com/articles/nature18005" class="sc-f9178328-0 bGFWdi"&gt;studying species other than our own&lt;/a&gt;, says Scott Pitnick, a professor of biology at Syracuse University in New York. Human sperm cells are microscopic, so we can't see them with the naked eye. But some fruit fly species produce sperm cells &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.nature.com/articles/nature18005" class="sc-f9178328-0 bGFWdi"&gt;20 times their own body length&lt;/a&gt;. That would be like a man producing sperm the length of a 40m (130ft) python.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;"Why do males in some species make a few giant sperm?" asks Pitnick. "The answer, it turns out, is because females have evolved reproductive tracts that favour them." That's "not really much of an answer", he adds, because it's just the redirects the question: why have females evolved this way? "We still don't understand that at all."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="quote-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;div class="sc-2b8ea91d-0 bgzaEJ"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-2b8ea91d-2 dYxeIv"&gt;Research suggests sperm counts are tumbling globally and the decline appears to be accelerating&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;But it does teach us that sperm as they exist in the male body is only half the story, says Pitnick. "There's a massive sex bias historically in science. There's been this obscenely biased male focus on male traits. But it turns out that what's driving the system is female evolution – and males are just trying to keep up."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;"It turns out the female reproductive tract is this incredibly, rapidly evolving environment," says Pitnick, "and we don't know much about what sperm do inside the female. That is the big, hidden world. I think the female reproductive tract is the greatest unexplored frontier for sexual selection, theory and speciation [the process by which &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.nature.com/scitable/knowledge/library/speciation-the-origin-of-new-species-26230527/" class="sc-f9178328-0 bGFWdi"&gt;new species are formed&lt;/a&gt;]."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;The fruit fly's long-tailed sperm, &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41559-024-02587-2" class="sc-f9178328-0 bGFWdi"&gt;suggests Pitnick&lt;/a&gt;, could be considered an ornament – much like a deer's antlers or a peacock's tail.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Ornaments are a "sort of a weapon in evolution", explains Pitnick. More than just a defence from predators, ornaments like antlers and horns often have two roles to play. "A lot of these weapons are about sex, and usually male-male competition. The [fruit fly's] long sperm flagellum really meets the definitional criteria of an ornament. We think the female tract has traits that bias fertilisation in favour of some sperm phenotypes over others."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;We know a lot about pre-mating sexual selection, Pitnick says. "Say, it's &lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.bbc.co.uk/future/article/20240902-how-controlled-burns-can-help-wildlife" class="sc-f9178328-0 bGFWdi"&gt;prairie chickens dancing&lt;/a&gt; out on a grassland, or a &lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/p023wbh0" class="sc-f9178328-0 bGFWdi"&gt;bird of paradise displaying&lt;/a&gt; in a rainforest. It's motion, it's colour, it's smells?" Processing this sensory input, explains Pitnick, leads to decision making – whether the pair mate or not.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;But, Pitnick says, the sexual selection that goes on inside the female after mating – and how this drives the evolution of sperm – largely remains a mystery. "We still understand very little about the genetics of ornaments and preferences," he says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 hoQmHM"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-d1200759-1 kycbVO"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20250611-093910-fc500e843d-web-2.23.1-1/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-d1200759-0 dkIvM hide-when-no-script"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/160xn/p0lj3gts.jpg.webp 160w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/240xn/p0lj3gts.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/320xn/p0lj3gts.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/480xn/p0lj3gts.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/640xn/p0lj3gts.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/800xn/p0lj3gts.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/1024xn/p0lj3gts.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/1376xn/p0lj3gts.jpg.webp 1376w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/1920xn/p0lj3gts.jpg.webp 1920w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/480xn/p0lj3gts.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Alamy Sperm are so tiny that they can be difficult to study. Samples can be stained to make them easier to see under a microscope (Credit: Alamy)" class="sc-d1200759-0 dvfjxj"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-d1200759-2 gwFzuU"&gt;Alamy&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jvncPH"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 FPsqq"&gt;Sperm are so tiny that they can be difficult to study. Samples can be stained to make them easier to see under a microscope (Credit: Alamy)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;To fully understand sperm, we need to think about how the entire lifecycle of the sperm – and the female body, explains Pitnick, plays a huge role in the sperm's development. "Sperm are not mature when they finish developing in the testes, they're not done developing." Complex – and critical – interactions occur between the sperm and the female reproductive tract, he says. "We're now spending a lot of time studying what we call &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://experts.syr.edu/en/publications/post-ejaculatory-modifications-to-sperm-pems" class="sc-f9178328-0 bGFWdi"&gt;post-ejaculatory modifications to sperm&lt;/a&gt; across the whole animal kingdom." &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;According to a &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.who.int/publications/i/item/978920068315" class="sc-f9178328-0 bGFWdi"&gt;2023 report&lt;/a&gt; published by the World Health Organisation (WHO), around one in six adults worldwide experience infertility – and male infertility contributes to roughly &lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.bbc.co.uk/future/article/20230327-how-pollution-is-causing-a-male-fertility-crisis" class="sc-f9178328-0 bGFWdi"&gt;half of all cases&lt;/a&gt;. (It's also worth noting that many people around the world are not having as many children as they want for other reasons too, such as the prohibitive cost of parenthood, as a &lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/clynq459wxgo" class="sc-f9178328-0 bGFWdi"&gt;recent United Nation population Fund report highlighted&lt;/a&gt;). &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;"With all those moving parts, there are so many things that could go wrong," says Hannah Morgan, a post-doctoral research associate in maternal and fetal health at the University of Manchester, UK. "It could be a mechanism: it doesn't swim very well, so it can't get to the egg. Or it could be something more intricate within the head of the sperm, or other regions of the sperm. It's so specialised in so many different ways, that lots of little things can go wrong."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;One way to see if a man may be infertile is to look inside the sperm, says Morgan. "How does the DNA look? How is it packaged? How fragmented is it? To break open the sperm, there's a whole range of stuff you could look at. But what is a good or bad measurement? We don't actually know." &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Perhaps by unravelling the mystery of sperm and how they function, Morgan says, we might begin to understand male infertility too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;&lt;i id="for-more-science,-technology,-environment-and-health-stories-from-the-bbc,-follow-us-on" class="sc-d16436d-0 fhKUCU"&gt;For more science, technology, environment and health stories from the BBC, follow us on &lt;/i&gt;&lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.facebook.com/BBCFuture/" class="sc-f9178328-0 bGFWdi"&gt;&lt;i id="facebook" class="sc-d16436d-0 fhKUCU"&gt;Facebook&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;i id="," class="sc-d16436d-0 fhKUCU"&gt;, &lt;/i&gt;&lt;a target="_blank" href="https://x.com/BBC_Future" class="sc-f9178328-0 bGFWdi"&gt;&lt;i id="x" class="sc-d16436d-0 fhKUCU"&gt;X&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;i id="and" class="sc-d16436d-0 fhKUCU"&gt; and &lt;/i&gt;&lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.instagram.com/bbcfuture_official/" class="sc-f9178328-0 bGFWdi"&gt;&lt;i id="instagram" class="sc-d16436d-0 fhKUCU"&gt;Instagram&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;i id="." class="sc-d16436d-0 fhKUCU"&gt;&lt;b id="." class="sc-d16436d-0 jpoiOL"&gt;.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i id="" class="sc-d16436d-0 fhKUCU"&gt; &lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BBC</author><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 09:01:50 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiowFBVV95cUxPektuVkZrZTRMWnRMSHF0UGdvNGRrUXF6OWpjeXRtNHZwUHdBMTlwVk0wY3ZfZGNDRFFZQ2RpeWlLRk1POVQtZXl0ZTdLODc5clVfWHg4N0lzcmpLRVJuZVVwbjVYbXpFME1WQzYwczd3VXJOc29SeXVKWklNUjFSQjNndldoV1pfZnhTWGhpNUpIeEw5NG5vcWduWDdTLVBfZVBz</guid></item><item><title>肠道问题、糖尿病或高血压？抛弃这些水果-印度时报 | Gut issues, Diabetes or High BP? Ditch these fruits - Times of India</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMi4wFBVV95cUxONDhfVHc1a3dwZ0M5amFUbTkwdDRuZ25ic3hpWmVBbG1xc2ZYMVNDNUUzWFRYUEdxYnRZdFJuTGRpS1JTTUlzc1FuZ3VFa2FFSHdoNEFobnZJVjZUMDVKelhZbUZoUXFSczZmTEVTdm14Zjdpdm8zOWh5cTVtLU9FNVplY2VDZEVyTjZpeXB6SFBVSy1xMW5tbG9vaTM1NWN3Mng3QThrc3UxcTdybFBXWTZheUlWWk1ydDRiak5TN3NHd01OeF9RQ2lEc2NyWDRKeXZLR3Z5UmUyblc2NUl1eWFESQ?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fruits are sometimes regarded as the ultimate health food, full of vitamins, fiber, and natural sugars, and our dearest friends. Most of the times, that is largely the case, but some fruits can actually increase certain medical conditions because of their sugar content, acidity, or nutrient burden.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="2"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Knowing what to steer clear of can assist you in controlling symptoms better and with more informed decisions. Below is a guide to which fruits may not be your friend if you have any of the following conditions. (source: Healthline)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="4"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="5"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Diabetes&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="7"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you have diabetes, blood glucose control is paramount. Fruits such as bananas and grapes can be harmful; they contain a high glycemic wallop. Their natural sugars are rapidly absorbed and will give your glucose levels a boost. You don't have to eliminate all fruits, but it's advisable to stick to lower-sugar choices such as berries and steer clear of overly ripe types altogether.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="11"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="12"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Kidney issues&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For those with compromised kidney function, potassium can build up to dangerous levels. Bananas and oranges are particularly high in potassium, which can strain the kidneys. It’s best to limit or avoid these fruits if your doctor has warned you about high potassium intake. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alternatives like apples or grapes are typically better tolerated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="16"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="17"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Joint Pain or inflammatory conditions&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="19"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you have arthritis or chronic joint inflammation, some of the fruits in the nightshade category, such as tomatoes and eggplants, trigger inflammation. While technically fruits, these may be included in main courses rather than desserts. Many people experience flare-ups if they eat them regularly, so an elimination trial could identify whether they're a trigger.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="22"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="23"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Bloating and gas&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Apples, watermelon, and cherries are gut fermenters. If you have issues with bloating or discomfort in the digestive system, these FODMAP-rich fruits may be the offender. Limiting the amount or cooking them lightly might help alleviate symptoms. Watch how your body reacts, particularly if your digestive system is already sensitive.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="25"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="26"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Skin issues&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="28"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Skin conditions such as acne, eczema, or psoriasis can be exacerbated by some tropical fruits. Mangoes, pineapples, and oranges are high in substances that could possibly cause inflammation or allergic responses in sensitive patients. If your flare-ups occur around fruit-laden meals, try reducing to observe if your skin improves.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="32"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="33"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Heart disease&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fatty or sugary fruits such as coconut and dried fruits are problematic for individuals with heart ailments. Dried fruits might be a healthy choice for snacks, but they tend to be calorie-rich and sugary. Coconut has been known to have saturated fat that might increase cholesterol levels. Be moderate about it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="37"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="38"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Stomach sensitivity&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="40"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you have acid reflux or a sensitive stomach lining, pineapples and citrus fruits can irritate your system. Their acidity level is extremely high, causing discomfort or aggravating gastritis. If you suffer from digestive flare-ups, go for less acidic fruits such as bananas or melons.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="42"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="43"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Low immunity&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Individuals with compromised immune systems need to exercise care with overripe or dried fruits. They may contain molds or provide a source of food for toxic gut bacteria, resulting in infections or imbalances. Fresh, well-washed fruits are always the best option, and anything which appears excessively soft or fermented or has been stored for long periods should be avoided.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="47"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="48"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;High cholesterol and migraine&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Coconut, dried fruits, and citrus could aggravate both. Coconut's saturated fat and dried fruits' concentrated sugars can lead to increased cholesterol. Citrus, on the other hand, has been reported to induce migraines in others. If you're susceptible to either, staying vigilant about your consumption can spell a difference.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="52"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fruits are usually a foundation of healthy eating, but when you have a chronic illness, it's all about personalization. It's not about vilifying any single fruit it's about making wiser, more individualised decisions for your body. Always speak with your doctor or a registered dietitian before removing foods from your diet, but being aware of these associations can make you feel more in charge of your health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="54"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 05:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi4wFBVV95cUxONDhfVHc1a3dwZ0M5amFUbTkwdDRuZ25ic3hpWmVBbG1xc2ZYMVNDNUUzWFRYUEdxYnRZdFJuTGRpS1JTTUlzc1FuZ3VFa2FFSHdoNEFobnZJVjZUMDVKelhZbUZoUXFSczZmTEVTdm14Zjdpdm8zOWh5cTVtLU9FNVplY2VDZEVyTjZpeXB6SFBVSy1xMW5tbG9vaTM1NWN3Mng3QThrc3UxcTdybFBXWTZheUlWWk1ydDRiak5TN3NHd01OeF9RQ2lEc2NyWDRKeXZLR3Z5UmUyblc2NUl1eWFESQ</guid></item><item><title>甜点中令人惊讶的成分会增加心脏病发作的风险-每日邮报 | Surprising ingredient in dessert favorites that raises your risk of a heart attack - Daily Mail</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMivgFBVV95cUxNSWNYUzV1cy1yOWpJNF9sc1o4NDZIay1hVHp6d3pYQy0yd2lHTmdIZXhMdC04RlRRZk1zdjJ3YnR6WWJwbHA4SThtaGFBUVF2Z0VIWUE0UHgyUndTWWtBSGxrcFRmMFhYSXc4cGg1ZVRQYVBEMlZFekVybE00WFdjTXVaSmtGQlM5UjY1V254SkQyblZaWlBIaG1tNzZ3VXM1VUplOEc4VU11SUVEVHd1czdiRnRYMWYxcmlDU0VB0gHDAUFVX3lxTE1aTTA3b0hFTXlkWU02Qi1zU2h4aTBzNXlNSzQ0OFJ0Vmw0OTVBM0NheGZYOGRKTExrbXkwR2ZIUzEzVTVmeVpUNmVCSWNLQVRGa0pqdXpJTmFrZE9OblFRTDRlWVZ2b0pmS3V2S1NrWkxtdHB0WjJQM2k0ZG8yUmVMSzdGdTZ5WHdxazR6R0xtRzhDdnFDcDhDd29wanBBZDF0SFBtMy1pdllnZmp2b3lzZWpyTWkxMzdFODFyRVlGbzRDcw?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div itemprop="articleBody"&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Cardiologists are warning of an often overlooked ingredient in desserts that can lead to high blood pressure if consumed in excess.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Typically a garnish on cookies, bread and butter, soft pretzels, and caramel treats, coarse sea salt contains more sodium than its less expensive grocery store alternative.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;People enjoy the added crunch and marriage of savory and sweet in desserts, but people are inadvertently eating too much salt.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Because coarse salt has larger crystals, it may feel less salty per bite, leading some people to use more than they would with fine salt.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Excessive sodium intake is linked to high blood pressure, heart disease, stroke, and kidney problems.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The body &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/health/article-14603535/Adding-salt-food-increase-risk-depression-anxiety-40-cent-study-finds.html"&gt;only needs a small amount&lt;/a&gt; of sodium to function properly. Sodium is an essential electrolyte that plays several critical roles in the body, including maintaining fluid balance and blood pressure, supporting nerve function, and enabling muscle contractions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Most Americans &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/news/article-2130801/Sodium-content-fast-food-varies-country--And-U-S-saltiest.html"&gt;consume too much sodium&lt;/a&gt;, though – 3,300 mg per day on average, or about 40 percent more than the recommended 2,300mg limit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;People tend to believe that coarse sea salt contains less sodium than standard fine salt, yet both contain about 40 percent sodium.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Typically a garnish on cookies, bread and butter, soft pretzels, and caramel treats, coarse sea salt contains more sodium than its less expensive grocery store alternative&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Salt lurks everywhere in the Western diet, not just in processed meats, snack foods, but in unsuspecting foods, including breads, canned soups, frozen meals, cheese, sauces, and marinades.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;An estimated 89 percent of adults and around 94 percent of children consume too much sodium, &lt;a target="_self" href="/health/article-11950525/Youve-heard-artificial-sweeteners-ready-artificial-salt.html"&gt;according to the CDC&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Eating too much salt is a major setup for high blood pressure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The World Health Organization also estimates that 1.9 million deaths globally each year can be attributed to eating too much salt.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;As sodium causes the body to retain fluids, blood volume and pressure on artery walls increase. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;High blood pressure is a significant risk factor for heart disease, stroke, kidney disease, and other serious health issues.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Dr Brent Egan, an internist and vice president of cardiovascular health at the American Medical Association, &lt;a class="" rel="noreferrer noopener" target="_blank" href="https://www.ama-assn.org/delivering-care/public-health/what-doctors-wish-patients-knew-about-sodium-consumption"&gt;said&lt;/a&gt;: ‘It would take us about a little over 1,000 milligrams a day to get from where we are to where the recommendation would be for the upper limit.’&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;“And if we did that, we’d probably see a significant reduction in blood pressure, heart attack and stroke.’&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;&lt;p class="clear"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Americans consume up to 45 percent more sodium per day than the recommended limit&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;The above graph shows the change in hypertension prevalence among all American adults, as well as among men and women from 1999 to 2023&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Roughly 116 million Americans &lt;a target="_self" href="/health/article-5947119/More-1-3-MILLION-American-teenagers-hypertension-CDC-report-reveals.html"&gt;have high blood pressure.&lt;/a&gt; Approximately 805,000 heart attacks occur each year, as well as 795,000 strokes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;‘If someone has high blood pressure, heart disease, that type of thing, 1,500 milligrams is probably a better target, but for the general population that’s really interested in limiting the burden of chronic disease, 2,300 milligrams is generally what is recommended,’ Dr Egan said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Too much sodium also causes bloating – the uncomfortable feeling that the stomach is swollen and tight. &lt;/p&gt;
    
    
    &lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Body parts like hands, feet, and ankles are likely to swell. And feelings of thirst take over due to dehydration.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Too much salt before bed can also cause restless sleep. Studies suggest high-salt diets may alter cortisol (stress hormone) levels, which regulate sleep-wake cycles.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;A &lt;a target="_self" href="/health/article-12737661/Reducing-salt-one-teaspoon-blood-pressure-medication.html" class=""&gt;recent study&lt;/a&gt; by researchers at Vanderbilt University found that reducing daily salt intake by just one teaspoon is as effective as blood pressure medication.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;They tested high and low-salt diets on hundreds of patients, some of whom had high blood pressure, and found that cutting out a can of Heinz soup each day lowered people's blood pressure by six percent within a week.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;This reduction was comparable to that of thiazide diuretic hydrochlorothiazide, a popular blood pressure medication.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;An estimated 89 percent of adults and around 94 percent of children consume too much sodium, according to the CDC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;“Obviously we need some sodium—it's essential for life,” Dr Egan said. But ‘here we are with an average intake of 3,400 milligrams.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;‘Now the body has to make a lot of adjustments, but we can get by with very little sodium,’ he said, noting ‘there's very little danger in this country that most people won't get enough sodium, even if they're eating those fresh foods and not processed foods.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;‘They'll still—for the most part—get more than sufficient sodium that the body needs,” said Dr. Egan. “We live in a state of pretty much constant excess.’&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
            

            
            
            
            
            &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Daily Mail</author><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 05:03:40 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMivgFBVV95cUxNSWNYUzV1cy1yOWpJNF9sc1o4NDZIay1hVHp6d3pYQy0yd2lHTmdIZXhMdC04RlRRZk1zdjJ3YnR6WWJwbHA4SThtaGFBUVF2Z0VIWUE0UHgyUndTWWtBSGxrcFRmMFhYSXc4cGg1ZVRQYVBEMlZFekVybE00WFdjTXVaSmtGQlM5UjY1V254SkQyblZaWlBIaG1tNzZ3VXM1VUplOEc4VU11SUVEVHd1czdiRnRYMWYxcmlDU0VB0gHDAUFVX3lxTE1aTTA3b0hFTXlkWU02Qi1zU2h4aTBzNXlNSzQ0OFJ0Vmw0OTVBM0NheGZYOGRKTExrbXkwR2ZIUzEzVTVmeVpUNmVCSWNLQVRGa0pqdXpJTmFrZE9OblFRTDRlWVZ2b0pmS3V2S1NrWkxtdHB0WjJQM2k0ZG8yUmVMSzdGdTZ5WHdxazR6R0xtRzhDdnFDcDhDd29wanBBZDF0SFBtMy1pdllnZmp2b3lzZWpyTWkxMzdFODFyRVlGbzRDcw</guid></item><item><title>大多数女性忽视这种症状是心脏病发作的微妙迹象，但它可能是生死攸关的问题- BuzzFeed | Most Women Ignore This Symptom As A Subtle Sign Of A Heart Attack, But It Could Be A Matter Of Life And Death - BuzzFeed</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMigAFBVV95cUxQMEFTZHJhakxhYWxHVFpncjR2RDdBQXNIZy1heXZFV1VHYzNlSHU4LVNrYktNcXlFSnlMVWYzaDBBUEk1TWplOUVUa29vb0tNUkRJdkdSc09PaE90Tm1uQ09tQTZkdXlpWDFfZmd3ZGJLQTVzNUFEeGZvRW5tLVppbw?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="subbuzz buzz-width--standard__subbuzz buzz-type--long__subbuzz subbuzz-text
  subbuzz-index-1
  
  
  
  
  " data-module="subbuzz-text"&gt;
  
  &lt;p id="138786352" class="subbuzz-anchor"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;





&lt;p&gt;In a recent segment on &lt;a href="https://www.today.com/health/disease/nausea-widowmaker-heart-attack-symptom-women-rcna136801" target="_blank" data-skimlinks-tracking="7888385" data-affiliate="true"&gt;the “Today” show&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://drchantrise.com/about/" target="_blank" data-skimlinks-tracking="7888385" data-affiliate="true"&gt;Chantrise Holliman&lt;/a&gt;, a mother, wife and heart health educator based in Georgia,&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;shared the story of her &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/life/topic/heart-attack" target="_blank" data-skimlinks-tracking="7888385"&gt;heart attack&lt;/a&gt; and what seemed like the fairly benign symptoms that accompanied it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Holliman experienced nausea, vomiting and mild chest pressure. The first two symptoms ― which aren’t commonly associated with heart attacks ― led her to believe the sensations had more to do with her dinner the night before than a serious medical concern.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Like Holliman, many people don’t know that stomach symptoms can, indeed, be signs of a heart attack. While not the most common warning sign (chest pain is most reported), nausea is also not uncommon during a cardiac event, according to &lt;a href="https://nyulangone.org/doctors/1316106776/sean-p-heffron" target="_blank" data-skimlinks-tracking="7888385" data-affiliate="true"&gt;Dr. Sean Heffron&lt;/a&gt;, a cardiologist at NYU Langone Health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It “tends to depend somewhat on which blood vessel in the heart is affected,” Heffron explained. Additionally, nausea is more commonly seen in women, Heffron said, &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/heartdisease/heart_attack.htm" target="_blank" data-skimlinks-tracking="7888385" data-affiliate="true"&gt;as is vomiting&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Other heart attack signs in women include jaw pain, neck pain, a dull feeling of chest discomfort, upper abdomen pain, back pain and excessive tiredness, according to the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“It’s so important to hear stories like this, because many women think it has to be like, ‘I’m clutching my chest and falling to the ground like you see in the movies,’ and it can be much more subtle,” Dr. Tara Narula, a cardiologist and NBC News medical contributor, &lt;a href="https://www.today.com/health/disease/nausea-widowmaker-heart-attack-symptom-women-rcna136801" target="_blank" data-skimlinks-tracking="7888385" data-affiliate="true"&gt;told “Today.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Heart attacks can look very different in women than in men, which means that sufferers and doctors alike sometimes dismiss them. But it’s important to recognize the signs, especially since heart disease “is the leading cause of death for women in this country,” Narula told “Today.” “One woman every 80 seconds dies of cardiovascular disease.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How to tell if your nausea is part of a heart attack&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BuzzFeed</author><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 00:31:03 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigAFBVV95cUxQMEFTZHJhakxhYWxHVFpncjR2RDdBQXNIZy1heXZFV1VHYzNlSHU4LVNrYktNcXlFSnlMVWYzaDBBUEk1TWplOUVUa29vb0tNUkRJdkdSc09PaE90Tm1uQ09tQTZkdXlpWDFfZmd3ZGJLQTVzNUFEeGZvRW5tLVppbw</guid></item><item><title>根据营养师的说法， 60岁以后应该多吃的6种食物- EatingWell | 6 Foods You Should Eat More of After 60, According to Dietitians - EatingWell</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMifkFVX3lxTE5KYzNmM3dibHhJTEtPT3dyM2lBUWJZSzYtbDh4b0NNQktXaHQtaXJjaG80dmd3dzM4b3Y2X3NSNk5qSTFoTnJnVThOSmFOY2dhSWNRMjI3WVA2N1VqOUZvV2VKWERDS0xtRWdDTlVmQURBcnFSbXY2dE9vZFRkZw?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-page_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-page mntl-block structured-content" data-sc-sticky-offset="90" data-sc-ad-label-height="24" data-sc-ad-track-spacing="100" data-sc-min-track-height="250" data-sc-max-track-height="600" data-sc-breakpoint="50em" data-sc-load-immediate="4" data-sc-content-positions="[1, 1250, 1550, 1950, 2350, 2750, 3150, 3550, 3950]" data-bind-scroll-on-start="true"&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-block_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-callout--summary mntl-sc-block-universal-callout--tips mntl-sc-block-universal-callout theme-summary callout--bordered" data-text="Key Points" data-tracking-id="mntl-sc-block-callout" data-tracking-container="true"&gt;
&lt;div class="mntl-sc-block-universal-callout__body"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Diet plays an important role in maintaining bone, heart, eye and brain health as you age.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;After age 60, prioritize nuts, legumes, leafy greens, cranberries and prunes.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Socializing, consistent sleep and staying physically and mentally active are key for healthy aging.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_2-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Reaching your 60s is a milestone worth celebrating. And while this decade can be filled with travel and more time spent with family, you may also experience some unexpected changes that aren’t quite as welcoming. To keep your energy levels up, mood stable and health on track year after year, it’s important to be intentional about &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/8067323/7-day-high-protein-meal-plan-for-healthy-aging/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;the food on your plate&lt;/a&gt;.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_3-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_4-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Certain foods can go a long way in supporting your body as it ages, whether it’s by &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/things-doctors-do-every-day-for-better-brain-health-11678638" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;boosting brain health&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/foods-for-bone-health-11745664" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;strengthening bones&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/heart-healthy-foods-to-eat-in-january-8768223" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="3"&gt;protecting your heart&lt;/a&gt;. According to dietitians, adding more of these six nutrient-packed foods to your routine can help you feel your best and stay active and energized throughout your golden years. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_5-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-1-walnuts"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_6-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; 1. Walnuts &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_7-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; One of the most powerful foods for longevity is one that you don’t actually need a lot of to see big benefits. “Walnuts provide plant-based omega-3s, antioxidants and polyphenols, all of which play a role in brain and heart health as we age,” says &lt;a href="https://samanthacassetty.com/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Samantha Cassetty, MS, RD&lt;/a&gt;, partner with California Walnuts. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_8-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_9-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Using data from the Nurses’ Health Study, researchers found that women who ate at least two servings or walnuts per week in their late 50s and early 60s were more likely to experience healthy aging, which includes being free from chronic disease, memory problems, physical disability and mental health issues after age 65 compared to those who did not eat walnuts regularly.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="1"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_10-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_11-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Aim to enjoy 2 ounces of &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/8069681/benefits-of-walnuts/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;walnuts&lt;/a&gt; weekly, either on their own or incorporated into recipes. Try adding these crunchy nuts to salads, overnight oats, homemade snack bars and more. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_12-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-2-legumes"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_13-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; 2. Legumes &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_14-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Maintaining bone density is critical for maintaining independence and overall quality of life as we age. Approximately 10 million adults over age 65 have osteoporosis, and while physical activity and &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/best-ways-to-maintain-muscle-mass-to-live-longer-8547770" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;strength training&lt;/a&gt; help, adding legumes to your diet can also support bone health.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="2"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; “Legumes are an excellent source of plant-based protein and fiber, supporting muscle maintenance, gut health and reduced inflammation,” says &lt;a href="https://erinpalinski.com" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;Erin Palinski-Wade, RD, CDCES&lt;/a&gt;.  
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_15-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_16-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Legumes include beans, lentils, peas and peanuts. While all legumes can &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/foods-for-bone-health-8737183" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;support strong bones&lt;/a&gt;, chickpeas may be particularly beneficial. The isoflavones and polyphenols in chickpeas may help prevent osteoporosis by supporting bone metabolism and reducing inflammation.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="3"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Palinski-Wade explains that these mechanisms are especially helpful and relevant for women post-menopause, who are most at risk for bone loss. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_17-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_19-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-3-pistachios"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_20-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; 3. Pistachios &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_21-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; “A handful of pistachios daily can help to improve intake of fiber and key nutrients, including healthy fats, protein and antioxidants, like lutein, which helps &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/best-nutrient-to-protect-your-vision-8773401" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;protect vision&lt;/a&gt; and supports overall health with age,” says Palinksi-Wade, a consultant for American Pistachio Growers. Additionally, one small study found that eating 2 ounces of &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/what-happens-to-your-body-when-you-eat-pistachios-regularly-8687923" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;pistachios daily&lt;/a&gt; for 4 months reduced oxidative damage and increased the gene expression of specific genes that may support the reversal of certain metabolic conditions that are more common with age, including insulin resistance.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="4"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_22-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_23-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; “Plus, as a good source of plant-based protein and fiber, pistachios can help to boost satiety with only 160 calories per serving, which can be beneficial when working towards maintaining a healthy body weight,” adds Palinski-Wade.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_24-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-4-leafy-greens"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_25-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; 4. Leafy Greens &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_26-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; “Leafy greens like spinach, kale and collard greens are rich in vitamin K and folate, which help support brain health and may slow age-related cognitive decline,” says &lt;a href="https://alexandria-hardy-rdn.clientsecure.me/#about" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1" rel="nofollow"&gt;Alexandria Hardy RDN LDN&lt;/a&gt;. Diets high in &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/leafy-green-packed-recipes-that-arent-salad-8619158" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;dark leafy greens&lt;/a&gt; have been associated with improved memory and overall cognitive function in older adults and may even help slow cognitive decline.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="5"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; “These vegetables are rich in brain-supportive nutrients like phylloquinone, beta-carotene and vitamin E, which are thought to support learning and memory,” says Cassetty.  
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_27-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-5-cranberries"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_28-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; 5. Cranberries &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_29-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Over 60% of older adults in the United States do not regularly eat dark leafy vegetables.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="5"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Certain medications, like blood thinners, require consistent intake of vitamin K, which is found in greens like spinach and kale. However, this doesn’t mean you need to avoid these vegetables completely. If you take blood thinners, or another medication that interacts with vitamin K, talk with a healthcare professional about how to safely incorporate leafy greens in your diet. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_30-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_31-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; For older adults with difficulties chewing, Hardy recommends steaming, sautéing or pureeing greens rather than enjoying them raw. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_32-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_33-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/cranberry-health-benefits-8726317" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Cranberries&lt;/a&gt; are rich in anthocyanins and proanthocyanins—antioxiants that support numerous aspects of health, from your brain to your urinary tract. Anthocyanins in cranberries are responsible for their vibrant red color and play a key role in protecting and supporting brain cells.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="6"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; “Thanks to their antioxidative and anti-inflammatory properties, anthocyanins are being studied for their potential role in reducing the risk of brain disorders like Alzheimer’s disease and Parkinson’s disease,” says &lt;a href="https://www.nutritionnowcounseling.com/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;Lauren Manaker MS, RDN, LD&lt;/a&gt;. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_34-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_35-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Cranberries can also be helpful for preventing &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/7962519/uti-bacteria-gut-health-new-research/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;urinary tract infections&lt;/a&gt; (UTIs). While both men and women can experience UTIs, it’s estimated that over 10% of women over age 65 and 30% of women 85 years and older have a UTI at least once a year.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="7"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; “There are compounds in cranberries called proanthocyanidins (PACs), which have been shown to maintain urinary tract health,” says Manaker. These compounds help prevent bacteria from adhering to the walls of the urinary tract, which can help decrease infection rates.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="8"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_36-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-6-prunes"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_37-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; 6. Prunes &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_38-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Bone loss is one of the most common and dangerous side effects of aging. Luckily, eating to protect and maintain bone health can be both delicious and simple. “Prunes contain bioactive compounds that may help blunt bone loss, so they're another tool in your toolkit to support healthy aging,” says Cassetty. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_39-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_40-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; In one study, postmenopausal women who ate 50 grams, or approximately 5–6 prunes, per day had reduced rates of total hip bone mineral density loss over 6 to 12 months, whereas women who did not eat prunes experienced increased fracture risk scores at 6 months.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="9"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Also noteworthy, this study had a 90% compliance rate, proving just how easy and simple it is to add &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/prunes-benefits-8694943" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;prunes&lt;/a&gt; to your diet. The delicious sweet taste and jelly-like texture make them a welcome addition to salads, toast and smoothies—or just to enjoy by the handful.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_41-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_42-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Regularly backed up? The high fiber content of prunes can also help &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/best-breakfast-foods-to-help-you-poop-that-arent-oatmeal-8708873" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;ease constipation&lt;/a&gt; to make bathroom visits smoother (literally).&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="10"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Just be sure to drink more water to minimize side effects associated with increased fiber intake, like gas and bloating.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_43-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_45-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-other-longevity-tips"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_46-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; Other Longevity Tips &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_47-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; What you put on your plate plays a key role in healthy aging, but it’s far from the only factor. The following strategies can help you feel your best now and support your health in the years to come. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_48-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_49-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Maintain a Regular Sleep Schedule&lt;/strong&gt;: Prioritize a &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/what-happens-if-you-dont-get-enough-sleep-11746534" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;consistent sleep&lt;/a&gt; and wake routine, even on days when you don’t have anywhere to be, encourages Palinski-Wade. Regular sleep may be more important than duration, with some studies showing that people getting consistent sleep have a 20 to 48% lower risk of death from any cause than those with irregular sleep patterns.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="11"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Stay Active:&lt;/strong&gt; Keep your body moving—and &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/8026823/what-is-joyful-movement/" class="pseudoStyle" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;make it enjoyable&lt;/a&gt;! “Find something you love, whether it's dancing, walking, gardening or yoga, and make it a regular part of your routine,” says Manaker. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Prioritize Connection&lt;/strong&gt;: Research suggests that &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/loneliness-dementia-risk-study-8733921" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="3"&gt;loneliness&lt;/a&gt; and social isolation have a mortality risk similar to smoking cigarettes, drinking alcohol, physical inactivity and obesity.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="12"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Make it a priority to stay connected with family and friends and consider joining a club or attending a fitness class once a week. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Keep Your Mind Active&lt;/strong&gt;: Staying mentally engaged through learning, puzzles, strategic games and other activities can support &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/habit-to-start-to-improve-your-memory-8415078" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="4"&gt;memory&lt;/a&gt; and cognition as you age. Researchers found that people under 75 who regularly participated in cognitively stimulating tasks and activities saw the greatest increases in cognitive function and memory.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="13"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_50-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-our-expert-take"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_51-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; Our Expert Take &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_52-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Aging well doesn’t have to mean overhauling your entire diet and lifestyle. Focusing on &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/7900915/foods-associated-with-living-longer-according-to-research/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;nutrient-dense foods&lt;/a&gt;, engaging in joyful movement and maintaining a consistent routine can help you feel your best well into your 60s, 70s and beyond.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>EatingWell</author><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMifkFVX3lxTE5KYzNmM3dibHhJTEtPT3dyM2lBUWJZSzYtbDh4b0NNQktXaHQtaXJjaG80dmd3dzM4b3Y2X3NSNk5qSTFoTnJnVThOSmFOY2dhSWNRMjI3WVA2N1VqOUZvV2VKWERDS0xtRWdDTlVmQURBcnFSbXY2dE9vZFRkZw</guid></item><item><title>博尔德县居民报告使用公共交通的麻疹病例- 9News | Measles case reported in Boulder County resident who used public transportation - 9News</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiswFBVV95cUxPMnAyNjF0OG1fWUx4TUlrMS1IY2tHYmpxd2lINDlGSzVDa1JYd3BvdFEwRWRPdEdNM3c2dVhrN3d1QmdhRlo3S0hhcW1BbkVDakNiV29wNEh0ZFNBaFdlaTZMMVNaT09EeE9DMW1RNHc0V0luREtLSWxTaVpFVkZvOTEzSE9qd0J2bkVjWkxGbnA0RU4xNk02ZFdBZG9Sdmg3WFlONUx3WF9xaEdkcWVjLUx3Zw?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Access Denied&lt;/h1&gt;
 
You don't have permission to access "http://www.9news.com/article/news/health/measles-boulder-county-colorado/73-08d6d64c-a5b4-4a9d-958e-57718cf3ea48" on this server.&lt;p&gt;
Reference #18.2c153b17.1749867325.d7334a2
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;https://errors.edgesuite.net/18.2c153b17.1749867325.d7334a2&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/body&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>9News</author><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 23:48:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiswFBVV95cUxPMnAyNjF0OG1fWUx4TUlrMS1IY2tHYmpxd2lINDlGSzVDa1JYd3BvdFEwRWRPdEdNM3c2dVhrN3d1QmdhRlo3S0hhcW1BbkVDakNiV29wNEh0ZFNBaFdlaTZMMVNaT09EeE9DMW1RNHc0V0luREtLSWxTaVpFVkZvOTEzSE9qd0J2bkVjWkxGbnA0RU4xNk02ZFdBZG9Sdmg3WFlONUx3WF9xaEdkcWVjLUx3Zw</guid></item><item><title>华盛顿州和俄勒冈州百日咳病例急剧上升，卫生官员敦促接种疫苗- KGW | Whooping cough cases rise sharply in Washington and Oregon, health officials urge vaccination - KGW</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiwwFBVV95cUxNNFZyT1dfaFJCd0xtSDVVRFczVHpHN2QzVEk5VGRjMFdEQ0d0ekhCckFhb3JMTXB3MUxWZmc0Wk1OUEJ6NmtDazNybi1sZ2VUTFd5UVFjOEdaRmcxVUZxSzVWNndSUWVROXVPcE1PZ3pFSWtZdFJaaC1EbVpmc0s4MmtjZll0XzNQc081VnVydEo2Q2RmV3NpcF9Na19sLXp0RlBsOUtGSUNVa1RzZTNlaXRNTkRKUWxUc3NvME9tRXRpTEE?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="article__summary"&gt;More than 1,300 cases have already been reported this year in Washington. There have been 877 reported cases in Oregon, with the majority in Washington County.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;div class="article__body"&gt;
                    &lt;div class="article__section article__section_type_text utility__text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PORTLAND, Ore. — Health officials in Washington and Oregon are warning the public about a sharp rise in pertussis cases, &lt;a href="/article/news/health/whooping-cough-cases-rising-again/507-b322a88b-1e12-4e48-af99-fec8d9364874" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;also known as whooping cough&lt;/a&gt;, and urging people to stay current on their vaccinations.&lt;/p&gt;                    &lt;/div&gt;
                    &lt;div class="article__section article__section_type_text utility__text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In Washington, more than 2,200 cases were reported statewide in 2024, a startling increase from just 87 cases in 2023, according to state health officials. As of May 2025, more than 1,300 cases have already been reported.&lt;/p&gt;                    &lt;/div&gt;
                        
                    &lt;div class="article__section article__section_type_text utility__text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Doctors said the illness can be particularly dangerous for infants and young children. They recommend that people ensure they and their children are up to date on pertussis vaccinations. Whooping cough is a highly contagious respiratory disease. Early symptoms are often similar to the common cold but can develop into violent coughing fits, difficulty breathing and other serious complications.&lt;/p&gt;                    &lt;/div&gt;
                    
                    &lt;div class="article__section article__section_type_text utility__text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In Oregon, the state recorded 123 cases of pertussis in May alone, according to the Oregon Health Authority. So far in 2025, there have been 877 reported cases statewide, with the majority in Washington County.&lt;/p&gt;                    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>KGW</author><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 23:32:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiwwFBVV95cUxNNFZyT1dfaFJCd0xtSDVVRFczVHpHN2QzVEk5VGRjMFdEQ0d0ekhCckFhb3JMTXB3MUxWZmc0Wk1OUEJ6NmtDazNybi1sZ2VUTFd5UVFjOEdaRmcxVUZxSzVWNndSUWVROXVPcE1PZ3pFSWtZdFJaaC1EbVpmc0s4MmtjZll0XzNQc081VnVydEo2Q2RmV3NpcF9Na19sLXp0RlBsOUtGSUNVa1RzZTNlaXRNTkRKUWxUc3NvME9tRXRpTEE</guid></item><item><title>根据一项新的研究- EatingWell ，您应该吃4种营养素来帮助降低痴呆风险 | 4 Nutrients You Should Be Eating to Help Lower Dementia Risk, According to a New Study - EatingWell</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMigAFBVV95cUxNMzNmb0ZhYWs2RHZCYy1tdFhoOGxfNVFXRHQ2eWxvM0VsSXJOSkF1aEtWVkpqS2NQcG4zMXRKbEpLYnY3aEo1b2YzdGZDU25vbVlubTd5Tm9lMDhBaXZJWUFkTE1KNUx4MktIczcwSE9CVURZWER4T25kVTk5LVM1Yg?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-page_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-page mntl-block structured-content" data-sc-sticky-offset="90" data-sc-ad-label-height="24" data-sc-ad-track-spacing="100" data-sc-min-track-height="250" data-sc-max-track-height="600" data-sc-breakpoint="50em" data-sc-load-immediate="4" data-sc-content-positions="[1, 1250, 1550, 1950, 2350, 2750, 3150, 3550, 3950]" data-bind-scroll-on-start="true"&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-block_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-callout--summary mntl-sc-block-universal-callout--tips mntl-sc-block-universal-callout theme-summary callout--bordered" data-text="Key Points" data-tracking-id="mntl-sc-block-callout" data-tracking-container="true"&gt;
&lt;div class="mntl-sc-block-universal-callout__body"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;A new study suggests that several nutrients are linked with a lower risk of dementia.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;These nutrients include vitamins and minerals that act as antioxidants, plus fiber.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;High sugar intake was related to an increased risk of dementia.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_2-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; As we age, it’s natural to become more forgetful. But when the occasional “Where did I leave my keys?” becomes forgetting loved ones’ names and your own address, it may be a sign of something more serious. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_3-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_4-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Dementia is a general term for &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/7903274/7-sneaky-signs-you-could-have-cognitive-decline-according-to-experts/" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;loss of memory&lt;/a&gt;, language, problem-solving and other thinking abilities, severe enough to interfere with everyday life.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="1"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/7893378/these-13-things-could-make-you-more-likely-to-get-alzheimers-according-to-a-new-study/" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;Alzheimer’s disease&lt;/a&gt; is the most common type of dementia. Unfortunately, &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/dementia-risk-doubling-study-8776659" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="3"&gt;dementia cases are expected to double&lt;/a&gt; by the year 2060. And the economic burden of unpaid dementia caregiving in the U.S. is expected to skyrocket from an average of $172 billion in 2020 to over $1.5 trillion by 2060.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="2"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; And this doesn’t take into account the emotional toll on families, friends and caregivers. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_5-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_6-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Since there is currently no cure for dementia, taking &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/activity-to-limit-for-reduced-risk-dementia-8548330" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;preventative measures&lt;/a&gt; can be a wise move. Columbia University researchers wanted to know which nutrients were related to a &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/lifestyle-factors-reduce-early-dementia-risk-new-study-8423035" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;reduced risk of dementia&lt;/a&gt;—and which ones might increase the risk. They recently published their findings in &lt;em&gt;Nutrients&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="3"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Let’s break down what they found. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_7-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_9-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-how-was-this-study-conducted"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_10-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; How Was This Study Conducted? &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_11-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Researchers drew data from the Health and Retirement Study (HRS), an ongoing U.S. study conducted biennially since 1992 that includes adults 50 years and older. In 2013, food consumption and nutrition intake was collected from a subset of the HRS called the Healthcare and Nutrition Study (HCNS).
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_12-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_13-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; To evaluate diet, participants completed a food frequency questionnaire that asked how frequently they consumed 163 different foods and beverages over the past 12 months. From this, the research team calculated nutrient intake based on participants’ responses for 101 nutrients. Individual nutrients were assessed regarding their relationship to dementia. In addition, researchers calculated composite scores for some groups of nutrients.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_14-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_15-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Participants’ cognitive abilities were assessed using two different methods. One method was via a telephone interview with participants and the other was via a proxy respondent. For the proxy method, someone close to the participant answered questions about the participant’s memory levels, limitations in instrumental activities of daily living and status of cognitive impairment. Researchers would use this information to look for associations between nutrient intake and dementia risk.  
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_16-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_17-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; This current study included 6,280 HCNS participants who met the researchers’ criteria, which included full diet information and cognitive assessments. Researchers also adjusted for demographic information like age, race, sex, BMI, education level, smoking status, alcohol intake and physical activity.  
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_18-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_20-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-what-did-this-study-show"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_21-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; What Did This Study Show? &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_22-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; After running statistical analyses, the results suggest that several nutrients were connected with a reduced risk of dementia. The five with the strongest association were:
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_23-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_24-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;li&gt;Isorhamnetin, a type of flavonol&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Manganese, a mineral&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Dietary fiber&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Beta-tocopherol and beta-tocotrienol, both forms of vitamin E&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_25-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_26-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; This study also adds to the mounting evidence that &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/sneaky-signs-eating-too-much-sugar-11721349" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;high sugar intake&lt;/a&gt; is linked with a higher risk of dementia.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="4"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="5"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; With that said, it also showed some controversial associations between some other nutrients and higher dementia risk. We say controversial because they conflict with previous research or add to mixed results. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_27-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_28-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; For example, this study suggests a link between certain components in milk and an increased risk of dementia, including glycerophosphocholine and vitamin D, both of which have been shown to support brain health in other studies. Researchers note that more research needs to be done, and that it could be due to other components in the food, not necessarily these nutrients. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_29-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_30-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; This study has several limitations. First, asking people to estimate how much they ate of certain foods over the last year leaves lots of room for bias, forgetfulness and guessing. Also, &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/7903274/7-sneaky-signs-you-could-have-cognitive-decline-according-to-experts/" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;cognitive abilities and dementia&lt;/a&gt; were not clinically evaluated, which also leaves room for bias. Lastly, researchers did not adjust for factors like genetics and environmental factors that play a role in dementia. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_31-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_33-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-how-does-this-apply-to-real-life"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_34-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; How Does This Apply to Real Life? &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_35-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Isorhamnetin is a flavonol found in fruits and vegetables, including onions, almonds, berries, cherries, pears, apples and green grapes.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="6"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;It’s also found in ginkgo biloba, an herb touted for its brain health benefits.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_36-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_37-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; You’ll find manganese in nuts, legumes, whole grains and leafy greens. Maple syrup and &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/7676558/what-is-maple-water-and-should-you-be-drinking-it/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;maple water&lt;/a&gt; are also rich sources of this trace mineral. Manganese plays a role in many bodily processes, including metabolism and immunity.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="7"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; While it’s a mineral, manganese plays a dual role and acts like an antioxidant, protecting cells from damage from free radicals. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_38-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_39-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Like manganese, vitamin E also has antioxidant properties, protecting cells from damage.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="8"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Nuts, seeds, wheat germ, and sunflower and safflower oils are good sources of vitamin E. You’ll also get some in spinach and broccoli.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_40-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_41-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; A whopping &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/how-much-fiber-should-you-be-eating-11752876" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;nine out of 10 Americans&lt;/a&gt; don’t have enough fiber in their diets. Fiber-rich foods include fruits, vegetables, nuts, seeds, whole grains and legumes. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_42-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_43-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; If you’re concerned that you’re not including enough of these nutrients in your day-to-day routine, consider shaking things up. An easy (and painless) way to do it is to swap out your typical snacks for nutrient-rich ones. For example, if you typically reach for chips, soda or a candy bar mid-afternoon, consider a handful of nuts and berries. Or how about some hummus and veggie sticks? 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_44-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_45-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; If you’re ready to go all in and want some guidance, check out our &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/30-day-mind-diet-meal-plan-for-cognitive-health-11700108" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;MIND diet meal plans&lt;/a&gt;. The MIND diet is a fusion of the Mediterranean and DASH diets, and is loaded with brain-healthy foods that are also good for your heart. &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/mind-diet-dementia-study-11748383" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;There is recent evidence&lt;/a&gt; that following this healthy eating pattern may reduce your risk of dementia by up to 25%.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_46-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_47-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; In addition to food, physical activity, managing your stressors and getting plenty of quality sleep also influence brain health. And make sure you’re also spending time with loved ones, as &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/loneliness-dementia-risk-study-8733921" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;loneliness has also been shown to increase dementia &lt;/a&gt;risk. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_48-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_50-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-the-bottom-line"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_51-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; The Bottom Line &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_52-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; This study suggests that certain nutrients, like vitamin E, manganese and isorhamnetin, all of which act like antioxidants, plus fiber, are linked with a lower risk of dementia. It also adds to existing evidence that high sugar intake may raise dementia risk. If possible, get these brain-protecting nutrients from food. If you have difficulty doing so, seek the advice of a registered dietitian or a healthcare professional who can help you integrate foods rich in these nutrients and determine if supplementation is a viable option for you.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>EatingWell</author><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 22:28:43 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigAFBVV95cUxNMzNmb0ZhYWs2RHZCYy1tdFhoOGxfNVFXRHQ2eWxvM0VsSXJOSkF1aEtWVkpqS2NQcG4zMXRKbEpLYnY3aEo1b2YzdGZDU25vbVlubTd5Tm9lMDhBaXZJWUFkTE1KNUx4MktIczcwSE9CVURZWER4T25kVTk5LVM1Yg</guid></item><item><title>博尔德县居民将Flatiron Flyer乘客暴露于麻疹-丹佛邮报 | Boulder County resident exposed Flatiron Flyer passengers to measles - The Denver Post</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMijgFBVV95cUxPZ0hZRERVLTRURXNlYkVvNmRxZE93emdQaHk3dVlEdmZKdDZaQ3VKRnNOblQ3eldLYWpZZE5xcTFaZm0tTUprcVJKMEJ3TmNxZGljcFBwcG5lNmxmU2w5SFlEcU5va3o2ZXBfM210N2NId0dGM0xuNjVZd3pwWTBJR1h5bnUxLUlLbXAwTUZn0gGTAUFVX3lxTFB0aVlBRmYzc3htakhSTmlNTHRENm5CLTBHS1JQYXFiREZaT0VZTzNZY0xuZlp3ZGx5bWYtUnJYOHVIWVNtSVNjeDlRS2JWSHA0aGlJMFhWamN1WjVrdXozY3lBNklBYjAwOUN0dzBtSXRVWE1keVR5UEE4b3FWTzl4WUpPY29Nb1VTQWJYLU9jYkppWQ?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="body-copy"&gt;&lt;p class="wp-remixd-voice-wrapper"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;People who took the Regional Transportation District’s Flatiron Flyer between Boulder and Denver last week should watch for measles symptoms after a contagious Boulder County resident rode that route six times.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The unidentified resident returned from a recent trip to Europe with measles, becoming the state’s 15th case this year, according to the Colorado Department of Public Health and Environment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The spike in measles cases in Colorado, the most the state has recorded in decades, comes after a deadly outbreak in Texas this year, and as other hot spots have emerged around the world for the highly contagious disease.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The infected Boulder County resident was an adult who was fully vaccinated, health officials said. Two shots of the vaccine are about 97% effective in preventing infection.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;State health officials say people should monitor themselves for symptoms for 21 days — and consider avoiding public gatherings — if they visited the following exposure locations in Boulder and Denver:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RTD Flatiron Flyer between Denver and Boulder&lt;/strong&gt;, both ways, from 6:45 to 9:35 a.m. and 4:05 to 7:15 p.m. June 3, June 5 and June 6.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Market Building&lt;/strong&gt;, 1400 16th St., Denver, from 8 a.m. to 6:15 p.m. June 3-6.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Little Finch Coffee Shop&lt;/strong&gt;, 1490 16th St., Denver, from noon to 2:15 p.m. June 4 and June 5.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Whole Foods&lt;/strong&gt;, 1701 Wewatta St., Denver, from noon to 2:30 p.m. June 4.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Rosetta Hall&lt;/strong&gt;, 1109 Walnut St., Boulder, from 7:30 to 10:45 p.m. June 6.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Early symptoms include a cough, runny nose, red eyes and a fever, with a red rash starting about four days after someone becomes contagious. People can begin to feel sick one to three weeks after exposure.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;People who feel ill after a possible exposure should call their health care provider or an urgent care center before seeking help, so the provider can reduce the risk the virus will spread to other patients.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Colorado has recorded at least eight measles cases tied to Denver International Airport and a Turkish Airlines flight that landed there with a contagious passenger on May 13. Other cases have been confirmed in Denver, Pueblo and Archuleta County.&lt;/p&gt;				
&lt;p&gt;In a typical year, Colorado has two or fewer measles cases. The last time the state recorded more than 10 in a year was in the 1990s.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://myaccount.denverpost.com/dp/preference"&gt;Sign up for our weekly newsletter to get health news sent straight to your inbox.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

			&lt;p class="time mng-originally-published"&gt;Originally Published: &lt;time datetime="2025-06-13 16:25:01"&gt;June 13, 2025 at 4:25 PM MDT&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Denver Post</author><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 22:25:01 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijgFBVV95cUxPZ0hZRERVLTRURXNlYkVvNmRxZE93emdQaHk3dVlEdmZKdDZaQ3VKRnNOblQ3eldLYWpZZE5xcTFaZm0tTUprcVJKMEJ3TmNxZGljcFBwcG5lNmxmU2w5SFlEcU5va3o2ZXBfM210N2NId0dGM0xuNjVZd3pwWTBJR1h5bnUxLUlLbXAwTUZn0gGTAUFVX3lxTFB0aVlBRmYzc3htakhSTmlNTHRENm5CLTBHS1JQYXFiREZaT0VZTzNZY0xuZlp3ZGx5bWYtUnJYOHVIWVNtSVNjeDlRS2JWSHA0aGlJMFhWamN1WjVrdXozY3lBNklBYjAwOUN0dzBtSXRVWE1keVR5UEE4b3FWTzl4WUpPY29Nb1VTQWJYLU9jYkppWQ</guid></item><item><title>Y染色体正在消失，这一事实已经给男性带来了问题- Earth.com | The Y chromosome is disappearing, and this fact is already causing problems for men - Earth.com</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMinAFBVV95cUxPaHBHVUVBUVJoMU5NODVHOGRiMGhSZDBEd2Zrak5rYzVVX0lGOGNlMHloWlhBSGhzamRRZXJtS1M5cU9UM3RGSE9wM0NHWDRZYnZPR3dQRUZ0YVlyTFVqcVdSM0dEUGxpT25LMFh5N2tPVGZDUGp1elJmYjZXMnQybTR4NlJUd3k2d2tnbDloN3Y5TVR1XzZ6bWg0cjM?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="page_content__AwOj6"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Flip open a high-school biology textbook, and the rule seems tidy: two X chromosomes mean girl, and an X paired with a Y means boy. That much smaller Y chromosome carries the SRY gene, which is the switch for testis development. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For the last 300 million years or so, this system has been working very well. Now, however, chatter in genetics circles hints that something is amiss. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Over time, the Y chromosome has been losing pieces of itself, and computer models suggest the last scraps could vanish in roughly 11 million years. This is no trivial matter, because what it holds – or drops – can sway everything from cancer risk to &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/mouse-with-two-dads-survives-to-adulthood-major-implications-for-same-sex-human-couples/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;how future humans reproduce&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Would that erase men from the planet, or would life simply shrug and invent a new plan? Rodents on remote islands and subtle changes inside aging human &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/blood-stem-cells-grown-in-the-lab-for-first-time-ever-leukemia-treatment/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;bone marrow&lt;/a&gt; are now providing clues. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One story shows how a mammal kept producing males after its Y disappeared entirely. The other warns how men already pay a price when some of their cells drift away from the chromosome during middle age.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-y-chromosome-fade-away"&gt;Y chromosome fade away&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/mothers-pass-down-x-chromosomes-that-accelerate-brain-aging/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;The X chromosome&lt;/a&gt; carries about 900 genes that do everything from wiring nerves to repairing DNA. Its partner, the Y, keeps only about 55. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Comparative work across mammals shows that, once our lineage split from the &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/how-do-animals-balance-their-sex-chromosomes/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;platypus&lt;/a&gt; some 166 million years ago, the Y began dropping about five genes every million years. Run that line forward, and the ledger hits zero in 11 million years – a geological heartbeat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most biologists once chalked that outcome up to hype. After all, many species never shed their sex chromosomes. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But the idea gained traction when researchers found the Japanese spiny rat and a few mole vole species thriving today without any Y at all. Somehow, they had rewired the traditional circuit for making testes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-rodents-changed-the-rules"&gt;Rodents changed the rules&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;In 2022, scientists found a duplicated piece of DNA near a gene called &lt;a href="https://medlineplus.gov/genetics/gene/sox9/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;SOX9&lt;/a&gt; in the spiny rat. Usually, another gene (SRY) turns SOX9 on to make male traits develop. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But in this rat, the new DNA copy does that job on its own – even without a Y chromosome – so a genetically female animal (XX) can still develop as male.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Drop the fragment into lab mice and testes still form. Evolution, it seems, can lay a new cable when the old one burns out.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That discovery hints that, should the human Y fizzle out one distant day, &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/lifes-rules-natural-selection-change-significantly-often-daphnia/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;natural selection&lt;/a&gt; could promote an alternative trigger. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Different populations might even settle on different triggers, eventually splitting into separate species that cannot interbreed. The idea sounds like science fiction, but the rodent reality shows it is genetically feasible.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-y-chromosomes-and-men-s-health"&gt;Y chromosomes and men’s health&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Long before any species-wide overhaul, countless men are already losing the Y chromosome cell by cell. Starting in their fifties, bone-marrow &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/living-mouse-created-with-stem-cells-that-predate-animals/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;stem cells&lt;/a&gt; sometimes mis-segregate it during division. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The resulting white-blood-cell lineages, missing their Y, multiply quietly. By 80 years old, more than 40 percent of men carry sizable pockets of this “mosaic loss of Y” in their blood.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tracking 1,153 Swedish men in their seventies and eighties, researchers found that those with the loss died 5.5 years earlier, suffered more solid tumors and heart disease, and faced a seven-fold rise in Alzheimer’s. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kenneth Walsh of the &lt;a href="https://www.virginia.edu/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;University of Virginia&lt;/a&gt; then bred mouse blood stem cells without the Y chromosome and transplanted them. The recipients developed fibrosis, failing hearts, and early death, showing the loss is the culprit, not a bystander.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-direct-link-to-the-immune-system"&gt;Direct link to the immune system&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;A gene on the Y chromosome called &lt;a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/gene/7404" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;UTY&lt;/a&gt; helps control the immune system. Without it, some immune cells stop working properly – one kind makes more scar tissue, and another becomes weaker, which helps cancer grow and spread. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In mice, tumors grow twice as fast without the Y. In men, bladder cancers missing the Y chromosome are more dangerous – except they respond better to a certain kind of cancer treatment called checkpoint inhibitors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The picture is complicated: a chromosome that underpins male development also tames inflammation and restrains tumors, yet its selective absence can make some drugs shine. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Medicine and evolution rarely share the same bottom line. Natural selection prizes reproductive success over a lifetime, while clinicians care about the here and now.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-offsetting-y-chromosome-loss"&gt;Offsetting Y chromosome loss&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/does-vaping-help-people-quit-smoking-cigarettes-new-study-breaks-it-down/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Cigarette smoke&lt;/a&gt;, air pollution, and certain industrial chemicals add extra DNA damage and accelerate the Y chromosome loss. Kicking tobacco, breathing cleaner air, and limiting exposure to mutagens therefore rank as simple defenses – all it takes is willpower.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;General habits that slow genomic wear – regular exercise, &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/mediterranean-diet-may-be-a-fountain-of-youth-for-women/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Mediterranean-style&lt;/a&gt; meals, and solid sleep – may also keep the Y chromosome in more cells for longer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Antifibrotic drugs cleared for lung disease are being tested to blunt heart damage from the loss. Oncologists already use chromosome status in bladder tumors to steer checkpoint therapy. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As single-cell sequencing gets cheaper, your physical exam might soon include a “Y-loss score” beside cholesterol.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-where-do-we-go-from-here"&gt;Where do we go from here?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Japanese spiny rat proves that mammals can reinvent the rulebook after the ‘puny little chromosome’ disappears. That prospect keeps evolutionary biologists buzzing. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yet the rodent’s triumph offers little comfort to a 60-year-old man whose marrow has already shed Y in a third of his white-blood-cell army. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Species-level salvation and individual-level hazard can coexist. That dichotomy – long-term adaptability versus immediate personal cost – will likely guide both medical practice and evolutionary debate in the years ahead.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Y chromosome is quirky but crucial. It shapes male development, steadies immunity, and may also be plotting its own disappearance. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, the good news is that the practical advice is simple: dodge mutagens, stub out cigarettes, consider a mid-life test for loss, and keep an eye on new research as this chromosome writes its final chapters.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Let’s go, men, you got this!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The full study was published in the journal &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cell.com/cell/fulltext/S0092-8674(23)00646-3" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Cell&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;—–&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Like what you read? &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/subscribe/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Subscribe to our newsletter&lt;/a&gt; for engaging articles, exclusive content, and the latest updates.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Check us out on &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/earthsnap/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;EarthSnap&lt;/a&gt;, a free app brought to you by &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/author/eralls/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Eric Ralls&lt;/a&gt; and Earth.com.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;—–&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Earth.com</author><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 21:55:56 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMinAFBVV95cUxPaHBHVUVBUVJoMU5NODVHOGRiMGhSZDBEd2Zrak5rYzVVX0lGOGNlMHloWlhBSGhzamRRZXJtS1M5cU9UM3RGSE9wM0NHWDRZYnZPR3dQRUZ0YVlyTFVqcVdSM0dEUGxpT25LMFh5N2tPVGZDUGp1elJmYjZXMnQybTR4NlJUd3k2d2tnbDloN3Y5TVR1XzZ6bWg0cjM</guid></item><item><title>新研究表明，这种日常习惯可以将慢性背痛风险降低23 ％ - EatingWell | This Daily Habit May Lower Chronic Back Pain Risk by 23%, New Study Says - EatingWell</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMia0FVX3lxTE5tNjc5dFBQZUFiRTlRLVZCaWpPekt0V2wwaXRwR3Rqby1YeHNsd01laG9Tbk5jV2U3OGc2eTc3a1g4VVZzTGMwell3SUxrUXg5LUJqWWpGWW1TT1pPWHZyUU1UZFpJb0hqYUdj?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-page_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-page mntl-block structured-content" data-sc-sticky-offset="90" data-sc-ad-label-height="24" data-sc-ad-track-spacing="100" data-sc-min-track-height="250" data-sc-max-track-height="600" data-sc-breakpoint="50em" data-sc-load-immediate="4" data-sc-content-positions="[1, 1250, 1550, 1950, 2350, 2750, 3150, 3550, 3950]" data-bind-scroll-on-start="true"&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-block_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-callout--summary mntl-sc-block-universal-callout--tips mntl-sc-block-universal-callout theme-summary callout--bordered" data-text="Key Points" data-tracking-id="mntl-sc-block-callout" data-tracking-container="true"&gt;
&lt;div class="mntl-sc-block-universal-callout__body"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Researchers connected walking 100 minutes per day to a 23% lower risk of lower back pain.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Moderate to brisk walking intensity may offer added benefits for reducing pain risk.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Older adults saw the most consistent back pain relief from daily walking habits.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_2-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Lower back pain is a not-so-gentle reminder that we’re human, not indestructible machines. It can rear its ugly head after you’ve lifted something heavy or spent hours in a chair that feels like it belongs in medieval times. Sometimes it’s a dull ache, other times it’s a sharp jab, and occasionally it’s that frustrating combo of both. Unfortunately, lower back pain is a common issue that affects people of all ages and is a leading cause of discomfort and disability worldwide.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="1"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; It is one of the primary causes of ongoing pain and contributes to significant health care costs, especially in the U.S.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="2"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Not to mention, it is a very uncomfortable thing to experience.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_3-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_4-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; To address lower back pain, &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/exercise-every-day-study-11707905" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;staying physically active&lt;/a&gt; is often recommended, yet there's no clear advice on whether specific activities, like walking, can help &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/walking-can-decrease-back-pain-episodes-8669356" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;reduce annoying aches&lt;/a&gt;. Walking is one of the easiest ways people stay active, and it’s already known to reduce the risk of other health conditions.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="3"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_5-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_6-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; While some studies show that exercise like strength training and stretching may help reduce the risk of lower back pain, research is still limited regarding the &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/is-walking-a-good-enough-form-of-exercise-11743962" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;benefits of walking&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="3"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; This has led researchers to explore whether walking more each day—or &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/walking-mistakes-and-how-to-fix-them-7158418" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;walking at a faster pace&lt;/a&gt;—might lower the chances of developing &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/the-best-30-day-walking-plan-for-back-pain-8707216" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="3"&gt;chronic lower back pain&lt;/a&gt;, and the results were published in &lt;em&gt;JAMA Network Open.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="4"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_7-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-how-was-this-study-conducted"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_8-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; How Was This Study Conducted? &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_9-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; This study looked at information from a large health project in Norway called the Trøndelag Health (HUNT) Study. More than 56,000 individuals were evaluated, and subjects came in for health checks and answered questions about their lifestyle and health between 2017 and 2019 to obtain baseline information. Later, between 2021 and 2023, these participants were invited to a follow-up study focused on COVID-19, and about 60% of them took part. Certain individuals were removed from the study to ensure accurate results, such as those missing specific data or already having chronic lower back pain. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_10-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_11-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; In what was called the HUNT4 study, 31,295 participants wore two small motion-tracking devices called accelerometers for a week to measure their physical activity. One device was placed on the thigh, and the other on the lower back. These devices tracked different types of movements and postures in short 5-second intervals. Walking was categorized into three types based on speed: slow, moderate and brisk. Days with no recorded activity, like sitting or walking, were excluded. The study calculated how much time participants spent walking each day on average, as well as their &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/add-six-hours-longevity-study-8754775" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;walking intensity&lt;/a&gt;, which was based on how much energy different walking speeds required.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_12-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_13-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Chronic lower back pain was evaluated using a simple set of questions. Participants were asked if they had experienced pain or stiffness in their muscles or joints lasting at least three months in the past year. If they said yes, they were then asked to specify where they felt the pain or stiffness. Those who indicated that the pain was in their lower back were classified as having chronic lower back pain.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_14-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_16-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-what-did-this-study-find"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_17-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; What Did This Study Find? &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_18-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Results showed that people who walked more each day had a lower risk of developing chronic lower back pain. Those who walked for at least 78 minutes daily saw a reduced risk, with the greatest benefit observed in those walking 125 minutes or more per day. Specifically, compared with walking less than 78 minutes per day, those who walked more than 100 minutes per day had a 23% reduced risk of chronic lower back pain. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_19-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_20-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; This effect was even stronger and more consistent in individuals aged 65 and older when compared to younger people. Additionally, walking at a faster pace or higher intensity led to similar benefits, showing that individuals with a brisk walking intensity also experienced a reduced risk of back pain. These findings did not differ based on gender or other factors like age when considering walking intensity.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_21-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_22-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; For individuals walking less than the highest daily volume (under 125 minutes per day), the risk of chronic lower back pain decreased when their walking intensity was higher than 3.00 MET per minute. MET refers to the metabolic equivalent of task— However, for those walking the most (125 minutes or more daily), this relationship was less clear. Interestingly, the impact of walking intensity on chronic lower back pain risk appeared consistent across all levels of daily walking volume. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_23-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_24-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; The relationship between how much you walk each day and your risk of developing chronic lower back pain isn’t straightforward. Generally, walking more reduces your risk, with the biggest benefits seen when walking up to about 100 minutes per day. If you walk more than that, the risk continues to decrease but at a slower rate. Similarly, the intensity of walking matters to some extent. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_25-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_26-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Walking at a moderate pace was linked to a lower risk of lower back pain, and walking faster didn’t necessarily add more benefits—in fact, it may slightly increase the risk. These findings suggest that both the amount and the intensity of daily walking play roles in reducing the risk of chronic lower back pain, but the benefits vary depending on how much and how fast you walk.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_27-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_28-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; When interpreting the results of this study, it's important to consider a few key limitations. Firstly, the researchers only measured daily walking and intensity over a short period, which may not capture changes over time. It’s also worth noting that this study is observational, so we can’t say for sure if certain walking habits cause lower back pain or are just associated with it. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_29-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_30-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Additionally, there might still be some unaccounted influences the researchers couldn’t fully control for, but this analysis suggests these wouldn’t drastically affect the results. Lastly, participants were asked to recall their back pain over the past year, which might lead to some inaccuracies. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_31-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_33-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-how-does-this-apply-to-real-life"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_34-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; How Does This Apply to Real Life? &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_35-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; If you're someone who experiences occasional back discomfort or wants to reduce the risk of chronic lower back pain, walking might be one of the simplest and most practical solutions to incorporate into your routine. For many, walking is a low-impact and accessible activity that doesn’t require any special equipment or gym membership. Whether it’s a brisk walk around your neighborhood, a stroll through a local park or running errands on foot, making walking a daily habit could contribute to better back health over time.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_36-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_37-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; The great thing about the findings from this study is how achievable these goals are for everyday people. Even walking for around 100 minutes a day may make a noticeable difference, and you don’t have to do it all at once; breaking it into smaller walks throughout the day works just as well. Additionally, picking up the pace occasionally or including some brisk walking may enhance the benefits. Walking not only helps with back health but also supports overall well-being, from &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/best-activity-for-heart-health-recommended-by-cardiologist-8419619" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;improving cardiovascular fitness&lt;/a&gt; to &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/8024858/walking-plan-to-reduce-stress/" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;reducing stress&lt;/a&gt;. Small changes like opting to take the stairs, parking farther away or taking walking breaks during your day may help make a big difference in the long term.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_38-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-the-bottom-line"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_39-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; The Bottom Line &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_40-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; This recent study published in &lt;em&gt;JAMA Network Open&lt;/em&gt; offers insights into the potential benefits of walking for reducing the risk of chronic lower back pain . By analyzing data from over 31,000 participants, researchers found that walking more each day (particularly up to 125 minutes) is linked to a lower risk of developing chronic lower back pain. Walking intensity also plays a role, with moderate to brisk walking showing added benefits for those not already walking the most. These findings are especially promising for older adults, as they seemed to experience the most consistent reductions in risk. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_41-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_42-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Ultimately, the takeaway is clear: regular walking, whether done in small increments or longer bouts, is an accessible and effective way to support back health. This aligns with walking's broader benefits for overall physical and mental well-being, making it an ideal activity for people of all ages and fitness levels. Although intensity and duration both matter, even modest increases in daily walking habits can make a difference.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>EatingWell</author><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 21:24:37 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMia0FVX3lxTE5tNjc5dFBQZUFiRTlRLVZCaWpPekt0V2wwaXRwR3Rqby1YeHNsd01laG9Tbk5jV2U3OGc2eTc3a1g4VVZzTGMwell3SUxrUXg5LUJqWWpGWW1TT1pPWHZyUU1UZFpJb0hqYUdj</guid></item><item><title>在废水中检测到COVID-19高峰后，克利夫兰发布公共卫生警报- Cleveland.com | Cleveland issues public health alert after spike in COVID-19 detected in wastewater - Cleveland.com</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMixgFBVV95cUxNdVhGbzNDMXdWR3Z3MUlrVUxBRDZlQ3JnR3N5ZVgxNWtPUjZUTlA0bUQyT0oxaEhlajdBSVBhMWpISktmZzlxT09kTG1WcUZjeE03b2c4V2VwZWZhOFdkYllrMUxISld1eDU4RjZEY0E4ZkRCSUpKOGtJWVF3YUJydmVBNWppNG9jOVVLQkxLdF92Zk9mWXQ1ak0yM0RTcGM3MDlmMlQ2cXA5VTZMZklLVjJGQWx6Vm16elNGU0xJSFdpZTNwSnfSAdoBQVVfeXFMTUFYVm1lU0xsU2lUTkVVaW5wSGZ4QUp6NGZONklqdnlJMFVJdzR2dG9SM3JpbzBHbEpObDZHU3pJNjZFeGNjQlZJOWhMNUFBWHhnQ0xzZS13VEtRRXNld0x0R0tmUjBTa05udFpib1FsRVhKUHYtWUpWcWVtNHFHWjdhazFDWUJOakkwYXNfanFXMmpUa0NIVlN4d3lhal9mVHFvN0ZhZXBjWUFTblo1VUNUVDFGYkNXV0NKTWtQNW9tX09ZUzdiTjJYdHNrazZCMjBiQmEzTGdWZ0E?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content "&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="2DDFWGF6GRDYTCI6KBKCAM2GKE"&gt;CLEVELAND, Ohio — Cleveland health officials are warning residents about a sharp increase in COVID-19 levels detected in the city’s wastewater, signaling a likely uptick in community spread in the coming weeks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-1" data-gaid="inarticle-1"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="TVHVG2YFTRCDZLBUQLAV5JOLZ4"&gt;According to the Cleveland Department of Public Health, recent samples collected from the Northeast Ohio Regional Sewer District’s Easterly Wastewater Treatment Plant showed levels of the virus that causes COVID-19 spiking more than 250% compared to the previous month’s average. The jump triggered notification thresholds set by the Ohio Department of Health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-2" data-gaid="inarticle-2"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="JSKHDHIP7VDJLJV33IM5F4WATU"&gt;“Increasing viral concentrations in wastewater are often a leading indicator of future spikes in illness, hospitalizations, and transmission throughout the community,” said Director of Public Health David Margolius. “This data provides us with an early warning system, and we’re encouraging residents and institutions to take preventive steps now.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-3" class="middleParagraph" data-gaid="inarticle-3"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="67LT2NMFYNCAHKMFDVYNAVHC3A"&gt;Wastewater surveillance has become a key tool for tracking community infection trends, including among people who may not seek testing or show symptoms. In addition to the COVID-19 virus surge, the same samples also revealed high levels of influenza and increasing levels of respiratory syncytial virus (RSV), though RSV remains in its baseline monitoring phase.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-4" data-gaid="inarticle-4"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="5M6ERRBDBFDWDKBCEM4FSOY2II"&gt;Health officials are urging residents to stay up to date on vaccinations for both COVID-19 and the flu. Those experiencing respiratory symptoms are advised to stay home or wear a mask if they need to go out.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-5" data-gaid="inarticle-5"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="DOT5MAANIZGX5HH5HJFIB5CH5A"&gt;The Cleveland Department of Public Health said it will continue to monitor the situation and provide updates as necessary. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-6" data-gaid="inarticle-6"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Cleveland.com</author><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 20:57:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMixgFBVV95cUxNdVhGbzNDMXdWR3Z3MUlrVUxBRDZlQ3JnR3N5ZVgxNWtPUjZUTlA0bUQyT0oxaEhlajdBSVBhMWpISktmZzlxT09kTG1WcUZjeE03b2c4V2VwZWZhOFdkYllrMUxISld1eDU4RjZEY0E4ZkRCSUpKOGtJWVF3YUJydmVBNWppNG9jOVVLQkxLdF92Zk9mWXQ1ak0yM0RTcGM3MDlmMlQ2cXA5VTZMZklLVjJGQWx6Vm16elNGU0xJSFdpZTNwSnfSAdoBQVVfeXFMTUFYVm1lU0xsU2lUTkVVaW5wSGZ4QUp6NGZONklqdnlJMFVJdzR2dG9SM3JpbzBHbEpObDZHU3pJNjZFeGNjQlZJOWhMNUFBWHhnQ0xzZS13VEtRRXNld0x0R0tmUjBTa05udFpib1FsRVhKUHYtWUpWcWVtNHFHWjdhazFDWUJOakkwYXNfanFXMmpUa0NIVlN4d3lhal9mVHFvN0ZhZXBjWUFTblo1VUNUVDFGYkNXV0NKTWtQNW9tX09ZUzdiTjJYdHNrazZCMjBiQmEzTGdWZ0E</guid></item><item><title>不同的自闭症基因，相同的大脑特征-神经科学新闻 | Different Autism Genes, Same Brain Signature - Neuroscience News</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiaEFVX3lxTE5ta0JKTzF6R0FuZloyZEpRU3JqNHRwdmE0QlpkZzQwUjBlLWtGQUpJTWRlc2lESDhRTUNJd0M5S3ZfREptd3FHS0liSDdIY0J1aS1FaVVaMUc3ZElLWVlQS194QzNZcmVQ?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content body-color clearfix link-color-wrap"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary: &lt;/strong&gt;New research shows that different genetic forms of autism may produce a shared brain activity pattern, revealing a potential common neural signature despite distinct genetic origins. Using brain-wide recordings in preclinical models, scientists observed that autism-linked mutations affected how expectations are updated during decision-making.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These models relied more heavily on frontal brain regions and less on sensory input, struggling to distinguish between predictable and unpredictable stimuli. The findings offer a promising bridge between genetic variation and behavioral traits in autism, opening new paths for targeted research.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Facts:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class="wp-block-list"&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Shared Brain Signature:&lt;/strong&gt; Distinct autism-linked genes produce similar patterns of brain activity.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sensory Processing Differences:&lt;/strong&gt; Autism models show impaired flexibility in updating expectations from sensory input.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Frontal Dominance:&lt;/strong&gt; Mutant models relied more on frontal brain regions, less on sensory areas during decision-making.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Source: &lt;/strong&gt;University of Minnesota&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;New research from the University of Minnesota Medical School suggests that different genetic forms of autism may lead to similar patterns in brain activity and behavior. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The findings were recently published in &lt;em&gt;Nature Neuroscience&lt;/em&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="wp-block-image size-full"&gt;&lt;picture fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" class="wp-image-110912"&gt; &lt;source type="image/webp" srcset="https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/06/ASD-genetics-behavior-neuroscience.jpg.webp 1200w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/06/ASD-genetics-behavior-neuroscience-300x200.jpg.webp 300w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/06/ASD-genetics-behavior-neuroscience-770x513.jpg.webp 770w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/06/ASD-genetics-behavior-neuroscience-1155x770.jpg.webp 1155w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/06/ASD-genetics-behavior-neuroscience-370x247.jpg.webp 370w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/06/ASD-genetics-behavior-neuroscience-293x195.jpg.webp 293w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/06/ASD-genetics-behavior-neuroscience-150x100.jpg.webp 150w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px"&gt;&lt;/source&gt; &lt;img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" src="https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/06/ASD-genetics-behavior-neuroscience.jpg" alt="This shows a brain." srcset="https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/06/ASD-genetics-behavior-neuroscience.jpg 1200w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/06/ASD-genetics-behavior-neuroscience-300x200.jpg 300w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/06/ASD-genetics-behavior-neuroscience-770x513.jpg 770w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/06/ASD-genetics-behavior-neuroscience-1155x770.jpg 1155w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/06/ASD-genetics-behavior-neuroscience-370x247.jpg 370w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/06/ASD-genetics-behavior-neuroscience-293x195.jpg 293w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/06/ASD-genetics-behavior-neuroscience-150x100.jpg 150w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px"&gt; &lt;/picture&gt;&lt;figcaption class="wp-element-caption"&gt;The particular circuit this research uncovered appears to drive behavioral anomalies in all three preclinical models of autism tested. Credit: Neuroscience News&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Using brain-recording technology, the research team observed neurons across the entire brain to explore whether different genetic forms of autism share patterns and establish commonalities in neural responses.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They found that, despite genetic differences, various forms may show a similar unique pattern of brain activity — also known as a brain signature.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“We hope this research will serve as a stepping stone linking genetic differences and behavioral atypicalities,” said Jean-Paul Noel, PhD, an assistant professor at the University of Minnesota Medical School. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study found that preclinical models with autism-linked genetic mutations struggled to adjust their expectations —or their predicted state of the world in the immediate future — based on new information when making decisions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Unlike typical models that could update their expectations more flexibly, they relied more heavily on the front part of the brain and less on sensory areas.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As a result, their brains focused more on long-term expectation differences, but their sensory systems had trouble distinguishing between predictable and unpredictable sensory stimuli. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The particular circuit this research uncovered appears to drive behavioral anomalies in all three preclinical models of autism tested. This feedback projection from frontal areas to visual cortex will be studied in more detail in subsequent projects.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Funding: &lt;/strong&gt;This research was supported by grants from the Wellcome Trust, Simons Foundation, National Institutes of Health [grant R00NS128075], a Simons Foundation Autism Research Initiative Pilot Grant, the University of Minnesota Clinical and Translational Science Institute and a Sloan Research fellowship. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;About this genetics and Autism research news&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="has-background"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Author: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#f899d58b95918c90b88d9596d69d9c8d" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Alexandra Smith&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Source: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://umn.edu" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;University of Minnesota&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Contact: &lt;/strong&gt;Alexandra Smith – University of Minnesota&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Image: &lt;/strong&gt;The image is credited to Neuroscience News&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="has-background"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Original Research: &lt;/strong&gt;Closed access.&lt;br&gt;“&lt;a href="https://dx.doi.org/10.1038/s41593-025-01965-8" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;A common computational and neural anomaly across mouse models of autism&lt;/a&gt;” by Jean-Paul Noel et al. &lt;em&gt;Nature Neuroscience&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr class="wp-block-separator has-text-color has-pale-cyan-blue-color has-alpha-channel-opacity has-pale-cyan-blue-background-color has-background"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Abstract&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A common computational and neural anomaly across mouse models of autism&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Computational psychiatry studies suggest that individuals with autism spectrum disorder (ASD) inflexibly update their expectations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Here we leveraged high-yield rodent psychophysics, extensive behavioral modeling and brain-wide single-cell extracellular recordings to assess whether mice with different genetic perturbations associated with ASD show this same computational anomaly, and if so, what neurophysiological features are shared across genotypes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mice harboring mutations in &lt;em&gt;Fmr1&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;Cntnap2&lt;/em&gt; or &lt;em&gt;Shank3B&lt;/em&gt; show a blunted update of priors during decision-making.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Compared with mice that flexibly updated their priors, inflexible updating of priors was associated with a shift in the weighting of prior encoding from sensory to frontal cortices.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Furthermore, frontal areas in mouse models of ASD showed more units encoding deviations from the animals’ long-run prior, and sensory responses did not differentiate between expected and unexpected observations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These findings suggest that distinct genetic instantiations of ASD may yield common neurophysiological and behavioral phenotypes.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p class="clear"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Neuroscience News</author><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 20:55:05 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiaEFVX3lxTE5ta0JKTzF6R0FuZloyZEpRU3JqNHRwdmE0QlpkZzQwUjBlLWtGQUpJTWRlc2lESDhRTUNJd0M5S3ZfREptd3FHS0liSDdIY0J1aS1FaVVaMUc3ZElLWVlQS194QzNZcmVQ</guid></item><item><title>随着卫生官员呼吁美国支持， Mpox在塞拉利昂飙升-《纽约时报》 | Mpox Surges in Sierra Leone as Health Officials Appeal for U.S. Support - The New York Times</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMigwFBVV95cUxNZFI2Y1RZcnlxTDVubzVSMWVOR1hnOTRpekIxSWdUV3hDcm8wdWh5amJKVUpiVjZ2LVU2WmlQT1RsUFNGc2dCcW5oZEhhRWxVM284S3NZLWFTdldFbmdqaXdjVTBsTTBCM19OSVNsVTZfcTRCUnlIcFczenBVdS10djBDMA?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The New York Times</author><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 20:45:06 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigwFBVV95cUxNZFI2Y1RZcnlxTDVubzVSMWVOR1hnOTRpekIxSWdUV3hDcm8wdWh5amJKVUpiVjZ2LVU2WmlQT1RsUFNGc2dCcW5oZEhhRWxVM284S3NZLWFTdldFbmdqaXdjVTBsTTBCM19OSVNsVTZfcTRCUnlIcFczenBVdS10djBDMA</guid></item><item><title>在医生对名人使用的药物发出重大警告后，病毒“无限药丸”如何影响大脑- LADbible | How viral 'limitless pill' affects the brain after doctors issue major warning over substance used by celebrities - LADbible</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMingFBVV95cUxNdHpYZmFFQmNVSy02XzZnUmtkZHRLaDczMnlYaXJXYUZYc01tNHJlNXp2eDBvbkY4Z251M25KRWRCTWY5RFZDUmt3TkpRM1U2dFNMYnVUNU1zYUZoNWpLb0lWb1hwc0R1SW14OEx2M2J1TTdUY1B4dHpNWHkxT0lCOUZteWxBSVl5RzF3RHZjMzNOalFGR2YtUlNvM2lXQQ?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;Here is what the viral ‘limitless pill’ currently being promoted on the internet is said to impact your brain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;Anyone who's taken a scroll through the &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.ladbible.com/health"&gt;health&lt;/a&gt; and wellness corner of the internet in the past few weeks will have likely noticed people raving about a new supplement which they claim is responsible for benefits such as boosting brain power, eliminating brain fog and improving our memory.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;No, we're not referring to a new type of superfood or multi-vitamin, we're talking about a substance known as &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.ladbible.com/community/methylene-blue-explained-doctors-warning-brain-fuel-656473-20250613"&gt;methylene blue&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="floating-video-player_container__u4D9_"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;Which to be honest, is something which likely sounds very appealing at 9am on a Monday morning when you're furiously gulping down the last dregs of your &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.ladbible.com/food-and-drink"&gt;coffee&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;But how accurate are these vague 'brain boosting' qualities which methylene blue users claim it has – and how safe is it actually?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What is methylene blue?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;div class="article-image_articleImage__eyzAn"&gt;&lt;cite class="image-credit_imageCredit__YMlqS"&gt;Methylene blue was originally used as a textile dye (Getty Stock Images)&lt;/cite&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;Methylene blue was originally discovered back in the 19th century and used as a textile dye, as well as disinfecting fish and diagnostic staining during &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.ladbible.com/science"&gt;biology&lt;/a&gt; research.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;The substance was later revealed to have certain medical uses, such as treating a blood disorder known as methemoglobinemia, which is when red blood cells cannot carry enough oxygen. It has also been used in the treatment of malaria and even as an antidote to cyanide poisoning.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;Wellness circles are now claiming the drug is a 'nootropic' - something which enhances cognitive function - which can slow down aging, enhance memory, improve mood and even prevent cancer – none of which appear to have been proven scientifically.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Celebrities that have endorsed methylene blue&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;Alongside wellness influencers, methylene blue has also gained several &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.ladbible.com/celebrity"&gt;celebrity&lt;/a&gt; endorsements.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;Among them is biohacker &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.ladbible.com/bryan-johnson"&gt;Bryan Johnson&lt;/a&gt;, the guy who spends $2 million a year to reverse aging and &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.ladbible.com/news/health/bryan-johnson-erection-test-viral-son-responds-128278-20250124"&gt;compares erections with his son&lt;/a&gt;, revealed on &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" target="_blank" rel="noopener" href="https://x.com/bryan_johnson/status/1896679614602482042"&gt;X&lt;/a&gt; that he had begun to take methylene blue back in March.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;Mel Gibson also &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" target="_blank" rel="noopener" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1rYtrS5IbrQ"&gt;revealed&lt;/a&gt; on an episode of &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.ladbible.com/joe-rogan"&gt;Joe Rogan&lt;/a&gt;'s podcast a friend of his had used the methylene blue to allegedly cure stage four &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.ladbible.com/cancer"&gt;cancer&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;"Methylene blue... It was a textile dye. Now they find it has profound effects on your mitochondria," Rogan said after the anecdote, to which Gibson replied: "This stuff works, man."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;&lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.ladbible.com/us-news"&gt;US&lt;/a&gt; Health and Human Services secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr was even seen putting what appeared to be methylene blue in his drink mid-flight (&lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" target="_blank" rel="noopener" href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/americas/us-politics/rfk-jr-drinking-flight-methylene-blue-b2693495.html"&gt;via&lt;/a&gt; The Independent). &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;However, he was never publicly spoken about using the substance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What we know about how methylene blue affects the brain&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;div class="article-image_articleImage__eyzAn"&gt;&lt;cite class="image-credit_imageCredit__YMlqS"&gt;However there is little evidence to back up the claims (Getty Stock Images)&lt;/cite&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;According to one health expert who &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" target="_blank" rel="noopener" href="https://www.sciencealert.com/can-this-blue-chemical-really-boost-your-brain-heres-what-we-know"&gt;discussed&lt;/a&gt; the topic with Science Direct, methylene blue is able to cross the protective tissue which surrounds the brain and penetrate the organ.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;Researchers also believe the dye may also have a positive impact on our mitochondria, something which is referred to as the 'powerhouse' of our cells.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;However, it's important to note that most studies regarding the impact of methylene blue on the brain have been conducted on rodents, meaning there's little evidence of benefits for humans.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;There are also numerous risks to taking methylene blue, with neuroscientist Anne-Sophie Fluri &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" target="_blank" rel="noopener" href="https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-14795783/doctors-verdict-longevity-elixir-Joe-Rogan-RFK-Jr-swear-reverses-aging.html"&gt;telling&lt;/a&gt; MailOnline: “Without solid evidence in humans, these claims are at best speculative and at worst potentially dangerous.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;"The brain is not a machine you can casually 'optimise' like a smartphone."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;Taking too high a dose of methylene blue and you find yourself at risk of developing conditions such as serotonin syndrome – something which Johnson directly acknowledged when revealing he was using the substance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>LADbible</author><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 20:01:22 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMingFBVV95cUxNdHpYZmFFQmNVSy02XzZnUmtkZHRLaDczMnlYaXJXYUZYc01tNHJlNXp2eDBvbkY4Z251M25KRWRCTWY5RFZDUmt3TkpRM1U2dFNMYnVUNU1zYUZoNWpLb0lWb1hwc0R1SW14OEx2M2J1TTdUY1B4dHpNWHkxT0lCOUZteWxBSVl5RzF3RHZjMzNOalFGR2YtUlNvM2lXQQ</guid></item><item><title>专家说，肯尼迪的HHS派国会“垃圾科学”来捍卫疫苗的变化- CNN | Kennedy’s HHS sent Congress ‘junk science’ to defend vaccine changes, experts say - CNN</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMif0FVX3lxTE5TbnlwUWpFZlZYbHVOSEg2dHlyTHQ2UWVqRVpxWlYyRTUtSHMwQ3VtcExTd3ptclpWdS1JUXpiSzVQS2tGSGZ6bVZBV05ZeVBVMXJ0N0ItMkxGdWM5R3BTeFptcVBGVE5pR0dTSGJfXzE0RU9jNlZyYjB6ckI1M0nSAYQBQVVfeXFMTWlNbXNEckRFbkhMTE9tWHlJWklYbFdzcm1DX19mSFZhc1YwUGgyUVBfUFZ6SUZTbXExMVFwS1pDblhaWUJJT3hjVWFibGgxTU5SU29lT1lLRldDMkt4MF90cG1YQUlmcmI1M084ZXhNcmlpbUc3TUFuNE1oeFBVdWtWanYx?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article__content" data-editable="content" itemprop="articleBody" data-reorderable="content"&gt;
                  &lt;div data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/action-bar/instances/cmbv635jf000r26qof6yxcv29@published" data-label-id-prefix="action-bar-start-of-article" class="action-bar" data-dynamic-breakpoint-placement='{"extraLarge":{"placement":".layout-article-elevate__left"}}' data-expand-conditions='{"follow":{"extraLarge":{"alwaysExpand":true}},"shareOptions":{"large":{"maxNumOfActions":1},"medium":{"maxNumOfActions":1},"extraLarge":{"withAction":"follow","maxNumOfActions":2}}}'&gt;
    &lt;p class="action-bar__overlay"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;div class="action-bar__action-sheet" tabindex="-1"&gt;
        
            &lt;div class="action-bar__action-sheet--action" data-title="follow"&gt;
                

  
&lt;div data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/follow-topics-bar/instances/cmbv635jf000v26qo72g89vpp@published" data-unauth-redirect="/account/register/follow" data-embed-max-topics="" class="follow-topics-bar follow-topics-bar_overlay follow-topics-bar--hide"&gt;
    &lt;div class="follow-topics-bar_overlay__inner"&gt;
        &lt;p class="follow-topics-bar_overlay__scroll-wrapper" tabindex="-1"&gt;
                  &lt;button data-unselectable="true" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/chip/instances/cmbv635jf000w26qo30obfmyl@published" class="chip follow-topics-chip " data-component-variation="follow-topics-chip" data-component-name="chip" data-zjs="click" data-enable-interstitial="true" data-override-success="" data-label="Vaccines" data-id="617c0361-7001-4fd9-87cb-f147c812ab03" data-reset-on-log-out="true"&gt;
    &lt;span class="chip__label"&gt;Vaccines&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class="chip__icon"&gt;
        &lt;span class="chip__icon--check"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
        &lt;span class="chip__icon--add"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/button&gt;

                  &lt;button data-unselectable="true" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/chip/instances/cmbv635jf000w26qo30obfmyl@published" class="chip follow-topics-chip " data-component-variation="follow-topics-chip" data-component-name="chip" data-zjs="click" data-enable-interstitial="true" data-override-success="" data-label="Federal agencies" data-id="874fe3a3-ab02-4ed7-8d3b-417b95049613" data-reset-on-log-out="true"&gt;
    &lt;span class="chip__label"&gt;Federal agencies&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class="chip__icon"&gt;
        &lt;span class="chip__icon--check"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
        &lt;span class="chip__icon--add"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/button&gt;

                  &lt;button data-unselectable="true" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/chip/instances/cmbv635jf000w26qo30obfmyl@published" class="chip follow-topics-chip " data-component-variation="follow-topics-chip" data-component-name="chip" data-zjs="click" data-enable-interstitial="true" data-override-success="" data-label="Congressional news" data-id="1b312755-3ccb-4bc0-b75c-527d4181e03d" data-reset-on-log-out="true"&gt;
    &lt;span class="chip__label"&gt;Congressional news&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class="chip__icon"&gt;
        &lt;span class="chip__icon--check"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
        &lt;span class="chip__icon--add"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/button&gt;

                  &lt;button data-unselectable="true" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/chip/instances/cmbv635jf000w26qo30obfmyl@published" class="chip follow-topics-chip " data-component-variation="follow-topics-chip" data-component-name="chip" data-zjs="click" data-enable-interstitial="true" data-override-success="" data-label="Respiratory viruses" data-id="dc4dc3db-08f5-47c8-b2fb-e0beaa158c04" data-reset-on-log-out="true"&gt;
    &lt;span class="chip__label"&gt;Respiratory viruses&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class="chip__icon"&gt;
        &lt;span class="chip__icon--check"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
        &lt;span class="chip__icon--add"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/button&gt;

        &lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p class="follow-topics-bar_overlay__fade follow-topics-bar_overlay__fade--hide"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
          &lt;a class="follow-topics-bar_overlay__explore-more-link" href="/follow"&gt;
            See all topics&lt;svg class="icon-ui-caret-right" viewbox="0 0 24 24" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"&gt;&lt;path d="M17.218 11.522c.28.261.28.685 0 .946L7.2 21.794c-.242.225-.632.28-.91.093a.613.613 0 01-.088-.975l9.579-8.917-9.538-8.878c-.242-.225-.3-.589-.1-.847a.721.721 0 011.048-.082l10.027 9.334z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;

          &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

            &lt;/div&gt;
            &lt;div class="action-bar__action-sheet--action" data-title="share options"&gt;
                  &lt;div data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/social-share/instances/cmbv635jf000u26qoffnb6gd4@published" class="social-share_labelled-list"&gt;
    &lt;div class="social-share_labelled-list__share-links vossi-social-share_labelled-list" data-type="share-links"&gt;
        &lt;button class="social-share_labelled-list__share" data-url="https://www.facebook.com/dialog/share?app_id=80401312489&amp;amp;href=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.cnn.com%2F2025%2F06%2F13%2Fhealth%2Fkennedy-hhs-congress-vaccine-changes&amp;amp;display=popup" data-type="facebook" aria-label="share with facebook" title="Share with Facebook"&gt;
                &lt;svg class="icon-facebook-circle" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 16 16" fill="none"&gt;
&lt;path d="M8.04139 1.33301C11.7458 1.33301 14.7488 4.33601 14.7488 8.04042C14.7488 11.3884 12.296 14.1632 9.08943 14.6663V9.97928H10.6523L10.9497 8.04042H9.08943V6.78225C9.08943 6.25182 9.34934 5.73475 10.1825 5.73475H11.0283V4.08409C11.0283 4.08409 10.2607 3.95309 9.52685 3.95309C7.99476 3.95309 6.99336 4.88165 6.99336 6.56269V8.04042H5.29031V9.97928H6.99336V14.6663C3.78677 14.1632 1.33398 11.3882 1.33398 8.04042C1.33398 4.33601 4.33699 1.33301 8.04139 1.33301Z" fill="#0C0C0C"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;
&lt;/svg&gt;

                &lt;span class="social-share_labelled-list__share-links--label"&gt;Facebook&lt;/span&gt;
        &lt;/button&gt;
        &lt;button class="social-share_labelled-list__share" data-url="https://twitter.com/intent/tweet?text=Check%20out%20this%20article%3A&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.cnn.com%2F2025%2F06%2F13%2Fhealth%2Fkennedy-hhs-congress-vaccine-changes" data-type="x" aria-label="share with x" title="Share with X"&gt;
                &lt;svg class="icon-x-share" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 16 16" fill="none"&gt;
&lt;path fill-rule="evenodd" clip-rule="evenodd" d="M5.99386 8.11503L0 0.666992H4.74756L8.44753 5.27039L12.4004 0.687719H15.0151L9.71175 6.84331L16 14.667H11.2666L7.2603 9.6887L2.98317 14.6532H0.354296L5.99386 8.11503ZM11.9565 13.287L2.91105 2.04698H4.0571L13.0912 13.287H11.9565Z" fill="#0C0C0C"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;
&lt;/svg&gt;

                &lt;span class="social-share_labelled-list__share-links--label"&gt;Tweet&lt;/span&gt;
        &lt;/button&gt;
        &lt;a class="social-share_labelled-list__share" href="mailto:?subject=CNN%20content%20share&amp;amp;body=Check%20out%20this%20article%3A%0Ahttps%3A%2F%2Fwww.cnn.com%2F2025%2F06%2F13%2Fhealth%2Fkennedy-hhs-congress-vaccine-changes" data-type="email" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" aria-label="share with email" title="Share with email"&gt;
                &lt;svg class="icon-email-share" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 24 24" fill="none"&gt;
&lt;path fill-rule="evenodd" clip-rule="evenodd" d="M2 6C2 4.89543 2.89543 4 4 4H20C21.1046 4 22 4.89543 22 6V18C22 19.1046 21.1046 20 20 20H4C2.89543 20 2 19.1046 2 18V6ZM4 6H20V9.11604L12 11.9396L4 9.11604V6ZM4 11.237V18H20V11.237L12.3328 13.943C12.1174 14.019 11.8825 14.019 11.6672 13.943L4 11.237Z" fill="#0C0C0C"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;
&lt;/svg&gt;

                &lt;span class="social-share_labelled-list__share-links--label"&gt;Email&lt;/span&gt;
        &lt;/a&gt;
        &lt;button class="social-share_labelled-list__share" data-url="https://www.cnn.com/2025/06/13/health/kennedy-hhs-congress-vaccine-changes" data-type="copy" aria-label="copy link to clipboard" title="Copy link to clipboard"&gt;
                &lt;svg class="icon-hyperlink" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 16 16" fill="none"&gt;
&lt;path fill-rule="evenodd" clip-rule="evenodd" d="M5.64373 10.3574C5.38338 10.0971 5.38338 9.67496 5.64373 9.41461L9.88637 5.17197C10.1467 4.91162 10.5688 4.91162 10.8292 5.17197C11.0895 5.43232 11.0895 5.85443 10.8292 6.11478L6.58654 10.3574C6.32619 10.6178 5.90408 10.6178 5.64373 10.3574Z" fill="#0C0C0C"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;
&lt;path d="M4.22952 8.94321L5.64373 7.52899C5.90408 7.26865 5.90408 6.84654 5.64373 6.58619C5.38338 6.32584 4.96127 6.32584 4.70092 6.58619L3.28671 8.0004C1.98496 9.30215 1.98496 11.4127 3.28671 12.7144C4.58846 14.0162 6.69901 14.0162 8.00075 12.7144L9.41497 11.3002C9.67532 11.0399 9.67532 10.6178 9.41497 10.3574C9.15462 10.0971 8.73251 10.0971 8.47216 10.3574L7.05795 11.7716C6.2769 12.5527 5.01057 12.5527 4.22952 11.7716C3.44847 10.9906 3.44847 9.72426 4.22952 8.94321Z" fill="#0C0C0C"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;
&lt;path d="M8.94356 4.22916L7.52935 5.64338C7.269 5.90373 6.84689 5.90373 6.58654 5.64338C6.32619 5.38303 6.32619 4.96092 6.58654 4.70057L8.00075 3.28635C9.3025 1.98461 11.4131 1.98461 12.7148 3.28635C14.0165 4.5881 14.0165 6.69865 12.7148 8.0004L11.3006 9.41461C11.0402 9.67496 10.6181 9.67496 10.3578 9.41461C10.0974 9.15426 10.0974 8.73215 10.3578 8.4718L11.772 7.05759C12.553 6.27654 12.553 5.01021 11.772 4.22916C10.9909 3.44812 9.72461 3.44811 8.94356 4.22916Z" fill="#0C0C0C"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;
&lt;/svg&gt;

                &lt;span class="social-share_labelled-list__share-links--label"&gt;Link&lt;/span&gt;
        &lt;/button&gt;
        
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;button class="social-share_labelled-list__open" data-type="open" aria-label="open social share" title="Open social share"&gt;
        &lt;svg class="icon-ui-share-os" viewbox="0 0 24 24" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"&gt;&lt;path d="M19 12c.394 0 .714.32.714.714v8.572c0 .394-.32.714-.714.714H4.714A.715.715 0 014 21.286v-8.572a.715.715 0 011.429 0v7.857h12.857v-7.857c0-.394.32-.714.714-.714zm-7.664-9.79a.73.73 0 011.024 0l.076.075 4.916 4.854c.183.18.27.449.188.69a.734.734 0 01-1.216.314L12.57 4.5v11.786c0 .357-.357.714-.714.714s-.714-.359-.714-.714V4.5L7.372 8.143a.73.73 0 01-1.102-.091c-.21-.289-.149-.694.106-.946l4.884-4.821z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;

    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;button class="social-share_labelled-list__close" data-type="close" aria-label="close social share" title="Close social share"&gt;
        &lt;svg class="icon-ui-close" viewbox="0 0 24 24" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"&gt;&lt;path d="M19.787 18.758l-6.792-6.781 6.746-6.735a.728.728 0 00-1.028-1.03l-6.747 6.737-6.711-6.7a.728.728 0 00-1.028 1.03l6.71 6.698-6.723 6.712a.727.727 0 101.027 1.03l6.725-6.714 6.793 6.782a.725.725 0 001.028 0 .727.727 0 000-1.03"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;

    &lt;/button&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

            &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/source/instances/cmbv635jf000s26qo6if8gtgj@published" data-component-name="source" class="source-elevate vossi-source inline-placeholder" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
    &lt;cite class="source__cite vossi-source__cite"&gt;
      &lt;span class="source__location vossi-source__location" data-editable="location"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;span class="source__text" data-editable="source"&gt;KFF Health News&lt;/span&gt;
         — 
    &lt;/cite&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmbv635jf000t26qoehm42a0x@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            A document the Department of Health and Human Services sent to lawmakers to support Secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr.’s decision to change U.S. policy on covid vaccines cites scientific studies that are unpublished or under dispute and mischaracterizes others.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmbv64d1k00073b6mvrtqb6hu@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            One health expert called the document “willful medical disinformation” about the safety of covid vaccines for children and pregnant women.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmbv64d1k00083b6m76gy4qqn@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “It is so far out of left field that I find it insulting to our members of Congress that they would actually give them something like this. Congress members are relying on these agencies to provide them with valid information, and it’s just not there,” said &lt;a href="https://www.bcm.edu/people-search/mark-turrentine-32066" target="_blank"&gt;Mark Turrentine&lt;/a&gt;, a professor of obstetrics and gynecology at Baylor College of Medicine.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmbv64d1k00093b6mk0wus2n1@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Kennedy, who was an anti-vaccine activist before taking a role in the Trump administration, announced May 27 that the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention would no longer recommend covid vaccines for pregnant women or healthy children, bypassing the agency’s formal process for adjusting its vaccine schedules for adults and kids. The announcement, &lt;a href="https://x.com/SecKennedy/status/1927368440811008138" target="_blank"&gt;made on the social platform X&lt;/a&gt;, has been met with outrage by many pediatricians and scientists.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmbv64d1k000a3b6mg2m7wl26@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The HHS document meant to support Kennedy’s decision, obtained by KFF Health News, was sent to members of Congress who questioned the science and process behind his move, according to one federal official who asked not to be identified because he wasn’t authorized to discuss the matter publicly.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmbv64d1k000b3b6mxulzu6ne@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The document has not been posted on the HHS website, though it is the first detailed explanation of Kennedy’s announcement from the agency.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmbv64d1k000c3b6m9b37tiyv@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Titled “Covid Recommendation FAQ,” the document distorts some legitimate studies and cites others that are disputed and unpublished, medical experts say.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmbv64d1k000g3b6m5v89pkhu@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            HHS director of communications Andrew Nixon told KFF Health News, “There is no distortion of the studies in this document. The underlying data speaks for itself, and it raises legitimate safety concerns. HHS will not ignore that evidence or downplay it. We will follow the data and the science.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmbv64d1k000h3b6mj3sb7z23@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            HHS did not respond to a request to name the author of the document.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmbv64d1k000i3b6mplf2ly6u@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            &lt;a href="https://journals.sagepub.com/doi/10.1177/20420986241226566" target="_blank"&gt;One of the studies&lt;/a&gt; the HHS document cites is under investigation by its publisher regarding “potential issues with the research methodology and conclusions and author conflicts of interest,” according to a link on &lt;a href="https://journals.sagepub.com/doi/10.1177/20420986241239903" target="_blank"&gt;the study’s webpage&lt;/a&gt;.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmbv64d1k000j3b6mwxsdmzup@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “This is RFK Jr.’s playbook,” said &lt;a href="https://medschool.cuanschutz.edu/accords/about/faculty-staff-directory/O-Leary-Sean-UCD11631" target="_blank"&gt;Sean O’Leary&lt;/a&gt;, chair of the Committee on Infectious Diseases for the American Academy of Pediatrics and an assistant professor of pediatrics at the University of Colorado School of Medicine. “Either cherry-pick from good science or take junk science to support his premise — this has been his playbook for 20 years.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmbv64d1k000k3b6m6cvgg210@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Another &lt;a href="https://www.medrxiv.org/content/10.1101/2024.05.20.24306810v1" target="_blank"&gt;study cited&lt;/a&gt; in the document is a preprint that has not been peer-reviewed. Under the study’s title is an alert that “it reports new medical research that has yet to be evaluated and so should not be used to guide clinical practice.” Though the preprint was made available a year ago, it has not been published in a peer-reviewed journal.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmbv64d1k000l3b6mexy48umn@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The FAQ supporting Kennedy’s decision claims that “post-marketing studies” of covid vaccines have identified “serious adverse effects, such as an increased risk of myocarditis and pericarditis” — conditions in which the heart’s muscle or its covering, the pericardium, suffer inflammation.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmbv64d1k000m3b6mytcf69j1@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            False claims that the 2024 preprint showed myocarditis and pericarditis only in people who received a covid vaccine, and not in people infected with covid, circulated on social media. One of the &lt;a href="https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/factcheck/2024/08/08/myocarditis-vaccinated-covid-19-oxford-fact-check/74639942007/?utm_source=substack&amp;amp;utm_medium=email" target="_blank"&gt;study’s co-authors&lt;/a&gt; publicly rejected that idea, because the study did not compare outcomes between people who were vaccinated and those infected with the covid virus. The study also focused only on children and adolescents. The HHS document omitted numerous &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/39826014/" target="_blank"&gt;other&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/39404761/" target="_blank"&gt;peer-reviewed&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/35993236/" target="_blank"&gt;studies&lt;/a&gt; that have shown that the risk of myocarditis and pericarditis is greater after contracting covid for both vaccinated and non-vaccinated people than the risk of the same complications after vaccination alone.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmbv64d1k000n3b6m5va2ty2o@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            O’Leary said that while some cases of myocarditis were reported in vaccinated adolescent boys and young men early in the covid pandemic, the rates declined after the two initial doses of covid vaccines were spaced further apart.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmbv64d1k000o3b6m8x16x1hx@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Now, adolescents and adults who have not been previously vaccinated receive only one shot, and myocarditis no longer shows up in the data, O’Leary said, referring to the CDC’s &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/vaccine-safety-systems/vsd/index.html#cdc_generic_section_5-access-and-use-vsd-data" target="_blank"&gt;Vaccine Safety Datalink&lt;/a&gt;. “There is no increased risk at this point that we can identify,” he said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmbv64d1k000p3b6mowflhssf@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            In two instances, the HHS memo makes claims that are &lt;a href="https://obgyn.onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1111/1471-0528.17721" target="_blank"&gt;actively refuted&lt;/a&gt; by &lt;a href="https://journals.lww.com/greenjournal/fulltext/2022/04000/in_vitro_fertilization_and_early_pregnancy.3.aspx%C2%A0" target="_blank"&gt;the papers&lt;/a&gt; it cites to back them up. Both papers support the safety and effectiveness of covid vaccines for pregnant women.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmbv64d1k000q3b6msjgjfu62@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The HHS document says that another &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0264410X24001270?via%3Dihub#s0090" target="_blank"&gt;paper it cites&lt;/a&gt; found “an increase in placental blood clotting in pregnant mothers who took the vaccine.” But the paper doesn’t contain any reference to placental blood clots or to pregnant women.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmbv64d1k000r3b6m8l7lpzj7@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “I’ve now read it three times. And I cannot find that anywhere,” said Turrentine, the OB-GYN professor.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmbv64d1k000s3b6m7rkrmviu@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            If he were grading the HHS document, “I would give this an ‘F,’” Turrentine said. “This is not supported by anything and it’s not using medical evidence.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmbv64d1k000t3b6mahkdmtpe@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            While members of Congress who are physicians should know to check references in the paper, they may not take the time to do so, said &lt;a href="https://www.uclahealth.org/providers/neil-silverman" target="_blank"&gt;Neil Silverman,&lt;/a&gt; a professor of clinical obstetrics and gynecology who directs the Infectious Diseases in Pregnancy Program at the David Geffen School of Medicine at UCLA. “They’re going to assume this is coming from a scientific agency. So they are being hoodwinked along with everyone else who has had access to this document,” Silverman said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmbv64d1k000u3b6m1utygbdi@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The offices of three Republicans in Congress who are medical doctors serving on House and Senate committees focused on health, including Sen. Bill Cassidy (R-La.), did not respond to requests for comment about whether they received the memo. Emily Druckman, communications director for Rep. Kim Schrier (D-Wash.), a physician serving on the House Energy and Commerce Committee, confirmed that Schrier’s office did receive a copy of the document.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmbv64d1k000v3b6m04p2ohkp@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “The problem is a lot of legislators and even their staffers, they don’t have the expertise to be able to pick those references apart,” O’Leary said. “But this one — I’ve seen much better anti-vaccine propaganda than this, frankly.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmbv64d1k000w3b6mwahzdy4o@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            C.J. Young, deputy communications director for the House Energy and Commerce Committee, confirmed that Democratic staff members of the committee received the document from HHS. In the past, he said, similar documents would help clarify the justification and scope of an administration’s policy change and could be assumed to be scientifically accurate, Young said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmbv64d1k000x3b6mxxuyaefn@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “This feels like it’s breaking new ground. I don’t think that we saw this level of sloppiness or inattention to detail or lack of consideration for scientific merit under the first Trump administration,” Young said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmbv64d1k000y3b6m683xobr4@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            On June 4, Rep. Frank Pallone (D-N.J.) and Schrier &lt;a href="https://www.congress.gov/119/bills/hr3701/BILLS-119hr3701ih.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;introduced a bill&lt;/a&gt; that would require Kennedy to adopt official vaccine decisions from the Advisory Committee on Immunization Practices, or ACIP. Young said the motivation behind the bill was Kennedy’s decision to change the covid vaccine schedule without the input of ACIP’s vaccine experts, who play a key role in setting CDC policies around vaccine schedules and access.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmbv64d1k000z3b6mkvy7hltk@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Kennedy announced June 9 on X that he would remove all 17 members of ACIP, citing alleged conflicts of interest he did not detail, and replace them. He announced eight replacements June 11, including people who had criticized vaccine mandates during the covid pandemic.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmbv636zg00003b6m5ewwg61y@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            &lt;a href="https://kffhealthnews.org/about-us/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;em&gt;KFF Health News&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt; is a national newsroom that produces in-depth journalism about health issues and is one of the core operating programs at &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.kff.org/about-us/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;em&gt;KFF&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt; — the independent source for health policy research, polling, and journalism.&lt;/em&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;

              &lt;/div&gt;
                &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>CNN</author><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 19:40:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMif0FVX3lxTE5TbnlwUWpFZlZYbHVOSEg2dHlyTHQ2UWVqRVpxWlYyRTUtSHMwQ3VtcExTd3ptclpWdS1JUXpiSzVQS2tGSGZ6bVZBV05ZeVBVMXJ0N0ItMkxGdWM5R3BTeFptcVBGVE5pR0dTSGJfXzE0RU9jNlZyYjB6ckI1M0nSAYQBQVVfeXFMTWlNbXNEckRFbkhMTE9tWHlJWklYbFdzcm1DX19mSFZhc1YwUGgyUVBfUFZ6SUZTbXExMVFwS1pDblhaWUJJT3hjVWFibGgxTU5SU29lT1lLRldDMkt4MF90cG1YQUlmcmI1M084ZXhNcmlpbUc3TUFuNE1oeFBVdWtWanYx</guid></item><item><title>是的， “唯物主义者”的肢体伸展手术是真实的- Popsugar | Yes, That "Materialists" Limb-Lengthening Procedure Is Real - Popsugar</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMieEFVX3lxTE9GbHZnY1FuaHhTVWdOZVhYYnlyZUFxN29NVC1BMlBJQlBBMmFjV0FVOUJUZVhBY01HbGZ4eDY2dVZGVXpoMWhXeTM0LUhRNlROb0hHOXhSblJUc2RIUnlINGUxYkZtdlZMMGxuLTNjRFpNUGNSWTUxMg?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="ParagraphBodyTextstyles__BodyText-sc-zv221u-0 iRfTZJ page-element paragraph undefined " data-element-type="ParagraphBodyText" data-element-index="2"&gt;&lt;p data-element-index="0"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Warning: spoilers for "Materialists" ahead.&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-element-index="1"&gt;A24's latest rom-com presents audiences with a unique but pressing question: what would you give to grow a couple inches? 
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-element-index="2"&gt;By now we know that height is (unfortunately) a major factor when it comes to dating. In fact, one &lt;a href="https://journals.sagepub.com/doi/10.1177/0192513X13519256?ref=popsugar.com&amp;amp;=___psv__p_49447489__t_w_" class="has-affiliate-link" target="_blank"&gt;2014 Journal of Family Issues study&lt;/a&gt; found that nearly 49 percent of women prefer to date men taller than them, while &lt;a href="https://repository.rice.edu/server/api/core/bitstreams/75dfc076-c1e1-479e-ab96-cd7d697f2c2b/content?ref=popsugar.com&amp;amp;=___psv__p_49447489__t_w_" class="has-affiliate-link" target="_blank"&gt;additional research&lt;/a&gt; attributes this preference to "masculine images of dominance and protector." As recently seen in "Materialists," however, there's a fix, albeit painful, for those who come up a bit short: leg-lengthening surgery. 
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-element-index="3"&gt;In the film, Lucy (Dakota Johnson) is a &lt;a href="https://www.popsugar.com/relationships/gen-z-matchmaking-49361002" target="_blank"&gt;skilled New York City matchmaker&lt;/a&gt; who also happens to witness just how often men fib about their heights in order to secure a date. But height is undeniably an important consideration for many of her women clients, too. So much so that Lucy's colleague notes some men have undergone leg-lengthening procedures to add a couple inches to their height. 
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-element-index="4"&gt;Lucy is taken aback by the information, especially since the surgery sounds drastic in nature. Then, while dating Harry (Pedro Pascal) — a handsome, wealthy "unicorn" of a love interest — she notices scars on his legs. Harry reveals he too had the leg-lengthening surgery, saying it boosted his confidence and upped his height by six inches. 
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-element-index="5"&gt;So, is leg-lengthening a real thing? Surprisingly yes. But while it's not a procedure made up for the A24 universe, it's also not the magical makeover the movie might make it out to be (sorry to disappoint). Here's what to know about leg-lengthening before getting your hopes too high.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-element-index="6" data-element-has-ending-title="true"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What Is Leg-Lengthening Surgery?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-element-index="7"&gt;Leg-lengthening (or more accurately, limb-lengthening) is a long, arduous, and painful procedure. According to &lt;a href="https://my.clevelandclinic.org/health/treatments/24316-limb-lengthening-surgery?ref=popsugar.com&amp;amp;=___psv__p_49447489__t_w_" class="has-affiliate-link" target="_blank"&gt;Cleveland Clinic&lt;/a&gt;, it's most commonly used for treating skeletal dysplasia, bone growth issues, and bone length differences. While people have used it with the sole cosmetic intent of increasing height, it's not exactly an easy way to land more dates. More on that in a minute. 
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-element-index="8" data-element-has-ending-title="true"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;How Does Leg-Lengthening Work?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-element-index="9"&gt;The science behind leg-lengthening is fairly simple. In essence, the surgeon cuts the bone into two segments (this is referred to as an "osteotomy"). From there, a limb-lengthening device is attached to the two segments of bone. This device can be one of two things:
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-element-index="10" data-element-has-ending-title="false"&gt;&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Internal Device&lt;/strong&gt;: Here, internal rods are placed inside the bone (so they can't be seen externally). Patients won't have any external devices to attend to, but they should still ensure their incision wounds are kept clean.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;External Device&lt;/strong&gt;: This option places screws in the bone, then attaches them to an external fixator (outside of the skin) via pins or wires. The metal fixator can be adjusted externally, per &lt;a href="https://medlineplus.gov/ency/imagepages/18021.htm?ref=popsugar.com&amp;amp;=___psv__p_49447489__t_w_" class="has-affiliate-link" target="_blank"&gt;Medline Plus&lt;/a&gt;. Patients should clean the pin sites daily to prevent infection.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-element-index="11"&gt;Once the device is attached, the two bone segments will begin to pull apart in a process called "distraction." As the gap between the two bone segments grows, the body will eventually create new bone to fill in the space. Once the desired length is reached, the new bone will need time to harden, according to the Cleveland Clinic. 
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-element-index="12" data-element-has-ending-title="true"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;How Long Does Leg-Lengthening Take?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-element-index="13"&gt;To give you a rough estimation of the timeline, it takes about three months to see an inch of bone growth. That means Harry's six-inch leg-lengthening would've taken &lt;em&gt;at least&lt;/em&gt; a year and a half. 
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-element-index="14"&gt;The operation isn't cheap either: As reported by &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/health/mens-health/leg-lengthening-surgery-gains-popularity-men-seeking-taller-rcna79819?ref=popsugar.com&amp;amp;=___psv__p_49447489__t_w_" class="has-affiliate-link" target="_blank"&gt;NBC News&lt;/a&gt;, limb-lengthening can cost upwards of $75,000, and often isn't covered by insurance — and that's not to mention the required physical therapy.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-element-index="15" data-element-has-ending-title="true"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;The Bottom Line&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-element-index="16"&gt;So is limb-lengthening real? Yes. Could you technically use it just to increase your height? Also yes. But ultimately, it's less of a cosmetic surgery, and more of a corrective operation. We understand &lt;a href="https://www.popsugar.com/love/moving-better-dating-scene-49369832"&gt;how frustrating dating can be&lt;/a&gt; (sadly, life doesn't always feel like a rom-com), but if you're still feeling a deep sense of dissatisfaction with your height or appearance in general, therapy may be cheaper and less painful in the long run.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="ParagraphBodyTextstyles__BodyText-sc-zv221u-0 iRfTZJ page-element paragraph undefined " data-element-type="ParagraphBodyText" data-element-index="4"&gt;&lt;p data-element-index="0" data-element-has-ending-title="true"&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-element-index="1"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.popsugar.com/author/chandler-plante"&gt;Chandler Plante&lt;/a&gt; (she/her) is an assistant health and fitness editor for PS. She has over four years of professional journalism experience, previously working as an editorial assistant for People magazine and contributing to Ladygunn, Millie, and Bustle Digital Group.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-element-index="2" data-element-has-ending-title="true"&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Popsugar</author><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 19:20:02 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMieEFVX3lxTE9GbHZnY1FuaHhTVWdOZVhYYnlyZUFxN29NVC1BMlBJQlBBMmFjV0FVOUJUZVhBY01HbGZ4eDY2dVZGVXpoMWhXeTM0LUhRNlROb0hHOXhSblJUc2RIUnlINGUxYkZtdlZMMGxuLTNjRFpNUGNSWTUxMg</guid></item><item><title>随着疫苗接种率的下降，西澳百日咳病例飙升-《西雅图时报》 | WA whooping cough cases soar as vaccination rates drop - The Seattle Times</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMipwFBVV95cUxPTFZzUnljUW9uY25raEFkZnJSczdGN0lXN2tvMU15ZHI0aFpQU3ZLV1RuMmpvaDNaazNlM2lHeVRkTlE5THJNeWZhLWU2WGVKSzR6Zjg0SWhhTWNyMWFnTlVBUG5nYUhsdzVxbkFPWm5Ra0x2TGd4dTAtMmFLOEFDZ1luRC1xUEl4UUFwTnh3YlhGTWlBODBGLXU5bFBQcDJmVVB6TkFxZw?oc=5</link><description>&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMipwFBVV95cUxPTFZzUnljUW9uY25raEFkZnJSczdGN0lXN2tvMU15ZHI0aFpQU3ZLV1RuMmpvaDNaazNlM2lHeVRkTlE5THJNeWZhLWU2WGVKSzR6Zjg0SWhhTWNyMWFnTlVBUG5nYUhsdzVxbkFPWm5Ra0x2TGd4dTAtMmFLOEFDZ1luRC1xUEl4UUFwTnh3YlhGTWlBODBGLXU5bFBQcDJmVVB6TkFxZw?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;WA whooping cough cases soar as vaccination rates drop&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Seattle Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMifkFVX3lxTE1RQ0N1aThlQnRVUC1TeVBoTy10UHkzYm9XSmNQOXBrOHN3VjU5ZktvQS1hdUNPVFJwVFVjbnVaWDNFbFhpeDcxcGhZM0sxT0x5YmxVWWRmcGlwcWR2UkFkTi1kc3V0cVRPQmNudWluY3NNVE51Nmp0Z1dQWEJ0UdIBgwFBVV95cUxPV0JuTWhUY1dGNGZfcXY5azlETThMTmVockowRllnekljaG1vMjFTOVhmZGVaelF1QXZNWTh4c2NFVjdrNGRtWFppQlVjNlpmaFVBNkRpWVJHS2o4eVlzdXo1NWlMNFZocW1oYmptaUR0WHExNEJ5WF9wYjc5aUJQbF94RQ?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;Taney County health officials see rise in whooping cough cases&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;OzarksFirst.com&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiqgFBVV95cUxNOHpSRkZNWm9oQWlpeFJDRTB1bFZjYjhtOHBjanNmclIxZWpCYlhFaHRyTGU3SF9GZ1ptQkkwLThpVVViQTRQS2pmang0bDVobmhGTTVsUFhvUjl5cnN5RzJOTEk2M1FVdTlfMkhVcnJ4eEt0R1p2TmFJRDcyeENkbGlTdzY0S3lyT2I0NElBU2ZJdExYdDM2V3ktWHd0UkZuQ1FGMVhyNF9pUdIBrwFBVV95cUxQaktSNVFPR2JqUVZNUTB3V09adFJ2NTBOc2tBNFdlVmlBRzVFOXYxR0xlMW5wRFB4N29aWGY0cHpaU2wxYldlampnN3poZVNoaE5paXEwV0d4ejhQUFcydDdhTGdJRnhzSE1Dczk3WnpoSktxUXR5VHpZM1IyckFLR1ZEcDAzNl8xVWpiMUhkMmk2VnhkZEZueDRNQ09KNFlhWERwTWx2MUpucVcyZ2M4?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;Washington reports ‘dramatic’ 25-fold increase in whooping cough cases&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;KOIN.com&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiogFBVV95cUxQOTd2eU1uc1EzMHVUSDUxOXRLdkRodThiRUFKS1hIelJ1bWgzS2c5YzNmS2hkR2dRdWl4RnE3d1BVNi14bGwxSW9VN3VOZFY0LWZGc2UyZzlmTzJ3aUZ4WlZRNzhBek1uLXo0b09MY1ZPLXdjQ0dDdXBLWTU3Z21Ia2FfbURiMUluSXg1NlVMYTl2MXJxaEpOYlcwOXJRZkZvZUE?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;Whooping cough cases rising in Louisiana, with babies hit hardest: "A horrible disease"&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Axios&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMi2gFBVV95cUxNQ3plTjktazY3SDlBZnFLVzJQNWY3X1hYSVZycWt5SkRHR18yM3BVYTU0a0tSaHV1NGpjNjF5emxDWTNydGxvaUVSMEpaSlhrVzJhSUFLSGhpSzNuajJ0ZlNHRVhmYnpwYzgzblVFM3BPZkZRNHZOYXB6VzRqSGpLbjVQLUFhOHVvbGxldjBIMEljbXM1aHIzc1lQaUJZYjllaEd3Ry14WE03akxMd19EelBkZ2xlRzJPZ3YtRk96SHpMNHdFQS05Rk1WR0J4Mk1DckpMZGdHMWp3Zw?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;Washington whooping cough cases up 25x, pediatric vaccinations fall&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;KXLY.com&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;</description><author>The Seattle Times</author><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 18:58:45 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipwFBVV95cUxPTFZzUnljUW9uY25raEFkZnJSczdGN0lXN2tvMU15ZHI0aFpQU3ZLV1RuMmpvaDNaazNlM2lHeVRkTlE5THJNeWZhLWU2WGVKSzR6Zjg0SWhhTWNyMWFnTlVBUG5nYUhsdzVxbkFPWm5Ra0x2TGd4dTAtMmFLOEFDZ1luRC1xUEl4UUFwTnh3YlhGTWlBODBGLXU5bFBQcDJmVVB6TkFxZw</guid></item><item><title>父亲， 39岁，有1个轻微症状。然后，在“毁灭性”诊断后，他被给予2年的生命- AOL.com | Father, 39, Has 1 Minor Symptom. Then He’s Given 2 Years to Live After 'Devastating' Diagnosis - AOL.com</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMibEFVX3lxTFBwVjRpODQtc2RRdlJEbXNNQ2taWEM1OG9xb0V4bW13NXIzWDM3OE1YYUlsdTB1Qm9PYnh1eUlnMjVQYVpsamlsRVZTQWpWeWM0MlRFWVpUbGxkcXF2WlV3eTJRRkY0cVExWlBITA?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="caas-body"&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure"&gt;&lt;div class="caption-wrapper caption-aligned-with-image"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption-collapse"&gt;&lt;p&gt;gofundme&lt;/p&gt; Andres Albaladejo.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;NEED TO KNOW&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul class="caas-list caas-list-bullet"&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Florida man's muscle spasms seemed harmless at first, but eventually progressed and led to a devastating diagnosis&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Andres Albaladejo was diagnosed with amyotrophic lateral sclerosis (ALS) in 2023&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;His wife Carmen has become his primary caretaker at home and has been documenting the family's journey on TikTok&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When a Florida man first noticed &lt;a href="https://www.tiktok.com/@calbaladej0/video/7512952654662880555?lang=en" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:muscle spasms;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;muscle spasms&lt;/a&gt; in one of his arms, he wasn’t immediately concerned that it could be a symptom of something more serious.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Andres Albaladejo, 41, and his wife Carmen told the &lt;a href="https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-14805097/motor-neurone-disease-early-symptom-father-stephen-hawking.html" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Daily Mail;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Daily Mail&lt;/a&gt; that they first noticed the twitching in his left arm around April 2023.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“It was bizarre. I asked if he could feel it, if he was doing anything to make it twitch, but he said no,” she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The spasms progressed for Albaladejo and he soon experienced arm weakness, difficulty gripping things, and high blood pressure, &lt;a class="link rapid-noclick-resp" href="https://www.newsweek.com/silly-little-symptom-leads-als-diagnosis-2083556?utm_term=Autofeed&amp;amp;utm_medium=Social&amp;amp;utm_source=Facebook&amp;amp;fbclid=IwY2xjawK5DRlleHRuA2FlbQIxMABicmlkETFNUG40ZWN2eG9uVmJDSFFzAR4GYdlcSt9DsIH1gC5T3EZCSbd3f9-elZ3QsLIAmEvjc_Me_P2lo0dGdQHBeA_aem_BmKQCgWPBSYsySYL3Yg2tA#Echobox=1749744873" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Newsweek;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas"&gt;Newsweek&lt;/a&gt; reported. Within months, doctors diagnosed him with amyotrophic lateral sclerosis (ALS), also known as Lou Gehrig’s Disease, a condition that causes progressive &lt;a href="https://www.mayoclinic.org/diseases-conditions/amyotrophic-lateral-sclerosis/symptoms-causes/syc-20354022" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:loss of muscle control;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;loss of muscle control&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I was heartbroken when I heard the news, like my life was being taken from me piece by piece – I still have so much of me to give,” he told DM.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Hearing the diagnosis was devastating, we were in complete shock,” Carmen said to Newsweek. “Sitting in that doctor's office, the weight of it all hit us at once. We broke down in tears. It was one of the hardest moments of our lives, filled with fear, sorrow, and so many unanswered questions.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure"&gt;&lt;div class="caption-wrapper caption-aligned-with-image"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption-collapse"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Getty&lt;/p&gt; Physical therapy (stock photo).&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;ALS symptoms can include difficulty walking, tripping, and slurred speech, among others, and it often first appears in the hands, feet, arms, or legs, according to the &lt;a href="https://www.mayoclinic.org/diseases-conditions/amyotrophic-lateral-sclerosis/symptoms-causes/syc-20354022" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Mayo Clinic;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Mayo Clinic&lt;/a&gt;. There is no cure, but medical treatment can slow the disease's progress.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Life changed in an instant for Albaladejo, who used to work as a school resource officer, and he worried about his family’s future, including his 11-year-old daughter Sophia. He was 39 years old when he received the diagnosis in late 2023, according to Newsweek.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I'm angry that I won't be here to see my little girl grow into the smart, kind, and beautiful woman I know she will be. I think that hurts the most,” Albaladejo said. “Instead, she has to watch me fall apart in front of her eyes.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But he wants to leave a legacy she can be proud of.  “I just hope that throughout all of this, my daughter still sees me as her hero, as I face this disease with determination and strength,” he added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Daily life in Tampa has shifted drastically for the couple, who &lt;a href="https://www.tiktok.com/@calbaladej0/photo/7402335127734390062" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:started dating;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;started dating&lt;/a&gt; when they were teenagers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“In eight months, our lives completely changed. We thought it was nerve compression, and now Albaladejo has a terminal illness with a prognosis of two to five years,” Carmen told the Daily Mail.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Never miss a story — sign up for &lt;a href="https://people.com/people-news-daily-newsletter-sign-up-8692701" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:PEOPLE's free daily newsletter;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;PEOPLE's free daily newsletter&lt;/a&gt; to stay up-to-date on the best of what PEOPLE has to offer​​, from celebrity news to compelling human interest stories. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Per Newsweek, Albaladejo relies on a wheelchair to get around and Carmen has become her husband’s primary caregiver.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"To see someone go from being completely independent to nearly fully dependent in under two years is truly heartbreaking," she told Newsweek.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Carmen has been documenting the &lt;a href="https://www.tiktok.com/@calbaladej0/video/7514004486549998894" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:family’s journey on TikTok;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;family’s journey on TikTok&lt;/a&gt; and Albaladejo’s sister started a &lt;a href="https://www.gofundme.com/f/support-andres-albaladejos-fight-against-als?utm_campaign=fp_ss_icons_ai&amp;amp;utm_content=amp1v3&amp;amp;utm_medium=customer&amp;amp;utm_source=copy_link" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:GoFundMe;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;GoFundMe&lt;/a&gt; that has already raised more than $26,000.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“It’s a cruel condition that robs a person of their vitality, strength and mobility,” Carmen wrote online in 2024. “It’s been a rough year for us and even through it all, we still do what we can to just live life every day.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Although there’s no cure, the Albaladejo family is pressing forward as best they can.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“At this point, we are getting our affairs in order, as we cannot see any promising treatments we can afford,” Carmen told the Daily Mail. “We are trying to stay strong and make the best out of our situation.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Read the original article on &lt;a href="https://people.com/florida-father-has-1-minor-symptom-before-he-s-given-2-years-to-live-11754248" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:People;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;People&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>AOL.com</author><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 18:35:21 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMibEFVX3lxTFBwVjRpODQtc2RRdlJEbXNNQ2taWEM1OG9xb0V4bW13NXIzWDM3OE1YYUlsdTB1Qm9PYnh1eUlnMjVQYVpsamlsRVZTQWpWeWM0MlRFWVpUbGxkcXF2WlV3eTJRRkY0cVExWlBITA</guid></item><item><title>科学家们精确地指出了检查您是否会患上早发性结肠癌的方法，准确率高达92 ％ -每日邮报 | Scientists pinpoint way to check if you're going to get early-onset colon cancer with up to 92% accuracy - Daily Mail</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMisgFBVV95cUxPOGU1dnBOa003N0hrUUNtS19YdS14X1EyTDNWc1RIZU1fV0NzdFhBZmt1T0phZk5NMTNqMVR0Rk1MN3lYY2lxdV80OWlydTJKc2ppTjlTWFJNUVl3ZGlCREdoeWtOdVNLa0NpRTdkUzhaemVMTXNaZG90OENxd3FMcndfanpSQUt1TDFNQ1FOb0FqNGk2OTlvWnFFMW1ON0cwOGphS3ZBZHpaV0tobUxMaFRR0gG3AUFVX3lxTFBvRXJ5ME9kMDJMMUV5SFVUT0k3SmdlRzIzTDBQZksyc2xleVo5MEp3S241R1NBdDJzWnczaHZINXhsN2VQallnNzdmc2c5em9FMks2dXVicmIzWFFiMFowQjZLaHlUZ1ZvWWFWekllbVhTOWNUcU9OSVp6ZXVEalE3UEhjNUdoa1FkU2YzN3BNTGd4UEdJZFVWY0gwdDVlX0phRlpmM2RvMFZXMVVralRsenBhalQ2bw?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div itemprop="articleBody"&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;A little-known at-home test can detect early-onset colon &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/cancer/index.html" id="mol-5395ccd0-485d-11f0-a3cb-3b7d494b4c7b"&gt;cancer&lt;/a&gt; before symptoms develop, increasing the chance of surviving a disease that is surging among young people. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The fecal immunochemical test (FIT) costs $49 and screens a person's feces for flecks of blood, a warning sign of the cancer — as tumors cause bleeding.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The test is FDA-approved and allows younger people a chance to screen for colon cancer before they reach the recommended age for a colonoscopy, 45 years. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;If blood is detected, a colonoscopy is performed, increasing the chances of catching colon cancer early when it is more treatable.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;And the American College of Surgeons says it is generally accurate, able to detect about 80 percent of all cases. If someone opts for the $600 FIT with DNA screening, which checks for abnormal changes in cells' DNA, accuracy rises to 92 percent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;A colonoscopy is about 99 percent accurate at detecting all cancers. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;A recent study found people that use the FIT method between the ages of 40 to 49 years old are 39 percent less likely to die from colon cancer than their peers who wait to get the test until they are 50 years old or above.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;An increasing number of younger people are seeking screening, as the US experiences a&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/health/article-14797635/colon-cancer-young-people-symptoms.html"&gt;surge in colon cancer among people under 50&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;, with young patients today about twice as likely to be diagnosed with the disease than their grandparents.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Pictured above is Christine Bronstein who was diagnosed with colon cancer at age 48 years after taking an at-home stool-based test for the disease. She said without the test, her cancer may have gone unnoticed&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The rising rates are prompting some physicians to urge Americans to &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/health/article-14766779/colon-cancer-screening-age-lowered-cases-surge.html"&gt;start getting screened for the disease &lt;/a&gt;before the age of 45 years, which is when US doctors recommend.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;For the test, which can be ordered online, customers are sent a package containing a collection tube.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;They are asked to collect a sample of their feces from the toilet bowl, place it in the tube and mail it to a lab. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Results take about five days to come back.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In the lab, scientists expose the feces to antibodies that can bind to human hemoglobin - a protein found in red blood cells.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;If they bind to an area of the feces, a positive test result is issued - and patients are advised to undertake further screening.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In the FIT with DNA, scientists also analyze cells found in the stool for abnormal changes - which could indicate cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Patients over 45 years old who have an average risk — meaning no family history of the disease — may be recommended the test, which is free for the group under health insurance plans.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But people can also buy the test, which is sold by labs like Everlywell for $49, or opt for other tests like Cologuard, which is priced at $121.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;While the test can be extremely helpful, doctors caution that about five to 10 percent of patients who get a positive result do not have colon cancer or advanced polyps.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The number of false positives after a colonoscopy is below one percent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;It is important to follow up with a doctor to discuss results.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;&lt;p class="clear"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Doctors diagnosed her with stage three cancer following the test, and a two-inch tumor was found in her rectum. She underwent chemotherapy to shrink her tumor (shown above) before doctors said they would remove it&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Shown above is a stock image of the FIT, which involves sending a sample of feces off to a lab&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    
    
    &lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Patients undertaking the test are recommended to do it every year, as this can help to catch early-onset cancers which are typically slower growing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Among patients to have their cancer caught after using an at-home stool-based test is Christine Bronstein, who was diagnosed with the cancer at age 48.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The Hawaii local exercises regularly, and avoids sugar and alcohol.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But after seeing blood in her stool in 2021, she became concerned and ordered a stool-based test.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;After results came back positive, she rushed to see her doctor and was eventually approved for a colonoscopy - which led to a stage three colon cancer diagnosis with a two-inch tumor found in her rectum.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Bronstein told &lt;a class="" rel="noreferrer noopener" target="_blank" href="https://www.today.com/health/health/colorectal-cancer-survivor-home-test-rcna25564"&gt;TODAY&lt;/a&gt;: 'I'm very lucky that I did my test when I did. This thing really takes people down right in their prime... I think the problem why this is becoming the No.1 killer for younger people is because their symptoms get denied.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Colon cancer cases are surging among under-50s in the US in an uptick that has stunned researchers, with adults born in the 1980s having double the risk of suffering from the cancer compared to their parents.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Among adults aged 25 to 29 years, colon cancer cancer rates have spiked 85 percent in two decades according to CDC data. At the same time, over the last 30 years cases have dropped among over-50s by 30 percent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
            

            
            
            
            
            &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Daily Mail</author><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 18:24:11 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMisgFBVV95cUxPOGU1dnBOa003N0hrUUNtS19YdS14X1EyTDNWc1RIZU1fV0NzdFhBZmt1T0phZk5NMTNqMVR0Rk1MN3lYY2lxdV80OWlydTJKc2ppTjlTWFJNUVl3ZGlCREdoeWtOdVNLa0NpRTdkUzhaemVMTXNaZG90OENxd3FMcndfanpSQUt1TDFNQ1FOb0FqNGk2OTlvWnFFMW1ON0cwOGphS3ZBZHpaV0tobUxMaFRR0gG3AUFVX3lxTFBvRXJ5ME9kMDJMMUV5SFVUT0k3SmdlRzIzTDBQZksyc2xleVo5MEp3S241R1NBdDJzWnczaHZINXhsN2VQallnNzdmc2c5em9FMks2dXVicmIzWFFiMFowQjZLaHlUZ1ZvWWFWekllbVhTOWNUcU9OSVp6ZXVEalE3UEhjNUdoa1FkU2YzN3BNTGd4UEdJZFVWY0gwdDVlX0phRlpmM2RvMFZXMVVralRsenBhalQ2bw</guid></item><item><title>你真正需要多少阳光来获得足够的维生素D ？ - Verywell Health | How Much Sun Do You Really Need to Get Enough Vitamin D? - Verywell Health</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMidEFVX3lxTFBQRWoyWmNiV0JZbUVqVFhVWmpMRnByUWxFYWFBc1o2eTlWdU1RZzM2ZzFwdVV6R0dGSlNtXzUyd0VBVEdEbzdnbG5FZ0FXQnlXY0VQYUJaSUpjenQxdm1qb0JjWjczWm1rTWg4QUVVbnlCUDFD?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="health-sc-page_1-0" class="comp health-sc-page mntl-sc-page mntl-block structured-content article-content expert-content right-rail__offset lock-journey" data-sc-sticky-offset="60" data-sc-ad-label-height="24" data-sc-ad-track-spacing="100" data-sc-min-track-height="250" data-sc-max-track-height="600" data-sc-breakpoint="50em" data-sc-load-immediate="4" data-sc-content-positions="[400, 1400, 1400, 1700, 2000, 2200, 2400, 2600, 2800]" data-bind-scroll-on-start="true"&gt;&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Spending just a few minutes in the sun can help your body produce vitamin D, a hormone that supports bone health. However, sun exposure carries a risk of skin cancer, and experts recommend getting vitamin D through diet or supplements instead.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_2-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-how-much-sun-do-you-need-for-vitamin-d"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_3-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block health-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; How Much Sun Do You Need for Vitamin D? &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_4-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; If you're using sunscreen and plan to be outside anyway, brief sun exposure may help with vitamin D production. Research shows that about 10 minutes of midday sun with 25% of the body exposed—such as the arms and legs—can meet daily vitamin D needs during spring and summer.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="1"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_5-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_6-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; “In winter, especially in northern regions, it may take up to two hours with only 10% of the body exposed, like the face and hands, to get the same amount,” said &lt;a href="https://www.nymc.edu/som/faculty/marmon-shoshana.php" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Shoshana Marmon, MD, PhD,&lt;/a&gt; an assistant professor of dermatology at New York Medical College.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_7-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-prolonged-sun-exposure-isnt-safe-for-your-skin"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_8-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block health-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; Prolonged Sun Exposure Isn't Safe for Your Skin &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_9-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.verywellhealth.com/how-to-choose-a-protective-sunscreen-for-the-summer-5323528" link-destination-recommendation="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Sunscreen&lt;/a&gt; may block some of the ultraviolet rays responsible for vitamin D production. However, you should still &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.verywellhealth.com/how-to-apply-sunscreen-correctly-7483616" link-destination-recommendation="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;wear sunscreen&lt;/a&gt; to &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.verywellhealth.com/how-many-sunburns-is-too-many-7547307" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="3"&gt;reduce the risk of skin cancer&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_10-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_11-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; “The sun is not a dependable source to ensure you have enough vitamin D,” &lt;a href="https://mdinseattle.com/about-modern-dermatology/our-physicians/heather-d-rogers-md/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Heather D. Rogers, MD,&lt;/a&gt; a dermatologist in Seattle, told Verywell. “The safest and most consistent way to get adequate vitamin D is through your diet—eating &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.verywellhealth.com/foods-rich-in-vitamin-d-8348470" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;vitamin D–rich foods&lt;/a&gt;, choosing fortified options, and using supplements as needed.” 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_12-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_13-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Although experts advise against relying on sun exposure for all your vitamin D needs, this doesn't mean you should avoid sunlight altogether. Even with sunscreen, your body may still produce some vitamin D. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_14-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_15-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; "Not having enough sun exposure can contribute to increased anxiety, depression, cognitive decline, and greater difficulty managing everyday stressors,” said &lt;a href="https://dignuswellness.com/AboutMe" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1" rel="nofollow"&gt;Samia Estrada, PsyD&lt;/a&gt;, a clinical psychologist based in Vacaville, CA. “Getting sun while also exercising has been found to have a favorable impact on stress management.”
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_16-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_18-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-where-should-you-get-vitamin-d"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_19-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block health-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; Where Should You Get Vitamin D? &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_20-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Vitamin D’s primary role is to help the body absorb calcium from the intestines, which helps strengthen your bones, said &lt;a href="https://medicine.yale.edu/profile/karl-insogna/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Karl Insogna, MD,&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;director of the Yale Bone Center at Yale Medicine.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_21-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_22-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Insgona said both &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.verywellhealth.com/vitamin-d-two-vs-d-three-7095309" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;vitamin D2 and D3&lt;/a&gt; naturally occur in foods such as salmon, tuna, mackerel, beef liver, and egg yolks. But because most people don’t eat enough of these foods, many products—including milk, certain cereals, and some orange juice brands—have been fortified with vitamin D.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_23-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-are-you-getting-enough-vitamin-d"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_24-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block health-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; Are You Getting Enough Vitamin D? &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_25-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Vitamin D is measured in international units (IU). The &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.verywellhealth.com/new-guidelines-supplemental-vitamin-d-8666125" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;recommended daily intake&lt;/a&gt; is 600 IU for ages 1 to 70, and 800 IU for those 71 and older.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="2"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_26-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_27-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; According to the National Institutes of Health, most people in the United States have adequate blood levels of vitamin D, but about 25% do not. As you age, your skin becomes less efficient at producing vitamin D, which may increase your need for supplements or vitamin D–rich foods.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_28-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_29-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; The U.S. Preventive Services Task Force currently states that there isn’t enough evidence to recommend for or against routine vitamin D testing in people without symptoms of a deficiency.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="3"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_30-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_31-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.verywellhealth.com/symptoms-of-vitamin-d-deficiency-7963631" link-destination-recommendation="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Symptoms of low vitamin D&lt;/a&gt; can include:&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="7"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_32-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_33-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;li&gt;fatigue&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;bone pain&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;muscle weakness&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;depression&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;frequent infections&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="5"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;hair loss&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="4"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;reduced appetite&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;slower wound healing&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="6"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_34-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_35-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Your healthcare provider may order a blood test to &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.verywellhealth.com/vitamin-d-test-4691741" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;measure your vitamin D levels&lt;/a&gt;—or you can ask for one. If your levels are low, your provider may recommend dietary changes or a supplement.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_36-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="health-sc-block-callout--exclamation_1-0" class="comp health-sc-block-callout--exclamation health-sc-block-callout-base mntl-sc-block-callout mntl-block theme-exclamation theme-exclamation" data-tracking-id="mntl-sc-block-callout" data-tracking-container="true"&gt;&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block-callout-heading_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block-callout-heading mntl-text-block"&gt;What This Means For You&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;div id="mntl-sc-block-callout-body_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block-callout-body mntl-text-block expert-content"&gt;&lt;p&gt;While brief sun exposure may contribute to vitamin D production, experts recommend getting the vitamin primarily through food or supplements to reduce skin cancer risk. If you're concerned about your vitamin D levels, talk to your healthcare provider about testing and safe ways to increase your intake.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;svg class="icon icon-exclamation "&gt;
&lt;use xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xlink:href="#icon-exclamation" href="#icon-exclamation"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;
&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id="post-article_1-0" class="comp post-article mntl-block"&gt;
&lt;div id="sources_1-0" class="comp sources mntl-block"&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-article-sources_1-0" class="comp mntl-article-sources mntl-expandable-block" data-scroll-offset="70"&gt;&lt;div class="loc expandable-content"&gt;&lt;div id="source-guidelines_1-0" class="comp source-guidelines mntl-text-block"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Verywell Health uses only high-quality sources, including peer-reviewed studies, to support the facts within our articles. Read our &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="/verywell-editorial-process-4777042"&gt;editorial process&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; to learn more about how we fact-check and keep our content accurate, reliable, and trustworthy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id="mntl-article-sources__citation-sources_1-0" class="comp mntl-article-sources__citation-sources mntl-citation-sources mntl-sources" data-tracking-container="true"&gt; &lt;ol class="mntl-sources__content"&gt;
&lt;li class="mntl-sources__source" id="citation-1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Serrano MA, Cañada J, Moreno JC, Gurrea G. &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.scitotenv.2016.09.102" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Solar ultraviolet doses and vitamin D in a northern mid-latitude&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;em&gt;Sci Total Environ&lt;/em&gt;. 2017;574:744-750. doi:10.1016/j.scitotenv.2016.09.102&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="mntl-sources__source" id="citation-2"&gt;&lt;p&gt;National Institutes of Health, Office of Dietary Supplements. &lt;a href="https://ods.od.nih.gov/factsheets/VitaminD-HealthProfessional/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Vitamin D fact sheet for health professionals&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="mntl-sources__source" id="citation-3"&gt;&lt;p&gt;U.S Preventive Services Task Force. &lt;a href="https://www.uspreventiveservicestaskforce.org/uspstf/recommendation/vitamin-d-deficiency-screening" class="pseudoStyle" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Vitamin D deficiency in adults: screening. Final recommendation statement&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="mntl-sources__source" id="citation-7"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cleveland Clinic. &lt;a href="https://my.clevelandclinic.org/health/diseases/15050-vitamin-d-vitamin-d-deficiency" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Vitamin D deficiency&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="mntl-sources__source" id="citation-5"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Delrue C, Speeckaert R, Delanghe JR, Speeckaert MM. &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.3390/ijms24032924" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Vitamin D deficiency: an underestimated factor in sepsis&lt;/a&gt;? &lt;em&gt;Int J Mol Sci&lt;/em&gt;. 2023;24(3):2924. doi:10.3390/ijms24032924&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="mntl-sources__source" id="citation-4"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gokce N, Basgoz N, Kenanoglu S, et al. &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.15167/2421-4248/jpmh2022.63.2S3.2765" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;An overview of the genetic aspects of hair loss and its connection with nutrition&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;em&gt;J Prev Med Hyg&lt;/em&gt;. 2022;63(2 Suppl 3):E228-E238. doi:10.15167/2421-4248/jpmh2022.63.2S3.2765&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="mntl-sources__source" id="citation-6"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Seth I, Lim B, Cevik J, et al. &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.jpra.2024.01.006" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Impact of nutrition on skin wound healing and aesthetic outcomes: a comprehensive narrative review&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;em&gt;JPRAS Open&lt;/em&gt;. 2024;39:291-302. doi:10.1016/j.jpra.2024.01.006&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id="author-bio_1-0" class="comp author-bio bio--expanded"&gt;
&lt;p class="author-bio__bio-text"&gt;
&lt;span class="author-bio__bio-title"&gt;By &lt;a href="https://www.verywellhealth.com/fran-kritz-5081944"&gt;Fran Kritz&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Kritz is a healthcare reporter with a focus on health policy. She is a former staff writer for U.S. News and World Report.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id="trust-ribbon_1-0" class="comp trust-ribbon trust-ribbon-expandable-block"&gt; 
&lt;div class="loc expandable-content"&gt;&lt;div id="trust-ribbon__feedback-block_1-0" class="comp trust-ribbon__feedback-block article-feedback mntl-article-feedback"&gt; 
&lt;div class="article-feedback__success-section js-success-section is-hidden"&gt;
&lt;p class="article-feedback__heading"&gt;Thanks for your feedback!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="article-feedback__feedback-section js-feedback-section is-hidden"&gt;
&lt;p class="article-feedback__heading"&gt;What is your feedback?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;button id="helpful-button_1-0" class="comp helpful-button mntl-button article-feedback__feedback-button"&gt; Helpful
&lt;/button&gt;
&lt;button id="report-error-button_1-0" class="comp report-error-button mntl-button article-feedback__feedback-button"&gt; Report an Error
&lt;/button&gt;
&lt;button id="other-button_1-0" class="comp other-button mntl-button article-feedback__feedback-button"&gt; Other
&lt;/button&gt;
&lt;svg class="icon icon-x close-button"&gt;
&lt;use xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xlink:href="#icon-x" href="#icon-x"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;
&lt;/svg&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Verywell Health</author><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 17:46:30 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMidEFVX3lxTFBQRWoyWmNiV0JZbUVqVFhVWmpMRnByUWxFYWFBc1o2eTlWdU1RZzM2ZzFwdVV6R0dGSlNtXzUyd0VBVEdEbzdnbG5FZ0FXQnlXY0VQYUJaSUpjenQxdm1qb0JjWjczWm1rTWg4QUVVbnlCUDFD</guid></item><item><title>Ambio的ibogaine治疗计划针对MS ，其他疾病-今日多发性硬化症新闻 | Ambio’s ibogaine therapy program targets MS, other conditions - Multiple Sclerosis News Today</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMitgFBVV95cUxNYVNTaEloTEdtbktiQmtBOFFsVVRNN2tGbFc2bTgxSkN2aTRLU1I4SkduNW1rWkFPbEI3dHcyTkVPZ1BKbkJKS2VhS0dxMWNsakMxaHUySzh5eThUWk14RUt1YjlsYjh0UGZHZ3NSOXdfR0ZBWEd1QVY2Y0RLN0k0azlYTk5hWm04UGxSYU1DcEtWWFJkdURuRzhOdVVQdGFyb2VlcnN0SklwVVl4d0NvTGdVOUMxZw?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="pf-content"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://ambio.life"&gt;Ambio Life Sciences&lt;/a&gt; has launched a clinical program to test ibogaine — an experimental, naturally occurring psychedelic — for neurodegenerative conditions such as &lt;a href="https://multiplesclerosisnewstoday.com/multiple-sclerosis-overview/"&gt;multiple sclerosis&lt;/a&gt; (MS). The program aims to offer therapeutic support in a safe, medically supervised setting.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now open to the public following a soft launch earlier this year, this &lt;a href="https://ambio.life/personal-change/ibogaine-regeneration/"&gt;neuroregenerative program&lt;/a&gt; is designed for patients considering ibogaine as part of their care strategy. It has already treated 30 patients in a dedicated treatment facility.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In addition to MS, the program is available for people with &lt;a href="https://parkinsonsnewstoday.com/what-is-parkinsons-disease/"&gt;Parkinson’s disease&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://alsnewstoday.com/what-is-als/"&gt;amyotrophic lateral sclerosis&lt;/a&gt;, stroke, traumatic brain injury, and other conditions. The goal is to explore ibogaine as a potential supportive treatment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“We’re creating a safe, structured environment for people with these conditions to explore ibogaine, and we could be on the cusp of uncovering how ibogaine may support brain healing in ways we don’t fully understand today,” Jonathan Dickinson, Ambio’s CEO and co-founder, said in a &lt;a href="https://www.globenewswire.com/news-release/2025/06/09/3095856/0/en/Ambio-Life-Sciences-Launches-World-s-First-Clinical-Ibogaine-Program-for-Patients-With-Neurodegenerative-Conditions.html"&gt;company press release&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h3&gt;Lesion volume reduced, symptoms eased in 2 patients&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In MS, damage to the brain and spinal cord results in a wide range of symptoms, including vision problems, poor coordination and balance, fatigue, and pain. Available treatments can prevent new damage from occurring and slow down the progression of disease, but they generally cannot help patients regain lost functions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ibogaine, currently illegal in the U.S., is a psychedelic found in the root bark of the African iboga plant. It works by acting on receptors — for example, NMDA and opioid receptors — that play a role in brain activity. Ibogaine also increases the production of molecules that help nerve cells survive and form new connections.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote class="bio-blockquote bio-blockquote--align-left"&gt;
  &lt;p class="bio-blockquote-text"&gt;As both a clinician and an MS patient, I’ve experienced the complexity of these conditions and the limitations of traditional treatments. The relief some patients are reporting so far is motivating, including improvements in eyesight, mobility, and neuropathic pain.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a &lt;a href="https://www.frontiersin.org/journals/immunology/articles/10.3389/fimmu.2025.1535782/full"&gt;recent report&lt;/a&gt;, ibogaine reduced lesion volume and eased symptoms of MS in two patients — one with &lt;a href="https://multiplesclerosisnewstoday.com/relapsing-remitting-multiple-sclerosis-rrms/"&gt;relapsing–remitting MS&lt;/a&gt; and the other with &lt;a href="https://multiplesclerosisnewstoday.com/secondary-progressive-multiple-sclerosis-spms/"&gt;secondary progressive MS&lt;/a&gt;. Following treatment, both patients also showed signs of improvement on brain scans suggestive of new connections between nerve cells and rewiring of brain circuitry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“As both a clinician and an MS patient, I’ve experienced the complexity of these conditions and the limitations of traditional treatments,” Lyndsey Ryan, Ambio’s chief therapy officer, said. “The relief some patients are reporting so far is motivating, including improvements in eyesight, mobility, and neuropathic pain.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In Ambio’s program, a loading dosing is optimized for tolerability, followed by extended microdosing (taking very small doses). Weekly group sessions offer ongoing support through and beyond the treatment period. In addition to providing safe access to ibogaine, the company will also collect real-world data.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While the program does not promise a cure, it gives patients a chance to participate in an emerging therapy that could support better quality of life and provide insights for future research.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Every participant is helping us learn what’s possible,” said Ryan, who is also the program’s lead therapist.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h3&gt;Ibogaine relived ‘MS hug’ for patient&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Country music artist Clay Walker and NFL Hall of Famer Brett Favre were among the first to try the program. Both were diagnosed with neurodegenerative diseases — Walker with MS in 1996, and Favre with Parkinson’s in early 2024.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I was told about ibogaine from a friend who completed the treatment and was blown away by the results,” said Favre. “Since coming to Ambio, I’ve felt a real shift, especially in my sleep and energy.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Walker shared a similar experience. “My journey with ibogaine was extraordinary,” Walker said. “It relieved what we call the ‘&lt;a href="https://multiplesclerosisnewstoday.com/multiple-sclerosis-symptoms/the-ms-hug/"&gt;MS hug&lt;/a&gt;,’ that painful tightness in the abdomen, and gave me clarity, focus, and real relief from stress. My hope is that ibogaine can one day complement the treatments MS patients already rely on.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ambio is working with Dalhousie University in Halifax, Canada, to explore how ibogaine works in people with neurodegenerative diseases, namely how it impacts biomarkers of neuroinflammation and disease models of Parkinson’s, MS, and stroke.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“This work may help define what ibogaine treatments for neurodegenerative diseases could look like in the future,” Dickinson said. “Even if we don’t fully know what shape that will take yet, preclinical research and each patient’s experience brings us closer to understanding how ibogaine may support neurorepair.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Multiple Sclerosis News Today</author><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 17:43:18 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMitgFBVV95cUxNYVNTaEloTEdtbktiQmtBOFFsVVRNN2tGbFc2bTgxSkN2aTRLU1I4SkduNW1rWkFPbEI3dHcyTkVPZ1BKbkJKS2VhS0dxMWNsakMxaHUySzh5eThUWk14RUt1YjlsYjh0UGZHZ3NSOXdfR0ZBWEd1QVY2Y0RLN0k0azlYTk5hWm04UGxSYU1DcEtWWFJkdURuRzhOdVVQdGFyb2VlcnN0SklwVVl4d0NvTGdVOUMxZw</guid></item><item><title>“停经”是真实的吗？ -《经济学人》 | Is the “manopause” real? - The Economist</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiiAFBVV95cUxQbFNMWVl6UFhVZVlhSWpEU3d6YXJrQ1VrWVE4OUxwZmdSd2d4Wm80UVk2MXlESUgzaUZuS3FSQUlkQV9zZVd1MmFiQWxtNnB4QVZBQnM5TlZtRlp0VmdnUnhlV1U4UElPTUxRMkhhVGhGbllLRGJrell1cGRGNmloT29HTUN5VEox?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="css-p6fe6o efq1yh21"&gt;&lt;p data-component="paragraph" class="css-1l5amll e1y9q0ei0"&gt;&lt;span data-caps="initial"&gt;H&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt;OT FLUSHES&lt;/small&gt;; insomnia; joint pains; loss of libido: for many women, the menopause is no fun. Why exactly women become infertile decades before they die is a &lt;a href="https://www.economist.com/science-and-technology/2017/01/14/intergenerational-conflict-may-explain-the-menopause"&gt;much-debated mystery&lt;/a&gt; in evolutionary biology. Besides humans, the only other mammals whose females experience so early a menopause in the wild seem to be some species of whale.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Economist</author><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 17:42:55 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiAFBVV95cUxQbFNMWVl6UFhVZVlhSWpEU3d6YXJrQ1VrWVE4OUxwZmdSd2d4Wm80UVk2MXlESUgzaUZuS3FSQUlkQV9zZVd1MmFiQWxtNnB4QVZBQnM5TlZtRlp0VmdnUnhlV1U4UElPTUxRMkhhVGhGbllLRGJrell1cGRGNmloT29HTUN5VEox</guid></item></channel></rss>