<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>GNews Health</title><link>https://news.google.com/</link><description></description><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>官员警告波士顿地区可能接触麻疹- WCVB</title><link>https://www.wcvb.com/article/measles-boston-westborough-massachusetts-texas-visitor/69857705</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-content--body-inner"&gt;
										&lt;div class="mobile"&gt;
													



																		&lt;div class="mobile"&gt;
							

&lt;section class="article-headline"&gt;
	
			&lt;p class="article-headline--title"&gt;Health officials warn about potential exposure to measles in Boston, Westborough&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;/section&gt;


							&lt;div class="article-branding"&gt;
						&lt;img data-src="https://kubrick.htvapps.com/htv-prod-media.s3.amazonaws.com/htv_default_image/site_branding/wcvb.png" class="lazyload lazyload-in-view branding" alt="WCVB logo"&gt;
								&lt;p class="article-headline--publish-date border-left"&gt;
			Updated: 11:17 AM EST Dec 24, 2025
		&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;a href="/article/hearst-television-news-policy-statements/14471973" class="editorial-standards border-left"&gt;Editorial Standards &lt;span class="info-icon"&gt;ⓘ&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;

							

&lt;p class="article-authors"&gt;
		&lt;/p&gt;


						&lt;/div&gt;
					&lt;/div&gt;
	
						
					&lt;p class="article-content--body-teaser"&gt;
						
					&lt;/p&gt;
	
					&lt;p class="article-content--body-text-raw"&gt;
						Massachusetts health officials issued a warning Wednesday about possible exposure to measles in locations visited by an infected tourist earlier this month. According to the Department of Public Health, a visitor from Texas arrived in the area on Dec. 11 on Airlines flight 2384, and departed on JetBlue flight 117 on Dec. 12. Potential exposures to the infected traveler may have occurred at:Logan Airport Terminal B, Boston, MA, 2:30 p.m.-4:45 p.m., Thursday, Dec. 11DoubleTree by Hilton Hotel Boston-Westborough, Westborough, MA, between 3:30 p.m., Thursday, Dec. 11, and 9 p.m., Friday, Dec. 12Logan Airport Terminal C, Boston, MA, 6 p.m.-11:30 p.m., Friday, Dec. 12Anyone who may have been exposed and begins to develop symptoms is advised to  call their healthcare provider before visiting an office, clinic, or emergency department."Measles is very contagious," DPH officials wrote in a statement. "However, the risk to most people in Massachusetts is low because the vaccination rate in the state is high. People who are not immune and visited any of the locations on the following dates and times may be at risk for developing measles."Video below: Expert 'On the Record' about vaccinesEarly symptoms may occur from one to three weeks after exposure and may resemble a cold. A skin rash follows a few days later. "This case is a reminder that everyone should be vaccinated against measles to protect themselves and others from this highly infectious disease. With multiple measles outbreaks across the country and increased travel around the holidays, now is an important time to ensure that you and your family are protected. Two doses of MMR vaccine are 97% effective at preventing measles and provides protection against mumps and rubella infection," said Dr. Bisola Ojikutu, Commissioner of Public Health for the City of Boston.
					&lt;/p&gt;
	
					&lt;div class="article-content--body-text"&gt;
						&lt;strong class="dateline"&gt;BOSTON —&lt;/strong&gt; 													&lt;p&gt;Massachusetts health officials issued a warning Wednesday about possible exposure to measles in locations visited by an infected tourist earlier this month. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to the Department of Public Health, a visitor from Texas arrived in the area on Dec. 11 on Airlines flight 2384, and departed on JetBlue flight 117 on Dec. 12. Potential exposures to the infected traveler may have occurred at:&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Logan Airport Terminal B, Boston, MA, 2:30 p.m.-4:45 p.m., Thursday, Dec. 11&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;DoubleTree by Hilton Hotel Boston-Westborough, Westborough, MA, between 3:30 p.m., Thursday, Dec. 11, and 9 p.m., Friday, Dec. 12&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Logan Airport Terminal C, Boston, MA, 6 p.m.-11:30 p.m., Friday, Dec. 12&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Anyone who may have been exposed and begins to develop symptoms is advised to  call their healthcare provider before visiting an office, clinic, or emergency department.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Measles is very contagious," DPH officials wrote in a statement. "However, the risk to most people in Massachusetts is low because the vaccination rate in the state is high. People who are not immune and visited any of the locations on the following dates and times may be at risk for developing measles."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Video below: Expert 'On the Record' about vaccines&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p id="cream-inline-rec" class="cream-inline hidden"&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Early symptoms may occur from one to three weeks after exposure and may resemble a cold. A skin rash follows a few days later. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"This case is a reminder that everyone should be vaccinated against measles to protect themselves and others from this highly infectious disease. With multiple measles outbreaks across the country and increased travel around the holidays, now is an important time to ensure that you and your family are protected. Two doses of MMR vaccine are 97% effective at preventing measles and provides protection against mumps and rubella infection," said Dr. Bisola Ojikutu, Commissioner of Public Health for the City of Boston.&lt;/p&gt;

							
											&lt;/div&gt;
	
	
						
						
														&lt;/div&gt;
	
																&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>WCVB</author><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilwFBVV95cUxNMW1IWEFDTU5xZE9QSGo3NEJhX2dYN09zUUMyUzNHdzFjbWIwVko4NWJZRGZINV9jZzA2eVRUcW1hdkVrbUhUcUFzTmtWWS1HMkVLaXUxakRiWDBfMko0WGpSUGxDWmZ0bHd6Ti1SV3ZsZXZqRTZzQWlKSF9HYWxRYnFTZEh5Z0pXTFdHU3pWcUpKYk94NWtz</guid></item><item><title>马萨诸塞州卫生官员警告可能在多个地点接触麻疹- NBC波士顿</title><link>https://www.nbcboston.com/news/local/measles-in-massachusetts-health-officials-warn-of-possible-exposure-in-boston-westborough/3867121/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-content rich-text"&gt;
									
					
&lt;p&gt;Health officials are issuing a warning about possible &lt;a href="https://www.mass.gov/info-details/measles"&gt;measles&lt;/a&gt; exposure in multiple locations in Massachusetts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The state Department of Public Health announced Wednesday that an out-of-state visitor who spent time in Boston and Westborough earlier this month was diagnosed with measles and visited multiple locations which could have resulted in other people being exposed to the virus.&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Health officials said the visitor arrived on Dec. 11 at 2:39 p.m. at Boston Logan International Airport on American Airlines flight 2384 from Dallas-Fort Worth, Texas. The visitor stayed at the DoubleTree by Hilton Hotel Boston-Westborough in Westborough and departed the state on Dec. 12 from Logan Airport at 9:19 p.m. on JetBlue flight 117 to Las Vegas, Nevada.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The state is now working with the U.S. Centers for Disease Control and Prevention and local partners to identify and notify anyone who might have been exposed to measles from this person.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Measles is a highly contagious, airborne disease, which has increased significantly in the United States because of the unfortunate decrease in vaccination rates. It is also a preventable disease,” said Robbie Goldstein, the state's public health commissioner. “This current situation serves as an important reminder of the critical role vaccination plays in protecting our communities. While Massachusetts has not had a measles case this year, 2025 saw the highest number of nationwide cases in more than a decade – nearly 2,000 in 44 jurisdictions, and sadly, three deaths. Fifteen years ago, measles had been considered eliminated in the United States, but that tremendous progress is at risk."&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Measles is very contagious. However, the risk to most people in Massachusetts is low because the vaccination rate in the state is high. People who are not immune and visited any of the locations on the following dates and times may be at risk for developing measles:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul class="wp-block-list"&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Logan Airport Terminal B, Boston, 2:30-4:45 p.m., on Thursday, Dec. 11&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;DoubleTree by Hilton Hotel Boston-Westborough, Westborough, between 3:30 p.m. on Thursday, Dec. 11 and 9 p.m. on Friday, Dec. 12&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;Logan Airport Terminal C, Boston, 6-11:30 p.m., on Friday Dec. 12&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Those who could have been exposed and begin to develop symptoms of measles should call their healthcare provider before visiting an office, clinic, or emergency department. Visiting a healthcare facility may put others at risk and should be avoided if possible. Anyone who has had measles in the past or has received two doses of the Measles, Mumps, and Rubella (MMR) vaccine is unlikely to develop measles even if exposed.&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;div class="recirc-module"&gt;
			&lt;h3 class="recirc__heading"&gt;Local&lt;/h3&gt;
			&lt;p class="recirc__subheading"&gt;In-depth news coverage of the Greater Boston and New England area.&lt;/p&gt;
											
											
					&lt;/div&gt;
	
&lt;p&gt;Early symptoms of measles occur seven to 21 days after exposure and may resemble a cold, with fever, cough, runny nose, and red eyes. A rash occurs on the skin two to four days after the initial symptoms develop. The rash usually appears first on the head and then moves downward. It typically lasts a few days and then disappears in the same order. People with measles could be contagious up to four days before the rash appears and for four days after the rash appears.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“This case is a reminder that everyone should be vaccinated against measles to protect themselves and others from this highly infectious disease. With multiple measles outbreaks across the country and increased travel around the holidays, now is an important time to ensure that you and your family are protected,” said Dr. Bisola Ojikutu, Boston's commissioner of public health.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Health care providers who suspect they might have measles are urged to call the Department of Public Health at 617-983-6800 for recommendations and testing guidance. Providers in Boston should call the Boston Public Health Commission at 617-534-5611.&lt;/p&gt;

									&lt;/div&gt;
												&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>NBC Boston</author><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 14:33:43 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi0AFBVV95cUxNcmVoVV9oRENIbHg4dDVLU1JwNlVMM3Rqa0hKZUZlVEJsandRaHBkQUN2ZGhlMTJ3alBIbVB6cTY5RE1RcXBUUy1CSUl1SnFyYmF4OFJVb3VaZzVKam1Cc284TkpqTXBkenRnOGIyRTVEeTUwU093aEFjYV9XNGc1OW9rWHZIU05OSjY5VTFYUUZMYk1VbDdQalIwMTQxNWlLWU5Fdm84TzIySTFhMWhaRmZaMWtWSzJhM0R1TERZbEl5Y1llZWZhVElIREdsZnpi0gHYAUFVX3lxTE9tMnFTUlBYNnQ3NHFmOUVYX0Y0dG51MXVnMDdsSzR1YWtWaENLS1k0QjFSV2dNcEcyLWhkLUpYcGNRV1pRV0J1NGtTUEZnenFwNWVBTjBUbkZhQWJoTld1VnZrRklJZGF1N3NORmJlQ3lXX3pORWFyemxZcGhaR0VfNllHMFJlVDBpYThHeWN3OThCUEVaMzgzbTdPZjhPX2tfbHlSVWFBcDNqYmZmZ2NaRmwtQktIMFphaVF4TFZqYzd0X3g1RVZvb200R1dCU0dfVTNFYUNFVg</guid></item><item><title>茶或咖啡对骨骼有益吗？ -《华盛顿邮报》</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/wellness/2025/12/24/tea-coffee-bones-osteoporosis/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="FYE4SUEE6ZGADAZEGNJFJ6UEIE" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Both &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/wellness/interactive/2022/coffee-vs-tea-nutrition-health/" target="_blank"&gt;tea and coffee&lt;/a&gt; have various health benefits, but tea may come out slightly on top when it comes to the health of your bones, a recent study suggests. And too much coffee — five or more cups a day — might have a negative effect on your bone health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 12:31:50 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiAFBVV95cUxOV1dUVWVUNmtrX1FHUXlBSFpsV090Vndyc2NwT1hDT1FkR1ppRXg3S0hWdUxZanpSWFFqMV9fOHktcmJJVjZDcS1KVVFUWEZDd2RaT1ZGRkpoZFNHQklDajdGbVNGWWRRaFE1OXIxa1NCREV6UkdrNXBMcHVIWGdfV21EWTQwRGY3</guid></item><item><title>多动症是“超级大国”吗？一项新研究对这种疾病的隐藏优势的看法-女性健康</title><link>https://www.womenshealthmag.com/health/a69811174/adhd-superpower-strengths-study/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div data-journey-body="standard-article" class="article-body-content article-body standard-body-content css-n3hm4j et2g3wt7"&gt;&lt;ul data-node-id="0" class="css-kw9lqy emevuu60"&gt;&lt;li data-node-id="0.0"&gt;&lt;em data-node-id="0.0.0"&gt;In a recent study, people with ADHD were more likely to strongly identify with 10 character strengths, including creativity and intuitiveness, over those without the condition.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-node-id="0.1"&gt;&lt;em data-node-id="0.1.0"&gt;People with ADHD were just as likely as those without the condition to recognize and apply those strengths in everyday life.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-node-id="0.2"&gt;&lt;em data-node-id="0.2.0"&gt;Researchers hope the findings will help people understand the strengths associated with ADHD.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;hr data-node-id="1" class="css-18pb4rg emevuu60"&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="2" class="css-6wxqfj emevuu60"&gt;When you have a condition like &lt;a href="https://www.womenshealthmag.com/health/a61015577/adhd-in-elite-athletes/" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.womenshealthmag.com/health/a61015577/adhd-in-elite-athletes/" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="attention-deficit/hyperactivity disorder" data-node-id="2.1" class="body-link css-7bauu1 emevuu60"&gt;attention-deficit/hyperactivity disorder&lt;/a&gt;, it can be easy to focus on the downsides. But new research suggests that having ADHD comes with some upsides too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="3" class="css-6wxqfj emevuu60"&gt;The study, which was published in &lt;em data-node-id="3.1"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cambridge.org/core/journals/psychological-medicine/article/role-of-psychological-strengths-in-positive-life-outcomes-in-adults-with-adhd/69B7CE4D4D9F370214929ABF53701567" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.cambridge.org/core/journals/psychological-medicine/article/role-of-psychological-strengths-in-positive-life-outcomes-in-adults-with-adhd/69B7CE4D4D9F370214929ABF53701567" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="Psychological Medicine" data-node-id="3.1.0" class="body-link css-7bauu1 emevuu60"&gt;Psychological Medicine&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;, discovered that people with ADHD were more likely to highlight certain character traits than those without the condition—and they were equally as likely to apply those strengths in their lives. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="4" class="css-6wxqfj emevuu60"&gt;The findings offer a more balanced way to think about an ADHD diagnosis. Here’s what the study found, and the key takeaways.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="6" class="body-tip css-mtq1aa emevuu60"&gt;&lt;strong data-node-id="6.0"&gt;Meet the experts&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;a href="https://www.radboudumc.nl/en/people/martine-hoogman" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.radboudumc.nl/en/people/martine-hoogman" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="Martine Hoogman, PhD" data-node-id="6.2" class="body-link css-7bauu1 emevuu60"&gt;Martine Hoogman, PhD&lt;/a&gt;, is the senior study author and assistant professor at Radboud University. Hillary Ammon, PsyD, is a clinical psychologist at the &lt;a href="https://cawewtherapy.com/" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-node-id="6.4" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://cawewtherapy.com/" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="Center for Anxiety &amp;amp; Women's Emotional Wellness" class="body-link css-7bauu1 emevuu60"&gt;Center for Anxiety &amp;amp; Women's Emotional Wellness&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;a href="https://researchportal.bath.ac.uk/en/persons/luca-hargitai/" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://researchportal.bath.ac.uk/en/persons/luca-hargitai/" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="Luca D Hargitai" data-node-id="6.6" class="body-link css-7bauu1 emevuu60"&gt;Luca D Hargitai&lt;/a&gt;, is the study co-author and post-graduate researcher at University of Bath.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="what-did-the-study-find" data-node-id="7" class="body-h2 css-1q3hln2 emevuu60"&gt;&lt;strong data-node-id="7.0"&gt;What did the study find?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="8" class="css-6wxqfj emevuu60"&gt;For the study, researchers asked 200 adults with ADHD and 200 adults without ADHD to examine how strongly they identify with 25 positive characteristics, like humor, creativity, and spontaneity. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="9" class="css-6wxqfj emevuu60"&gt;People with ADHD were more likely to strongly endorse 10 strengths they had over those without the condition. Those included:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-node-id="10" class="css-kw9lqy emevuu60"&gt;&lt;li data-node-id="10.0"&gt;       Hyperfocus (the ability to deeply concentrate on things that interested them)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-node-id="10.1"&gt;       Humor&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-node-id="10.2"&gt;       Creativity&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-node-id="10.3"&gt;       Spontaneity&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-node-id="10.4"&gt;       Intuitiveness&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="11" class="css-6wxqfj emevuu60"&gt;While having ADHD comes with potential challenges, the researchers discovered that people with the condition were just as likely as those without ADHD to recognize and apply their strengths in everyday life. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="12" class="css-6wxqfj emevuu60"&gt;“People with ADHD asked me to dive into this topic as a scientist,” says &lt;a href="https://www.radboudumc.nl/en/people/martine-hoogman" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.radboudumc.nl/en/people/martine-hoogman" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="Martine Hoogman, PhD" data-node-id="12.1" class="body-link css-7bauu1 emevuu60"&gt;Martine Hoogman, PhD&lt;/a&gt;, senior study author and assistant professor at Radboud University. “There are many claims about positive aspects, strengths—superpowers?—of ADHD on the web, but the scientific base is thin.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="13" class="css-6wxqfj emevuu60"&gt;There’s a growing push to look at the positive sides of ADHD, adds &lt;a href="https://researchportal.bath.ac.uk/en/persons/luca-hargitai/" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://researchportal.bath.ac.uk/en/persons/luca-hargitai/" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="Luca D Hargitai" data-node-id="13.1" class="body-link css-7bauu1 emevuu60"&gt;Luca D Hargitai&lt;/a&gt;, study co-author and post-graduate researcher at University of Bath. “People are recognizing that, while this neurodevelopmental condition is associated with difficulties in various domains, there may also be strengths associated with ADHD,” she says. “Much of the research in this area has focused on creativity and divergent thinking.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="why-does-this-matter" data-node-id="14" class="body-h2 css-1q3hln2 emevuu60"&gt;&lt;strong data-node-id="14.0"&gt;Why does this matter?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="15" class="css-6wxqfj emevuu60"&gt;This can help people with ADHD look at their diagnosis in a different way, says Hillary Ammon, PsyD, a clinical psychologist at the &lt;a href="https://cawewtherapy.com/" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-node-id="15.1" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://cawewtherapy.com/" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="Center for Anxiety &amp;amp; Women's Emotional Wellness" class="body-link css-7bauu1 emevuu60"&gt;Center for Anxiety &amp;amp; Women's Emotional Wellness&lt;/a&gt;. “For years, children and adults with ADHD were often encouraged to fit into a neurotypical ‘mold’ in school and in work settings,” she says. “As such, it likely worsened symptoms of depression or anxiety, as the ADHD brain is not wired the same way—it has different strengths and limitations.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="16" class="css-6wxqfj emevuu60"&gt;But the findings suggest that adults with ADHD who are aware of their strengths and actually use them have higher confidence and quality of life as a result, Ammon says. “This is novel and important research as clinicians working with children, teens, and adults with ADHD can start to increase the focus on the individuals’ strengths, some of which may be unique to individuals with ADHD, as opposed to only exploring how to compensate for their deficits associated with ADHD,” she says. “By doing so, I suspect this will aid in improving confidence in individuals with ADHD.”   &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="what-should-people-take-away-from-this" data-node-id="18" class="body-h2 css-1q3hln2 emevuu60"&gt;&lt;strong data-node-id="18.0"&gt;What should people take away from this?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="19" class="css-6wxqfj emevuu60"&gt;Hoogman says she hopes the findings will help people understand the strengths associated with ADHD. “My other studies show that adults with ADHD frequently, in addition to their deficits, also experience benefits from their ADHD characteristics,” she says. “If we take a more balanced approach towards ADHD, acknowledging challenges and benefits, this may lead to increased well-being for people with ADHD and lowering stigma related to ADHD in our society.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-journey-blur="partial" data-ad-exclude="true" class="css-19m4yzp e1jy25xv0"&gt;&lt;div class="css-sfzxfp ev8dhu59"&gt;&lt;span class="css-3mrz81 ev8dhu51"&gt;&lt;img src="https://hips.hearstapps.com/rover/profile_photos/ea27d1a6-ecd9-4da8-b2a7-049a03b4ab93_1528214135.file?fill=1:1&amp;amp;resize=120:*" alt="Headshot of Korin Miller" title="Headshot of Korin Miller" decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="css-o0wq4v ev8dhu53"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="css-1dsojn8 ev8dhu55"&gt;&lt;p class="css-1y37fga ev8dhu54"&gt;Korin Miller is a freelance writer specializing in general wellness, sexual health and relationships, and lifestyle trends, with work appearing in Men’s Health, Women’s Health, Self, Glamour, and more. She has a master’s degree from American University, lives by the beach, and hopes to own a teacup pig and taco truck one day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-ad-exclude="true" id="journey-inline" class="css-ciejky e1ye6jr30"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Women's Health</author><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiAFBVV95cUxObl84X2dVenRqY01vcHQyczMzYTlaamh1REZvMnRYaHZRbGZXZmhzaVRic0RyS0QyaGJXSXlWMWtiMXR4bjMwZXNNNEFxcmZ2eHhiMXhneGU0NHVNZndDR3lDRk95WFlBeWVqYUtEUms2ekg1RENjRk5uS2dJa3hWMlJiNUZ4N0Yx</guid></item><item><title>随着疫苗接种率下降，医生担心破伤风病例会上升- NBC新闻</title><link>https://www.nbcnews.com/health/kids-health/tetanus-cases-rise-vaccine-rates-down-dtap-children-shots-rcna244685</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body__content"&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-979779" class="body-graf"&gt;Doctors are worried about even a small uptick in the terrible infection, often called lockjaw. Symptoms, which can take &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/tetanus/hcp/clinical-overview/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;three to 21 days to appear&lt;/a&gt;, include muscle spasms that make it difficult to breathe. As the infection takes hold, a patient’s jaw clenches, forcing the face into what appears to be a wide smile, and the back muscles contort into a painful arch.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-6f7325" class="body-graf"&gt;“It looks terrible,” said Dr. Mobeen Rathore, chief of pediatric infectious diseases and immunology at the University of Florida College of Medicine-Jacksonville.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-5f8dc7" class="body-graf"&gt;Tetanus bacteria live in soil and manure. An infection can occur from a puncture wound, and the disease can persist through weeks of medical care.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-fae9cf" class="body-graf"&gt;Treatment can be arduous and costly. A 6-year-old &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/health/kids-health/unvaccinated-boy-almost-died-tetanus-hospital-bill-was-more-800-n981256" target="_blank"&gt;unvaccinated boy in Oregon&lt;/a&gt; racked up almost $1 million in medical bills after he contracted tetanus in 2019, according to a Centers for Disease Control and Prevention case report.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-eb11cd" class="body-graf"&gt;Rathore compared the cost of vaccines to the cost of intensive care.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-7f9aac" class="body-graf"&gt;“It’s not even pennies to dollars; it’s pennies to hundreds of thousands of dollars,” Rathore said. “It’s very expensive.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-74be7c" class="body-graf"&gt;When a 9-year-old unvaccinated patient came to Rathore with muscle spasm in Florida this year, he recognized the signs. He remembered the tetanus wards from his medical school days where patients were cared for in dark and silent isolation. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-fe29b0" class="body-graf"&gt;“The slightest noise would cause many of these patients to go into spasm,” Rathore said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-c55b43" class="body-graf"&gt;Tetanus spasms, which can also be triggered by light (known as “photophobia”), are extremely painful and can constrict the muscles around the airway.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-adb10b" class="body-graf"&gt;Amid the bright lights, loud noises and incessant beeping of the hospital’s intensive care unit, the options were limited for minimizing stimulation for Rathore's young patient. The 9-year-old was sedated, intubated and given tetanus immune globulin antibodies and the vaccine to reduce future risk of disease. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-7d45a0" class="body-graf"&gt;The child was hospitalized for 37 days.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-7013b7" class="body-graf"&gt;Dr. Matthew Davis, enterprise physician-in-chief and chief scientific officer at Nemours Children’s Health in Florida and Delaware, said that “it wasn’t until we had widespread vaccination that we saw a decline in cases of tetanus and thereby a reduction in the risk of mortality from it.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-9e939a" class="body-graf"&gt;John Johnson, a vaccination and epidemic response adviser at Doctors Without Borders, works in countries such as the Democratic Republic of the Congo (DRC) where tetanus remains a concern. Last year, there were 540 cases in the DRC, &lt;a href="https://immunizationdata.who.int/global/wiise-detail-page/tetanus-reported-cases-and-incidence?CODE=COD&amp;amp;DISEASE=TTETANUS&amp;amp;YEAR=" target="_blank"&gt;according to the World Health Organization&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-013172" class="body-graf"&gt;“It’s one of those things that’s so stupidly easy to prevent,” Johnson said. “If you see one case of tetanus in the U.S., it’s a shame. There’s no reason we should be seeing this disease anymore.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="anchor-93be9d" class="body-heading"&gt;'My jaw was completely locked shut'&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-db2b3f" class="body-graf"&gt;After the initial series in childhood, a booster dose is recommended every 10 years for adults, although many are unaware of the need. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-73689d" class="body-graf"&gt;Nikki Arellano, 42, hadn't had a tetanus shot since 2010 when she was injured while she was helping her friend set up for a wedding last month. An accident with a metal arch at the altar led to a minor cut on her leg. The following week, she found it difficult to chew during lunch at work because of pain in her jaw. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-8af84a" class="body-graf"&gt;Two days later, she couldn’t open her mouth.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-170eb8" class="body-graf"&gt;“My jaw was completely locked shut,” said Arellano, of Reno, Nevada. “I went to the ER, and they tried to give me a bunch of sedatives and pain medicine and muscle relaxers to get my jaw to open, and nothing was making it open.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-5a1d3d" class="body-graf"&gt;Arellano was diagnosed with tetanus and admitted to the hospital. She was connected to an intravenous pump so she could get antibiotics. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-9f7f34" class="body-graf"&gt;“Every time that it would run out, it was like a really, really loud beeping noise. When that started is when my muscle contractions would pop off,” she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-3b39f1" class="body-graf"&gt;Arellano said her spasms initially started in one arm, then progressed to both arms and then to full body spasms. “It would arch your back really bad, like, it was really, really painful muscle spasms.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-781b05" class="body-graf"&gt;Arellano began to have difficulty swallowing, prompting worries that her airway might become compromised. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-3c3539" class="body-graf"&gt;“It was very scary,” she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-09781e" class="body-graf"&gt;She was hospitalized for nearly a week and is still recovering.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="anchor-db35be" class="body-heading"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Heightened risk with climate change&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-a3a276" class="body-graf"&gt;Natural disasters such as hurricanes, tornadoes and floods are known risk factors for tetanus outbreaks. As people rummage through the wreckage, they are also likelier to be injured by loose nails or broken shards of glass.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-153105" class="body-graf"&gt;“As the Earth warms, there’s already a documented increase in the frequency, intensity and duration of many extreme weather and climate events,” said Kristie Ebi, an epidemiologist and professor of global health at the University of Washington who studies the health effects of climate change. “And as there are more flooding events, then fewer vaccinations for diseases like tetanus means that people would be at greater risk.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-15b0b6" class="body-graf"&gt;Some states that are at highest risk of significant natural disasters, including Florida, Texas and Kansas, are recording notable declines in tetanus vaccination, according to NBC News data. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>NBC News</author><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 10:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMisAFBVV95cUxQeDYwZHdfd0N6ZlFZdkI4QVJ2SEZESVo1U250Nl81QmdLVlV6YzBwM2xmWnBxNk9KaWcxWTg4V1RpbmlqZWF0OGRpV3RfRGxxNVBMTHBEaktpZzFzX1NEbE1xaXljNFR4Tng2T1p1SmRkRmRXWGx5TnBFT1RNSmZrbGoyeV9KTXcxN3A2WFJyVmZUemxuQUxiY3UtdjdkNmVIbjdueWZ1bkNaem5lYnJlU9IBVkFVX3lxTE1ZUHpsNXRJTHNVQXhOMUl0T1FpSGFMaThoLWJFbF92aGozWnA3a19VczFiRnBnSHhCNVV1am5IdlEzaGNJVXFWRmdTRDJtX2VDZThITlh3</guid></item><item><title>减肥药物结束了他们的性生活。它会反弹吗？ -《纽约时报》</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/12/24/well/weight-loss-drugs-ended-their-sex-life-could-it-bounce-back.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The New York Times</author><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 10:00:44 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipwFBVV95cUxOLTFncnVEUVFvZ0VJZ084ZHhLWVpOeWE1QWY0OTVSR3FkNDVJaFB2ZmhudVNQd1A5VTRKTkNEV2JvdG9NRkNEWDFwWEs3Nm9UOW5UWFZWOERxR19FdkRSNVp0TVNiTGVBaU9UNS0tMDV4TWRyX2dvdGNCTnRyVEhBSHZZYWNZaE5vMi1Gd3JBcm9BVTFaRnhjc0NfcmxQdllMOUNnNG05VQ</guid></item><item><title>是什么杀死了世界上最大的鳄鱼之一？对黑醋栗的尸检暗示了一个隐藏的杀手- IFLScience</title><link>https://www.iflscience.com/what-killed-one-of-the-worlds-biggest-crocs-a-necropsy-of-cassisus-suggests-a-hidden-killer-81983</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p data-pasted="true"&gt;Cassius the crocodile cheated death for more than a century until his wild life finally caught up with him last year in Australia. Now, experts dealing with his necroscopy have revealed what ultimately led to the giant's demise.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="piano-gate" id="piano-gate"&gt;&lt;p&gt;The 5.5-metre (nearly 18-foot) saltwater crocodile &lt;a href="https://www.iflscience.com/rip-cassius-worlds-largest-captive-crocodile-dies-at-approximately-110-years-old-76633" target="_blank"&gt;died in November 2024&lt;/a&gt; at the Marineland Melanesia wildlife park on Green Island off the coast of Cairns, where he had been housed for four decades. At the grand age of around 110-120, he was one of the &lt;a href="https://www.iflscience.com/at-123-years-old-henry-is-the-worlds-oldest-known-crocodile-and-hes-an-absolute-unit-76112" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;oldest known crocodiles&lt;/a&gt; in captivity. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Strangely enough, the world-famous reptile had been given the all-clear just a few weeks before his death by veterinarians, who noted he appeared "bright, alert and happy". Then, out of the blue, he passed away. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Speaking to &lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2025-12-12/world-record-crocodile-cassius-taxidermied-new-exhibit/106131178" target="_blank"&gt;ABC News&lt;/a&gt;, the Darwin-based Centre for Crocodile Research says its necropsy revealed that Cassius died of an infection related to an injury he had suffered in the wild more than 40 years ago.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The injury triggered an infection that became sealed inside a tough fibrous capsule, lying dormant for decades. Over time, that protective bubble broke down and eventually ruptured, allowing the infection to swarm through the crocodile’s body.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="trendmd-suggestions" data-pid-resource="RRUGNY3"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr Sally Isberg, Managing Director at the Centre for Crocodile Research, told the media outlet that while so-called fibriscesses are “well-documented” in crocodiles, Cassius’ case was extraordinary due to how long the infection was contained. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="piano-inline"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;With further snooping, the team concluded that the hidden infection may have been linked to an injury sustained in the 1980s when Cassius was struck by a boat propeller, resulting in the loss of his front left leg, part of his snout, and the end of his tail. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“What we didn't know was that the rib cage had also been damaged in that injury," said Dr Isberg.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The reason was that everything was perfectly healed — there were no signs of infection or recent scarring. Upon necropsy, his left rib was distended compared to his right one, so longer," she added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“This is a perfect example of the effect of old age — he was no longer able to continue that fibrous casing around that infection."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span contenteditable="false" draggable="true" class="fr-video fr-deletable fr-fvc fr-dvb fr-draggable"&gt;&lt;iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/-FTIeYNvQpQ?&amp;amp;wmode=opaque&amp;amp;rel=0" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="" class="fr-draggable"&gt;VIDEO&lt;span class="fr-mk"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="fr-mk"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="fr-mk"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="fr-mk"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="fr-mk"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="fr-mk"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="fr-mk"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="fr-mk"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="fr-mk"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="fr-mk"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="fr-mk"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="fr-mk"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="fr-mk"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="fr-mk"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="fr-mk"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cassius was captured in 1984 in the Finniss River near Darwin and transported by road and boat, eventually arriving at Marineland Melanesia in 1987. Owing to his size and power, he was named after Cassius Clay, the birth name of boxer Muhammad Ali.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He was recognized as the world’s largest captive crocodile for some time, according to &lt;a href="https://www.guinnessworldrecords.com/news/2023/8/largest-crocodile-cassius-went-from-terrifying-predator-to-dreamy-eyed-dad-756676" target="_blank"&gt;Guinness World Records&lt;/a&gt;, although the title was snatched by an &lt;a href="https://www.iflscience.com/at-62-meters-lolong-was-the-largest-crocodile-ever-recorded-and-captured-80905" target="_blank"&gt;even larger individual called Lolong&lt;/a&gt; in 2012. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But the legacy of Cassisu lives on. The taxidermied body of the Aussie beast (still missing its left leg and tail tip) has just arrived home to Marineland Melanesia, where it is now on display at a new exhibition.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>IFLScience</author><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 09:17:55 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiwgFBVV95cUxNaWkxWmJIcUVVeG41Yi1FSktvWGxNLUNTZWVnQlQteDJmUVVWcG1yU2hyOXYxYWdkQ042S0RHZmFuZ3piYTY5d2NGY3NCdzUxcWZiLXpHRVBXRVRTdlNQc0RIS0c5WElNRFQwZHhheTJvRzc1TlQweDYtVloyY2NoT2poU245bTlGVWVTMl90aWFVb1JzUVFqenpIWmg5Q0pwWVV4OGo2cmR2QkdEX0xrYmpoblJCS0xZWEdoS0l1YWFfUQ</guid></item><item><title>如果我感染HPV ，我是否更容易患宫颈癌？ -《独立报》</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/health-and-families/hpv-nhs-screening-b2890006.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="sc-jbiisr-0 gIQPHK sc-jbiisr-1" id="main"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="hydrate-root sc-10wlkbs-0" data-component="SupportNSCNative" data-loading="lazy" data-theme-name="base"&gt;&lt;aside class="sc-hez36s-0 dFpFuY"&gt;&lt;div class="sc-hez36s-1 iBibVd"&gt;&lt;h3 data-testid="support-nsc-title" class="sc-hez36s-2 jVZWGn"&gt;Your support helps us to tell the story&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;div class="sc-hez36s-8 juUDRT"&gt;&lt;div class="sc-hez36s-13 cqPbFA"&gt;&lt;div class="sc-aja53j-0 rAFIl sc-hez36s-16 jZSKtc"&gt;&lt;div class="sc-aja53j-6 PdmgT"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="dropdown-with-gradient-collapsed-content-container" class="sc-aja53j-5 eZqxmv"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div data-testid="dropdown-with-gradient-collapsed-content" class="sc-aja53j-4 tawua"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div data-testid="support-nsc-collapsed-content-tablet" class="sc-hez36s-7 gZmYS"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-1uza6dc-0 iCTyfe"&gt;From reproductive rights to climate change to Big Tech, The Independent is on the ground when the story is developing. Whether it's investigating the financials of Elon Musk's pro-Trump PAC or producing our latest documentary, 'The A Word', which shines a light on the American women fighting for reproductive rights, we know how important it is to parse out the facts from the messaging.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-1uza6dc-0 iCTyfe"&gt;At such a critical moment in US history, we need reporters on the ground. Your donation allows us to keep sending journalists to speak to both sides of the story.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-1uza6dc-0 iCTyfe"&gt;The Independent is trusted by Americans across the entire political spectrum. And unlike many other quality news outlets, we choose not to lock Americans out of our reporting and analysis with paywalls. We believe quality journalism should be available to everyone, paid for by those who can afford it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;strong class="sc-1uza6dc-1 cglitp"&gt;Your support makes all the difference.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;button class="sc-aja53j-1 keLMOw sc-aja53j-7 eMEmGu"&gt;&lt;span data-testid="dropdown-with-gradient-dropdown-tablet" class="sc-aja53j-3 dHXFkr"&gt;&lt;span data-action-type="Read more" class="sc-aja53j-2 dcYUYI"&gt;Read more&lt;/span&gt;&lt;svg class="sc-eaj12q-0 hUgQwJ sc-culv3z-0 eifaJK sc-a5wy94-0 hyKPon"&gt;&lt;use href="#ee6613da15642019"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Although most of us will be exposed human papillomavirus (HPV) at some point in our lives, it remains widely misunderstood.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Receiving a positive &lt;a href="/topic/hpv"&gt;HPV&lt;/a&gt; result can be worrying and confusing, yet the link between HPV and cervical cancer is more nuanced than many people realise.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We spoke to Miss Adeola Olaitan, consultant gynaecological oncologist at &lt;a rel="nofollow" target="_blank" href="https://www.hcahealthcare.co.uk/locations/hospitals/the-wellington-hospital"&gt;The Wellington Hospital&lt;/a&gt;, part of HCA Healthcare UK, who explained what HPV is, how it relates to cervical cancer and addressed some common myths around this topic.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="article-im-prompt"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What is HPV?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“HPV is a family of viruses that infect the skin and the mucosal tissue,” explains Olaitan. “There are different subtypes of HPV which are denoted by numbers.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="taboola-mid-article-thumbnails-ii" class="sc-looa6c-0 cPCVUJ"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You can get HPV from any skin-to-skin contact of the genital area, vaginal, anal or oral sex or through sharing sex toys, according to the &lt;a rel="nofollow" target="_blank" href="https://www.nhs.uk/conditions/human-papilloma-virus-hpv/"&gt;NHS website&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most of the time HPV does not cause any problems, highlights the gynaecological oncologist.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“In most cases, HPV is a transient, harmless condition, and most people clear it without even knowing that they had it,” says Olaitan. “It will usually clear naturally within two years.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What is the biggest misconception about HPV?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I think the biggest misconception about HPV is the stigma surrounding it,” says Olaitan. “Because it’s a sexually associated infection, people think it has connotations of promiscuity, which it doesn’t. You can have sex once and get HPV.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Which types of HPV can increase your risk of cervical cancer?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There are over 200 types of HPV, according to &lt;a rel="nofollow" target="_blank" href="https://eveappeal.org.uk/resource/hpv/"&gt;The Eve Appeal&lt;/a&gt;, and they are split into two groups: low-risk HPV and high-risk HPV.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Around 14 types of HPV are considered high risk for cervical cancer and two of these types (HPV 16 and HPV 18) cause about 70 out of 100 (70%) of all cervical cancer cases, according to &lt;a rel="nofollow" target="_blank" href="https://www.cancerresearchuk.org/about-cancer/cervical-cancer/risks-causes"&gt;Cancer Research UK&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“HPV 16 and HPV 18 can infect the cervix, and if the infection persists then they can increase the risk of cervical cancer,” explains Olaitan.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How can you find out if you have HPV?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“There are usually no symptoms of HPV, so if you don’t go to a cervical cancer screening, you won’t know you have it,” says Olaitan. “The knowledge of whether you have HPV or not is only important because it marks people out as having a greater risk of having abnormal cells, which if left undetected or untreated can increase the risk of cervical cancer.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Everyone with a cervix should be invited for screening by the &lt;a href="/topic/nhs"&gt;NHS&lt;/a&gt; every five years from the age 25 to 64, according to the &lt;a rel="nofollow" target="_blank" href="https://www.nhs.uk/tests-and-treatments/cervical-screening/what-is-cervical-screening/"&gt;NHS website&lt;/a&gt;. It also states that during the screening appointment, a small sample of cells is taken from your cervix and the sample is checked for high-risk HPV types that can cause changes to the cells of your cervix.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“If the initial screening finds high-risk HPV, a reflex cytology test would be conducted on the same sample to look for abnormal cells,” explains Olaitan. “If that finds no abnormal cells, you will be told to come back for a screening at a shorter interval. However, if abnormal cells are found you will be referred for a colposcopy to have a closer look at the cervix.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Can protect yourself against HPV?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The HPV vaccine is very effective at protecting people against HPV,” says Olaitan. “It’s typically given to children between the ages of 11 and 13 and is licensed to the age of 45, but it’s less effective the older you are.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“But you can have it even if you’ve been exposed to HPV or you have a current HPV infection, and it gives immunity that’s stronger and longer lasting than natural immunity alone. So, it’s still good to have it, but it’s better to have it when you’re young.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What are some symptoms of cervical cancer to look out for?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The most common symptoms of cervical cancer are bleeding after sex, bleeding in between periods, bleeding after the menopause, or an offensive, persistent vagina discharge,” highlights Olaitan. “Most of the time these symptoms are indicative of benign conditions, but it’s important that they’re not ignored and that you go and get them checked to exclude anything more serious going on.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="taboola-mid-article-thumbnails-iii" class="sc-looa6c-0 cPCVUJ"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What’s the most important thing people should know about HPV and cervical cancer?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Remember that cervical cancer is preventable, and people who go for regular screenings are unlikely to get cancer,” says Olaitan. “&lt;a href="/topic/screening"&gt;Screening&lt;/a&gt; and being vaccinated are two of the most important things you can do for your health.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Independent</author><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 09:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilwFBVV95cUxQT2RfMlZad0k0ejVuOVgyd2REanVRZ25wR0MwWmVJcm9MWW1EWTc4dlh5aEJQaGpMNVRpb0NsMVFHeXBnYklOUl9VdjQtZ2xZYlM1VG5nMHE2QlhSVnNobzUwM0VieWh4WTNZeGRtX25lZEZpOU1mZUQ5bThZdFRoSWpqbkxLNWU4NGdtMU5ER3RIcmotVThz</guid></item><item><title>专栏|询问Eric ：告诉朋友她没有被邀请参加团体旅行？还是让她知道？ -《华盛顿邮报》</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/advice/2025/12/24/asking-eric-cruise-excluding-friend/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="763I6PNCHVFMPEU53KTH3C7CB4" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dear Eric:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i&gt; Three friends and I are planning an eight-day cruise in January.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="WC5FGPYYCZBBRCVAIMKF3TPM3I" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;&lt;i&gt;Two other people found out about the trip and are now coming as well. We are fine with that but are not looking to make it a larger group and I am definitely not looking to turn into the “cruise director” for the group as often seems to happen.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 06:31:52 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijgFBVV95cUxOT3ZRc1RXTC1DZ0VJRUptdWVXMkFvamxOTFlYSHJOc1N5MXo3Qm03c1l0QlFpNUtEVmF5Zl9wSGJaSTdhUm1WZFlONkREX3g0cTB5MTlXbjRUWlVFNHRfb2NoSEFTdGtOZlIxSEdSdDlsSTg0alIzVEZWaldEbUNpdUpfb1hmM051cWR6Qm53</guid></item><item><title>以前未知的脑细胞功能可能改变脊髓损伤治疗- SciTechDaily</title><link>https://scitechdaily.com/previously-unknown-brain-cell-function-could-transform-spinal-cord-injury-treatment/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>SciTechDaily</author><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 06:15:48 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMirgFBVV95cUxPcW9IMGJOZUhhM0l6TzBLVjk1LWZuVGdyRFlTSmNiY1ZkUVl2QkYteUtZVEVjRGtYX0dXRzlubGVPWEFMdGNPTUNYc1dXYllXVV9WYVVrdzB0ejF2cFdoNnFlMjFIMXEycmNNTVBQQkwteDlXbEF5SHBJS00zal9hMkROd1JIOXhCUGFranJMM1ZEOWVZdlRlUllBUUItLVNUZ09ZQWxZSnI2VGd0Y0E</guid></item><item><title>简单的补充剂可显著减少透析患者的严重心脏并发症- SciTechDaily</title><link>https://scitechdaily.com/simple-supplement-dramatically-reduces-serious-heart-complications-in-dialysis-patients/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>SciTechDaily</author><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 05:40:54 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiswFBVV95cUxQMlVMOE1oSTV0UEt6ckpxdzNPd19hMUNMcG5UU3NDTjcyVGtKRTh5V2N1TlZfR2pyaUhnZ1VvSmh2UXN4NUMtQkxrWUpwZ3JUYktkcDNUcEtnR0JwWW9SYmcyME9zUURTcVZLRjdJV0diaVgzaWplTGFQYXk0MmZUUE82dW93dXdvSm1BRFFlQ3daa1o5eG14SDhvMC1JS0V0OExuWHdfZWdWUEE3eGlXYXRrZw</guid></item><item><title>斯坦福大学科学家发现为什么基于mRNA的COVID-19疫苗会导致心肌炎- SciTechDaily</title><link>https://scitechdaily.com/stanford-scientists-discover-why-mrna-based-covid-19-vaccines-can-cause-myocarditis/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>SciTechDaily</author><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 05:05:10 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMirgFBVV95cUxPdjA5QlJXclE4X3lGNXYzaDd5TGJmdE1HUFBudC04REVBaWQ4SVBsNFJ1NWowWEo2aG9tVy1MV3o0c25XbG4yYkdoQVEzcjlYTDZEa2ZleVRQS1BlQkZmdXRJMkluVGZOU1F2NFZPU051NlQ1X1d1c0oxYWVWbElpTmZJVjRwUkx0dW9FZnU0S01iV0VWRVVhRE0tQUZGXzB3b1pqNFhBSVhqUWprb2c</guid></item><item><title>随着呼吸道感染的增加，两人死亡- nationnews.com</title><link>https://nationnews.com/2025/12/24/two-die-as-respiratory-infections-rise/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="tdb-block-inner td-fix-index"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Two people, including a known asthmatic, were hospitalised and died as Barbados recorded a rise in respiratory illness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Those deaths were up to December 12, with the number of new infections ranging from 14 in one week to 24 and then 39.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While respiratory illness is not uncommon at this time of year, the Ministry of Health and Wellness is advising Barbadians to practise good hygiene, especially when interacting with the vulnerable, to reduce the transmission of these viruses.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The statement follows in full:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As is not uncommon at this time of the year, a growing rise in cases of respiratory illness has been noted, especially in adults in Barbados.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Over the past four weeks, numbers ranged from 14 to 24, up to 39 in the week ending December 12, 2025, some of whom have been hospitalised. Among the hospitalised, two acute deaths were recorded up to December 12, one is a known asthmatic.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Expected numbers would be no more than six to eight cases per week. The main causes identified have been the Influenzas (AH3N2 or H1N1 or Influenza B) and the respiratory syncytial virus, RSV. A few cases of COVID-19 and the common-cold virus were also identified.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Ministry of Health and Wellness advises that it is important for Barbadians to continue to practise good respiratory hygiene, especially when interacting with vulnerable persons, including the elderly, as this is the most effective way of reducing the transmission of respiratory viruses. Masks should be worn when visiting healthcare institutions. Masks may be worn by vulnerable persons in crowded areas.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These practices also include washing hands with soap and water for at least 20 seconds and drying them with disposable tissue. If soap and water are not available, the use of an alcohol-based hand sanitiser is recommended.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Health officials also advise people to keep unwashed hands away from the eyes, nose and mouth, and to generally avoid touching these areas as germs can enter the body this way.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Ministry also reminds the public to cover the nose and mouth with tissue when coughing or sneezing. Alternatively, persons should cough or sneeze into the inner side of the elbow. Used tissues should be discarded in a bin or a tied plastic bag.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Providers are being asked to check oxygen saturations in ill persons, especially those with asthma, and refer those with low saturations. Providers are also reminded to obtain Nasopharyngeal swabs to verify the infecting agent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As in prior years, persons at risk for severe illness from influenza illness (persons with asthma, diabetes, or other NCDs) are advised to take their maintenance medications as prescribed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>nationnews.com</author><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 04:27:52 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMifkFVX3lxTFAzaGlSNHpZSVkySmJGNkpFUk5YemNLQkZSaVdoQjdmR3hHT0o3VExyM0FMTFJyOEhKSVZEUEV4RG1kYncyV2tJb3ByQnRvOUtJdGt3Z3hHRkNERFg5czh6VVJSbWMtZ3BaMjBaVzJKUU44OF9fNjZSdjAyY0ZTZw</guid></item><item><title>你的大脑年龄在五个不同的阶段，新的研究表明-华尔街日报</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/health/wellness/brain-stages-aging-five-study-nature-a015101e</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Wall Street Journal</author><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 04:00:23 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiAFBVV95cUxOTmczTV83LXBBRm1sTG1ZWl9OdjVRRkczR01MQVZEeF9PYW1UTG1zQ0ZqTWRSZzB1RmxQSG9KYTlMcWlFbGFRb3FDNnhvVXhLaU80X0pmaVZraWRKU25UeElWRjlWajBBazVuSnF3UTlJRnlfX19SbV9oYjI0SFdZZTRUTTk0d1Fw</guid></item><item><title>关于飙升的“冬季呕吐虫”及其传染性新变种- Axios的须知事项</title><link>https://www.axios.com/2025/12/24/norovirus-winter-vomiting-bug-variant-symptoms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Axios</author><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 02:03:26 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihgFBVV95cUxORWh2SllPS19RSTUzUHZ3UldrUUpWLTk2M1VNUTU2eTU5Vkl3UWRhMzFhemhTT21QQVRlM0M4blVoVE04NHNEVDBNNjc2X3dmN3RkVkZMSGkwVTdtM19fZlJTVDZpWWVTMldJWGZIUkVTUkwzNzUtNnZaMUw0VW5HNjJPR2Zudw</guid></item><item><title>新的流感变异袭击南加州，引起公共卫生专家的担忧- ABC7洛杉矶</title><link>https://abc7.com/post/new-flu-variant-hits-southern-california-raises-concerns-among-public-health-experts/18310392/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="xvlfx ZRifP TKoO eaKKC EcdEg bOdfO qXhdi NFNeu UyHES " data-testid="prism-article-body"&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao MvWXB TjIXL aGjvy ebVHC "&gt;&lt;span class="oyrPY qlwaB AGxeB  "&gt;LOS ANGELES (KABC) -- &lt;/span&gt;Holiday travel is in full swing and flu cases are ramping up. Some experts are pretty worried about a new flu variant making its way to Southern California.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;So now is the time to take the steps to protect you and your loved ones.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Many schools across the nation closed early for winter break because of an onslaught of illness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Mother of two, Audrey Garrett, says flu-like symptoms hit her family hard.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;"We actually are just coming back from being sick. He caught a fever. My daughter had that nasty cough, you know that honking cough at night," Garrett said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;"Last year was a pretty bad seasonal flu year for Los Angeles, so it is scary to hear that this year might be worse," Dr. Dawn Tereshita said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Dr. Tereshita monitors acute communicable disease at L.A. County's Department of Public Health. She warns of an emerging H3N2 flu variant that's difficult for our immune systems to recognize.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;"This subclade K is new," Dr. Tereshita said. "We don't know what's going to happen yet, but since it is circulating pretty widely, we are watching it very carefully."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;The new variant isn't a match for this season's flu vaccine, but experts believe a flu shot will still help reduce the risk of severe illness, including hospitalization and death.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;"Any reason to not go to the hospital is, in my mind, very worth it. There are also antivirals, which you can take if you get sick," Tereshita explained.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;These include Tamiflu and the new Xofluza. Talk to your doctor if you have a fever, sore throat, cough and body aches because these meds should be taken near the onset of symptoms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;"The main messages are wash your hands, stay home when you're sick, and if you have to go out, wear a mask," Dr. Tereshita said&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;While we are seeing a lot of respiratory illnesses, Dr. Terashita says flu activity in California remains low.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;But, now is the time to get a flu shot if you haven't because the flu usually peaks in January and February.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC eTIW sUzSN "&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="uvrxY zOGtW "&gt;Copyright © 2025 KABC Television, LLC. All rights reserved.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ABC7 Los Angeles</author><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 01:39:55 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMitwFBVV95cUxNWk9vcTBSNmtlcFhadGRwMkFRZVhrTW5fOTNJNGpkcGdHX0JiOWZaZkJIbUdhajg4MTRwVW1wVzdHU2VLalUzRVhVdHQySER2VS1zV1pXYlFMWkxyWkVhVGZPenliVTlrNTl2eDQ4cmNBc2RGVXRBRmJ0REcxLXBZZWRpSjR0bm1nVTdHR0NlMExyQjRVemxZbmNuZDNhMnpNNGo3Nzc2T1NDTHpyQ19zYlZSazdsdzjSAbwBQVVfeXFMT1dKSk84ZExtdm43REtkUWRKR0x3Yjc3WnFrTnVWSURWeHI2SjZFbHpRS1lwbnlxdHVXUXRoNV95R0ZQak1sNFNKaTZhR1plejJtakxtX2xHZ01qNHVSRm4ta1d3RG52YV9kcDdNTTlsU2F0eVQ4MU43akhnSEIxcjVMckFXSmZoSjNsR2RHWnhpbEFHc3o5S3hybDMtNjZ5LWlTaW9VX3VDa01fMHY2akN5Z2d0TnJnR3pGY3o</guid></item><item><title>拉什大学医学中心的Steven Flamm博士谈论酒精使用，肝脏疾病，新年前饮酒的影响- ABC7芝加哥</title><link>https://abc7chicago.com/post/rush-university-medical-centers-dr-steven-flamm-talks-alcohol-use-liver-disease-impact-drinking-ahead-new-year/18310620/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="xvlfx ZRifP TKoO eaKKC EcdEg bOdfO qXhdi NFNeu UyHES " data-testid="prism-article-body"&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao MvWXB TjIXL aGjvy ebVHC "&gt;&lt;span class="oyrPY qlwaB AGxeB  "&gt;CHICAGO (WLS) -- &lt;/span&gt;As a new year approaches, many people are rethinking their habits, including how much alcohol they're drinking.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Rush University Medical Center's Dr. Steven Flamm joined ABC7 on Tuesday night to talk about alcohol's impact on the body.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="shortcode-centertext EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Flamm talked about how much alcohol it takes to develop liver disease and how alcohol impacts men and women differently.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Flamm also weighed in on the Illinois Department of Public Health's &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://dph.illinois.gov/resource-center/news/2025/december/release-20251215.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;alcohol use survey&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="RxNCg ykkUm PvZ nIjPJ PMXYp LmsHF SfAHY mNgye lNbol LBPRq rBLIK "&gt;Facts about alcohol:&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;People who consume alcohol can have severe alcohol-related liver disease with as little as two drinks per day in women and three drinks per day in men.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;The liver-related toxicity for alcohol is double in women compared to men.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Alcohol-associated hepatitis is a severe and life-threatening condition that can develop in a matter of weeks. It frequently happens in young people, has no good medical therapies and has a high mortality.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;The only therapy for alcohol-related liver disease is alcohol abstinence.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC eTIW sUzSN "&gt;There has been a dramatic increase in alcohol associated liver disease in the U.S., including Illinois, since the start of the COVID-19 pandemic.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="uvrxY zOGtW "&gt;Copyright © 2025 WLS-TV. All Rights Reserved.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ABC7 Chicago</author><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 01:29:39 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi4wFBVV95cUxNY2NIZGo5MlE2QmdwcjJPVkxZa2pVU1RYZ09LNVhUMHhlaXk4bmFIcnRIRkFsQi1NTl9uV0E5SjlfNGtWMDFEbEwzZW1jNUNHeGJRWHFmaGtwNTNjSUVBY2RfTG9aRTlTSzZMNEhnWHlId3NzWHdBLS1fRV9WUEpjSWJ1SXJZNjdYd295RnZTc3dYZURiRWRIY2l6SjhMMlBVX0ViNUhVTHJ6dGtOdHlydnlvY2hXSThHaWR5MEtEUWJCV1VIRW1hREcwemp3TTljdkh5RXZiZXJ1M0NpNTd3SHI2SdIB6AFBVV95cUxQY3NJd3ZIM3JfTVdvU3lZc1c0MURScHZtcGdnNHV0bkhTaEpCUDdJTkFKaENKb1ZmN0o3bU81QmNvZUQxT1VGNHF6STY3V0Y3TWJIRGRibXk0UTdvX09lS3pKVGdQRDJMMHRlODNJMWFkenppZXJQQkhuOUYtaHJUdUdZMnQxaHBGbnJzcHdBNFZmVTdGbDI4Xy13YlA5Nzl2N0xFMGhMMWx6RFB1R3NRdGRRZ3VaZmR5azAtSFRRVVZEM09JZU55WGotdzB4MzFOTTFMSXZPTE9JczV0VWZDRTREaWNVQmsz</guid></item><item><title>科学家说，人类实际上可能有30多种感官- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/humans-may-actually-have-over-30-senses-scientists-say</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Stuck in front of our screens all day, we often ignore our senses beyond sound and vision. And yet they are always at work. When we're more alert, we feel the rough and smooth surfaces of objects, the stiffness in our shoulders, the softness of bread.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the morning, we may feel the tingle of toothpaste, hear and feel the running water in the shower, smell the shampoo, and later the aroma of freshly brewed  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/how-does-caffeine-wake-you-up" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73115" data-postid="186802" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;coffee&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aristotle told us there were &lt;a href="https://www.jstor.org/stable/2184311"&gt;five senses&lt;/a&gt;. But he also told us the world was made up &lt;a href="https://www.cabinet.ox.ac.uk/fifth-element-and-medieval-cosmology-2"&gt;of five elements&lt;/a&gt;, and we no longer believe that. And modern research is showing we may actually have dozens of senses.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/a-scientist-reveals-5-amazing-facts-about-your-sense-of-smell"&gt;A Scientist Reveals 5 Amazing Facts About Your Sense of Smell&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Almost all of our experience &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/topics/senses-1914"&gt;is multisensory&lt;/a&gt;. We don't see, hear, smell, and touch in separate parcels. They occur simultaneously in a unified experience of the world around us and of ourselves.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What we feel affects &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1163/22134808-bja10003"&gt;what we see&lt;/a&gt;, and what we see affects &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.3389/fpsyg.2014.00725"&gt;what we hear&lt;/a&gt;. Different odours in shampoo &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S0950329309000202"&gt;can affect how you&lt;/a&gt; perceive the texture of hair. The fragrance of roses makes hair seem silkier, for instance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Odours in low-fat yogurts can make them feel richer and thicker on the palate without adding more emulsifiers. Perception of odours &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S0304394006010020"&gt;in the mouth&lt;/a&gt;, rising to the nasal passage, is modified by the viscosity of the liquids we consume.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_186808" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-186808" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/12/child_eating_yoghurt_642.jpg" alt="child eating yoghurt" class="wp-image-186808 size-full" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/12/child_eating_yoghurt_642.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/12/child_eating_yoghurt_642-600x421.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-186808" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;The odours of liquids in our mouth affect how they feel. (&lt;a href="https://www.canva.com/photos/MAEEqTBRquA/"&gt;Antonio D'Albore/Getty Images Signature/Canva&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;My long-term collaborator, Professor Charles Spence from the Crossmodal Laboratory in Oxford, told me his neuroscience colleagues &lt;a href="https://www.sciculture.ac.uk/files/2014/07/AHRC-Rethinking-the-Senses-Case-Study.pdf"&gt;believe there are&lt;/a&gt; anywhere between 22 and &lt;a href="https://www.gla.ac.uk/research/az/cspe/projects/rethinking-the-senses/"&gt;33 senses&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These include &lt;a href="https://www.britannica.com/science/proprioception"&gt;proprioception&lt;/a&gt;, which enables us to know where our limbs are without looking at them. Our sense of balance draws on the &lt;a href="https://www.britannica.com/science/ear/The-physiology-of-balance-vestibular-function"&gt;vestibular system&lt;/a&gt; of ear canals as well as sight and proprioception.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another example is interoception, by which we sense changes in our own bodies, such as a slight increase in our heart rate and hunger. We also have a sense of agency when moving our limbs: a feeling that can go missing &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/nrn.2017.14"&gt;in stroke patients&lt;/a&gt; who sometimes even believe someone else is moving their arm.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There is the &lt;a href="https://academic.oup.com/brain/article/147/2/390/7319594"&gt;sense of ownership&lt;/a&gt;. Stroke patients sometimes feel their arm is not their own, for instance, even though they may still feel sensations in it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/newsletter?utm_source=promo_generic_health"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-642x273.jpg" alt="Subscribe to ScienceAlert's free fact-checked newsletter" class="alignnone wp-image-182810 size-medium" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-642x273.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-768x326.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-600x255.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final.jpg 850w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some of the traditional senses are combinations of several senses. Touch, for instance, involves pain, temperature, itch, and tactile sensations. When &lt;a href="http://www.nature.com/nature/journal/v486/n7403_supp/full/486S6a.html"&gt;we taste something&lt;/a&gt;, we are actually experiencing a combination of three senses: touch, smell, and taste – or gustation – which combine to produce the flavours we perceive in food and drinks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gustation covers sensations produced by receptors on the tongue that enable us to detect salt, sweet, sour, bitter, and umami (savoury). What about mint, mango, melon, strawberry, raspberry?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We don't have raspberry receptors on the tongue, nor is raspberry flavour some combination of sweet, sour, and bitter. There is no taste arithmetic for fruit flavours.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We perceive them through the &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/smell-triggers-the-same-brain-response-as-taste-does-even-if-you-havent-eaten-anything-264922"&gt;combined workings&lt;/a&gt; of the tongue and the nose. &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.3390/foods11121686"&gt;It is smell&lt;/a&gt; that contributes the lion's share to what we call tasting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is not inhaling odours from the environment, though. Odour compounds are released as we chew or sip, travelling from the mouth to the nose through the nasal pharynx at the back of the throat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://scholar.archive.org/work/sn5ora556nerbd2gwndzdut5t4"&gt;Touch plays its part too&lt;/a&gt;, binding tastes and smells together and fixing our preferences for runny or firm eggs, and the velvety, luxurious gooeyness of chocolate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sight is influenced by our vestibular system. When you are on board an aircraft on the ground, look down the cabin. Look again when you are in the climb.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It will "look" to you as though the front of the cabin is higher than you are, although optically, everything is in the same relation to you as it was on the ground. What you "see" is the combined effect of sight and your ear canals telling you that you are tilting backwards.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_186809" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-186809" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/12/aircraft_cabin_seats_642.jpg" alt="aircraft cabin" class="wp-image-186809 size-full" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/12/aircraft_cabin_seats_642.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/12/aircraft_cabin_seats_642-600x421.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-186809" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;The rise of the aisle in an aircraft cabin is determined by your vestibular system. (&lt;a href="https://www.canva.com/photos/MAGZKtbMSrc/"&gt;Jeffry S.S./Pexels/Canva&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;The senses offer a rich seam of research, and philosophers, neuroscientists, and psychologists work together at the Centre for the Study of the Senses at the University of London's School of Advanced Study.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In 2013, the centre launched its Rethinking the Senses project, directed by my colleague, the late Professor Sir Colin Blakemore. We discovered how modifying the sound of your own footsteps can make your body feel lighter or heavier.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We learned how audioguides in the Tate Britain art museum that address the listener as if the model in a portrait was speaking enable visitors to remember more visual details of the painting. We discovered how aircraft noise interferes with our perception of taste and why you should always drink tomato juice on a plane.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While our perception of salt, sweet, and sour is reduced in the presence of white noise, umami is not, and tomatoes and tomato juice are &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1186/2044-7248-3-2"&gt;rich in umami&lt;/a&gt;. This means the aircraft's noise will enhance the savoury flavour.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/scientists-think-theyve-identified-an-unknown-taste-in-human-cells"&gt;Scientists Think They've Identified an Unknown Taste in Human Cells&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At our latest interactive exhibition, &lt;a href="https://www.kingscross.co.uk/event/club-curling"&gt;Senses Unwrapped&lt;/a&gt; at Coal Drops Yard in London's King's Cross, people can discover for themselves how their senses work and why they don't work as we think they do.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For example, the size-weight illusion is illustrated by a set of small, medium, and large curling stones. People can lift each one and decide which is heaviest. The smallest one feels heaviest, but people can then place them on balancing scales and discover that they are all the same weight.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But there are always plenty of things around you to show how intricate your senses are, if you only pause for a moment to take it all in. So next time you walk outside or savour a meal, take a moment to appreciate how your senses are working together to help you feel all the sensations involved.&lt;img loading="lazy" decoding="async" src="https://counter.theconversation.com/content/270697/count.gif?distributor=republish-lightbox-basic" alt="The Conversation" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade"&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/profiles/barry-smith-128876"&gt;Barry Smith&lt;/a&gt;, Director of the Institute of Philosophy, &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/institutions/school-of-advanced-study-university-of-london-1058"&gt;School of Advanced Study, University of London&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This article is republished from &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com"&gt;The Conversation&lt;/a&gt; under a Creative Commons license. Read the &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/humans-could-have-as-many-as-33-senses-270697"&gt;original article&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 00:32:06 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiwFBVV95cUxQcGdUZTYyb25pQmtSYThyUm5GNm9Ybm84R2p2TFNuM0hZajdkT2dKN19xWHB1RXJUM3ZzNl9sanJHR1E4dVJ0NFN4STg0SGdBNUZlZjFnd1FfbUNIajI0TExNSENZM0ZWYmxLVVJVTHQzR3QzUXBOdnIzLXZ6UXlkMnVuX3ZibklsVWow</guid></item><item><title>心理健康护理：姐妹30年的斗争如何帮助兄弟对抗精神分裂症，启发了一部电影-印度快报</title><link>https://indianexpress.com/article/health-wellness/caregiving-for-mental-health-how-a-sisters-30-year-fight-helped-a-brother-battle-schizophrenia-inspired-a-film-10434485/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="pcl-full-content" class="story_details"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Surviving mental illness is a dual effort. Sometimes the strongest fighters are not just the ones who recover but also those who refuse to abandon them when they are at their lowest. Like Ila Basu who did not give up on her 67-year-old brother Tarun Das, who was diagnosed with schizophrenia, a severe, chronic brain disorder causing distorted perceptions of reality, which manifests as hallucinations and delusions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For three decades, Ila has looked after him and even undertaken crash courses in rehabilitation, inspiring the 2004 Marathi film Devrai. “My brother Tarun is the youngest child in a large and accomplished family. Our father N. M. Das, served in the Air Force and my mother Nilima Das devoted her life to raising seven children. My siblings are bright and talented, doctors, nurses, teachers – all of them high achievers. And then little Tarun, small and gentle for his age, followed them everywhere with innocence and admiration,” Ila, now settled in &lt;a rel="noamphtml" class="keywordtourl" href="https://indianexpress.com/section/cities/pune/"&gt;Pune&lt;/a&gt;, tells The &lt;a rel="noamphtml" class="keywordtourl" href="https://indianexpress.com/"&gt;Indian Express&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img class="lazyloading" decoding="async" src="https://indianexpress.com/wp-content/themes/indianexpress/images/default-ie.jpg" data-lazy-type="lazyloading-image" data-src="https://data.indianexpress.com/election2019/track_1x1.jpg" data-lazy-src="https://data.indianexpress.com/election2019/track_1x1.jpg" alt=""&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While their early years were spent in Mysuru, the children shifted schools. Recalling the time Tarun stepped into adolescence, Ila says, “It was like a silent storm had begun inside him. As this condition is closely associated with a loss of gray matter density in the brain, Tarun struggled with his studies. His body and mind developed much slower than his classmates and he lagged behind in development milestones.” Teachers misunderstood his difficulty and school after school closed their doors to him. He began to lose friends, confidence and eventually his connection with the world around him. “A boy who once loved cricket and laughter slowly slipped into isolation and confusion. His mind, still growing and trying to understand life, was overtaken by an illness, which nobody recognised at the time. His behaviour changed. Communication faded. He withdrew into silence. He became lost inside himself. Those days, there was no mental health awareness or a support system. Only frustration, fear and stigma,” says Ila.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As Tarun’s condition worsened, he got addicted to smoking and was later treated at NIMHANS (National Institute for Mental Health and neuro Sciences), &lt;a rel="noamphtml" class="keywordtourl" href="https://indianexpress.com/section/cities/bangalore/"&gt;Bengaluru&lt;/a&gt;, where for the first time his therapy was pivoted on structure, routine and care. “However, with my father passing away in the middle of his treatment, Tarun returned home. With no family support and understanding of his illness, he collapsed again — this time deeper than ever. He lost everything. A home, identity, routine, dignity… even his human rights. He became invisible to the world,” says Ila.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ev-engagement group-name="contentLogin"&gt;&lt;/ev-engagement&gt;&lt;ev-engagement group-name="myNotification"&gt;&lt;/ev-engagement&gt;&lt;div class="ev-meter-content ie-premium-content-block"&gt;&lt;p id="taboola-mid-article-personalisation"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Where others saw a problem, Ila saw her brother&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She decided to fight when others gave up. From 1996 onward, Ila and her family took responsibility for Tarun’s entire life: medical care, emotional care, ensuring dignity, compliance of daily routine and rehabilitation as well as protection from stigma and love without condition. By then, the family had shifted to Pune and Ila would encourage Tarun to paint. The familiar surroundings gave a sense of stability to Tarun that worked.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Once she took one of his paintings and went to Sassoon Hospital where she met psychiatrist Dr Neha Pandey. Moved by Ila’s commitment to her brother, the doctor offered her a job. Ila became part of the group therapy team, helping her brother as well as other patients live a life of dignity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;The science of caregiving for schizophrenia&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A decade later, Ila and her family have added meaning to Tarun’s life by filling his days with rituals like reading, writing, exercising, walking, watching television and teaching him to use the mobile phone. Thanks to technology, he could snap out of his imagined world and connect to reality. Tarun met his childhood friends through the internet as his best friend came to meet him in Pune.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="adboxtop adsizes"&gt;&lt;p class="ie-adtext"&gt;Story continues below this ad&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="gpt_ad_IE_ROS_ROTATE_1_300X250" class="ad-slot "&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;According to Ila, a caregiver’s job is a patient one. “The first step is to create a safe space for mutual communication by attempting to understand even the patient’s non-verbal cues,” she says. A caregiver often validates the patient’s feelings and experiences, opening a bridge of communication. If it’s a family member, then it is easier to understand a loved one’s reality without judgment and eases their sense of isolation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At the first step, a caregiver should not challenge delusions simply because it is pointless to reason with psychosis. The idea is to listen to the patient and gently redirect them to reality. Encourage them in doing things for themselves, which steers them closer to their immediate reality. Ila involved her brother in various activities and hobbies that would keep him grounded to reality and gently encouraged interaction with friends, family, and social outings to combat isolation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She learnt about schizophrenia to understand symptoms and behaviours so that she could deal with her brother’s anxieties better. In fact, becoming a caregiver-therapist helped her experience different manifestations of the disease and understand them better. Amid all this, Ila ensured that she stayed fit and alert. She watched her own sleep, diet, exercise and relaxation techniques to prevent burnout.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;What care-giving does: Low dose psychiatric medication, no relapse&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At BJ Government Medical College and Sassoon General Hospital in Pune, Ila coordinated with associate professor Dr Nishikant Thorat to supervise Tarun. He gradually reduced Tarun’s psychiatric medication and he did not have any bouts of relapse. “Ila has studied his silence, learnt his non-verbal language and built a world around his comfort and safety. She taught the family how to love him, not fear his illness. Alongside her stood her husband, son Tavish, and daughter-in-law, who gave up comfort, time and personal life to become Tarun’s protectors and support system. They gave him more than care, they gave him belonging,” Dr Thorat said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="adboxtop adsizes"&gt;&lt;p class="ie-adtext"&gt;Story continues below this ad&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="gpt_ad_IE_ROS_ROTATE_2_300X250" class="ad-slot "&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tarun’s struggle continues with age bringing in illnesses like kidney failure, cardiac issues, diabetes and other orthopaedic issues. Dialysis has become a part of his life. “Patients suffering from long standing psychiatric illnesses like schizophrenia pose a challenge. Psychotropic medications can sometimes have a negative impact on the kidneys. That’s why he requires regular dialysis thrice a week to manage his kidney issues. We are able to reduce his psychotropic medications to a bare minimum dose so as not to have any negative impact on his treatment for kidney failure. In fact, since the last three years, he is behaviourally stable, interactive and taking his dialysis sessions regularly,” says Dr Thorat.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tarun now lives a life of dignity. His mind may not match his age but his heart recognises love and finds joy in friendship, paintbrush, music and people who approach him with kindness.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p id="taboola-mid-article-personalisation-premium"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;												&lt;/div&gt;
												&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Indian Express</author><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 00:14:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi_wFBVV95cUxNaWlpQlAyZ1VzZVlidmZVOXdBMEFxMjhZY05IZkVjbm1YOHZDaHZLTDkxMDdiSlllbkRablc2NW51dURSOTduZW5RQlhzWkhEdkY5YzR1RUhXRzBSTEltSndXdnd1YXdvYk1PSVBZN1RjLWRwX0VDVmZmTHJzTzJnOGFiUjc3NHN0VzJEcjBqc2hueUdwNDdUdGJnazJrTmI1MXl1MVZNUXNKN3lWMzJoMEd6UnB0VVNFejNGRVdWWGxDWGZLRDhZZXNtamE4UmFKMnBDWUo3MkpCallGakpXT3lzQXFrVFdCejJxajJibzJYVUNUQ2Q4bmpVaV9OS2vSAYYCQVVfeXFMTXFHSW9OMEljTDBhaFpUeHFIeG1pRTRBY3lLUWQ1S2wzdnp6RWpZeldQVFNjNEhXanVFdnFITVlsN3RLVmxQUXFCSmZMX0pKSTJLdTY4NFFJLWRSVl9pTXl4U0NiMTlSR2xfX0ZQR2cwQnhpYnlOTjhqNXhTVzNmWlJqWmkwLU1QZEdaa1dVZU51NlhaeHdtRXdCY1Z1VXhZVFljdElibklGOHZCTGk3ZEZra05WTkFPQy1iaUdoLTVkVDgtSU9Tanp0QTZCel9hc21pZnFUV3gtUFp2bDlvYzJQMGh5V3ZNekZvbHBYUG5mOVVHdnd6bUx5UDZ1RU9ZSzlTNEtiUQ</guid></item><item><title>我是一名皮肤科医生—如何知道一个人长大后是否会皱纹更多- AOL.com</title><link>https://www.aol.com/articles/m-dermatologist-always-tell-person-110000964.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="caas-body"&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure align-caption-with-image"&gt;&lt;div class="no-margin"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="caption-wrapper"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption-collapse"&gt;Everyone gets wrinkles, but some people are more likely to have early lines and deeper grooves. Dr. Kseniya Kobets reveals three major tell-tale signs of accelerated aging.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Call ’em laugh lines, battle blemishes or experience etchings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wrinkles are a natural and universal part of aging. &lt;a href="https://nypost.com/2024/01/12/health/what-causes-wrinkles-groundbreaking-new-study-may-have-found-answer/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:These creases primarily form;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;These creases primarily form&lt;/a&gt; as the skin loses collagen and elastin, which provide structure, firmness and elasticity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Certain habits can accelerate this process, making lines and grooves appear earlier and deeper. Blame genetics, hormones, dehydration, insufficient sleep, poor diets, stress and repeated facial expressions such as squinting, smiling or frowning.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure align-caption-with-image"&gt;&lt;div class="no-margin"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="caption-wrapper"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption-collapse"&gt;Everyone gets wrinkles, but some people are more likely to have early lines and deeper grooves. Dr. Kseniya Kobets reveals three major tell-tale signs of accelerated aging. courtesy of Montefiore Einstein Advanced Care&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Stress has a lot to do with aging and reactive oxygen species,” &lt;a href="https://doctors.montefioreeinstein.org/providers/1912296674/kseniya-kobets" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Dr. Kseniya Kobets;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Dr. Kseniya Kobets&lt;/a&gt;, director of cosmetic dermatology at &lt;a href="https://montefioreeinsteinadvancedcare.org/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Montefiore Einstein Advanced Care;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Montefiore Einstein Advanced Care&lt;/a&gt;, told The Post.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Someone who doesn’t have a healthy lifestyle and doesn’t eat healthy vegetables or fruits once in a while is also more likely to have less healthy skin.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kobets reveals three major ways she can tell if someone is more likely to develop smile souvenirs as they age.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Steady sun-worshipping&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The sun is good for you — it helps your body make &lt;a href="https://nypost.com/2023/11/27/health/vitamin-d-recommended-levels-should-be-10x-higher-report/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:vitamin D;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;vitamin D&lt;/a&gt; for strong bones, enhances mood by boosting serotonin and regulates your body’s internal clock for better sleep.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But too many rays can be really bad for skin. Just ask New Jersey “tan mom” &lt;a href="https://nypost.com/2022/05/23/tan-mom-patricia-krentcil-im-a-totally-different-person/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Patricia Krentcil;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Patricia Krentcil&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure align-caption-with-image"&gt;&lt;div class="no-margin"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="caption-wrapper"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption-collapse"&gt;Sunscreen prevents wrinkles by protecting skin from UV rays, which break down collagen and elastin. verona_studio – stock.adobe.com&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kobets worries about fair-skinned people who live in sun-soaked areas or participate in outdoor activities like hiking, biking, skiing or vacationing in the tropics.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“They are more prone to developing wrinkles and especially other issues like sun damage and, God forbid, precancerous lesions and &lt;a href="https://nypost.com/2025/08/25/health/abcdes-of-skin-cancer-9-clues-you-shouldnt-ignore/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:skin cancers;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;skin cancers&lt;/a&gt;,” she explained.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;UV rays generate free radicals that destroy collagen and elastin, damage DNA, trigger inflammation and speed up skin aging.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;How much sun is OK is really dependent on your skin type and the daily UV index.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Everyone needs protection, including hats, &lt;a href="https://nypost.com/article/best-sunglasses-brands-men-women/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:sunglasses;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;sunglasses&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://nypost.com/2025/06/09/health/what-to-know-about-picking-sunscreen-including-2-key-ingredients/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:SPF 30+ sunscreen;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;SPF 30+ sunscreen&lt;/a&gt;, when the index reaches 3 or higher (moderate risk).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Rawdogging skincare&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sunscreen is the cornerstone of any good skincare regimen, which is key to fending off wrinkles.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“If someone doesn’t really have a consistent skin care routine, particularly one that includes daily sunscreen use, even if they’re not outdoors, they are more likely to develop wrinkles over time,” Kobets said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure align-caption-with-image"&gt;&lt;div class="no-margin"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="caption-wrapper"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption-collapse"&gt;A good skincare routine emphasizes sun protection, hydration (moisturizers, hyaluronic acid), retinoids for cell turnover and antioxidants like vitamin C. Rido – stock.adobe.com&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Besides &lt;a href="https://nypost.com/article/best-mineral-sunscreens-per-experts/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:mineral sunscreen;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;mineral sunscreen&lt;/a&gt;, which reflects and scatters UV rays, Kobets recommends topical and oral antioxidants.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That means consuming vitamin C, &lt;a href="https://nypost.com/2024/05/03/health/im-a-dietitian-eat-this-to-get-more-collagen/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:collagen;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;collagen&lt;/a&gt; and peptides, short amino acid chains that tell skin cells to pump out more collagen and elastin, and applying topical peptides and occasionally, a topical retinol.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“These are very important factors, not to mention wearing hats and staying in the shade, even if you are wearing sunscreen,” Kobets said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Puffing pores&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Baking in the sun is lousy for your skin, but smoking is often considered worse because it narrows blood vessels, breaks down collagen and elastin and amplifies sun damage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nicotine constricts blood vessels, limiting the flow of oxygen and essential nutrients to the skin.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“If the person is smoking — although there are a lot of genetic and environmental factors at play — they’re more likely to have thinner skin and wrinkles, especially around their mouth,” Kobets said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That’s a nice way to describe &lt;a href="https://nypost.com/2019/11/01/study-confirms-that-cigarettes-will-give-you-ugly-smokers-face/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:“smoker’s face,”;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;“smoker’s face,”&lt;/a&gt; a phenomenon characterized by deep wrinkles around the eyes and lips from the smoker constantly drawing on cigarettes and repeatedly squinting to keep smoke out of their eyes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Smokers also often suffer from sagging skin, a dull, yellowish-gray complexion and premature contours.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>AOL.com</author><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 23:31:37 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihAFBVV95cUxQNmFwQ0FpY2NGeW9ZVVluZUZtOVNHNF9QeHNLdnBLdTJvTTR2MjZadzF2aHR2Rzl5eGhNLUhsODZYb0tHTXBxaUxiY0k3TEtpZC1lcEZPMFdUMV9PSDIwUlBJTWtfdEJDSlZSMmtuUWNKU2o0RTlodEdFbkVjaGxvWFdpMmg</guid></item><item><title>每天只喝一杯与印度口腔癌风险增加50 ％有关- SciTechDaily</title><link>https://scitechdaily.com/just-one-drink-a-day-linked-to-50-higher-mouth-cancer-risk-in-india/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>SciTechDaily</author><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 23:30:38 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimAFBVV95cUxOanJ1UEEzU2RnbHQtYWtFSWNZY2NqbDZKVFBvMUFCWG5wX09GWE00S3I0V3ZUMV9fWWR2dUpXUVcwdjBlU21ZWjdNSjJzaWJOXy1LYjF4QXEtTTVkdF9TbkZEZVlORkdlM1FiWFpJOFh6UHRKeVoxQkwzaVgzeHJWR2lJMU9ZZHoyc1ZhbTgzV18tUTBkNG9EMw</guid></item><item><title>近80年的法律可能会妨碍RFK Jr.重新制定疫苗接种计划的动力- CIDRAP</title><link>https://www.cidrap.umn.edu/childhood-vaccines/nearly-80-year-old-law-could-hamper-rfk-jr-s-drive-remake-vaccine-schedule</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="clearfix text-formatted field field--name-field-body field--type-text-long field--label-hidden field__item"&gt;&lt;p&gt;As the secretary of the Department of Health and Human Services (HHS), Robert F. Kennedy Jr. has broad powers to shape federal vaccine policy. In June, he &lt;a href="https://www.cidrap.umn.edu/adult-non-flu-vaccines/kennedy-removes-all-acip-members-eyes-replacements"&gt;fired all 17 members&lt;/a&gt; of an influential panel on immunization policy, then handpicked their replacements. In August, he &lt;a href="https://www.cidrap.umn.edu/public-health/cdc-director-fired-after-she-refused-rubber-stamp-kennedys-vaccine-directives"&gt;fired the director&lt;/a&gt; of the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention (CDC) after they clashed over vaccines.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But even Kennedy’s authority has limits.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Making a unilateral decision to scrap the US pediatric immunization schedule and replace it with recommendations from Denmark, as Kennedy &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2025/12/18/health/hhs-childhood-vaccine-changes"&gt;was reportedly ready&lt;/a&gt; to do last week, requires far more than a press conference, legal experts told CIDRAP News.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kennedy and other agency heads must obey the Administrative Procedure Act (APA), a law passed by Congress that requires federal officials to follow an open, deliberative process when issuing rules and regulations, said Lawrence Gostin, JD, founding director of the O'Neill Institute for National and Global Health Law at Georgetown University.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“As a matter of law, Secretary Kennedy has final authority to make federal policy,” Gostin said. “But he must follow a reasoned process.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;A drive to reduce the number of vaccinations&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kennedy’s announcement was canceled at the last minute. Although the HHS office of public affairs blamed a scheduling conflict, Politico has reported that Kennedy &lt;a href="https://www.politico.com/news/2025/12/20/rfk-kennedy-danish-vaccine-schedule-denmark-00701999"&gt;backed off from a plan to overhaul&lt;/a&gt; the vaccine schedule—which had been described to the press as an “announcement regarding children’s health”— after advisers told him it was legally and politically risky.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In an email to media, HHS suggested the press conference would be rescheduled, noting that it was “postponing our children's health announcement to after the first of the new year.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A spokesman for HHS declined to confirm that Kennedy planned to overhaul the vaccine schedule at the press conference. “Unless you hear it from HHS directly, this is pure speculation,” spokesman Andrew Nixon said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kennedy, a long-time anti-vaccine activist, has made no secret of his eagerness to revamp the immunization schedule. After President Trump &lt;a href="https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/12/aligning-united-states-core-childhood-vaccine-recommendations-with-best-practices-from-peer-developed-countries/"&gt;issued a memo earlier this month&lt;/a&gt; directing HHS to align the vaccination schedule with that of countries such as Denmark, Kennedy &lt;a href="https://x.com/SecKennedy/status/1997104582128754854?s=20"&gt;posted on X,&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; “&lt;/span&gt;Thank you, Mr. President. We’re on it.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But Kennedy needs to proceed cautiously to prevent any policy changes from being dismissed by a judge, said Dorit Reiss,&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;PhD, a law professor at the University of California Law, San Francisco. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;As a matter of law, Secretary Kennedy has final authority to make federal policy....But he must follow a reasoned process.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to the APA, courts can “hold unlawful and &lt;a href="https://www.law.cornell.edu/uscode/text/5/706"&gt;set aside agency action&lt;/a&gt;, findings, and conclusions found to be arbitrary, capricious, an abuse of discretion, or otherwise not in accordance with law.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Simply holding a press conference to announce that the United States will now recommend Denmark’s vaccine schedule would leave the Trump administration “very, very vulnerable to an arbitrary and capricious claims,” Reiss said. “Short videos simply don't do it.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Following established procedures&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;For six decades, vaccine recommendations have been formulated by the Advisory Committee on Immunization Practices (ACIP), which normally votes on national recommendations after reviewing medical evidence and soliciting input from experts and the public. The CDC director can accept or reject those recommendations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The CDC’s recommendations are not mandates. Even if Kennedy were to switch the current vaccine recommendations to match those of Denmark, states would not have to follow along. Although CDC recommendations carry great weight, states make individual decisions about school vaccine requirements, Gostin said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A court is likely to take a dim view of any federal vaccine policy changes that don’t go through the ACIP, Reiss said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If the administration wants to follow Denmark’s example, “they need to address the major issues and explain why they are changing from a schedule developed in a deliberative manner over years.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And Trump’s memo carries little to no legal weight, Reiss added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The president's memo is not cover, because the will of the president is not enough to justify a change of position under Supreme Court jurisprudence,” Reiss said. “The agency also has to justify the decision on the merits.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Legal challenges to Trump administration policy&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Numerous lawsuits filed against the Trump administration in recent months claim that he and federal agency heads have violated the APA.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The American Academy of Pediatrics (AAP) and other medical groups, for example, &lt;a href="https://www.cidrap.umn.edu/covid-19/medical-groups-sue-hhs-kennedy-over-covid-vaccine-policy-changes"&gt;filed a law suit against Kennedy&lt;/a&gt; in July claiming that he violated the APA when he &lt;a href="https://litigationtracker.law.georgetown.edu/litigation/american-academy-of-pediatrics-et-al-v-robert-f-kennedy-jr-et-al/"&gt;issued a directive&lt;/a&gt; removing the COVID-19 vaccine from the CDC immunization schedule for children and pregnant women.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The concerns and legal issues all come back to whether he followed a process and looked at evidence,” said Richard H. Hughes IV, JD, MPH, who teaches vaccine law at George Washington University and represents the AAP and other plaintiffs in their lawsuit against Kennedy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Numerous medical societies and public health groups &lt;a href="https://www.cidrap.umn.edu/childhood-vaccines/pediatricians-reject-cdc-advisers-guidance-plan-continue-vaccinating-all"&gt;have criticized Kennedy&lt;/a&gt; and the ACIP for more recent changes to the vaccination schedule, such as removing a recommendation to routinely vaccinate all newborns against hepatitis B. Scientists and public health advocates predict that decision &lt;a href="https://www.cidrap.umn.edu/childhood-vaccines/doctor-groups-form-united-front-against-rfk-jr-s-efforts-limit-vaccine-access"&gt;will allow many children to suffer&lt;/a&gt; and die needlessly from a vaccine-preventable illness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Neither Kennedy “nor the ACIP is taking the proper steps to evaluate the full range of evidence that is normally reviewed prior to recommendation changes,” Hughes said. “All of that is textbook ‘arbitrary and capricious’ under the Administrative Procedure Act.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But that doesn’t mean that Kennedy can’t find other ways to alter the vaccine schedule, Gostin noted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“If he follows a deliberative process, the ultimate decision is his,” Gostin said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Although the APA could be interpreted to mean that Kennedy needs to work with the ACIP to change vaccine recommendations, “that is not a high bar for Kennedy since he handpicked ACIP's members,” Gostin said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Justifying a change to vaccine recommendations would be easier than changing federal regulations, a process that typically takes months and includes proposals and opportunities for public comments, Gostin said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kennedy “would have even more onerous procedures to follow if he proposed a legal regulation,” Gostin said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
      
  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>CIDRAP</author><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 21:59:13 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMivAFBVV95cUxQREd5aFpWYzJQb2huYVBnTnc3ZFZwTUxSTDRaRWJpVDdaWlhiNVR0MS1FSTlhUl9MUlF6VTFOM3dsYUd3RWxvWWotZTByZXFsOUl3a0FVb1JFdUNXUzRvRUlQazhpaHNfand1bXktOUROYVdheE4xMHNISGtSNW1qZDd3MjBwTmtYSjUwTG01OThJaW1TQnA1b1AzMWI4V1BGQnBCN09lTUdpMnFJY1o5eUNZVzFldVdMbzJNcg</guid></item><item><title>如果我听医生的话，我现在早就死了- HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffpost.com/entry/women-doctor-cancer-tumor-hysterectomy_n_694b0046e4b0d09497f9e0b1</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;section class="entry__content-list js-entry-content js-cet-subunit"&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most doctors are intelligent, compassionate human beings, but they &lt;em&gt;are&lt;/em&gt; human. And medicine is a business, which means doctors can be overworked, pressed for time and dismissive of patient complaints, &lt;a href="https://www.northwell.edu/katz-institute-for-womens-health/articles/gaslighting-in-womens-health" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="especially if that patient is a woman" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="694b0046e4b0d09497f9e0b1" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.northwell.edu/katz-institute-for-womens-health/articles/gaslighting-in-womens-health" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="0"&gt;especially if that patient is a woman&lt;/a&gt;. In my case, the casual dismissal of my symptoms almost cost me my life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was October 2019 when my new OB-GYN ― let’s call her Dr. Can’t Be Bothered ― gave me what I considered to be life-changing news.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“You have a two-centimeter tumor on your uterine cervix,” she said, without even a hint of concern. For me, those words felt like a knife to the gut. A tumor? Me? How?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Then her phone rang, and she left the room.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;By the time she returned, tears had welled up in my eyes. “Do I have cancer?” I asked, terrified and confused. As a non-doctor, when I hear the word “tumor,” my first thought is cancer. Hers was not.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“No, no,” Dr. Can’t Be Bothered assured me. “This is not how cancer behaves.” Then she added a sentence I’ll never forget: “For you to have cancer at this age, with this medical history, it would be like winning the lottery.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;This did not make me feel better. She seemed unconcerned about the tumor growing in my pelvis, but I was not. She explained I would need a biopsy, but assured me it was probably fibroids, a benign growth, maybe a polyp, or a million other little non-cancer things. I would have to go under anesthesia for the biopsy, and it would be an “all-day” affair. Not wanting this tumor-thingy hanging over my head, I asked to schedule the surgery as quickly as possible.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr. CBB once again told me there was no rush, even though the radiology report stated the tumor was “of concern.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;In fact, she was going on vacation for two weeks and her schedule was full. We would have to put off the procedure for at least four weeks. I asked if I could get in sooner ― perhaps a different doctor could perform the biopsy?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“It’s not necessary,” she said. “Just be patient.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;blockquote class="cli cli-pullquote"&gt;&lt;p class="cli-pullquote__placeholder"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="cli-pullquote__content"&gt;&lt;p class="cli-pullquote__quote accent-cli"&gt;“I let it go ― after all, she'd gone to medical school and I hadn't. She wore a white coat, and I was a 34-year-old whose work wardrobe still included yoga pants.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;She made me feel like I was overreacting, like I was ignorant of how “these things work.” I peppered her with questions about the Big C, to which she kept saying, “No, no, that’s not how cancer behaves.” I let it go ― after all, she’d gone to medical school and I hadn’t. She wore a white coat, and I was a 34-year-old whose work wardrobe still included yoga pants. It was not my place to argue with her.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;On my drive home I called my mother. I explained everything the doctor told me, but I couldn’t stop crying. I felt that something was wrong ― like, &lt;em&gt;really&lt;/em&gt; wrong. And I was angry the doctor wasn’t taking this seriously. My mother agreed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;On instinct, I called up my old OB-GYN. Sobbing, I explained my situation and begged for an urgent appointment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;When it comes to certain cancers, time matters. Forty-eight hours later I was once again sitting in a doctor’s office, only this time, it was a completely different experience.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;My old doctor spoke to me with kindness and concern. He explained exactly what the ultrasound revealed, and went over all the tests he was about to perform, including another ultrasound, a colposcopy, and an in-office biopsy with no anesthesia and no surgery required. He even said to me, “I know you’re scared, but we’re going to do everything we can to figure out what’s going on.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Turns out, I &lt;em&gt;had&lt;/em&gt; won the lottery.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;The biopsy revealed I had a &lt;a href="https://tarynhillin.medium.com/a-rare-cancer-thats-killing-young-women-and-no-one-knows-how-to-cure-dc4a4d91d9ed" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="very rare cancer called high-grade small-cell neuroendocrine" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="694b0046e4b0d09497f9e0b1" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://tarynhillin.medium.com/a-rare-cancer-thats-killing-young-women-and-no-one-knows-how-to-cure-dc4a4d91d9ed" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="1"&gt;very rare cancer called high-grade small-cell neuroendocrine&lt;/a&gt;. I would need a radical hysterectomy ― where they remove the uterus, cervix, ovaries, fallopian tubes, a third of the vaginal canal, and multiple pelvic lymph nodes ― along with adjuvant chemotherapy and radiation. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;After my diagnosis, my entire world turned upside down. It was an onslaught of appointments, scans, and hard bathroom-floor crying. My imaging showed only “local disease,” which means it had not metastasized to other parts of my body. My surgical oncologist said she was relieved. “Often patients with neuroendocrine cancer walk in at stage 4 ― it’s that aggressive,” she said. “You’re lucky you came when you did.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure class="cli cli-image js-no-inject"&gt;&lt;p class="cli-image__spacer"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="cli-image__source-wrapper"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="cli-image__caption caption-cli"&gt;The author with her husband, Max Gamble, after she completed chemotherapy for stage 3C neuroendocrine cancer.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Indeed, that’s an understatement. Even with the quick biopsy, I ended up at stage 3C. My odds of survival were a mere &lt;a href="https://ijgc.bmj.com/content/29/6/986" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="0% to 7%" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="694b0046e4b0d09497f9e0b1" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://ijgc.bmj.com/content/29/6/986" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="2"&gt;0% to 7%&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;The truth is, high-grade small-cell neuroendocrine cancer is highly aggressive, with poor prognosis rates. Even at stage 1, the survival rate is only about 30%. The time between my scans, which showed local disease, and my surgery, which found cancer in one lymph node, was just five days. Had I waited for Dr. CBB to care about my condition, I would have been stage 4 at diagnosis and probably dead now. Median survival is less than 16 months. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Weeks later, after my surgery was completed, I finally got a call from Dr. Couldn’t Be Bothered’s office. They wanted to schedule the&lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt;biopsy she’d put off. I laughed. “Are you kidding me?” I asked. “I’m about to start chemotherapy!” Then I angrily hung up the phone. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;I know I am lucky to be alive. I have now been cancer-free for two years. My oncologist recently said I was a “miracle.” In order for me to survive this cancer, &lt;em&gt;everything&lt;/em&gt; had to go my way. I was fortunate that the second doctor I saw spent over an hour with me, listened to my concerns, tested me for everything on the spot and cared enough to pay attention to me. If my surgery, chemotherapy or radiation had been delayed by four weeks ― as Dr. CBB wanted ― it would have cost me my life. Instead, a team of doctors stepped up and recognized a needle-in-a-haystack cancer. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;My intention is not to vilify doctors, but rather the system they are forced to operate in. According to studies, 56% of primary care physicians &lt;a href="https://mobius.md/2021/10/09/how-much-time-do-physicians-spend-with-patients/" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="spend less than 16 minutes" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="694b0046e4b0d09497f9e0b1" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://mobius.md/2021/10/09/how-much-time-do-physicians-spend-with-patients/" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="3"&gt;spend less than 16 minutes&lt;/a&gt; with patients, and much of that time is &lt;a href="https://www.fiercehealthcare.com/practices/for-each-patient-visit-physicians-spend-about-16-minutes-ehrs-study-finds" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="spent filling out electronic health records" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="694b0046e4b0d09497f9e0b1" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.fiercehealthcare.com/practices/for-each-patient-visit-physicians-spend-about-16-minutes-ehrs-study-finds" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="4"&gt;spent filling out electronic health records&lt;/a&gt;. Indeed, the bureaucratic side of American health care &lt;a href="https://www.ama-assn.org/practice-management/physician-health/what-doctors-wish-patients-knew-about-physician-burnout" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="is not what doctors signed up for" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="694b0046e4b0d09497f9e0b1" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.ama-assn.org/practice-management/physician-health/what-doctors-wish-patients-knew-about-physician-burnout" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="5"&gt;is not what doctors signed up for&lt;/a&gt;. Between growing pressure to see more patients, &lt;a href="https://www.ama-assn.org/practice-management/physician-health/what-doctors-wish-patients-knew-about-physician-burnout" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="insurance pre-authorization codes" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="694b0046e4b0d09497f9e0b1" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.ama-assn.org/practice-management/physician-health/what-doctors-wish-patients-knew-about-physician-burnout" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="6"&gt;insurance pre-authorization codes&lt;/a&gt;, after-hours phone calls, portal messages, peer-to-peer insurance consults, &lt;a href="https://www.hhrinstitute.org/exploratory-study-identifies-key-factors-associated-with-time-pressure-in-primary-care-clinicians/" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="patient paperwork" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="694b0046e4b0d09497f9e0b1" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.hhrinstitute.org/exploratory-study-identifies-key-factors-associated-with-time-pressure-in-primary-care-clinicians/" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="7"&gt;patient paperwork&lt;/a&gt; and medical history reviews, many physicians are burned out. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;blockquote class="cli cli-pullquote"&gt;&lt;p class="cli-pullquote__placeholder"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="cli-pullquote__content"&gt;&lt;p class="cli-pullquote__quote accent-cli"&gt;“Women are underdiagnosed for depression, cardiovascular disease and many types of cancer, often seeing multiple doctors and waiting more than a year for a diagnosis.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;That said, studies have shown women are &lt;a href="https://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/full/10.1111/j.1553-2712.2008.00100.x" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="often dismissed" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="694b0046e4b0d09497f9e0b1" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/full/10.1111/j.1553-2712.2008.00100.x" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="8"&gt;often dismissed&lt;/a&gt; in health care settings. They’re told severe abdominal pain can be chalked up to period cramps, while painful conditions like uterine fibroids, endometriosis and ovarian cysts &lt;a href="https://labblog.uofmhealth.org/rounds/understanding-racial-disparities-for-women-uterine-fibroids" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="go undiagnosed for months or years" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="694b0046e4b0d09497f9e0b1" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://labblog.uofmhealth.org/rounds/understanding-racial-disparities-for-women-uterine-fibroids" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="9"&gt;go undiagnosed for months or years&lt;/a&gt;. In fact, the American College of Obstetricians and Gynecologists estimates that endometriosis &lt;a href="https://www.webmd.com/women/news/20180607/why-women-are-getting-misdiagnosed" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="takes an average of six to 10 years for a diagnosis" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="694b0046e4b0d09497f9e0b1" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.webmd.com/women/news/20180607/why-women-are-getting-misdiagnosed" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="10"&gt;takes an average of six to 10 years for a diagnosis&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Not to mention, women in America have the &lt;a href="https://www.vox.com/2020/1/30/21113782/pregnancy-deaths-us-maternal-mortality-rate" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="highest maternal mortality rate" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="694b0046e4b0d09497f9e0b1" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.vox.com/2020/1/30/21113782/pregnancy-deaths-us-maternal-mortality-rate" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="11"&gt;highest maternal mortality rate&lt;/a&gt; compared to other developed nations, and for Black women, it’s even worse. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;But the dismissal of women’s pain is not exclusive to gynecological or pregnancy-related conditions. Women are underdiagnosed for depression, cardiovascular disease and many types of cancer, often seeing multiple doctors and &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://journals.plos.org/plosone/article?id=10.1371/journal.pone.0127717" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="waiting more than a year for a diagnosis" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="694b0046e4b0d09497f9e0b1" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://journals.plos.org/plosone/article?id=10.1371/journal.pone.0127717" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="12"&gt;&lt;span&gt;waiting more than a year for a diagnosis&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;. Women are 50% more likely to be &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.webmd.com/women/news/20180607/why-women-are-getting-misdiagnosed" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="misdiagnosed for cardiovascular disease" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="694b0046e4b0d09497f9e0b1" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.webmd.com/women/news/20180607/why-women-are-getting-misdiagnosed" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="13"&gt;&lt;span&gt;misdiagnosed for cardiovascular disease&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; than men, and 30% more likely to be misdiagnosed when presenting symptoms of a stroke. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Women have to advocate for themselves the moment they walk into a doctor’s office, because that’s the health care system we live in. We have to fight to get tests, labs and appointments, all while being labeled pushy, hysterical and overdramatic. And don’t even get me started on weight stigma. News flash: Not every condition can be solved by losing weight (cancer comes to mind). What’s more, too many women (and too many people in general) don’t have access to insurance, affordable health care or the resources and time to take advantage of it, but that’s a whole other battle. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Ultimately, if battling a rare and deadly cancer has taught me anything, it’s to never stop fighting for yourself. I spent countless hours fighting with insurance, begging labs and imaging centers for earlier appointments, and emailing every oncologist in the country for help. It’s your health, and your life. If you have to ruffle a few white-coated feathers, so be it. You’re worth it. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This piece was originally published in January 2022 and we’re rerunning it now as part of HuffPost Personal’s “Best Of” series.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Taryn Hillin is a journalist, screenwriter and cancer survivor. She is currently in the Sony Television Diverse Writers program. Prior to that, she was a writer and producer at TMZ, HuffPost and Fusion. When she’s not writing, Taryn helps cancer patients, and people suffering from chronic illness, through her Instagram, &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/theanticancerlife/?hl=en" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="@TheAntiCancerLife" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="694b0046e4b0d09497f9e0b1" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.instagram.com/theanticancerlife/?hl=en" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="14"&gt;@TheAntiCancerLife&lt;/a&gt; and TikTok, &lt;a href="https://www.tiktok.com/@theanticancerlife" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="@TheAntiCancerLife" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="694b0046e4b0d09497f9e0b1" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.tiktok.com/@theanticancerlife" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="15"&gt;@TheAntiCancerLife&lt;/a&gt;. She is a graduate of Yale.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Do you have a compelling personal story you’d like to see published&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt; on HuffPost? Find out what we’re looking for &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/entry/how-to-pitch-huffpost-opinion-personal_n_5a5e0726e4b0fcbc3a1388f0" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-internal-link" data-vars-item-name="here" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="694b0046e4b0d09497f9e0b1" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="5a5e0726e4b0fcbc3a1388f0" data-vars-target-content-type="buzz" data-vars-type="web_internal_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="16"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="mailto:pitch@huffpost.com" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="send us a pitch" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="694b0046e4b0d09497f9e0b1" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="mailto:pitch@huffpost.com" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="17"&gt;send us a pitch&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>HuffPost</author><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 20:52:46 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMinAFBVV95cUxQU2xvbFQzcWZ4LUcwMHgzSFhnYW9SX1cxQkt6N3NYSmRuZW5YVDRrNEN2d2JiTEprcFFHa0JRbGpJeERfdXhGZGNnRGE1NUZxTlNhWXN1aVV0bEpoeDJva3hNUkhlMi1CcDI4U1l1NU5yTE9LTXczUXl2bTRfMDgzVGtGQTBTRTVsYk8tRHBuQmFaNkNLYTBLOXlVTzHSAaIBQVVfeXFMTUxqUlBQLUp0N1BrLTJqcjh3VFFQM0E4eUtYeDJfU0djT0xsd1NXLWR5cFNOYkQtNlJaVVFKdHJITEJCaGRKUlFscnItVVZvdjJiWGc4OV9IZnFDY3lySm9VTC01RDZDdHRCcW4wRDZHd3g3R1hsREpkOEhkWVRXM1RsT1lVMU1iQXZXdUo3Q09TZEFSdTNJaTNrcUdmS3NCYW5n</guid></item><item><title>波士顿卫生官员在114%的流感病例激增中发出警告- Boston.com</title><link>https://www.boston.com/news/health/2025/12/23/boston-health-officials-issue-warning-amid-114-spike-in-flu-cases/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article class="content-well content-well--article" role="main"&gt;
									&lt;p id="presentedby"&gt;
						
					&lt;/p&gt;
								&lt;header class="m-article-header m-article-header--standard"&gt;
												&lt;span id="article-header-primary-term"&gt;
								&lt;a class="a-term a-term--primary" href="https://www.boston.com/tag/health/"&gt;
								Health								&lt;/a&gt;
							&lt;/span&gt;
							
					&lt;h1 class="m-article-header__headline"&gt;Boston health officials issue warning amid 114% spike in flu cases&lt;/h1&gt;
					&lt;h2 class="m-article-header__sub-headline"&gt;The city’s flu surge is happening about a month earlier this year, health officials said.&lt;/h2&gt;

					&lt;figure class="a-photo m-article-header__photo "&gt;
&lt;img src="https://bdc2020.o0bc.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/ZLJV25IMCKTLAERPZSTCMV3RW4-694af8e4bd7a4-768x432.jpg" class="attachment-16:9 size-16:9 wp-post-image" alt="" decoding="async" srcset="https://bdc2020.o0bc.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/ZLJV25IMCKTLAERPZSTCMV3RW4-694af8e4bd7a4-768x432.jpg?width=200 200w, https://bdc2020.o0bc.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/ZLJV25IMCKTLAERPZSTCMV3RW4-694af8e4bd7a4-768x432.jpg?width=300 300w, https://bdc2020.o0bc.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/ZLJV25IMCKTLAERPZSTCMV3RW4-694af8e4bd7a4-768x432.jpg?width=400 400w, https://bdc2020.o0bc.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/ZLJV25IMCKTLAERPZSTCMV3RW4-694af8e4bd7a4-768x432.jpg?width=500 500w, https://bdc2020.o0bc.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/ZLJV25IMCKTLAERPZSTCMV3RW4-694af8e4bd7a4-768x432.jpg?width=600 600w, https://bdc2020.o0bc.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/ZLJV25IMCKTLAERPZSTCMV3RW4-694af8e4bd7a4-768x432.jpg?width=700 700w, https://bdc2020.o0bc.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/ZLJV25IMCKTLAERPZSTCMV3RW4-694af8e4bd7a4-768x432.jpg?width=800 800w, https://bdc2020.o0bc.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/ZLJV25IMCKTLAERPZSTCMV3RW4-694af8e4bd7a4-768x432.jpg?width=900 900w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px"&gt;	&lt;figcaption class="a-photo__caption"&gt;
	&lt;em&gt; Joe Raedle / Getty Images, File&lt;/em&gt;	&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

					&lt;div class="m-article-header__meta"&gt;
						&lt;div class="m-article-header__byline"&gt;
							&lt;p class="m-article-header__author"&gt;
								By &lt;a class="a-link a-link--inline" href="https://www.boston.com/author/abby-patkin/"&gt;Abby Patkin&lt;/a&gt;							&lt;/p&gt;

															&lt;time class="m-article-header__date"&gt;
									December 23, 2025 | 3:41 PM								&lt;/time&gt;
							
															&lt;p class="m-article-header__word-estimate"&gt;&lt;span&gt;1 minute to read&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
													&lt;/div&gt;
						
					&lt;/div&gt;
				&lt;/header&gt;

				&lt;p&gt;Boston public health officials are warning of an earlier &lt;a href="https://www.boston.com/news/local-news/2025/09/25/boston-to-offer-free-covid-and-flu-vaccines-at-more-than-a-dozen-locations/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;flu surge&lt;/a&gt; this season, reporting a dramatic 114% spike in cases just days before Christmas.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Flu-related trips to the emergency room have also increased 44% in recent days, and the rate of infection is increasing most rapidly among children, the Boston Public Health Commission said in a &lt;a href="https://www.boston.gov/news/city-boston-and-public-health-commission-warn-residents-significant-increase-flu-cases" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;press release&lt;/a&gt; Tuesday. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The city’s flu surge is happening about a month earlier this year, health officials said; last flu season, Boston didn’t hit these case numbers until January.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Flu cases are on the rise in Boston, and we are urging residents to protect themselves and their loved ones from respiratory illnesses which can cause hospitalization and severe illness,” said Dr. Bisola Ojikutu, the city’s public health commissioner.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The city is urging residents to get their annual flu vaccine, particularly children and high-risk adults. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Flu spreads easily during this time of the year when we gather together indoors,” Ojikutu said. “It is not too late to get vaccinated. Vaccination is the best tool we have to prevent serious illness.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Although the Public Health Commission has vaccinated more than 2,500 people across 27 free vaccination clinics to date, only 30% of Boston residents had received their flu shot as of Dec. 6, according to the press release. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ojikutu said health officials will be hosting &lt;a href="https://www.boston.gov/government/cabinets/boston-public-health-commission/viral-respiratory-illness-protection" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;additional clinics&lt;/a&gt; throughout Boston in January. The Public Health Commission also advised hand washing, masking, and staying home when sick to help cut down on the spread. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tuesday’s warning came as seasonal flu activity continues to &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/respiratory-viruses/data/activity-levels.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;ramp up nationwide&lt;/a&gt; amid chatter about a new &lt;a href="https://www.bostonglobe.com/2025/12/22/metro/super-flu-virus-children-kids/?p1=Article_Inline_Text_Link#:~:text=a%20newer%20flu%20strain%20known%20as%20subclade%20K%2C%20a%20subvariant%20of%20the%20H3N2%20subtype%20of%20influenza%20A%20that%20has%20drawn%20attention%20for%20driving%20an%20earlier%2Dthan%2Dusual%20spike%20in%20flu%20cases%20in%20the%20UK%20and%20several%20other%20countries." target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;“super flu” variant&lt;/a&gt;. Data from the Massachusetts Department of Public Health indicates the level of influenza-like illness is &lt;a href="https://www.mass.gov/info-details/influenza-reporting" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;“high” or “very high”&lt;/a&gt; throughout most of the state.&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;div class="o-author-single has-avatar"&gt;

	
	&lt;section class="author-info"&gt;
		&lt;div class="m-author__section"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Abby Patkin is a general assignment news reporter whose work touches on public transit, crime, health, and everything in between.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;	&lt;/section&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="m-block m-generic-cta
	 m-generic-cta--post-content	 m-generic-cta--dark	 m-generic-cta--homepage	 m-generic-cta--email-signup		 m-generic-cta-block-style--default 
	t-amp__generic-cta"&gt;
		&lt;div class="m-generic-cta__wrap"&gt;
		
		
		&lt;div class="m-generic-cta__content"&gt;
							&lt;h3 class="m-generic-cta__title"&gt;Sign up for the Today newsletter&lt;/h3&gt;
			
							&lt;p class="m-generic-cta__subtitle"&gt;Get everything you need to know to start your day, delivered right to your inbox every morning.&lt;/p&gt;
					&lt;/div&gt;
		

			&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

								&lt;p class="content-below-article"&gt;
					&lt;/p&gt;
				
		&lt;p&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;


			&lt;/article&gt;
					&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Boston.com</author><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 20:41:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMisgFBVV95cUxPWFJNRGs2djJTR1RoR0ctMEpGSVZPbThVZWhxT0czaGVLZkR3M2NPMURUX210QVRVUVN1dkFISU9JdFl5V0VoT2RfY1FwTHk5bFM4QWRqR0oxSmZQdmpBVkRxYVhsc0txcTh1eHpXNkk5dFA3VTl1VEhHN182RzVVOUYxVjRvck44X0Z6RGJTUU9vbEVUQ3JyOEd6OHdyLUtHS3NEWWpnQzU5RnQtajZiT3dR</guid></item><item><title>PAWS芝加哥关于芝加哥狗狂犬病病例的官方声明- PAWS芝加哥</title><link>https://www.pawschicago.org/news-resources/news-features/paws-chicago-news/paws-chicago-news-item/showarticle/paws-chicago-official-statement-on-rabies-case-in-chicago-dog</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>PAWS Chicago</author><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 20:29:33 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigAJBVV95cUxPLWs4a19INkZjYW1XOS1TVGJpN0dkV0ZYWGhlVGkzQVRyQXdDVTBnRHZMMU9BWlU0aVg4RWpaUzd1NUo0Q3ZOT3RoSGVrLUlmVFJwWm5fd0xpYTR5bkExeWRTQVRBeHNQT2lOZFBIM2w5eEFjcEVkX2hoS1hzYkcxZHdGVzJiSks3WGlDeXFVaVAwTzkxUlA5M3h1N1otZzR5QUNFT0d3bmhyVTRoUkNVcTdEWnhRenRaUUMwTTRGb3VlWTM5VHV1M1ViTEZyZDdjaVZTRXBDbjAxX1NVa3dFb2RKMW4wbmVYa0hRUFJlbGoxZGZ4dzZLc1otQjVDdFpR</guid></item><item><title>哲学专家分享亚里士多德的简单方法，了解您是否有“伟大的头脑” - Upworthy</title><link>https://www.upworthy.com/philosophy-expert-shares-aristotle-s-simple-way-to-know-if-you-have-a-great-mind</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="body-description"&gt;&lt;p&gt;One of the strangest things about &lt;a data-linked-post="2674400997" href="https://www.upworthy.com/these-10-weird-habits-might-be-an-indicator-of-high-intelligence" target="_blank"&gt;highly intelligent people &lt;/a&gt;is that they are very aware of what they don’t know. The psychological phenomenon known as the &lt;a data-linked-post="2659482310" href="https://www.upworthy.com/dunning-kruger-effect" target="_blank"&gt;Dunning-Kruger &lt;/a&gt;effect suggests that the more&lt;a data-linked-post="2674282254" href="https://www.upworthy.com/8-emotionally-intelligent-phrases-that-will-strengthen-your-marriage" target="_blank"&gt; intelligent&lt;/a&gt; someone is, the more they fixate on their perceived gaps in intelligence, leading them to underestimate themselves. Conversely, those who aren’t very intelligent overestimate their &lt;a data-linked-post="2656403033" href="https://www.upworthy.com/jimmy-kimmel-men-test-female-anatomy-rp7" target="_blank"&gt;knowledge&lt;/a&gt; on a subject.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The great mind might be more preoccupied with the gaps in its knowledge than the smaller mind that thinks it knows everything. How can someone see if they have a great mind? &lt;a href="https://www.good.is/research-on-600000-college-students-shows-that-studying-philosophy-makes-them-better-thinkers" target="_blank"&gt;Philosophy&lt;/a&gt; expert Julian de Medeiros says it all goes back to Aristotle's “rule of thumb.” De Medeiros &lt;a href="https://julianphilosophy.substack.com/" target="_blank"&gt;writes a Substack&lt;/a&gt; on philosophy and has over 1.4 million&lt;a href="https://www.tiktok.com/@julianphilosophy?" target="_blank"&gt; followers on TikTok&lt;/a&gt;, where he analyzes the mysteries of love, intelligence, and friendship.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;How to know you are brilliant&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;div class="rm-shortcode" data-rm-shortcode-id="a5f7e6afc780f8b9cd59cad0a626a032" data-thumbnail="" id="ec62a"&gt;&lt;blockquote cite="https://www.tiktok.com/@julianphilosophy/video/7295512220010794286" class="tiktok_lazy_shortcode" data-video-id="7295512220010794286"&gt;&lt;section&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.tiktok.com/@julianphilosophy" target="_blank" title="@julianphilosophy"&gt;@julianphilosophy&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;Simple theory about intelligence #intelligent #intelligence #smart #genius #creative #power&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Here's a simple sign that you are intelligent, that you have a great mind, and it's a simple theory, a rule of thumb, that goes back to an observation by the philosopher Aristotle, who once wrote: ‘No great mind has ever existed without a touch of madness,’” de Medeiros says. “By which he meant that there's a fine line indeed between being a genius and being a madman.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Schopenhauer on what makes a genius&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;“As the philosopher Schopenhauer once wrote: ‘Talent is when you can hit a target no one else can hit. Genius is when you can hit a target no one else can see,” de Medeiros continued. “Now to have a great mind, therefore, means that you can see and think things that other people can't. But this puts you on a kind of border where there's a liminal line between what is real and what is not. Your mind is a double-edged sword, both a blessing and a curse, and that very intelligent people can also fall off the edge into the abyss.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aristotle lived more than 2,300 years ago, when our knowledge of mental and physical health was a fraction of what we know now. But, interestingly, he was correct in believing that highly intelligent people may face greater psychological struggles than those of normal intelligence.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A study&lt;a href="https://www.us.mensa.org/learn/about/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;u&gt; published by&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; Mensa foundthat knowledgeable people are are 20% more likely to have an autism spectrum disorder (ASD) diagnosis. They are 80% ore liekly to be diagnosed with ADHD and 182% more likely to have a mood disorder.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why is it that highly intelligent people are more likely to suffer from mental disorders? &lt;a href="https://www.hanleycenter.org/why-are-intelligent-people-more-prone-to-mental-illness/" target="_blank"&gt;A study found&lt;/a&gt; that it may be caused by psychological excitability. Highly intelligent people are known to fixate on things. This can be a big help when you are problem-solving at work, but it can become a problem when you become preoccupied with a comment from your boss or a social interaction that you can't stop playing over and over in your head.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There is a funny way that life always seems to balance things out. You can either be unintelligent and think you know everything, or be brilliant and focused on everything you don’t know. It shows that, with respect to intelligence, having a psychological understanding of yourself is one of the keys to living a healthy and happy life. Or, as Aristotle once put it: “Knowing yourself is the beginning of all wisdom.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Upworthy</author><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 19:07:30 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiqAFBVV95cUxPSjNDdndhYmFiZFo4V2w0dHhjTXhxUXJXS2dISUE4WHJueHFabEd3VlV0aXFqRzROS2o0OWpxYlBOUnczdlJtNURjRUtWMkViTVluTFhOc0x1czFxSFpodVExRFFFdnBYTENTbUszSG9nZEpJaFREOUY4aVFGUEcybTFRdVV6TW9kVUF6SUVUUUdLRHlucWF0M0lyVVhuNEI1NHVVWEMtd2U</guid></item><item><title>科学家创造人类子宫内膜复制品并植入早期胚胎-《卫报》</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/science/2025/dec/23/scientists-create-replica-human-womb-lining-and-implant-early-stage-embryos</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body-commercial-selector article-body-viewer-selector dcr-hdpgoq"&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Researchers have created the lining of a womb in a dish, which promises to shed light on the mysterious early stages of human pregnancy and the glitches that can lead to miscarriage and medical complications.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;In laboratory experiments, early-stage human embryos donated from couples after &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/society/ivf" data-link-name="in body link" data-component="auto-linked-tag"&gt;IVF&lt;/a&gt; treatment successfully implanted into the engineered lining and began to churn out key compounds, such as the hormone that results in a blue line on positive pregnancy tests.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="sign-in-gate"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The approach allowed scientists to eavesdrop on the chemical chatter that arises between the embryo and the womb lining as it embeds and begins to be nourished in the first weeks of gestation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“It’s incredible to see it,” said Dr Peter Rugg-Gunn, a senior author on the study and group leader at the Babraham Institute in Cambridge. “Previously we’ve only had snapshots of this critical stage of pregnancy. This opens up a lot of new directions for us.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Implantation takes place a week or so after fertilisation when the developing embryo attaches and then embeds itself into the uterus wall. It is a crucial phase in pregnancy, but the process is poorly understood because it is so hard to observe. Much of what is known comes from studies of hysterectomies that were performed in early pregnancy more than half a century ago.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;To build the replica womb lining, Rugg-Gunn and his colleagues obtained uterine tissue from healthy women who donated biopsy samples. From this, the scientists isolated two different types of cells: stromal cells that give structural support to the womb lining, and epithelial cells, which form the lining’s surface. They encapsulated the stromal cells in a biodegradable material called a hydrogel and put the epithelial cells on top.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The researchers tested the engineered womb lining with donated early-stage IVF embryos. Writing in &lt;a href="https://www.cell.com/cell/fulltext/S0092-8674(25)01232-2" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;the journal Cell&lt;/a&gt;, they describe how the microscopic balls of cells attached and implanted as hoped. They then ramped up secretion of a hormone called human chorionic gonadotropin (hCG), the biochemical marker detected by pregnancy tests, along with other pregnancy-related compounds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The technique enabled scientists to watch embryos grow for up to 14 days post-fertilisation, the legal limit for research. During the process, the embryos formed specialised cells and other cells involved in the growth of the placenta.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;To understand the process more deeply, the scientists zoomed in on the spots where embryos had embedded in the engineered womb lining and decoded the molecular signals that passed back and forth. Such signals are critical for achieving and maintaining a healthy pregnancy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure data-spacefinder-role="inline" data-spacefinder-type="model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.NewsletterSignupBlockElement" class="dcr-173mewl"&gt;&lt;gu-island name="EmailSignUpWrapper" priority="feature" deferuntil="visible" props="{&amp;quot;index&amp;quot;:9,&amp;quot;listId&amp;quot;:4156,&amp;quot;identityName&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;morning-briefing&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;description&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;Our morning email breaks down the key stories of the day, telling you what’s happening and why it matters&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;name&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;First Edition&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;frequency&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;Every weekday&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;successDescription&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;We'll send you First Edition every weekday&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;theme&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;news&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;idApiUrl&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;https://idapi.theguardian.com&amp;quot;}"&gt;&lt;/gu-island&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figure id="77432e95-1196-4fe5-b3b3-287a709945f5" data-spacefinder-role="richLink" data-spacefinder-type="model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.RichLinkBlockElement" class="dcr-47fhrn"&gt;&lt;gu-island name="RichLinkComponent" priority="feature" deferuntil="idle" props='{"richLinkIndex":10,"element":{"_type":"model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.RichLinkBlockElement","prefix":"Related: ","text":"Equivalent of one child in every British classroom now born via IVF, data shows","elementId":"77432e95-1196-4fe5-b3b3-287a709945f5","role":"richLink","url":"https://www.theguardian.com/society/2025/jun/26/one-child-every-british-classroom-born-via-ivf-fertility"},"ajaxUrl":"https://api.nextgen.guardianapps.co.uk","format":{"design":0,"display":0,"theme":0}}'&gt;&lt;/gu-island&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Scientists will now use the approach to investigate how pregnancies become established and what can go awry. “We know that half of all embryos fail to implant and we have no idea why,” Rugg-Gunn said. Finding answers could provide a much-needed boost to IVF success rates.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Further experiments will explore what happens after implantation when the placenta starts to form. Many serious complications of pregnancy are thought to arise at this stage. In the study, the researchers used a chemical to block a particular signal between the embryo and the lining, producing severe defects in the tissue that forms the placenta, demonstrating its power for testing the impact of signalling problems.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;In a &lt;a href="https://www.cell.com/cell/fulltext/S0092-8674(25)01230-9" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;separate study&lt;/a&gt; in the journal, Chinese researchers created their own replica womb lining and identified drugs that might improve implantation rates in patients with recurrent implantation failure (RIF), where good-quality IVF embryos fail to establish a pregnancy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;John Aplin, a professor of reproductive medicine at the University of Manchester, said that during 40-plus years of assisted reproduction, implantation rates had remained stubbornly low.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“As the embryo implants, a programme is initiated to begin development of the placenta, which will supply nutrients and oxygen to the foetus,” he said. “The earliest stages are crucial to the progression of the pregnancy, are not well understood, and frequently fail. This work will allow treatments to be explored that seek to improve implantation efficiency.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Guardian</author><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 18:56:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiwAFBVV95cUxObGxvOTVkbnRQd2dtZWxQbTBuRWxJYnEzQkZMSERVaDNXdmVKTTZ0ak85NXcyc2U3eHZpa0x4RlJPT3Fqc2pJUXpLTVJ4UnIxYU1WLVBlMHRIUnc2N3Rud1hSaHhITjVvOU80SVFRcnIxY2NObzFiZWlhWFpkRmF5YnBEWUxXWURGaE45MWhSSmNlRXg2R1l1SWlIbGgyemhFWmNYa1RCajhaM3ZFRTBrOG4yWlJ2a0hUSkltN0g3eTg</guid></item><item><title>不考虑任何事情：迈向心灵消失的大脑特征- Medical Xpress</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-12-brain-signature-mind-blanking.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="success-screen" id="successScreen"&gt;
            &lt;p class="success-icon"&gt;✓&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;h2 class="success-title"&gt;Verification Complete&lt;/h2&gt;
            &lt;p class="success-subtext"&gt;This page will redirect in a moment...&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Medical Xpress</author><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 18:45:51 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMifkFVX3lxTFBiR05ldFdDR3Z0a1p4VEZ4cnRCVlVmeHc5dl9tc2h6R0VxS2ZPemFvTFJOTG0yaWZmVU5EaDU1dGV1RE1YYllyMmZ5Rm01eEFJNktWVHJtWm4yZF95ZVRJQnFDRUtETURLM3RYbnJGdWlOSVZmMURVTThzZFNNUQ</guid></item><item><title>医院在呼吸道疾病增加的情况下暂时实施访客限制- WHIO TV</title><link>https://www.whio.com/news/local/hospitals-temporarily-limit-visitor-restrictions-amid-increase-respiratory-illness/EMQ7PUCYF5DZPMVYZYFNF3PBZA/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article class="default__ArticleBody-sc-tl066j-1 jPcFTl article-body-wrapper"&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 lofITx body-paragraph"&gt;DAYTON — Hospitals across the region are implementing temporary visitor restrictions amid a recent increase in respiratory illness beginning Dec. 26. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 lofITx body-paragraph"&gt;&lt;b&gt;[DOWNLOAD: &lt;/b&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.whio.com/mobile-apps/" target="_self" rel="" title="https://www.whio.com/mobile-apps/"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Free WHIO-TV News app for alerts as news breaks&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;b&gt;]&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 lofITx body-paragraph"&gt;Area hospitals are currently seeing higher-than-normal volumes of patients with positive cases of respiratory illnesses, including influenza, COVID-19, and other seasonal viruses, according to the Greater Dayton Area Hospital Association &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 lofITx body-paragraph"&gt;&lt;b&gt;TRENDING STORIES:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="taboola-read-more" class="taboola-read-more"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 lofITx body-paragraph"&gt;When implemented, the restrictions will be as follows: &lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;No visitation by anyone who is ill with any respiratory symptoms including coughing, fever, chills, headache, vomiting, sore throat, muscle aches or diarrhea&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;No visitation by anyone under age 14 even if they have received the seasonal influenza vaccine or receive the appropriate vaccine when it becomes available&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 lofITx body-paragraph"&gt;Hospitals are asking community members to postpone visiting if they are feeling unwell, especially if experiencing symptoms such as fever, cough, sore throat, or congestion. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 lofITx body-paragraph"&gt;Visitor restrictions are temporary and will be reviewed regularly, GDAHA said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 lofITx body-paragraph"&gt;GDAHA is a member-service organization representing 29 hospitals and health systems in the Dayton region. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="taboola-read-more-8" class="taboola-read-more-8"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 lofITx body-paragraph"&gt;&lt;b&gt;[SIGN UP: &lt;/b&gt;&lt;a href="https://membercenter.whio.com/newsletters" target="_self" rel="" title="https://membercenter.whio.com/newsletters"&gt;&lt;b&gt;WHIO-TV Daily Headlines Newsletter&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;b&gt;]&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 lofITx body-paragraph"&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 lofITx body-paragraph body-copyright"&gt;©2025 Cox Media Group&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>WHIO TV</author><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 18:25:03 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi2gFBVV95cUxOWG5OV0V1aVoxSkRIeTYwa1FqNF95TFVPR25NS3BERUJQR0tOSVVTb0pnWkNjTENtQ1hGUlFpUXd1c1NzdTVMS0xuRTVsN2NiZ3A4c1J0emRoNktkSnFJMzFhUEJQTEJQcjZ1QmtfSXU2TDA3Y0hDd2ZjcTNFTjZtWG1UaUtxSmNCa0VJb3FlUE5Mcy1WbFJMSEx1YWdiRTFFZjNJY1hNTEVlcTY4aVdPVDlqeWV3QmdBRzA2TnViZGZwUmE1eF9kSmRjOTN2SUctc0pocjkzQUREZ9IB7gFBVV95cUxNQmpQVkNuTkhnNnJUbGFqYk9MQjI2b3QtZzFjZVdBbnNQbnRBZkd2TlJyVHRoeUxnaXl3cHJGakJRY0pTejYxR3ZLa0ZJSGJDTHNqMWxmbnNaU2Ywd0VydWgwX2w2RDNYWEg4bXlXRTRMMDZPYnJzMkRUV3pOUlV5RmVYd0tEMVNBRlZiMDVrSFRqSlFKNGRKXzBBS2Z0V0VWY09iMGdIQ2NYak1DN1dDcUdLZVVkNW9yZjRtb2ZWUlBnZDg1LVVjNFRZR0lCci1IbEFUVE9iajA4RDhPaVo1dngwV2VKWXp1MEVpM3VR</guid></item><item><title>数据是减缓与年龄相关疾病的关键- WIRED</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/data-holds-the-key-in-slowing-age-related-illnesses/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="body__inner-container"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="lead-in-text-callout"&gt;In 2026, we&lt;/span&gt; will see the beginning of precision medical forecasting. Just as there have been remarkable advances in weather forecasting with the use of large language models, so will there be for determining an individual’s risk of the major age-related diseases (cancer, cardiovascular, and neurodegenerative). These diseases share common threads, such as a long incubation phase before any symptoms are manifest, usually two decades or more. They also have the same biologic underpinnings of immunosenescence and inflammaging, terms that characterize an immune system that has lost some of its functionality and protective power, and the accompanying heightened inflammation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;The science of aging has given us new ways to track these processes with body-wide and organ clocks, along with specific protein biomarkers. That enables us to determine whether a person or an organ within a person is aging at an accelerated pace. Along with that, new AI algorithms can see things that medical experts cannot, such as accurately interpreting medical images like retinal scans to predict cardiovascular and neurodegenerative diseases many years in advance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="GenericCalloutWrapper-IJXIe ejayGs callout--has-top-border" data-testid="GenericCallout"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;These added layers of data can be combined with a person’s electronic medical records, which include their structured and unstructured notes, lab results, scans, genetic results, wearable sensors, and environmental data. In aggregate, this provides an unprecedented depth of information about the person’s health status, enabling a forecast for risk of the three major diseases. Unlike a polygenic risk score which can detect a person’s risk for heart disease, the common cancers and Alzheimer’s, precision medical forecasting takes it to a new level by providing the projected temporal arc—the “when” factor. When all of the data is analyzed with large reasoning models, it can provide a person’s vulnerabilities, and an individualized, aggressive preventive program.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Container-VgtPr ekoLDG"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;We already know the risk of these three diseases can be reduced with lifestyle factors, such as an optimal anti-inflammatory diet, frequent exercise, and a regular, high-quality sleep pattern. But, along with attention to these factors, which are far more likely to be implemented when an individual is cognizant of their risk, we will have medications that will promote a healthy, protective immune system and reduce body-wide and brain inflammation. Already the GLP-1 medicines have been shown to be a front-runner for achieving these goals, but many more medications are in the pipeline.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;The potential for precision medical forecasting has to be demonstrated and validated via prospective clinical trials that show, using the same metrics of aging, that a person’s risk is decreased. An example for people with increased risk of Alzheimer’s is the blood test known as &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41398-024-03084-7"&gt;p-tau217&lt;/a&gt;, and that risk can be markedly reduced with improved lifestyle factors, especially exercise. That could be confirmed with a brain organ clock and body-wide aging clocks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;This is a new frontier in medicine—the potential for primary prevention of the three age-related major diseases that compromise our health span and quality of life. It would not be possible without the advances in both the science of aging and AI. For me, this is the most exciting future use of AI in medicine: an unparalleled opportunity to prevent the major diseases from occurring, something that has been dreamed about but has not been possible at scale due to the deficiency in data and analytics. In 2026, it finally will.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>WIRED</author><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 18:11:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihwFBVV95cUxQMXVjb0dGSW1kYnQta3ptaTBUZmJYVENWbnFTR3hWUl9NTzVFMzVUa0JHM2t2TmFJdUVVY013WTBRNmlNSlhOTDlNRlpHNlA3VU9namk5OFkxSXFuYnJwdzZZUEtzaEVjbndtV1VVTXlib2dXS1hsZWNHTjg2dnc2dl9rWnB0RGc</guid></item><item><title>4项日常锻炼，让您比大多数60岁以上的40岁儿童更强壮-吃这个不是那个</title><link>https://www.eatthis.com/daily-exercises-stronger-than-40-year-olds-after-60/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="content single-post-content"&gt;
																			&lt;p class="tagline"&gt;Build and maintain strength after 60 with these four seamless daily moves.&lt;/p&gt;
												
																			
																		
						
						
						&lt;p&gt;Once you reach 60, one thing’s for certain—building strength is essential. The reason? &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://www.eatthis.com/15-minute-standing-workout-reverse-muscle-loss-after-55/" target="_blank"&gt;Sarcopenia&lt;/a&gt;, the natural loss of strength and muscle you endure with age. There are many things that cause sarcopenia, including hormonal changes, inactivity, diet, and more. It’s important to take the right steps to &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://www.eatthis.com/5-minute-evening-routine-build-muscle-after-50/" target="_blank"&gt;strengthen your muscles&lt;/a&gt; so you can continue to perform daily tasks and live an independent life.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We spoke with &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer external" href="https://domenicangelino.com/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Domenic Angelino, CPT&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt; with &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer external" href="https://traineracademy.org/" target="_blank"&gt;International Personal Trainer Academy&lt;/a&gt;, which offers NCCA-accredited Personal Trainer (CPT) and Certified Nutrition Specialist (CNS) programs, who shares four &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://www.eatthis.com/daily-exercises-women-over-55-maintain-strength/" target="_blank"&gt;daily exercises&lt;/a&gt; that can do exactly that. In fact, performing them regularly will keep you stronger than most 40-year-olds after 60.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“If you don’t use your muscles, they will get weaker over time,” Angelino tells us. “One way to reduce the loss of muscle over time is to regularly lift weights at the gym. Another way to go about it is to naturally maintain an active lifestyle. If you’re always moving around, your body will act to preserve your muscle mass, and therefore strength, because you’re using it more. So, making movement a part of your day can have some benefits—although, you’ll see the biggest benefit from more traditional exercise using heavy resistance.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So without further ado, Angelino breaks down the best exercises to weave into your daily routine to build strength and overall fitness.&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;h2 id="dumbbell-goblet-squats" class="o-slide-title" data-num="1"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Dumbbell Goblet Squats&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
	
&lt;p&gt;&lt;iframe title="YouTube video player" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/mF5tnEBrdkc?si=TANmBVMueAI87ZmU" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"&gt;VIDEO&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“This is a solid all-around strength exercise for your lower body. It also requires you to engage your upper body muscles to hold the dumbbell right in front of your chest, so it gets a lot done in a short period of time,” Angelino explains. “You can start with body weight to work up to using a dumbbell if you need to.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;​​Stand tall, feet slightly wider than shoulder-width.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Grasp a dumbbell with both hands, and hold the weight in front of your chest with your elbows pointing down and tucked in.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hinge at the hips and bend your knees to squat, keeping the weight in place.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Squat as far as you can with a straight back.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Push through your heels to return to the starting position.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Perform 3 sets of 6 to 8 reps.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p class="karma_unit karma_unit--distinct inline karma_unit--mobile hide-desktop karma_unit--sliding htlad-lazy-mob-square-fixed karma_unit--halfpage"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;h2 id="dumbbell-bench-press" class="o-slide-title" data-num="2"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Dumbbell Bench Press&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
	
&lt;p&gt;&lt;iframe title="YouTube video player" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/ZaDlbm8E8Tg?si=qLIV4--aegBRTsa-" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"&gt;VIDEO&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“This trains about half of your most important upper-body muscles,” Angelino points out.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lie flat on your back on a workout bench.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hold a dumbbell in each hand just outside your chest.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Keep your feet flat on the ground and maintain an engaged core.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Press the dumbbells over your chest until your arms are extended but not locked out.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Use control to lower the weights.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Perform 3 sets of 6 to 8 reps.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

	&lt;h2 id="dumbbell-bent-over-rows" class="o-slide-title" data-num="3"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Dumbbell Bent-Over Rows&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
	
&lt;p&gt;&lt;iframe title="YouTube video player" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/6gvmcqr226U?si=BXqcXyBmUZ8U5s4I" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"&gt;VIDEO&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“This trains the other half of your most important upper body muscles,” Angelino says.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Stand tall, feet hip-width apart and a dumbbell in each hand in front of you.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hinge at the hips until your torso is parallel to the ground.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maintain a flat back and soft knees.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Allow the weights to lower with your arms completely extended.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Row the dumbbells up toward your torso.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lower to the start position with control.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Perform 3 sets of 6 to 8 reps.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;RELATED:&lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://www.eatthis.com/7-bodyweight-exercises-strong-after-50/" target="_blank"&gt; 7 Simple Bodyweight Exercises That Keep You Stronger Than Most 30-Year-Olds After 50&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span aria-hidden="true"&gt;6254a4d1642c605c54bf1cab17d50f1e&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;h2 id="plank" class="o-slide-title" data-num="4"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Plank&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
	
&lt;p&gt;&lt;iframe title="YouTube video player" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/ao5nY7lb088?si=OzfIMpDkhcb66Dyr" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"&gt;VIDEO&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“This exercise helps improve your core stability by strengthening the part of your abdominal muscles most responsible for doing so,” Angelino says. “It might seem intimidating at first, but you can perform this exercise on your forearms and knees at first to get used to it. And, you can work up to regular planks over time. It’s also important to do these over a soft surface to keep your joints, like your knees, safe.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assume a forearm plank with your forearms on the floor—elbows under your shoulders—and body straight from head to heels.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Engage your legs, glutes, and core.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Perform 3 sets of 30 to 45-second holds.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

																		
																	&lt;/div&gt;
										&lt;div class="c-article-short-bio"&gt;
	&lt;p class="c-article-short-bio__name"&gt;Alexa Mellardo&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;div class="c-article-short-bio__bio"&gt;&lt;p&gt;
		Alexa is a freelance writer, editor, and content strategist based in Greenwich, CT. She has 11+ years of experience covering wellness, fitness, food, travel, lifestyle, and home.					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a class="c-article-short-bio__more" href="https://www.eatthis.com/author/alexa-mellardo/"&gt;Read more about Alexa &lt;/a&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
					&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Eat This Not That</author><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 17:40:40 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiggFBVV95cUxQSEhLMUhFMlZWeV85eEJJWFk2c2JHTkVuTGZiVHNoRWVIQ0NSSjFMYlZ1YWVQdTlQZV9kYlo4V2JIUXpYblVxRmRCa2hCRHJhVVliOHVwVDRaQlk1d3ZVeFVYTVhBLWpIbjM0V0drNzlrQ0RIdFR5c2ZSbW9sd0dhUzZn</guid></item></channel></rss>