<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>GNews Health</title><link>https://news.google.com/</link><description></description><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>Marylander has measles after international travel. Here's what to know - WBAL TV Baltimore</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMijgFBVV95cUxNUGNEYWl0R3JlazZJRGowYUtnSXVNOGRDT3JoRlFweXdHdEhvQjRfeVdNWVl3MldxYVVLdmZpTnk4YUdicTR4TDdxU1EwOXktbFJTNTdRYmdlYmlVaHNJa2N0MDdyZ21zaGUzcTlEZTVEcUk4RzQ4NUpnQzV3NjNFaVh4Q1I5QXM3WmRfaDJR?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="article-content--body-text-raw"&gt;
						A positive case of measles was confirmed in a Howard County resident who recently traveled internationally, according to health officials.The Maryland Department of health said this case is not associated with a measles outbreak in Texas and New Mexico.Out of an abundance of caution, health officials are trying to identify people who might have been exposed. State and county health officials are trying to get in touch with potentially exposed passengers on specific flights as follows.Washington Dulles International Airport: The international arrivals area on March 5 between 4-9 p.m.Johns Hopkins Howard County Medical Center Pediatric Emergency Department on March 7 between 3:30-7:30 p.m.Early symptoms of measles are a fever of more than 101 degrees Fahrenheit, runny nose, cough, and red, watery eyes. Usually, one to four days after the early symptoms, a red rash appears on the face and spreads to the rest of the body. Measles symptoms typically develop 10-14 days after exposure to the virus but can develop as soon as seven days and as long as 21 days after exposure. A person with measles is contagious, beginning four days before the rash appears until four days after the rash begins.MDH said people are generally considered immune to measles if they have had two measles vaccine shots, previously had measles or laboratory evidence of immunity or infection, or were born in the United States before 1957.Those who are most at risk of complications from measles infection are pregnant women, infants less than 1 year old, and those who are immune compromised. People in these at risk groups who may have potentially been exposed and are not immune should contact their health care provider or call Howard County Health Department's Infectious Disease Surveillance and Response Program at 410-313-6284 for additional guidance. Virginia residents with additional questions about their potential exposure can call the Virginia Department Health at 804-363-2704 or email epi_response@vdh.virginia.gov.People, especially those not vaccinated or otherwise immune to measles, who were at any of these locations during the possible exposure times should monitor themselves for any early symptoms of measles for 21 days after the potential exposure. People who develop a fever or other symptoms of measles should not go to childcare, school, work, or out in public, and should contact their health care provider. They should call their health care provider first rather than showing up in the waiting room or emergency room so that the office can take measures to prevent spread to other patients.Measles cases do occur sporadically in Maryland with one case of measles identified in Maryland in 2024, one in 2023, and no cases from 2020-2022.This report will be updated.
					&lt;/p&gt;
	
					&lt;div class="article-content--body-text"&gt;
						&lt;strong class="dateline"&gt;BALTIMORE —&lt;/strong&gt; 													&lt;p&gt;A positive case of measles was confirmed in a Howard County resident who recently traveled internationally, according to health officials.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Maryland Department of health said this case is not associated with a &lt;a href="https://www.wbaltv.com/article/measles-is-popping-up-in-the-us-how-to-avoid/64040348" target="_blank"&gt;measles outbreak in Texas and New Mexico&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Out of an abundance of caution, health officials are trying to identify people who might have been exposed. State and county health officials are trying to get in touch with potentially exposed passengers on specific flights as follows.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Washington Dulles International Airport: The international arrivals area on March 5 between 4-9 p.m.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Johns Hopkins Howard County Medical Center Pediatric Emergency Department on March 7 between 3:30-7:30 p.m.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Early symptoms of measles are a fever of more than 101 degrees Fahrenheit, runny nose, cough, and red, watery eyes. Usually, one to four days after the early symptoms, a red rash appears on the face and spreads to the rest of the body. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Measles symptoms typically develop 10-14 days after exposure to the virus but can develop as soon as seven days and as long as 21 days after exposure. A person with measles is contagious, beginning four days before the rash appears until four days after the rash begins.&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;p&gt;MDH said people are generally considered immune to measles if they have had two measles vaccine shots, previously had measles or laboratory evidence of immunity or infection, or were born in the United States before 1957.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="cream-inline-rec" class="cream-inline hidden"&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Those who are most at risk of complications from measles infection are pregnant women, infants less than 1 year old, and those who are immune compromised. People in these at risk groups who may have potentially been exposed and are not immune should contact their health care provider or call Howard County Health Department's Infectious Disease Surveillance and Response Program at 410-313-6284 for additional guidance. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Virginia residents with additional questions about their potential exposure can call the Virginia Department Health at 804-363-2704 or email &lt;a href="mailto:epi_response@vdh.virginia.gov" target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;epi_response@vdh.virginia.gov&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;People, especially those not vaccinated or otherwise immune to measles, who were at any of these locations during the possible exposure times should monitor themselves for any early symptoms of measles for 21 days after the potential exposure. People who develop a fever or other symptoms of measles should not go to childcare, school, work, or out in public, and should contact their health care provider. They should call their health care provider first rather than showing up in the waiting room or emergency room so that the office can take measures to prevent spread to other patients.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Measles cases do occur sporadically in Maryland with one case of measles identified in Maryland in 2024, one in 2023, and no cases from 2020-2022.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This report will be updated&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;


							
											&lt;/div&gt;
	
	
						
						
																			

																				&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>WBAL TV Baltimore</author><pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijgFBVV95cUxNUGNEYWl0R3JlazZJRGowYUtnSXVNOGRDT3JoRlFweXdHdEhvQjRfeVdNWVl3MldxYVVLdmZpTnk4YUdicTR4TDdxU1EwOXktbFJTNTdRYmdlYmlVaHNJa2N0MDdyZ21zaGUzcTlEZTVEcUk4RzQ4NUpnQzV3NjNFaVh4Q1I5QXM3WmRfaDJR</guid></item></channel></rss>