<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>GNews Health</title><link>https://news.google.com/</link><description></description><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>The Heartbreaking Case of the Youngest Person to Ever Face Alzheimer’s — A Condition So Rare, Even Scientists Are Speechless - Indian Defence Review</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMi6AFBVV95cUxQU1l4RUliUUhUQmhWSUxzdmgwdUJoQWlzak1FR0xQQnI4bjBqYWFlQ2t6WjVPTjkzNV80bVZYWkhza2hxZl9zdm5KNmNub0Y3cVVoVG8xa1AxTHRCbnhwYnlRX2RyWW9uYm5yTkVYR283MW9DSFotZUZQem5Xb1Z4Wl9EQ202Sk4wdlVuaFJCTEJGQzdHMWNrSE44YUVNb0JxNnZvOXhCc2xUX0FlcDVvZE5GLVN2RGxGUkdUdkFkRFRLMmF3YTdKTkVsVGVUb1ZZZEwzaXpOaWgwb1doQkRDUlprcjhFLTRG?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="dynamic-entry-content"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A &lt;strong&gt;19-year-old&lt;/strong&gt; from China has been diagnosed with &lt;strong&gt;Alzheimer’s disease (AD)&lt;/strong&gt;, making him the youngest known patient ever recorded. The case challenges current medical assumptions about how and why the disease develops, especially in younger individuals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="code-block code-block-5"&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="code-block code-block-2"&gt;


&lt;ins class="adsbygoogle" data-ad-client="ca-pub-6966113680805338" data-ad-slot="5777932750" data-ad-format="auto" data-full-width-responsive="true"&gt;&lt;/ins&gt;


&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;A Rare Diagnosis at an Unprecedented Age&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Typically associated with the elderly, &lt;strong&gt;Alzheimer’s&lt;/strong&gt; is a progressive neurodegenerative disease that leads to cognitive decline and memory loss. Early-onset cases—those appearing before the age of 65—account for &lt;strong&gt;about 10%&lt;/strong&gt; of diagnoses. However, almost all cases in young patients are linked to genetic mutations associated with &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.alzforum.org/early-onset-familial-ad/overview/what-early-onset-familial-alzheimer-disease-efad" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;familial Alzheimer’s disease &lt;/a&gt;(FAD)&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;This &lt;strong&gt;teenage patient&lt;/strong&gt; had no family history of dementia, no genetic markers of the condition, and no prior infections or head trauma that could explain his symptoms. Yet, by the time he was referred to a &lt;strong&gt;memory clinic&lt;/strong&gt;, his cognitive abilities had already deteriorated significantly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="code-block code-block-3"&gt;


&lt;ins class="adsbygoogle" data-ad-client="ca-pub-6966113680805338" data-ad-slot="4788484402" data-ad-format="auto" data-full-width-responsive="true"&gt;&lt;/ins&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;The Unexplained Progression of Symptoms&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The patient first began experiencing memory issues &lt;strong&gt;at 17&lt;/strong&gt;, struggling with concentration and recall. Over time, his short-term memory worsened—he often forgot events from the previous day and misplaced belongings.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;By the time he was 19, tests showed that his &lt;strong&gt;memory function was severely impaired&lt;/strong&gt;, with his recall ability scoring nearly&lt;strong&gt; 87% lower&lt;/strong&gt; than his peers. MRI scans revealed &lt;strong&gt;shrinkage in the hippocampus&lt;/strong&gt;, a key brain region responsible for memory, while cerebrospinal fluid tests indicated the presence of &lt;strong&gt;biomarkers &lt;/strong&gt;linked to Alzheimer’s.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;What Makes This Case Unique?&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Before this case, the youngest confirmed Alzheimer’s patient was &lt;strong&gt;21 years old&lt;/strong&gt; and carried a mutation in the &lt;strong&gt;PSEN1 gene&lt;/strong&gt;, which leads to toxic protein buildup in the brain. This newly diagnosed teenager, however, &lt;strong&gt;had no detectable genetic abnormalities&lt;/strong&gt;, making his case even more mysterious.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="code-block code-block-3"&gt;


&lt;ins class="adsbygoogle" data-ad-client="ca-pub-6966113680805338" data-ad-slot="4788484402" data-ad-format="auto" data-full-width-responsive="true"&gt;&lt;/ins&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;p&gt;Scientists have long known that Alzheimer’s is &lt;strong&gt;not a one-size-fits-all disease&lt;/strong&gt;. While common in older adults, early-onset cases may develop &lt;strong&gt;t&lt;/strong&gt;hrough different, still unknown mechanisms. This case is forcing researchers to rethink their understanding of how and why Alzheimer’s begins.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;The Future of Alzheimer’s Research&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Experts say this unusual case raises critical scientific questions. If a previously healthy teenager can develop &lt;strong&gt;Alzheimer’s without a genetic link&lt;/strong&gt;, are there other unknown environmental or biological factors at play?&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Neurologists at &lt;strong&gt;Capital Medical University in Beijing&lt;/strong&gt;, who published the case study in the &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://content.iospress.com/articles/journal-of-alzheimers-disease/jad221065" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Journal of Alzheimer’s Disease&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;, emphasized the need for more research on young patients. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="code-block code-block-3"&gt;


&lt;ins class="adsbygoogle" data-ad-client="ca-pub-6966113680805338" data-ad-slot="4788484402" data-ad-format="auto" data-full-width-responsive="true"&gt;&lt;/ins&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;p&gt;They believe studying&lt;strong&gt; early-onset cases &lt;/strong&gt;could unlock new insights into the fundamental causes of Alzheimer’s, potentially leading to earlier detection and better treatments.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;In the words of the researchers, “Exploring the mysteries of young people with Alzheimer’s disease may become one of the most challenging scientific questions of the future.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Indian Defence Review</author><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 12:45:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi6AFBVV95cUxQU1l4RUliUUhUQmhWSUxzdmgwdUJoQWlzak1FR0xQQnI4bjBqYWFlQ2t6WjVPTjkzNV80bVZYWkhza2hxZl9zdm5KNmNub0Y3cVVoVG8xa1AxTHRCbnhwYnlRX2RyWW9uYm5yTkVYR283MW9DSFotZUZQem5Xb1Z4Wl9EQ202Sk4wdlVuaFJCTEJGQzdHMWNrSE44YUVNb0JxNnZvOXhCc2xUX0FlcDVvZE5GLVN2RGxGUkdUdkFkRFRLMmF3YTdKTkVsVGVUb1ZZZEwzaXpOaWgwb1doQkRDUlprcjhFLTRG</guid></item><item><title>The Scramble After a White House Showdown, and R.F.K. Jr.’s Measles Response - The New York Times</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMioAFBVV95cUxNWmw1clIyMXJocDM1dlFiYjFfWGxUUW5IT21tZ2N4MWNiUHJtUXhLUE9EdXctcGNLTzFIdHA5NFZPSnVNYm43amdTcGJmYXd6MVlRaUdmTVBnbmpKRFFweFB1QUFrRzV2Y3lZSjZBSlBqcEVrZFFaajVocU5Qd0dSdEsyMVFvUUdSV2ZjWjVaa2pleDA5VlJtMkt5U2NSR3dS?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The New York Times</author><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 11:24:44 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMioAFBVV95cUxNWmw1clIyMXJocDM1dlFiYjFfWGxUUW5IT21tZ2N4MWNiUHJtUXhLUE9EdXctcGNLTzFIdHA5NFZPSnVNYm43amdTcGJmYXd6MVlRaUdmTVBnbmpKRFFweFB1QUFrRzV2Y3lZSjZBSlBqcEVrZFFaajVocU5Qd0dSdEsyMVFvUUdSV2ZjWjVaa2pleDA5VlJtMkt5U2NSR3dS</guid></item><item><title>Chewing wood may boost memory and brain antioxidants, study finds - PsyPost</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMikwFBVV95cUxNV2Y3Z29Gd3kxR3RiRzktVU5MT2hXUko4aE01OU5mWlVuQjZMbkdJanVCMEtRQjBVcjZlWkx0WFE5YTJQV0JzRnJzTmVCUzhyUXJxZVBIOVVYNDRlOUpaU2taSEM4X2VuNGpIazd3OEVndkxCZEFJZjdTSzRHaVdGSFJMUktsT2gteFdtSlpjVWE5RmM?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="content-inner "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chewing on moderately hard foods, like wood, might do more than just break down your lunch; new research suggests it could actually boost brainpower by increasing levels of a natural antioxidant, which in turn may improve memory. A recent study published in &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.frontiersin.org/journals/systems-neuroscience/articles/10.3389/fnsys.2024.1489919/full" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Frontiers in Systems Neuroscience&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; explored how chewing different materials affects the brain and found that chewing on wood, compared to chewing gum, led to a significant increase in a brain antioxidant called glutathione.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Previous research has suggested that the act of chewing can influence brain activity and blood flow. This is important because the brain requires a constant supply of oxygen and nutrients to function properly, and blood flow is the delivery system for these essential resources. Some studies have even shown that people with chewing difficulties tend to experience poorer cognitive abilities. However, exactly what metabolic changes occur in the brain when chewing improves blood flow has remained unclear.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One area of interest is oxidative stress in the brain. Oxidative stress is essentially damage to brain cells caused by harmful molecules called reactive oxygen species. This kind of damage is thought to play a significant role in the decline of brain function as we age. The brain is especially vulnerable to oxidative stress because it uses a lot of oxygen and contains fats that are easily damaged. To protect itself, the brain uses antioxidants, and one of the most important is glutathione.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Glutathione acts like a bodyguard for brain cells, neutralizing harmful reactive oxygen species. Researchers in this study were curious if chewing, and specifically chewing materials of different hardness, could influence the levels of this protective antioxidant, glutathione, in the brain. They also wanted to see if any changes in glutathione were related to changes in thinking skills.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To investigate these questions, the researchers recruited 52 healthy university students in South Korea. They divided the students into two groups: one group would chew gum, and the other group would chew small wooden sticks, similar to popsicle sticks. The researchers made sure the groups were similar in age, gender, and education level.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Before the chewing began, and again after five minutes of chewing, the researchers used a special brain scanning technique called Magnetic Resonance Spectroscopy to measure the levels of glutathione in a specific area of the brain called the anterior cingulate cortex. This brain region is known to be important for cognitive control and thinking processes. Magnetic Resonance Spectroscopy is a non-invasive method that allows scientists to measure the concentration of different chemicals in the brain. The specific technique they used, called MEGA-PRESS, is particularly good at measuring glutathione.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;During the chewing task, participants were positioned comfortably and instructed to chew for five minutes. To keep the chewing consistent, they were asked to chew on the right side of their mouth at a rate of once per second, alternating between 30 seconds of chewing and 30 seconds of rest. One group chewed paraffin wax gum, which is a standard type of chewing gum used in research. The other group chewed on wooden tongue depressors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Both before and after the chewing session, all participants also completed a cognitive test called the Korean Repeatable Battery for the Assessment of Neuropsychological State. This test is designed to quickly assess different aspects of thinking skills, including memory, attention, language, and visual-spatial abilities. This allowed the researchers to see if there was any change in cognitive function related to the chewing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;After analyzing the data, the researchers found some interesting results. First, they looked at the glutathione levels in the anterior cingulate cortex before and after chewing. In the group that chewed wood, they observed a significant increase in glutathione levels after chewing compared to before. This means that chewing wood seemed to boost the amount of this important antioxidant in that brain region.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, in the gum-chewing group, there was no significant change in glutathione levels after chewing. While there wasn’t a statistically significant difference in the change in glutathione levels between the gum and wood groups directly, the trend was clearly towards a greater increase in the wood-chewing group.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Next, the researchers examined the relationship between changes in glutathione levels and performance on the cognitive tests. They found that in the wood-chewing group, the increase in glutathione levels was positively related to scores on immediate memory and story memory tests. This means that participants who showed a larger increase in glutathione after chewing wood also tended to perform better on memory tasks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Interestingly, this relationship was not found in the gum-chewing group. There was no link between changes in glutathione and memory performance for those who chewed gum. In essence, chewing wood seemed to both increase brain antioxidant levels and improve certain aspects of memory, and these two changes appeared to be connected.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But the study, like all research, has some limitations to consider. Firstly, the participants were all young, healthy university students in their twenties. It’s not clear if these findings would be the same in older adults or in people with health conditions. Future studies should include a wider range of ages to see if the effects of chewing on glutathione and cognition are consistent across the lifespan.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Secondly, the study focused on just one specific brain region, the anterior cingulate cortex. While this region is important for thinking, it would be beneficial to investigate other brain areas to get a more complete picture of how chewing affects the brain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thirdly, the chewing period was relatively short, only five minutes. It’s possible that longer chewing durations, or different patterns of chewing, could have different effects. Also, while the study compared gum and wood, these materials differ in more ways than just hardness. Texture and other properties could also play a role. Future research could explore a wider variety of chewing materials and try to objectively measure the hardness of what people are chewing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“In summary, this study yielded two major findings. Firstly, the wood-chewing group experienced stimulated of brain [glutathione (GSH)] synthesis, leading to increased GSH levels in the brain,” the researchers concluded. “Secondly, correlation analysis indicated that the higher GSH levels in the wood-chewing group were associated with improved scores in cognitive measures. Since there are currently no drugs or established practices for boosting brain GSH levels, our findings suggest that chewing moderately hard material could serve as an effective practice for increasing GSH levels in the brain. Based on these results, consuming harder foods might prove more effective in enhancing brain antioxidant defenses through elevated GSH levels.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study, “&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.3389/fnsys.2024.1489919" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Effect of Chewing Hard Material on Boosting Brain Antioxidant Levels and Enhancing Cognitive Function&lt;/a&gt;,” was authored by Seungho Kim, Ji-Hye Kim, Hansol Lee, Sung Ho Jang, Ralph Noeske, Changho Choi, Yongmin Chang, and Youn-Hee Choi.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>PsyPost</author><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 11:19:04 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikwFBVV95cUxNV2Y3Z29Gd3kxR3RiRzktVU5MT2hXUko4aE01OU5mWlVuQjZMbkdJanVCMEtRQjBVcjZlWkx0WFE5YTJQV0JzRnJzTmVCUzhyUXJxZVBIOVVYNDRlOUpaU2taSEM4X2VuNGpIazd3OEVndkxCZEFJZjdTSzRHaVdGSFJMUktsT2gteFdtSlpjVWE5RmM</guid></item><item><title>The Flu Is Different This Year, And Cases Are Surging. An Expert Explains Why. - ScienceAlert</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMipwFBVV95cUxQZDI4UG13MWo1OWlyWGdabFFpY2JNSGhIeEt1TGx2aExTN3RZUEZjZDJlWWFFNUMtX25mSmo5NmVOOEFzcHc4SlpqQnIwWUFPT0RRMllfV3lEWnpOUWhNZTlqQmdDcFo0djhPRVVUYVgwOUVLaFF4bDRZcXVnN3g0M3lzYUx5UG5oaDlnLW9fekxOQk4tb1YtYWFqTzM2UWYzSWF1OHNaWQ?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;In February 2025,  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/what-is-influenza" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="103478" data-postid="153901" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;flu&lt;/a&gt; rates spiked to the &lt;a href="https://www.pbs.org/newshour/health/u-s-facing-most-intense-flu-season-in-at-least-15-years"&gt;highest levels seen in at least 15 years&lt;/a&gt;, with &lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/news/flu-deaths-surpass-covid-for-first-time-since-pandemic-started/"&gt;flu outpacing COVID-19 infections and hospitalizations&lt;/a&gt; for the first time since the beginning of the  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/coronavirus" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73041" data-postid="153901" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;COVID-19&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/pandemic" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73047" data-postid="153901" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;pandemic&lt;/a&gt;. The Centers for Disease Control and Prevention has classified this &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/flu/php/surveillance/in-season-severity.html"&gt;flu season as having "high" severity&lt;/a&gt; across the U.S.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Conversation asked &lt;a href="https://scholar.google.com/citations?user=Pu3L9HkAAAAJ&amp;amp;hl=en"&gt;epidemiologist&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://ph.ucla.edu/about/faculty-staff-directory/annette-regan"&gt;Annette Regan&lt;/a&gt; to explain why this flu season is different from last year's and what people can do to help reduce the spread.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;How do flu cases and hospitalizations this year compare with previous years?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Beginning in late January and extending through February 2025, flu hospitalizations &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/fluview/surveillance/2025-week-07.html"&gt;have been higher&lt;/a&gt; than any other week &lt;a href="https://gis.cdc.gov/GRASP/Fluview/FluHospRates.html"&gt;since before 2009&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Most flu cases appear to be from  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/what-is-influenza" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="103478" data-postid="153901" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;influenza&lt;/a&gt; A strains, with a split between influenza A/H3N2 and influenza A/H1N1. These are &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/flu/about/viruses-types.html"&gt;two different subtypes&lt;/a&gt; of the influenza A  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/virus" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73053" data-postid="153901" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;virus&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Researchers believe that historically seasons that are predominated by influenza A/H3N2 infections &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.jhin.2023.06.024"&gt;tend to be more severe&lt;/a&gt;, but infections from influenza A/H1N1 &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/S2666-5247(23)00187-8"&gt;can still be very severe&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This year's season is also peaking "late" compared with the past three flu seasons, which peaked in early or late December.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Unfortunately, there have been a number of deaths from flu too this season. Since Jan. 1, 2025, alone, over &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/fluview/surveillance/2025-week-06.html#cdc_data_surveillance_section_6-mortality-surveillance"&gt;4,000 people, including 68 children, have died&lt;/a&gt; from flu. While the number of deaths do not mark a record number, it shows that flu can be a serious illness, even in children.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;p class="aspect-w-16 aspect-h-9 youtube-iframe relative"&gt;&lt;iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/fH6v_uQYPs4?wmode=transparent&amp;amp;start=0" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen&gt;VIDEO&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;Unless directed otherwise, everyone ages 6 months and older should get a flu shot.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Why are flu cases so high this year?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;There are a number of factors behind any severe season, including poor community protection from low immunization rates and low natural immunity, virus characteristics, vaccine effectiveness and increased human contact via travel, office work or schools.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Unfortunately, flu vaccination rates have declined since the COVID-19 pandemic. At the end of the 2023-24 flu season, &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/fluvaxview/dashboard/adult-vaccinations-administered.html"&gt;9.2 million fewer doses&lt;/a&gt; were administered in pharmacies and doctors' offices compared with an average year before the pandemic.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In addition, since 2022, fewer and fewer doses of flu vaccine &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/fluvaxview/dashboard/vaccine-doses-distributed.html"&gt;have been distributed&lt;/a&gt; by private manufacturers. Flu vaccination rates for adults have historically been in the 30% to 60% range, &lt;a href="https://odphp.health.gov/healthypeople/objectives-and-data/browse-objectives/vaccination/increase-proportion-people-who-get-flu-vaccine-every-year-iid-09"&gt;much lower than the recommended 70%&lt;/a&gt;. Before the COVID-19 pandemic, flu vaccination rates were increasing by &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/adultvaxview/publications-resources/vaccination-coverage-adults-2019-2020.html"&gt;around 1% to 2% every year&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Flu vaccination rates began dropping after the COVID-19 pandemic, especially in higher-risk groups. Flu vaccination &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/fluvaxview/dashboard/children-vaccination-coverage.html"&gt;in children has dropped&lt;/a&gt; from 59% in 2019-20 to 46% in 2024-25. In adults 65 years and older, the group with the greatest risk of hospitalization and death, flu vaccination rates dropped &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/fluvaxview/dashboard/adults-65-years-and-older.html"&gt;from 52% in 2019-20 to 43% in 2024-25&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lower vaccination rates mean a greater portion of the population is not protected by vaccines. Data shows that vaccination &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1080/21645515.2017.1321722"&gt;reduces the risk of flu hospitalization&lt;/a&gt;. Even if a vaccinated person gets infected, they may be &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/S1473-3099(22)00493-5"&gt;less likely to experience severe illness&lt;/a&gt;. As a result, low vaccination rates could contribute to higher flu severity this season.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;However, low vaccination rates are probably not the only reason for the high rates of flu this season. In previous severe seasons, &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/S2666-5247(24)00067-3"&gt;genetic changes to the viruses&lt;/a&gt; have made them better at infecting people and more likely to cause severe illness.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The effectiveness of annual flu vaccines varies depending on how well the vaccine matches the circulating virus. The effectiveness of vaccines &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/fluvaxview/coverage-by-season/2023-2024.html"&gt;ranges from 19% to 60%&lt;/a&gt; in any given season. In the 2023-24 flu season, the vaccine was 42% effective.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Similarly, early 2024-25 data from the U.S. shows that the vaccine was &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/mmwr/volumes/74/wr/mm7406a2.htm?s_cid=mm7406a2_e&amp;amp;ACSTrackingID=USCDC_921-DM145368&amp;amp;ACSTrackingLabel=This%20Week%20in%20MMWR%3A%20Vol.%2074%2C%20February%2027%2C%202025&amp;amp;deliveryName=USCDC_921-DM145368"&gt;41% to 55% effective&lt;/a&gt; against flu hospitalizations in adults and &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/mmwr/volumes/74/wr/mm7406a2.htm?s_cid=mm7406a2_e&amp;amp;ACSTrackingID=USCDC_921-DM145368&amp;amp;ACSTrackingLabel=This%20Week%20in%20MMWR%3A%20Vol.%2074%2C%20February%2027%2C%202025&amp;amp;deliveryName=USCDC_921-DM145368"&gt;63% to 78% effective&lt;/a&gt; against flu hospitalizations in children.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;
&lt;p class="aspect-w-16 aspect-h-9 youtube-iframe relative"&gt;&lt;iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/8DhgzpELrPI?wmode=transparent&amp;amp;start=0" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen&gt;VIDEO&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;Something as simple as regular handwashing could keep you from getting the flu.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;h2&gt;How do seasonal flu symptoms differ from COVID-19 and other illnesses?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;It's important to remember that people often incorrectly refer to "the flu" when they have a common cold. Flu is caused only by the influenza virus, which tends to be &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/flu/about/coldflu.html"&gt;more severe than common colds&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.ucsfhealth.org/education/cold-or-flu"&gt;more commonly causes a fever&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Many of the signs and symptoms for flu, COVID-19 and other respiratory  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/virus" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73053" data-postid="153901" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;viruses&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/flu/about/flu-vs-covid19.html"&gt;are the same&lt;/a&gt; and can range from mild coldlike symptoms to  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/pneumonia" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73057" data-postid="153901" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;pneumonia&lt;/a&gt; and respiratory distress. Common flu symptoms are  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/fever" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73066" data-postid="153901" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;fever&lt;/a&gt;, cough and fatigue, and may also include shortness of breath, a sore throat, nasal congestion, muscle aches and headache.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some symptoms, such as changes in or loss of taste and smell, are &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.3390/jcm9061753"&gt;more common for COVID-19&lt;/a&gt;. For both COVID-19 and flu, the symptoms do not start until about &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/flu/about/flu-vs-covid19.html"&gt;one to four days after infection&lt;/a&gt;, and symptoms seem to last longer for COVID-19.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The only way to know what virus is causing an infection is to test. This can be done using a rapid test, &lt;a href="https://www.fda.gov/medical-devices/coronavirus-covid-19-and-medical-devices/home-otc-covid-19-diagnostic-tests"&gt;some of which now test for flu and COVID-19 together&lt;/a&gt;, or by seeing a doctor and getting tested using a nasal swab. There are prescription antiviral medications available to treat flu and COVID-19, but they need to be taken near the time that symptoms start.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some people are at &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/flu/highrisk/index.htm"&gt;high risk of severe flu&lt;/a&gt; and COVID-19, such as those who are immunosuppressed, have  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/diabetes" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73018" data-postid="153901" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;diabetes&lt;/a&gt; or have chronic heart or lung conditions. In these cases, it is important to seek early care and treatment from a health care professional. Some doctors will also prescribe via telehealth calls, which can help reduce the strain on doctors' offices, urgent care centers and emergency rooms when infection rates are high.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;What can people do now to help steer clear of the flu?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;There are a number of ways people can reduce their risk of getting or spreading flu. Since the flu season is still underway, it's not too late to get a flu vaccine. Even in seasons when the vaccine's effectiveness is low, it is likely to offer better protection compared with remaining unvaccinated.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/clean-hands/about/index.html"&gt;Handwashing&lt;/a&gt; and disinfecting high-traffic surfaces can help reduce contact with the flu virus. Taking efforts to avoid contact with sick people can also help, including wearing a mask when in health care facilities.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Finally, remember to take care of yourself. &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/flu/prevention/actions-prevent-flu.html"&gt;Exercising, eating healthy and getting sufficient sleep&lt;/a&gt; all help support a healthy immune system, which can help reduce chances of infection.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Those who have been diagnosed with flu or are experiencing flu-like symptoms should avoid contact with other people, especially in crowded spaces. Covering coughs and sneezes can help reduce the amount of virus that is spread.&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://counter.theconversation.com/content/250252/count.gif?distributor=republish-lightbox-basic" alt="The Conversation" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" loading="lazy"&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/profiles/annette-regan-210075"&gt;Annette Regan&lt;/a&gt;, Adjunct Associate Professor of Epidemiology, &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/institutions/university-of-california-los-angeles-1301"&gt;&lt;em&gt;University of California, Los Angeles&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This article is republished from &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com"&gt;The Conversation&lt;/a&gt; under a Creative Commons license. Read the &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/as-flu-cases-break-records-this-year-vaccine-rates-are-declining-particularly-for-children-and-65-adults-250252"&gt;original article&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 11:01:41 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipwFBVV95cUxQZDI4UG13MWo1OWlyWGdabFFpY2JNSGhIeEt1TGx2aExTN3RZUEZjZDJlWWFFNUMtX25mSmo5NmVOOEFzcHc4SlpqQnIwWUFPT0RRMllfV3lEWnpOUWhNZTlqQmdDcFo0djhPRVVUYVgwOUVLaFF4bDRZcXVnN3g0M3lzYUx5UG5oaDlnLW9fekxOQk4tb1YtYWFqTzM2UWYzSWF1OHNaWQ</guid></item><item><title>84% IT employees in India have fatty liver disease, 71% obese, study finds - Deccan Herald</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiwwFBVV95cUxOdVlMSUlhcjc1MFJyN2RMYWJodkdlaGNZeHROTmk3Z2xhN1piRERpRV9mTThqWGM5SGoxaUI3MXdfU2h4WmlHekhiSnVPenV5Vk9aMWVJYWFUaVI3dmszZFFKN3NqbVdmUVQ5ZmtjZm96ZmhNMWFrZkhYWjhERW9ZVGxQX0ZaRUQ0TTVlR1pGZC03ZE5qUjZaZDJMdTJjdENQSkhTN0QzdlMtRkszMTNvdHZBT2czd0V2ZjV2eWxmMXFsaDg?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="story-content-9558fb8d-8b46-4d61-8156-17212fb5fa0b" class="story-cards taboola-read-more-container"&gt;&lt;p class="wW6Na"&gt;Published 03 March 2025, 10:59 IST&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Deccan Herald</author><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 10:59:06 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiwwFBVV95cUxOdVlMSUlhcjc1MFJyN2RMYWJodkdlaGNZeHROTmk3Z2xhN1piRERpRV9mTThqWGM5SGoxaUI3MXdfU2h4WmlHekhiSnVPenV5Vk9aMWVJYWFUaVI3dmszZFFKN3NqbVdmUVQ5ZmtjZm96ZmhNMWFrZkhYWjhERW9ZVGxQX0ZaRUQ0TTVlR1pGZC03ZE5qUjZaZDJMdTJjdENQSkhTN0QzdlMtRkszMTNvdHZBT2czd0V2ZjV2eWxmMXFsaDg</guid></item><item><title>What Hormone Therapy Can Do For Menopause and Long-term Health - The New York Times</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMimAFBVV95cUxPcTdQem94ZVByNlctcHdCNmRkNnlvRHpYNUM0T2tiTzk0VHZHRW5oekZZWldIRndDWGM3YWtpUWpkVW16bEQySXZPWXJ2Z3FtdEppei1PNHl3VTNPaUtPQ21UWmttMXNDU19DSkxwUE53MTRuWDBPbFZIUWtlb0J5VVVLOUxxZVJzaTloX2ZVMzVmZ0lkRE5FMg?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="css-s99gbd StoryBodyCompanionColumn" data-testid="companionColumn-0"&gt;&lt;div class="css-53u6y8"&gt;&lt;p class="css-at9mc1 evys1bk0"&gt;At Dr. Monica Christmas’s clinic these days, she sees two kinds of menopausal patients. The first, she said, is suffering from the symptoms associated with this &lt;a class="css-yywogo" href="https://www.nytimes.com/2023/02/01/magazine/menopause-hot-flashes-hormone-therapy.html" title=""&gt;life phase&lt;/a&gt;, but is also wary of hormone therapy because she’s heard there are health risks associated with it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="css-at9mc1 evys1bk0"&gt;The second kind of patient is almost the exact opposite: she may not have symptoms at all, but nonetheless is asking for hormones because she’s heard they will make her healthier.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="css-at9mc1 evys1bk0"&gt;“We seem to like these extremes,” said Dr. Christmas, the director of the Menopause Program and Center for Women’s Integrated Health at the University of Chicago.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="css-at9mc1 evys1bk0"&gt;Prescription data reflects a persistent anxiety around the health risks: In a study &lt;a class="css-yywogo" href="https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jama-health-forum/fullarticle/2823976?utm_campaign=articlePDF&amp;amp;utm_medium=articlePDFlink&amp;amp;utm_source=articlePDF&amp;amp;utm_content=jamahealthforum.2024.3128" title="" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;published in September&lt;/a&gt;, researchers found that only 5 percent of menopausal women used hormones in 2020 despite the fact that roughly 80 percent of women experience symptoms. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="css-s99gbd StoryBodyCompanionColumn" data-testid="companionColumn-1"&gt;&lt;div class="css-53u6y8"&gt;&lt;p class="css-at9mc1 evys1bk0"&gt;On the flip side, in the last few years, a growing number of &lt;a class="css-yywogo" href="https://www.nytimes.com/2024/10/30/well/dr-mary-claire-haver-menopause.html" title=""&gt;social media influencers&lt;/a&gt; and celebrities, like Oprah Winfrey, have loudly endorsed hormone therapy, presenting it as a “magic elixir,” Dr. Christmas said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="css-at9mc1 evys1bk0"&gt;“Now there’s this messaging that every woman who is menopausal should be on hormone therapy,” she said. But women need more clarity around what hormone therapy can and can’t do. “We’ve got to find our way back to the middle ground.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="css-1336jj"&gt;&lt;div class="css-121kum4"&gt;&lt;p class="css-171quhb"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="css-asuuk5"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;div class="css-7axq9l" data-testid="optimistic-truncator-noscript"&gt;&lt;svg viewbox="0 0 24 24" aria-hidden="true" class="css-1b5b8u1"&gt;&lt;path fill="currentColor" fill-rule="evenodd" d="M2.5 12a9.5 9.5 0 1 1 19 0 9.5 9.5 0 0 1-19 0Zm8.5 1.75v-7.5h2v7.5h-2Zm0 2v2h2v-2h-2Z" clip-rule="evenodd"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;div data-testid="optimistic-truncator-noscript-message" class="css-6yo1no"&gt;&lt;p class="css-3kpklk"&gt;We are having trouble retrieving the article content.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="css-3kpklk"&gt;Please enable JavaScript in your browser settings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;div class="css-1dv1kvn" id="optimistic-truncator-a11y" tabindex="-1"&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thank you for your patience while we verify access. If you are in Reader mode please exit and &lt;a href="https://myaccount.nytimes.com/auth/login?response_type=cookie&amp;amp;client_id=vi&amp;amp;redirect_uri=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.nytimes.com%2F2025%2F03%2F03%2Fwell%2Fhormone-therapy-for-menopause-risks-and-benefits.html&amp;amp;asset=opttrunc"&gt;log into&lt;/a&gt; your Times account, or &lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/subscription?campaignId=89WYR&amp;amp;redirect_uri=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.nytimes.com%2F2025%2F03%2F03%2Fwell%2Fhormone-therapy-for-menopause-risks-and-benefits.html"&gt;subscribe&lt;/a&gt; for all of The Times.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="css-1g71tqy"&gt;&lt;svg viewbox="0 0 24 24" aria-hidden="true" class="css-63woee" data-testid="optimistic-truncator-spinner"&gt;&lt;g fill="currentColor"&gt;&lt;path d="M11.28 22.8a.72.72 0 1 0 1.44 0v-6.72a.72.72 0 1 0-1.44 0v6.72Z" opacity=".37"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="M17.766 21.16a.72.72 0 1 0 1.165-.846l-3.95-5.436a.72.72 0 1 0-1.165.846l3.95 5.437Z" opacity=".26"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="M1.506 14.653a.72.72 0 0 0 .445 1.37l6.391-2.078a.72.72 0 1 0-.445-1.369l-6.39 2.077Z" opacity=".61"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="M5.07 20.314a.72.72 0 0 0 1.164.847l3.95-5.437a.72.72 0 1 0-1.165-.846l-3.95 5.436Z" opacity=".48"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="M22.049 16.022a.72.72 0 0 0 .445-1.37l-6.391-2.076a.72.72 0 1 0-.445 1.37l6.39 2.076Z" opacity=".17"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="M22.494 9.347a.72.72 0 1 0-.445-1.37l-6.391 2.078a.72.72 0 1 0 .445 1.369l6.39-2.077Z" opacity=".09"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="M6.234 2.84a.72.72 0 0 0-1.165.846l3.95 5.436a.72.72 0 0 0 1.165-.846l-3.95-5.437Z" opacity=".87"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="M1.951 7.978a.72.72 0 1 0-.445 1.37l6.391 2.076a.72.72 0 1 0 .445-1.37l-6.39-2.076Z" opacity=".74"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="M18.93 3.686a.72.72 0 0 0-1.164-.847l-3.95 5.437a.72.72 0 0 0 1.165.846l3.95-5.436Z" opacity=".02"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="M12.72 1.2a.72.72 0 1 0-1.44 0v6.72a.72.72 0 0 0 1.44 0V1.2Z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/g&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;div data-testid="optimistic-truncator-message" class="css-6yo1no"&gt;&lt;p class="css-3kpklk"&gt;Thank you for your patience while we verify access.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="css-3kpklk"&gt;Already a subscriber? &lt;a data-testid="log-in-link" class="css-z5ryv4" href="https://myaccount.nytimes.com/auth/login?response_type=cookie&amp;amp;client_id=vi&amp;amp;redirect_uri=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.nytimes.com%2F2025%2F03%2F03%2Fwell%2Fhormone-therapy-for-menopause-risks-and-benefits.html&amp;amp;asset=opttrunc"&gt;Log in&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="css-3kpklk"&gt;Want all of The Times? &lt;a data-testid="subscribe-link" class="css-z5ryv4" href="https://www.nytimes.com/subscription?campaignId=89WYR&amp;amp;redirect_uri=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.nytimes.com%2F2025%2F03%2F03%2Fwell%2Fhormone-therapy-for-menopause-risks-and-benefits.html"&gt;Subscribe&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The New York Times</author><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 10:01:02 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimAFBVV95cUxPcTdQem94ZVByNlctcHdCNmRkNnlvRHpYNUM0T2tiTzk0VHZHRW5oekZZWldIRndDWGM3YWtpUWpkVW16bEQySXZPWXJ2Z3FtdEppei1PNHl3VTNPaUtPQ21UWmttMXNDU19DSkxwUE53MTRuWDBPbFZIUWtlb0J5VVVLOUxxZVJzaTloX2ZVMzVmZ0lkRE5FMg</guid></item><item><title>CDC estimates flu vaccine effectiveness as cases slam the region - TribLIVE</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiogFBVV95cUxOdlRDWUQ3dThmMVNQU3BBN09nWmpxcU5kOEdFYUY5cndUV2FvdExQZzVQU0dzTHRnUzZ5TzY5REZyeEg1TVd4VlF0Q2YyX1EteGhYTDNHa3pNUDBaUm5YeDF6ekRHYXpGblJTRFpnTU1RWVVleWcyLXhKcGNiSThteEJmWG5RWjVWbVZ6UE1JTXVNREw3Y1Q0MnJoLVhtU3J6dkE?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="container"&gt;
	
		

				
		
		&lt;a class="logo triblive-logo-link" href="/"&gt;
    		&lt;img src="https://triblive.com/wp-content/themes/TribLIVE2/assets/visuals/images/icons/head/TribLIVElogo.png" alt="TribLive" class="triblive-logo"&gt;
		&lt;/a&gt;
	
		
	
		&lt;h1&gt;&lt;i class="fa-solid fa-shield-halved"&gt;&lt;/i&gt; NOTICE OF YOUR PRIVACY RIGHTS  IN Virginia &lt;/h1&gt;

		
		&lt;p&gt;Because you are coming from a location (Virginia) covered by a Privacy Law, many of the features of TribLIVE.com, like videos and social media elements are disabled.  If you wish to proceed to the site under those conditions (doing so will effectively opt you out of the sale of your personal data) &lt;a href="#" id="setCookieLinkOut"&gt;click here&lt;/a&gt;. However you will not experience the full features of TribLIVE.com that rely upon third party networks that may require your personal data.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="privacy-boxes"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="#" id="setCookieLinkIn"&gt;Click here&lt;/a&gt; to agree to experience the full features of TribLIVE.com and to opt in to the use of your personal data to provide that experience and advertising.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
			
			
		&lt;p&gt;Bookmark this page to manage your preferences any time in the future. &lt;/p&gt;
	
	&lt;div class="privacy-boxes"&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;If YOU ARE NOT visiting us as a resident of Virginia?  Please update your location to ensure you are presented with the best experience. &lt;/p&gt;
	


		
		
	&lt;/div&gt;
		
		


		
		&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>TribLIVE</author><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 10:01:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiogFBVV95cUxOdlRDWUQ3dThmMVNQU3BBN09nWmpxcU5kOEdFYUY5cndUV2FvdExQZzVQU0dzTHRnUzZ5TzY5REZyeEg1TVd4VlF0Q2YyX1EteGhYTDNHa3pNUDBaUm5YeDF6ekRHYXpGblJTRFpnTU1RWVVleWcyLXhKcGNiSThteEJmWG5RWjVWbVZ6UE1JTXVNREw3Y1Q0MnJoLVhtU3J6dkE</guid></item><item><title>Living a long time isn't just about good genes, a new study says. 4 lifestyle changes that can improve your longevity. - Yahoo Life</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMi8wFBVV95cUxOUl95TjVlRk50SVB0eGtUNTVtSUZ2cl95c0o1ZDdQdER4a2hCMVk1LU54TkNkVFVSYTQyZDRVWmtxM0VZYnVVNzdSUXcyOVF2c080Z3YtSWZvVTEyaGNCbVVFVENwMkNReVRKUzA4VFhiMFB4aEJuVEdfWjdhNzk5aWF5eVN4eFNWdFlCbXl1a2JSRzYxRnl5a0lRQ214aGJ5enpXdlFROUJtUks3UGVKaVpNT0JBaEdMNUluX1VSRG9xRkhWSmZSV1pkSVNfY0tKOHVoemx3TUZLYmpEZlFVVm9Kb0ZLcV9zZWUxODl3ZlhQSTg?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="" data-article-body="true"&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;If you have a parent or grandparent who’s reached their 90s or even become a &lt;a data-i13n="elm:context_link;elmt:doNotAffiliate;cpos:1;pos:1" class="link  yahoo-link" href="https://www.yahoo.com/lifestyle/lessons-on-aging-from-the-oldest-people-in-the-world-eat-your-veggies-avoid-toxic-people-move-your-body-and-more-201123414.html" data-ylk="slk:centenarian;elm:context_link;elmt:doNotAffiliate;cpos:1;pos:1;itc:0;sec:content-canvas;outcm:mb_qualified_link;_E:mb_qualified_link;ct:story;"&gt;centenarian&lt;/a&gt;, someone’s probably said to you, “Oh, you have good genes!” But if longevity doesn’t seem to run in your family, fret not: &lt;a data-i13n="elm:context_link;elmt:doNotAffiliate;cpos:2;pos:1" class="link  yahoo-link" href="https://www.yahoo.com/lifestyle/the-us-has-the-biggest-lifespan-health-span-gap-in-the-world-new-study-shows-were-living-longer-lives--but-not-in-good-health-170707093.html" data-ylk="slk:Lifespan;elm:context_link;elmt:doNotAffiliate;cpos:2;pos:1;itc:0;sec:content-canvas;outcm:mb_qualified_link;_E:mb_qualified_link;ct:story;"&gt;Lifespan&lt;/a&gt; has more to do with your life&lt;em&gt;style&lt;/em&gt; and environment than with your genetics, according to a &lt;a data-i13n="elm:context_link;elmt:doNotAffiliate;cpos:3;pos:1" class="link " href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41591-024-03483-9#MOESM1" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:study;elm:context_link;elmt:doNotAffiliate;cpos:3;pos:1;itc:0;sec:content-canvas"&gt;study&lt;/a&gt; published in the journal Nature Medicine&lt;em&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;In other words, there’s a lot you can do to take control of your own destiny when it comes to longevity, regardless of how long your relatives lived. Here’s what to know.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mb-4 text-xl font-bold md:text-2xl" data-jump-link-target="" id="what-the-study-found"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What the study found&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Using data on nearly half a million people from the U.K., Oxford University researchers looked for patterns in who died prematurely, or before the age of 75. They also looked at markers of biological aging in a smaller subset of the study group (over 45,000 people). Their analysis included comparisons of genetic risk factors for disease as well as what some scientists have termed the “exposome.” Our DNA makes up our genome, whereas the exposome is made up of all the exposures we encounter throughout life. This includes everything from what we eat, drink and inhale to the &lt;a data-i13n="elm:context_link;elmt:doNotAffiliate;cpos:4;pos:1" class="link  yahoo-link" href="https://www.yahoo.com/lifestyle/green-spaces-walking-paths-little-traffic-7-features-of-a-healthy-neighborhood-090012442.html" data-ylk="slk:neighborhoods we live in;elm:context_link;elmt:doNotAffiliate;cpos:4;pos:1;itc:0;sec:content-canvas;outcm:mb_qualified_link;_E:mb_qualified_link;ct:story;"&gt;neighborhoods we live in&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="md:hidden"&gt;&lt;div class="mx-auto mb-5 flex flex-col overflow-hidden rounded-xl pb-5 shadow-[0_0_1px_rgba(200,160,251,.63),0_2px_6px_1px_#F3E6FE]"&gt;&lt;h3 class="m-auto block px-4 pb-4 pt-2 text-lg font-bold leading-6"&gt;Trusted news and daily delights, right in your inbox&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="m-auto px-4 pb-4 text-sm font-normal"&gt;See for yourself — The Yodel is the go-to source for daily news, entertainment and feel-good stories.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;While genetics accounted for less than 2% of the difference in people’s risks of death, environmental factors were behind 17% of the disparity, the scientists found. Smoking, socioeconomic status — a measure of factors like income, neighborhood, education and occupation — physical activity levels and living conditions had the greatest influence on someone’s biological aging and risk of death.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Some of these factors — such as how much money you make or whether you can afford to own a home in a nice neighborhood — are hard to change. But overall, 23 out of 25 of the environmental variables the researchers looked at are modifiable. And many of them are pretty simple.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mb-4 text-xl font-bold md:text-2xl" data-jump-link-target="" id="do-genes-not-matter-when-it-comes-to-longevity"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Do genes not matter when it comes to longevity?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;No, they definitely do. But to what extent varies a lot depending on the specific genes, the diseases that they put you at risk for and what you do throughout your life. For example, which variants of the &lt;a data-i13n="elm:context_link;elmt:doNotAffiliate;cpos:5;pos:1" class="link  yahoo-link" href="https://www.yahoo.com/news/genes-known-increase-risk-alzheimer-151136656.html" data-ylk="slk:APOE gene;elm:context_link;elmt:doNotAffiliate;cpos:5;pos:1;itc:0;sec:content-canvas;outcm:mb_qualified_link;_E:mb_qualified_link;ct:story;"&gt;APOE gene&lt;/a&gt; you carry is highly predictive of your risk for Alzheimer’s disease; the same goes for &lt;a data-i13n="elm:context_link;elmt:doNotAffiliate;cpos:6;pos:1" class="link  yahoo-link" href="https://www.yahoo.com/lifestyle/jenna-wolfe-hysterectomy-brca-gene-232125745.html" data-ylk="slk:BRCA1 and BRCA2 variants and breast cancer;elm:context_link;elmt:doNotAffiliate;cpos:6;pos:1;itc:0;sec:content-canvas;outcm:mb_qualified_link;_E:mb_qualified_link;ct:story;"&gt;BRCA1 and BRCA2 variants and breast cancer&lt;/a&gt;. And these diseases can have a lot to do with your biological aging and life expectancy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;But even these genes are influenced by your behavior and environment. And, in most cases, our choices and the lives we lead have a huge impact on what those genes will mean for our health. “Someone put a comment on our paper, saying ‘genetics loads the dice, but it’s up to us to play our hand,’” &lt;a data-i13n="elm:context_link;elmt:doNotAffiliate;cpos:7;pos:1" class="link " href="https://www.atgu.mgh.harvard.edu/people/austin-argentieri-phd/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Austin Argentieri,;elm:context_link;elmt:doNotAffiliate;cpos:7;pos:1;itc:0;sec:content-canvas"&gt;Austin Argentieri,&lt;/a&gt; a research fellow at Massachusetts General Hospital who led the new study while he was a researcher at Oxford Population Health, tells Yahoo Life. Even if your genetic makeup predisposes you to diseases that could cut your life short, “in most cases, you can mitigate that risk through lifestyle, behavior, or taking different drugs or treatments,” explains Argentieri.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mb-4 text-xl font-bold md:text-2xl" data-jump-link-target="" id="changes-that-can-set-you-up-for-a-longer-life"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Changes that can set you up for a longer life&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;h3 class="mb-4 text-lg font-bold" data-jump-link-target="" id="1-dont-smoke"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. Don’t smoke.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;By now, it’s hardly a surprise that &lt;a data-i13n="elm:context_link;elmt:doNotAffiliate;cpos:8;pos:1" class="link  yahoo-link" href="https://www.yahoo.com/lifestyle/smoking-rates-declining-too-lung-120036320.html" data-ylk="slk:smoking;elm:context_link;elmt:doNotAffiliate;cpos:8;pos:1;itc:0;sec:content-canvas;outcm:mb_qualified_link;_E:mb_qualified_link;ct:story;"&gt;smoking &lt;/a&gt;is bad for you. But, aside from a person’s age, smoking has a greater bearing on longevity and aging than any other factor — genetic or environmental — according to the new study. Second to age, the factor that most influenced mortality risk was “smoking pack years,” meaning the number of packs of cigarettes a person smoked daily, for how many years. And smoking status — whether someone currently, formerly or never smoked — was the fourth-most-influential factor (sex was third; men are more likely to die earlier than women). “If you can do one thing, don’t smoke,” says Argentieri.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="mb-4 text-lg font-bold" data-jump-link-target="" id="2-get-good-sleep"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2. Get good sleep.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;People who are tired frequently or don’t get very much sleep at night are more likely to both age quickly and die prematurely. &lt;a data-i13n="elm:context_link;elmt:doNotAffiliate;cpos:9;pos:1" class="link  yahoo-link" href="https://www.yahoo.com/lifestyle/how-much-sleep-do-i-need-201727574.html" data-ylk="slk:How much sleep you need;elm:context_link;elmt:doNotAffiliate;cpos:9;pos:1;itc:0;sec:content-canvas;outcm:mb_qualified_link;_E:mb_qualified_link;ct:story;"&gt;How much sleep you need&lt;/a&gt; varies from person to person, but for most adults, you should aim to get seven to nine hours a night. And try to have good “&lt;a data-i13n="elm:context_link;elmt:doNotAffiliate;cpos:10;pos:1" class="link  yahoo-link" href="https://www.yahoo.com/lifestyle/sleep-hygiene-140453735.html" data-ylk="slk:sleep hygiene;elm:context_link;elmt:doNotAffiliate;cpos:10;pos:1;itc:0;sec:content-canvas;outcm:mb_qualified_link;_E:mb_qualified_link;ct:story;"&gt;sleep hygiene&lt;/a&gt;” by going to bed and waking at consistent times, &lt;a data-i13n="cpos:11;pos:1" href="https://www.yahoo.com/lifestyle/babies-have-sleep-routines-heres-why-adults-should-too-205345568.html" data-ylk="slk:having a bedtime routine;cpos:11;pos:1;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas;outcm:mb_qualified_link;_E:mb_qualified_link;ct:story;" class="link  yahoo-link"&gt;having a bedtime routine&lt;/a&gt;, keeping your room dark and keeping your phone away from your bed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="mb-4 text-lg font-bold" data-jump-link-target="" id="3-get-moving"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3. Get moving.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;After tiredness, physical activity “is close in the running for the top” factor influencing biological aging and risk of death, says Argentieri. That’s in part because many of the chronic conditions that accelerate aging and lead to early death are cardiometabolic diseases, such as heart disease, diabetes and stroke. Obesity increases risks for these conditions, while exercise, in combination with a healthy diet, can reduce those risks. Diet may have more influence, but “that doesn’t mean that exercise shouldn’t be part of the plan,” &lt;a data-i13n="elm:context_link;elmt:doNotAffiliate;cpos:12;pos:1" class="link " href="https://gero.usc.edu/faculty/longo/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Valter Longo;elm:context_link;elmt:doNotAffiliate;cpos:12;pos:1;itc:0;sec:content-canvas"&gt;Valter Longo&lt;/a&gt;, a University of Southern California professor of gerontology who studies how nutrition and fasting can influence longevity, tells Yahoo Life. &lt;a data-i13n="elm:context_link;elmt:doNotAffiliate;cpos:13;pos:1" class="link  yahoo-link" href="https://www.yahoo.com/lifestyle/want-to-live-a-longer-healthier-life-new-research-sheds-light-on-the-lifestyle-factors-that-matter-150908451.html" data-ylk="slk:In combination with other habits, exercising;elm:context_link;elmt:doNotAffiliate;cpos:13;pos:1;itc:0;sec:content-canvas;outcm:mb_qualified_link;_E:mb_qualified_link;ct:story;"&gt;In combination with other habits, exercising&lt;/a&gt; can help you live healthier, for longer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="mb-4 text-lg font-bold" data-jump-link-target="" id="4-eat-for-longer-living"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;4. Eat for longer living.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The study found that while what people ate didn’t have much effect on their biological aging, it was predictive of their risk of death. That may be because many people change their diets to be healthier &lt;em&gt;because&lt;/em&gt; they have a health problem, such as prediabetes. But Longo’s research suggests that eating a &lt;a data-i13n="elm:context_link;elmt:doNotAffiliate;cpos:14;pos:1" class="link  yahoo-link" href="https://www.yahoo.com/lifestyle/longevity-diet-researcher-valter-longo-173410025.html" data-ylk="slk:diet;elm:context_link;elmt:doNotAffiliate;cpos:14;pos:1;itc:0;sec:content-canvas;outcm:mb_qualified_link;_E:mb_qualified_link;ct:story;"&gt;diet&lt;/a&gt; that consists of lots of plants and fish and little red meat is associated with a longer life. A diet that includes &lt;a data-i13n="elm:context_link;elmt:doNotAffiliate;cpos:15;pos:1" class="link  yahoo-link" href="https://www.yahoo.com/lifestyle/how-much-protein-does-your-body-need-its-a-bit-complicated-our-guide-can-help-235954440.html" data-ylk="slk:sufficient but low levels of protein;elm:context_link;elmt:doNotAffiliate;cpos:15;pos:1;itc:0;sec:content-canvas;outcm:mb_qualified_link;_E:mb_qualified_link;ct:story;"&gt;sufficient but low levels of protein&lt;/a&gt; helps to prevent aging acceleration by altering the way certain genes associated with the breakdown of our bodies work, Longo says (though this changes around age 65, when we need more protein, he notes).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Yahoo Life</author><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 10:00:07 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi8wFBVV95cUxOUl95TjVlRk50SVB0eGtUNTVtSUZ2cl95c0o1ZDdQdER4a2hCMVk1LU54TkNkVFVSYTQyZDRVWmtxM0VZYnVVNzdSUXcyOVF2c080Z3YtSWZvVTEyaGNCbVVFVENwMkNReVRKUzA4VFhiMFB4aEJuVEdfWjdhNzk5aWF5eVN4eFNWdFlCbXl1a2JSRzYxRnl5a0lRQ214aGJ5enpXdlFROUJtUks3UGVKaVpNT0JBaEdMNUluX1VSRG9xRkhWSmZSV1pkSVNfY0tKOHVoemx3TUZLYmpEZlFVVm9Kb0ZLcV9zZWUxODl3ZlhQSTg</guid></item><item><title>Living a long time isn't just about good genes, a new study says. 4 lifestyle changes that can improve your longevity. - Yahoo Life</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMifkFVX3lxTE1vaFBuUkxtWUhGWUdVSWJBempDMUVBMWZBX2hIa2VrVGo0UVAyRlJOZGs5UTE2Qzg3Tm5QNUFWb0NnTFY1UExaV0pTZ0pKbmx1UEc4Q1JyRTJtblUxQUdsRmtXUTMxV21SbENDM0dfekNFcTlPVGZZd1lreDhIdw?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="" data-article-body="true"&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;If you have a parent or grandparent who’s reached their 90s or even become a &lt;a data-i13n="elm:context_link;elmt:doNotAffiliate;cpos:1;pos:1" class="link  yahoo-link" href="https://www.yahoo.com/lifestyle/lessons-on-aging-from-the-oldest-people-in-the-world-eat-your-veggies-avoid-toxic-people-move-your-body-and-more-201123414.html" data-ylk="slk:centenarian;elm:context_link;elmt:doNotAffiliate;cpos:1;pos:1;itc:0;sec:content-canvas;outcm:mb_qualified_link;_E:mb_qualified_link;ct:story;"&gt;centenarian&lt;/a&gt;, someone’s probably said to you, “Oh, you have good genes!” But if longevity doesn’t seem to run in your family, fret not: &lt;a data-i13n="elm:context_link;elmt:doNotAffiliate;cpos:2;pos:1" class="link  yahoo-link" href="https://www.yahoo.com/lifestyle/the-us-has-the-biggest-lifespan-health-span-gap-in-the-world-new-study-shows-were-living-longer-lives--but-not-in-good-health-170707093.html" data-ylk="slk:Lifespan;elm:context_link;elmt:doNotAffiliate;cpos:2;pos:1;itc:0;sec:content-canvas;outcm:mb_qualified_link;_E:mb_qualified_link;ct:story;"&gt;Lifespan&lt;/a&gt; has more to do with your life&lt;em&gt;style&lt;/em&gt; and environment than with your genetics, according to a &lt;a data-i13n="elm:context_link;elmt:doNotAffiliate;cpos:3;pos:1" class="link " href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41591-024-03483-9#MOESM1" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:study;elm:context_link;elmt:doNotAffiliate;cpos:3;pos:1;itc:0;sec:content-canvas"&gt;study&lt;/a&gt; published in the journal Nature Medicine&lt;em&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;In other words, there’s a lot you can do to take control of your own destiny when it comes to longevity, regardless of how long your relatives lived. Here’s what to know.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mb-4 text-xl font-bold md:text-2xl" data-jump-link-target="" id="what-the-study-found"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What the study found&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Using data on nearly half a million people from the U.K., Oxford University researchers looked for patterns in who died prematurely, or before the age of 75. They also looked at markers of biological aging in a smaller subset of the study group (over 45,000 people). Their analysis included comparisons of genetic risk factors for disease as well as what some scientists have termed the “exposome.” Our DNA makes up our genome, whereas the exposome is made up of all the exposures we encounter throughout life. This includes everything from what we eat, drink and inhale to the &lt;a data-i13n="elm:context_link;elmt:doNotAffiliate;cpos:4;pos:1" class="link  yahoo-link" href="https://www.yahoo.com/lifestyle/green-spaces-walking-paths-little-traffic-7-features-of-a-healthy-neighborhood-090012442.html" data-ylk="slk:neighborhoods we live in;elm:context_link;elmt:doNotAffiliate;cpos:4;pos:1;itc:0;sec:content-canvas;outcm:mb_qualified_link;_E:mb_qualified_link;ct:story;"&gt;neighborhoods we live in&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="md:hidden"&gt;&lt;div class="mx-auto mb-5 flex flex-col overflow-hidden rounded-xl pb-5 shadow-[0_0_1px_rgba(200,160,251,.63),0_2px_6px_1px_#F3E6FE]"&gt;&lt;h3 class="m-auto block px-4 pb-4 pt-2 text-lg font-bold leading-6"&gt;Trusted news and daily delights, right in your inbox&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="m-auto px-4 pb-4 text-sm font-normal"&gt;See for yourself — The Yodel is the go-to source for daily news, entertainment and feel-good stories.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;While genetics accounted for less than 2% of the difference in people’s risks of death, environmental factors were behind 17% of the disparity, the scientists found. Smoking, socioeconomic status — a measure of factors like income, neighborhood, education and occupation — physical activity levels and living conditions had the greatest influence on someone’s biological aging and risk of death.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Some of these factors — such as how much money you make or whether you can afford to own a home in a nice neighborhood — are hard to change. But overall, 23 out of 25 of the environmental variables the researchers looked at are modifiable. And many of them are pretty simple.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mb-4 text-xl font-bold md:text-2xl" data-jump-link-target="" id="do-genes-not-matter-when-it-comes-to-longevity"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Do genes not matter when it comes to longevity?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;No, they definitely do. But to what extent varies a lot depending on the specific genes, the diseases that they put you at risk for and what you do throughout your life. For example, which variants of the &lt;a data-i13n="elm:context_link;elmt:doNotAffiliate;cpos:5;pos:1" class="link  yahoo-link" href="https://www.yahoo.com/news/genes-known-increase-risk-alzheimer-151136656.html" data-ylk="slk:APOE gene;elm:context_link;elmt:doNotAffiliate;cpos:5;pos:1;itc:0;sec:content-canvas;outcm:mb_qualified_link;_E:mb_qualified_link;ct:story;"&gt;APOE gene&lt;/a&gt; you carry is highly predictive of your risk for Alzheimer’s disease; the same goes for &lt;a data-i13n="elm:context_link;elmt:doNotAffiliate;cpos:6;pos:1" class="link  yahoo-link" href="https://www.yahoo.com/lifestyle/jenna-wolfe-hysterectomy-brca-gene-232125745.html" data-ylk="slk:BRCA1 and BRCA2 variants and breast cancer;elm:context_link;elmt:doNotAffiliate;cpos:6;pos:1;itc:0;sec:content-canvas;outcm:mb_qualified_link;_E:mb_qualified_link;ct:story;"&gt;BRCA1 and BRCA2 variants and breast cancer&lt;/a&gt;. And these diseases can have a lot to do with your biological aging and life expectancy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;But even these genes are influenced by your behavior and environment. And, in most cases, our choices and the lives we lead have a huge impact on what those genes will mean for our health. “Someone put a comment on our paper, saying ‘genetics loads the dice, but it’s up to us to play our hand,’” &lt;a data-i13n="elm:context_link;elmt:doNotAffiliate;cpos:7;pos:1" class="link " href="https://www.atgu.mgh.harvard.edu/people/austin-argentieri-phd/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Austin Argentieri,;elm:context_link;elmt:doNotAffiliate;cpos:7;pos:1;itc:0;sec:content-canvas"&gt;Austin Argentieri,&lt;/a&gt; a research fellow at Massachusetts General Hospital who led the new study while he was a researcher at Oxford Population Health, tells Yahoo Life. Even if your genetic makeup predisposes you to diseases that could cut your life short, “in most cases, you can mitigate that risk through lifestyle, behavior, or taking different drugs or treatments,” explains Argentieri.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mb-4 text-xl font-bold md:text-2xl" data-jump-link-target="" id="changes-that-can-set-you-up-for-a-longer-life"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Changes that can set you up for a longer life&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;h3 class="mb-4 text-lg font-bold" data-jump-link-target="" id="1-dont-smoke"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. Don’t smoke.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;By now, it’s hardly a surprise that &lt;a data-i13n="elm:context_link;elmt:doNotAffiliate;cpos:8;pos:1" class="link  yahoo-link" href="https://www.yahoo.com/lifestyle/smoking-rates-declining-too-lung-120036320.html" data-ylk="slk:smoking;elm:context_link;elmt:doNotAffiliate;cpos:8;pos:1;itc:0;sec:content-canvas;outcm:mb_qualified_link;_E:mb_qualified_link;ct:story;"&gt;smoking &lt;/a&gt;is bad for you. But, aside from a person’s age, smoking has a greater bearing on longevity and aging than any other factor — genetic or environmental — according to the new study. Second to age, the factor that most influenced mortality risk was “smoking pack years,” meaning the number of packs of cigarettes a person smoked daily, for how many years. And smoking status — whether someone currently, formerly or never smoked — was the fourth-most-influential factor (sex was third; men are more likely to die earlier than women). “If you can do one thing, don’t smoke,” says Argentieri.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="mb-4 text-lg font-bold" data-jump-link-target="" id="2-get-good-sleep"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2. Get good sleep.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;People who are tired frequently or don’t get very much sleep at night are more likely to both age quickly and die prematurely. &lt;a data-i13n="elm:context_link;elmt:doNotAffiliate;cpos:9;pos:1" class="link  yahoo-link" href="https://www.yahoo.com/lifestyle/how-much-sleep-do-i-need-201727574.html" data-ylk="slk:How much sleep you need;elm:context_link;elmt:doNotAffiliate;cpos:9;pos:1;itc:0;sec:content-canvas;outcm:mb_qualified_link;_E:mb_qualified_link;ct:story;"&gt;How much sleep you need&lt;/a&gt; varies from person to person, but for most adults, you should aim to get seven to nine hours a night. And try to have good “&lt;a data-i13n="elm:context_link;elmt:doNotAffiliate;cpos:10;pos:1" class="link  yahoo-link" href="https://www.yahoo.com/lifestyle/sleep-hygiene-140453735.html" data-ylk="slk:sleep hygiene;elm:context_link;elmt:doNotAffiliate;cpos:10;pos:1;itc:0;sec:content-canvas;outcm:mb_qualified_link;_E:mb_qualified_link;ct:story;"&gt;sleep hygiene&lt;/a&gt;” by going to bed and waking at consistent times, &lt;a data-i13n="cpos:11;pos:1" href="https://www.yahoo.com/lifestyle/babies-have-sleep-routines-heres-why-adults-should-too-205345568.html" data-ylk="slk:having a bedtime routine;cpos:11;pos:1;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas;outcm:mb_qualified_link;_E:mb_qualified_link;ct:story;" class="link  yahoo-link"&gt;having a bedtime routine&lt;/a&gt;, keeping your room dark and keeping your phone away from your bed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="mb-4 text-lg font-bold" data-jump-link-target="" id="3-get-moving"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3. Get moving.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;After tiredness, physical activity “is close in the running for the top” factor influencing biological aging and risk of death, says Argentieri. That’s in part because many of the chronic conditions that accelerate aging and lead to early death are cardiometabolic diseases, such as heart disease, diabetes and stroke. Obesity increases risks for these conditions, while exercise, in combination with a healthy diet, can reduce those risks. Diet may have more influence, but “that doesn’t mean that exercise shouldn’t be part of the plan,” &lt;a data-i13n="elm:context_link;elmt:doNotAffiliate;cpos:12;pos:1" class="link " href="https://gero.usc.edu/faculty/longo/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Valter Longo;elm:context_link;elmt:doNotAffiliate;cpos:12;pos:1;itc:0;sec:content-canvas"&gt;Valter Longo&lt;/a&gt;, a University of Southern California professor of gerontology who studies how nutrition and fasting can influence longevity, tells Yahoo Life. &lt;a data-i13n="elm:context_link;elmt:doNotAffiliate;cpos:13;pos:1" class="link  yahoo-link" href="https://www.yahoo.com/lifestyle/want-to-live-a-longer-healthier-life-new-research-sheds-light-on-the-lifestyle-factors-that-matter-150908451.html" data-ylk="slk:In combination with other habits, exercising;elm:context_link;elmt:doNotAffiliate;cpos:13;pos:1;itc:0;sec:content-canvas;outcm:mb_qualified_link;_E:mb_qualified_link;ct:story;"&gt;In combination with other habits, exercising&lt;/a&gt; can help you live healthier, for longer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="mb-4 text-lg font-bold" data-jump-link-target="" id="4-eat-for-longer-living"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;4. Eat for longer living.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The study found that while what people ate didn’t have much effect on their biological aging, it was predictive of their risk of death. That may be because many people change their diets to be healthier &lt;em&gt;because&lt;/em&gt; they have a health problem, such as prediabetes. But Longo’s research suggests that eating a &lt;a data-i13n="elm:context_link;elmt:doNotAffiliate;cpos:14;pos:1" class="link  yahoo-link" href="https://www.yahoo.com/lifestyle/longevity-diet-researcher-valter-longo-173410025.html" data-ylk="slk:diet;elm:context_link;elmt:doNotAffiliate;cpos:14;pos:1;itc:0;sec:content-canvas;outcm:mb_qualified_link;_E:mb_qualified_link;ct:story;"&gt;diet&lt;/a&gt; that consists of lots of plants and fish and little red meat is associated with a longer life. A diet that includes &lt;a data-i13n="elm:context_link;elmt:doNotAffiliate;cpos:15;pos:1" class="link  yahoo-link" href="https://www.yahoo.com/lifestyle/how-much-protein-does-your-body-need-its-a-bit-complicated-our-guide-can-help-235954440.html" data-ylk="slk:sufficient but low levels of protein;elm:context_link;elmt:doNotAffiliate;cpos:15;pos:1;itc:0;sec:content-canvas;outcm:mb_qualified_link;_E:mb_qualified_link;ct:story;"&gt;sufficient but low levels of protein&lt;/a&gt; helps to prevent aging acceleration by altering the way certain genes associated with the breakdown of our bodies work, Longo says (though this changes around age 65, when we need more protein, he notes).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Yahoo Life</author><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 10:00:07 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMifkFVX3lxTE1vaFBuUkxtWUhGWUdVSWJBempDMUVBMWZBX2hIa2VrVGo0UVAyRlJOZGs5UTE2Qzg3Tm5QNUFWb0NnTFY1UExaV0pTZ0pKbmx1UEc4Q1JyRTJtblUxQUdsRmtXUTMxV21SbENDM0dfekNFcTlPVGZZd1lreDhIdw</guid></item><item><title>Battle of the thermostat: The science behind your central heating arguments - BBC.com</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiugFBVV95cUxOVUJuWWo0VEI4SnhuZ3oyUEtKRTJtbTRvSWVNS1FvdnQ2ckY4X0x2elJTdVEtVmNoTTItbkJwenQ2ajdyM05Fa0NtakJSQ3huMUY2aWNwNVJXUGdBeC1OS29hNTVVa2VEempNeWRXWV84UGwyVXVwQ1VTdFY1bnlGeWxxVF9iUFJhMnNLWEFrUElrcm5pUHpqSnN6d1RlOHM4V1FVamNzQVZ3ZmZ1ODdJbU41ZmVYTW1PcEE?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article&gt;&lt;p data-component="headline-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 eeiVGB"&gt;&lt;h1 class="sc-518485e5-0 itISwu"&gt;Battle of the thermostat: The science behind your central heating arguments&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 EXUng"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="hero-image" class="sc-a34861b-1 jxzoZC"&gt;&lt;img src="/bbcx/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-a34861b-0 cOpVbP hide-when-no-script"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/160xn/p0kv838q.jpg.webp 160w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/240xn/p0kv838q.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/320xn/p0kv838q.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/480xn/p0kv838q.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/640xn/p0kv838q.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/800xn/p0kv838q.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/1024xn/p0kv838q.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/1376xn/p0kv838q.jpg.webp 1376w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/1920xn/p0kv838q.jpg.webp 1920w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/480xn/p0kv838q.jpg.webp" loading="eager" alt="Getty Images Boy and dog cuddled up together under a blanket on a sofa (Credit: Getty)" class="sc-a34861b-0 efFcac"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-a34861b-2 hesJxn"&gt;Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 dlWCEZ"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;&lt;b id="being-too-hot-or-too-cold-can-be-bad-for-your-health.-so,-what-is-the-optimum-temperature-for-your-home?" class="sc-7dcfb11b-0 kVRnKf"&gt;Being too hot or too cold can be bad for your health. So, what is the optimum temperature for your home?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 dlWCEZ"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;As someone who feels the cold – but is reluctant to constantly turn up the thermostat – a hot water bottle and a thick fleece are two of my closest friends. And as &lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.bbc.co.uk/future/article/20250115-how-the-polar-vortex-brings-arctic-weather-to-the-us" class="sc-c9299ecf-0 beIoQm"&gt;relentless winter storms&lt;/a&gt; sweep the east coast of the US and Canada – and other countries across the globe are trawling through what feels like a very long winter – you might also be wondering: what is the best indoor temperature for your health and comfort? The answer, it turns out, is not straightforward.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 dlWCEZ"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;In the 1860s, German physician &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://academic.oup.com/cid/article-abstract/18/3/458/739639?redirectedFrom=fulltext&amp;amp;login=false%2523google_vignette" class="sc-c9299ecf-0 beIoQm"&gt;Carl Wunderlich&lt;/a&gt; took the temperatures of around 25,000 people and found that the average was &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/books/NBK331/" class="sc-c9299ecf-0 beIoQm"&gt;37C (98.6F)&lt;/a&gt;. This figure has been widely accepted ever since. However, &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.health.harvard.edu/blog/time-to-redefine-normal-body-temperature-2020031319173" class="sc-c9299ecf-0 beIoQm"&gt;new data&lt;/a&gt; suggests that this isn't strictly true. Body temperature can &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/books/NBK331/" class="sc-c9299ecf-0 beIoQm"&gt;vary&lt;/a&gt; between individuals, with modern &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC2278431/" class="sc-c9299ecf-0 beIoQm"&gt;research&lt;/a&gt; suggesting that gender, metabolism, hormones, activity, age and menstruation all have an influence. So, with such variations to consider, is there an optimum temperature at which to keep your home?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 dlWCEZ"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;"We recognise healthy homes are one of the key building blocks for good health. So that means homes that are accessible, safe, comfortable and warm help to protect our health, and support our communities to be healthy and resilient," says Rebecca Wilson, senior public health specialist at Public Health Wales in the UK, an organisation which advocates for improving links between homes and health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 dlWCEZ"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;The results of Public Health Wales's &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://phwwhocc.co.uk/wp-content/uploads/2024/11/Keeping-warm-at-home-during-winter-in-Wales.pdf" class="sc-c9299ecf-0 beIoQm"&gt;2022 and 2023 winter surveys&lt;/a&gt; found that people were increasingly experiencing stress or anxiety in the three months leading up to winter due to rising heating costs (a jump from 57.2% to 66.5%). When the cold set in, more people set their thermostats to lower temperatures at home, and chose to heat specific rooms rather than the whole house – and, instead, turned to hot water bottles or blankets to stay warm.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 jFCfG"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-a34861b-1 jxzoZC"&gt;&lt;img src="/bbcx/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-a34861b-0 cOpVbP hide-when-no-script"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/160xn/p0kv83mp.jpg.webp 160w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/240xn/p0kv83mp.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/320xn/p0kv83mp.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/480xn/p0kv83mp.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/640xn/p0kv83mp.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/800xn/p0kv83mp.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/1024xn/p0kv83mp.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/1376xn/p0kv83mp.jpg.webp 1376w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/1920xn/p0kv83mp.jpg.webp 1920w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/480xn/p0kv83mp.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Alamy An increasing number of people are turning to hot water bottles and blankets to keep warm indoors (Credit: Alamy)" class="sc-a34861b-0 efFcac"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-a34861b-2 hesJxn"&gt;Alamy&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 bdPeAJ"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-8353772e-0 iUqqeb"&gt;An increasing number of people are turning to hot water bottles and blankets to keep warm indoors (Credit: Alamy)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 dlWCEZ"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;"We know that all people who live in cold homes or face frugal poverty are affected. But the research does show that there's certain population groups such as older people, children, and people with disabilities and health conditions, who might be more impacted," says Wilson. &lt;i id="(read-more-about" class="sc-7dcfb11b-0 kKcaog"&gt;(Read more about &lt;/i&gt;&lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.bbc.co.uk/future/article/20221107-energy-crisis-how-living-in-a-cold-home-affects-your-health" class="sc-c9299ecf-0 beIoQm"&gt;&lt;i id="how-cold-homes-can-affect-health" class="sc-7dcfb11b-0 kKcaog"&gt;how cold homes can affect health&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;i id=")" class="sc-7dcfb11b-0 kKcaog"&gt;)&lt;/i&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 dlWCEZ"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;Equally, overheating is also a &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.who.int/news-room/fact-sheets/detail/climate-change-heat-and-health" class="sc-c9299ecf-0 beIoQm"&gt;health risk&lt;/a&gt; for those living in warmer climates, with an increased likelihood of heat exhaustion and heatstroke as the body desperately tries to cool itself, in turn putting stress on the heart and kidneys. Overheating can also exacerbate existing health conditions and &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.thelancet.com/journals/lancet/article/PIIS0140-6736(21)01208-3/fulltext" class="sc-c9299ecf-0 beIoQm"&gt;negatively impact&lt;/a&gt; mental health, with links found to an &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S0033350618302130?via=ihub" class="sc-c9299ecf-0 beIoQm"&gt;increased suicide&lt;/a&gt; risk. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 dlWCEZ"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;It's a bleak picture. &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.thelancet.com/journals/lanplh/article/PIIS2542-5196(21)00081-4/fulltext" class="sc-c9299ecf-0 beIoQm"&gt;Research&lt;/a&gt; has shown a global link between both cold and heat exposure and mortality over the 21st Century, with experts calling for more public awareness of non-optimal temperatures as a health risk. This is becoming an increasing problem due to climate change and a &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.cambridge.org/core/books/climate-change-2021-the-physical-science-basis/weather-and-climate-extreme-events-in-a-changing-climate/5BCB24C5699F1D42B2DE379BDD4E2119" class="sc-c9299ecf-0 beIoQm"&gt;longer duration and intensity of extreme weather events&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 dlWCEZ"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;Babies, young children and elderly people are also particularly vulnerable as they are less able to &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/books/NBK507838/" class="sc-c9299ecf-0 beIoQm"&gt;thermoregulate&lt;/a&gt; – meaning they are less able to maintain a core body temperature by balancing heat generation with heat loss. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 dlWCEZ"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;For example, according to &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.lullabytrust.org.uk/safer-sleep-advice/safer-sleep-basics/baby-room-temperature/" class="sc-c9299ecf-0 beIoQm"&gt;The Lullaby Trust&lt;/a&gt; in the UK, the recommended room temperature for babies is slightly lower than average, at 16-20C (60-68F). If babies overheat, there is a &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.nhs.uk/conditions/baby/caring-for-a-newborn/reduce-the-risk-of-sudden-infant-death-syndrome/#:~:text=Overheating%20can%20increase%20the%20risk,off%20some%20of%20the%20bedding" class="sc-c9299ecf-0 beIoQm"&gt;risk of sudden infant death syndrome&lt;/a&gt;, so the charity advises using a thermometer to test the temperature of the room but also check your baby by feeling the back of their neck and chest to see if they are hot or sweaty. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 dlWCEZ"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;The average body temperature of a newborn or a young child is slightly &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/books/NBK279457/" class="sc-c9299ecf-0 beIoQm"&gt;higher&lt;/a&gt; than an older child or adult, usually between 36.5 and 37.5C (97.7F and 99.5F). This is because their metabolism is more active, and their &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/books/NBK279457/%23:~:text=Babies%2520and%2520young%2520children%2520have,C%2520and%252037.5%25C2%25B0C" class="sc-c9299ecf-0 beIoQm"&gt;body surface area is larger in relation to their body weight&lt;/a&gt;. As their bodies grapple with thermoregulation, it takes longer for them to sweat, so their bodies hold more heat. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 dlWCEZ"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;Elderly people, on the other hand, may need their homes a little warmer as they tend to have a &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/books/NBK507838/" class="sc-c9299ecf-0 beIoQm"&gt;lower&lt;/a&gt; resting body temperature compared to young adults. Metabolic rate &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.researchgate.net/publication/280698071_Energy_consumption_in_buildings_and_female_thermal_demand" class="sc-c9299ecf-0 beIoQm"&gt;decreases&lt;/a&gt; with age, meaning it's harder for older people's bodies to produce heat. They are also more likely to be taking medication, or be suffering from a chronic illness – both of which can affect the body's ability to thermoregulate. &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.nia.nih.gov/health/diabetes/diabetes-older-people" class="sc-c9299ecf-0 beIoQm"&gt;Diabetes&lt;/a&gt;, for example, can prevent the blood flowing normally to provide warmth. Even slightly cooler homes at 18C (65F) can lead to &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.nia.nih.gov/health/safety/cold-weather-safety-older-adults" class="sc-c9299ecf-0 beIoQm"&gt;hypothermia&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 dlWCEZ"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;&lt;a target="_blank" href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/24855113/" class="sc-c9299ecf-0 beIoQm"&gt;One study&lt;/a&gt; observed that the physical performance of older women between the ages of 70 and 95 in a moderately cold environment at 15C (59F) and warmer at 25C (77F). Results showed that their physical ability significantly worsened within 45 minutes at the colder temperature – highlighting the potential safety risks for older adults living independently, such as balance problems and heightened risk of falling. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 jFCfG"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-a34861b-1 jxzoZC"&gt;&lt;img src="/bbcx/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-a34861b-0 cOpVbP hide-when-no-script"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/160xn/p0kv83qz.jpg.webp 160w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/240xn/p0kv83qz.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/320xn/p0kv83qz.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/480xn/p0kv83qz.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/640xn/p0kv83qz.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/800xn/p0kv83qz.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/1024xn/p0kv83qz.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/1376xn/p0kv83qz.jpg.webp 1376w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/1920xn/p0kv83qz.jpg.webp 1920w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/480xn/p0kv83qz.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Getty Images Couples often find themselves in an endless battle of the thermostat (Credit: Getty Images)" class="sc-a34861b-0 efFcac"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-a34861b-2 hesJxn"&gt;Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 bdPeAJ"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-8353772e-0 iUqqeb"&gt;Couples often find themselves in an endless battle of the thermostat (Credit: Getty Images)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 dlWCEZ"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;Menstruation also has a role to play, as core body temperature &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.tandfonline.com/doi/full/10.1080/23328940.2020.1735927" class="sc-c9299ecf-0 beIoQm"&gt;fluctuates&lt;/a&gt; throughout the cycle, hitting its highest point in the &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/33123618/" class="sc-c9299ecf-0 beIoQm"&gt;luteal phase&lt;/a&gt; after ovulation. And &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://theconversation.com/mondays-medical-myth-men-are-hotter-than-women-6738" class="sc-c9299ecf-0 beIoQm"&gt;pregnancy and hormonal contraceptives&lt;/a&gt; containing &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/26674572/" class="sc-c9299ecf-0 beIoQm"&gt;progesterone&lt;/a&gt; can also increase core temperature. However, as women are typically smaller in build and have a &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/8125870/%23:~:text=Measured%2525252520RMR%2525252520was%252525252023%2525252525%2525252520higher,%252525252C%2525252520peak%2525252520VO2%252525252C%2525252520and%2525252520gender." class="sc-c9299ecf-0 beIoQm"&gt;lower resting metabolic rate&lt;/a&gt; than men, which reduces heat production when exposed to the cold, they can also feel the cold more, despite having a higher core body temperature.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 dlWCEZ"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;The extent of the variation of thermal comfort between men and women is disputed. While some &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC6853289/" class="sc-c9299ecf-0 beIoQm"&gt;research&lt;/a&gt; indicates that it is marginal, &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S0360132306000242" class="sc-c9299ecf-0 beIoQm"&gt;one study&lt;/a&gt; from Finland suggests that it might be more significant. Take the office environment, for example. While it's unlikely that there's a temperature which pleases everyone due to our individual thermoregulation, overall the study found that women were often dissatisfied with the room temperature, feeling both uncomfortably colder and hotter than men. Another study of office temperatures in Japan showed a &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S0378778802000129" class="sc-c9299ecf-0 beIoQm"&gt;3.1C (37F) difference in neutral temperature&lt;/a&gt; between female and male workers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 dlWCEZ"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;In the home, meanwhile, reaching an optimal core body temperature may not be a "golden ticket" to a perfect sleep, says Bill Wisden, a sleep expert and director of the UK Dementia Research Institute at Imperial College London, "but it would help".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 dlWCEZ"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;Sleep, he says, is "&lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S0031938406003933" class="sc-c9299ecf-0 beIoQm"&gt;temporally related&lt;/a&gt; to the circadian rhythm of core body temperature and skin temperature". In other words, a couple of hours before we go to sleep, our core body temperature begins to &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S2468867319301804" class="sc-c9299ecf-0 beIoQm"&gt;decrease&lt;/a&gt; when melatonin, the hormone that regulates the sleep cycle, is produced. Body temperature continues to &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.sleepfoundation.org/bedroom-environment/best-temperature-for-sleep" class="sc-c9299ecf-0 beIoQm"&gt;drop&lt;/a&gt; throughout the night reaching a low point in the early morning before gradually warming up as the morning progresses.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 jFCfG"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-a34861b-1 jxzoZC"&gt;&lt;img src="/bbcx/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-a34861b-0 cOpVbP hide-when-no-script"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/160xn/p0kv8430.jpg.webp 160w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/240xn/p0kv8430.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/320xn/p0kv8430.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/480xn/p0kv8430.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/640xn/p0kv8430.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/800xn/p0kv8430.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/1024xn/p0kv8430.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/1376xn/p0kv8430.jpg.webp 1376w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/1920xn/p0kv8430.jpg.webp 1920w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/480xn/p0kv8430.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Getty Images Elderly people are more vulnerable to temperature changes as they are less able to thermoregulate (Credit: Getty Images)" class="sc-a34861b-0 efFcac"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-a34861b-2 hesJxn"&gt;Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 bdPeAJ"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-8353772e-0 iUqqeb"&gt;Elderly people are more vulnerable to temperature changes as they are less able to thermoregulate (Credit: Getty Images)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 dlWCEZ"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;One thing that can help you fall asleep is the "&lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S1087079218301552?via=ihub" class="sc-c9299ecf-0 beIoQm"&gt;hot bath effect&lt;/a&gt;". Wisden says that having a hot bath before bedtime can help induce sleep. "We've done physiological experiments with mice and found that if you warm the skin, that sends signals to the hypothalamus in the base of the brain – and that triggers an induction of sleep and a cooling of the body." &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 dlWCEZ"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;So, getting under a thick duvet at night can help the body prepare the body for &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S2468867319301804" class="sc-c9299ecf-0 beIoQm"&gt;longer episodes of sleep or deeper sleep.&lt;/a&gt; Snuggling up like this – to warm the skin – is not unique to humans. Wisden adds: "Pets, cats and dogs curl up – and some animals build a nest… that provides a kind of thermal insulation." &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 dlWCEZ"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;But once you're fast asleep, a cool room temperature is ideal: between 16-18C (60-65F). While &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/37474050/" class="sc-c9299ecf-0 beIoQm"&gt;older adults might sleep more comfortably&lt;/a&gt; in a room that's a couple of degrees warmer, being in a room that's too warm can cause &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S001393511500033X?via=ihub" class="sc-c9299ecf-0 beIoQm"&gt;poor sleep quality&lt;/a&gt;. This can lead to waking up throughout the night, as well as a lack of non-REM sleep – the most &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/books/NBK526132/" class="sc-c9299ecf-0 beIoQm"&gt;restful&lt;/a&gt; stage of sleep. "Being too hot during sleep is bad. It's exactly like a noise, or a sensation on your skin, or a pain. Being hot while you're asleep stimulates sensory perception and wakes you up," Wisden says. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 dlWCEZ"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;Ultimately, while we can be guided by research, it seems it may be impossible to find an optimal temperature that will please everyone. From age to gender, hormones to metabolism, there are many factors at play that might influence whether you prefer a hotter or colder room.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 dlWCEZ"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;So, the battle of the thermostat rages on.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 dlWCEZ"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;&lt;i id="for-more-science,-technology,-environment-and-health-stories-from-the-bbc,-follow-us-on" class="sc-7dcfb11b-0 kKcaog"&gt;For more science, technology, environment and health stories from the BBC, follow us on &lt;/i&gt;&lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.facebook.com/BBCFuture/" class="sc-c9299ecf-0 beIoQm"&gt;&lt;b id="facebook" class="sc-7dcfb11b-0 kVRnKf"&gt;&lt;i id="facebook" class="sc-7dcfb11b-0 kKcaog"&gt;Facebook&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;i id="," class="sc-7dcfb11b-0 kKcaog"&gt;, &lt;/i&gt;&lt;a target="_blank" href="https://x.com/BBC_Future" class="sc-c9299ecf-0 beIoQm"&gt;&lt;b id="x" class="sc-7dcfb11b-0 kVRnKf"&gt;&lt;i id="x" class="sc-7dcfb11b-0 kKcaog"&gt;X&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;i id="and" class="sc-7dcfb11b-0 kKcaog"&gt; and &lt;/i&gt;&lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.instagram.com/bbcfuture_official/" class="sc-c9299ecf-0 beIoQm"&gt;&lt;b id="instagram" class="sc-7dcfb11b-0 kVRnKf"&gt;&lt;i id="instagram" class="sc-7dcfb11b-0 kKcaog"&gt;Instagram&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;b id="." class="sc-7dcfb11b-0 kVRnKf"&gt;&lt;i id="." class="sc-7dcfb11b-0 kKcaog"&gt;.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BBC.com</author><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiugFBVV95cUxOVUJuWWo0VEI4SnhuZ3oyUEtKRTJtbTRvSWVNS1FvdnQ2ckY4X0x2elJTdVEtVmNoTTItbkJwenQ2ajdyM05Fa0NtakJSQ3huMUY2aWNwNVJXUGdBeC1OS29hNTVVa2VEempNeWRXWV84UGwyVXVwQ1VTdFY1bnlGeWxxVF9iUFJhMnNLWEFrUElrcm5pUHpqSnN6d1RlOHM4V1FVamNzQVZ3ZmZ1ODdJbU41ZmVYTW1PcEE</guid></item><item><title>I tried walking yoga and I was amazed by how calm it made me feel - Fit and Well</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiowFBVV95cUxNNzFvQmJ3LWRUejRsUHBPa0gyX3h4Rk1xRkJlVkJFQmZBZ3I5WHhwdDZPV0RCeWcxVTNKaVhYX0MzbDJ5QWN3Nk1fNzBDbGdzNGxON3dfQkRMZjNtZU9ZSXFsc3hJVG56LWdsdTNNQWw0WFVGMFJZR09vSHJmdUQwR3BPVEh3N2xPRnViSFZrTTQyR3pTLTdRTmlXTDkxMDZQVzA0?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="article-body" class="article__body "&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’m a big fan of walking and I do my best to hit 7,500 steps every day. &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.fitandwell.com/features/what-is-mindful-walking" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.fitandwell.com/features/what-is-mindful-walking"&gt;Mindful walking&lt;/a&gt; is nothing new to me, but I had never heard of walking yoga until Sophia Drozd, a yoga instructor and creator of the &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.yogaforpainapp.com/" data-url="https://www.yogaforpainapp.com/" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;Yoga for Pain &lt;/a&gt;app, brought it to my attention.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="ad-unit-1" class="ad-unit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Drozd explained that it was first established in the 1970s as a way of combining yoga and breathwork with an everyday activity: walking. I decided to give it a go, forgoing my usual headphones and music for some focus and breathwork.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To do it, all I had to do was synchronize my steps with my breath and be mindful of my body and surroundings while I walked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="article-body__section" id="section-what-i-found"&gt;&lt;span&gt;What I found: &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. You have to concentrate&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;This may seem obvious to anyone who has ever tried to pat their head and rub their tummy at the same time, but I was surprised at how much focus was required for me to synchronize my breathing with my steps. Because I was concentrating, my mind didn’t wander and I didn’t spend time analyzing my day — a habit that can make me feel stressed or anxious even in lovely weather.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2. Mindfulness came naturally &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="ad-unit-2" class="ad-unit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Once my breath and steps were synchronized, I grew aware of my surroundings and how I felt in my body. I was amazed at how the breathwork made me feel, cutting through the noise in my head and reconnecting me with myself. The rhythmic, repetitive nature of syncing my breath and steps felt calming—almost hypnotic&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3. I was more aware of the beauty around me&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Without the distraction of my headphones or thoughts, I noticed the beauty of the natural world. I chose a fantastic day to try walking yoga: the sun was shining, the birds were chirping and I could smell spring in the air. When I got back and thought about it, I realized that the weather had been the same the day before. I just hadn’t noticed because I had been so wrapped up in my thoughts. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;4. It slowed down my walking pace&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div id="slice-container-newsletterForm-articleInbodyContent-Ys5bdHaDp675H8urbx4zAk" class="slice-container newsletter-inbodyContent-slice newsletterForm-articleInbodyContent-Ys5bdHaDp675H8urbx4zAk slice-container-newsletterForm"&gt;&lt;div data-hydrate="true" class="newsletter-form__wrapper newsletter-form__wrapper--inbodyContent"&gt;&lt;div class="newsletter-form__container"&gt;&lt;section class="newsletter-form__main-section"&gt;&lt;p class="newsletter-form__strapline"&gt;Start your week with achievable workout ideas, health tips and wellbeing advice in your inbox.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;I timed my inhale and exhale to coincide with my left foot striking the ground, so I was taking two steps per breath. This was only sustainable if I slowed my walking pace down. I tried other breathing patterns but nothing else worked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="article-body__section" id="section-how-to-start-walking-yoga"&gt;&lt;span&gt;How to start walking yoga&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Start small," advises Drozd, "Especially if you're not a daily yogi or walker." She encourages starting with five minutes a day in a place you know well—your session could even form part of a larger walk. You can then gradually increase by five minutes every few days.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"This will give you time for your muscles to adjust to your new routine," she says. "Keep increasing until you get to 20 minutes a day. If you can't spare 20 minutes every day or want to mix walking yoga sessions into your weekly routine, I would recommend doing 30 minutes, three days a week."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Regular mindful practice for your mind and body can help reduce stress, boost your mood, and improve concentration and body awareness, says Drozd.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div id="slice-container-person-Ys5bdHaDp675H8urbx4zAk-MyDJbt1rjt5tjKEvYfiK703BiJyE5fIC" class="slice-container person-wrapper person-Ys5bdHaDp675H8urbx4zAk-MyDJbt1rjt5tjKEvYfiK703BiJyE5fIC slice-container-person"&gt;&lt;div class="person person--separator person--strapline"&gt;&lt;span class="person__strapline"&gt;About our expert&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="person__heading"&gt;&lt;span class="person__strapline-inline"&gt;About our expert&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="person__name-socials"&gt;&lt;span class="person__name"&gt;Sophia Drozd&lt;/span&gt;&lt;nav class="button-social-group person__social-buttons" aria-labelledby="button-social-group- person__social-buttons"&gt;&lt;p id="button-social-group- person__social-buttons"&gt;Social Links Navigation&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a class="button-social   " href="https://www.instagram.com/yogaforpainapp/%20" target="_blank" aria-label="INSTAGRAM"&gt;&lt;span class="button-social__icon"&gt;&lt;svg class="icon_instagram" viewbox="0 0 24 24" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"&gt;&lt;circle cx="12" cy="12" fill="#de3073" r="12"&gt;&lt;/circle&gt;&lt;path d="M18.958 9.116a5.121 5.121 0 00-.336-1.708 3.557 3.557 0 00-2.044-2.044 5.12 5.12 0 00-1.694-.322C14.142 5.014 13.89 5 12 5s-2.142.014-2.884.042a5.213 5.213 0 00-1.708.322 3.665 3.665 0 00-2.044 2.044 5.213 5.213 0 00-.322 1.708C5.014 9.858 5 10.1 5 12s.014 2.142.042 2.884a5.12 5.12 0 00.322 1.694 3.44 3.44 0 00.812 1.246 3.4 3.4 0 001.232.8 5.175 5.175 0 001.708.336c.742.028.98.042 2.884.042s2.142-.014 2.884-.042a5.082 5.082 0 001.694-.336 3.456 3.456 0 002.044-2.044 5.006 5.006 0 00.336-1.694C18.986 14.142 19 13.9 19 12s-.014-2.142-.042-2.884zM17.7 14.828a3.946 3.946 0 01-.252 1.3 2.189 2.189 0 01-.518.8 2.165 2.165 0 01-.8.532 4.641 4.641 0 01-1.3.238c-.742.028-.966.042-2.828.042s-2.1-.014-2.828-.042a3.837 3.837 0 01-1.3-.252A2.258 2.258 0 016.54 16.13a3.91 3.91 0 01-.238-1.3c-.028-.742-.042-.966-.042-2.828s.014-2.086.042-2.828a3.787 3.787 0 01.238-1.3A2.445 2.445 0 017.87 6.54a3.856 3.856 0 011.3-.238c.742-.028.952-.042 2.828-.042s2.086.014 2.828.042a3.787 3.787 0 011.3.238 2.445 2.445 0 011.33 1.33 4.641 4.641 0 01.238 1.3c.027.742.042.952.042 2.828s-.011 2.088-.036 2.83zM12 8.4a3.6 3.6 0 103.6 3.6A3.6 3.6 0 0012 8.4zm.181 5.929a2.338 2.338 0 01-.362-4.662 2.43 2.43 0 01.362 0 2.338 2.338 0 010 4.662zm3.557-6.909a.84.84 0 11-.84.84.84.84 0 01.84-.838z" fill="#fff"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a class="button-social   " href="https://www.yogaforpainapp.com/" target="_blank" aria-label="WEBSITE"&gt;&lt;span class="button-social__icon button-social__icon-website"&gt;&lt;svg class="icon-website" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 1000 1000"&gt;&lt;path d="M1000 500A501 501 0 0 0 503 0h-6A501 501 0 0 0 0 500c0 275 223 499 498 500h4a501 501 0 0 0 498-500zM529 936V765h133c-31 90-79 154-133 171zM337 765h134v171c-54-17-101-81-134-171zM61 539h176a899 899 0 0 0 22 167H110a439 439 0 0 1-49-166zM471 64v191H331c31-101 82-173 140-191zm199 191H529V64c58 18 109 90 140 191zm270 226H763c-1-59-7-115-18-167h155a438 438 0 0 1 40 167zm-235 0H529V314h156a857 857 0 0 1 19 167zM471 314v167H296a859 859 0 0 1 19-167h156zM237 481H60a438 438 0 0 1 41-167h154a921 921 0 0 0-18 167zm59 58h175v167H320a837 837 0 0 1-24-166zm233 167V539h175a831 831 0 0 1-24 167H529zm234-166h176a436 436 0 0 1-49 166H741a893 893 0 0 0 22-166zm104-285H731c-20-68-47-126-81-169a443 443 0 0 1 217 169zM350 86c-33 43-61 101-81 169H133A443 443 0 0 1 350 86zM148 765h127c20 59 45 110 75 150a442 442 0 0 1-202-150zm502 150c30-39 56-91 75-150h127a442 442 0 0 1-202 150z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/nav&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="person__bio"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sophia Drozd is the owner and founder of &lt;a href="https://www.yogaforpainapp.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Yoga for Pain&lt;/a&gt;  (Y4P), and is a qualified yoga teacher, lifelong practitioner and chronic pain warrior. Diagnosed with fibromyalgia, scoliosis and carpel tunnel syndrome, Drozd has lived with pain all of her adult life. She is on a mission to share Y4P, a pioneering yoga app for the chronic pain community, which uses yoga and breathwork to ease pain, paving the way for a more mobile and fulfilling life for its users.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Fit and Well</author><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 08:07:39 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiowFBVV95cUxNNzFvQmJ3LWRUejRsUHBPa0gyX3h4Rk1xRkJlVkJFQmZBZ3I5WHhwdDZPV0RCeWcxVTNKaVhYX0MzbDJ5QWN3Nk1fNzBDbGdzNGxON3dfQkRMZjNtZU9ZSXFsc3hJVG56LWdsdTNNQWw0WFVGMFJZR09vSHJmdUQwR3BPVEh3N2xPRnViSFZrTTQyR3pTLTdRTmlXTDkxMDZQVzA0</guid></item><item><title>Hunters: Beware of ‘zombie’ deer - Food Safety News</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMieEFVX3lxTE0xSm5ybTV5ZldVYm5NbjZVVUVVX254VTdnQ1UtMFVEOTYyS3BuWlhWeWR0RHhhM0M5U29sRVFZVEQwNVItdG1UaEhkNThpZ00xcEk3Rjg3NWZJZXptX3hVRWRLTVNPY0F2QktxNE9PSHJaYVNZUzh2Zw?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="lxb_af-post_content lxb_af-clear"&gt;

				
			
					
						
			
&lt;p&gt;An incurable infectious brain disease that’s deadly to deer, elk and moose continues to stalk the land. By 2015, it had expanded to 23 states and two Canadian province since it was first identified in a Colorado captive mule deer research center in 1967.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Now, with Washington state’s first case of chronic wasting disease confirmed in an adult female white-tailed deer that was found dead north of Spokane, the disease, CWD, has been identified in 35 states and 6 Canadian provinces.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;In other recent news, an Indiana county is reporting its first case of chronic wasting disease (CWD), less than a year after the state’s first detection.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;A 2.5-year-old white-tailed buck in Posey County tested positive after being harvested by a hunter.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Also concerning is that just several weeks ago, the Wyoming Game and Fish Department announced its second and third cases of CWD had been discovered on an elk feedground — both detected in cow carcasses at the Dell Creek Feedground in the Bondurant area. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CWD travels&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;figure class="wp-block-image size-large"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.foodsafetynews.com/files/2025/02/timeline-chronic-wasting-disease.png"&gt;&lt;img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" src="https://www.foodsafetynews.com/files/2025/02/timeline-chronic-wasting-disease-656x348.png" alt="" class="wp-image-247344" srcset="https://www.foodsafetynews.com/files/2025/02/timeline-chronic-wasting-disease-656x348.png 656w, https://www.foodsafetynews.com/files/2025/02/timeline-chronic-wasting-disease-320x170.png 320w, https://www.foodsafetynews.com/files/2025/02/timeline-chronic-wasting-disease-240x127.png 240w, https://www.foodsafetynews.com/files/2025/02/timeline-chronic-wasting-disease-768x407.png 768w, https://www.foodsafetynews.com/files/2025/02/timeline-chronic-wasting-disease-1536x814.png 1536w, https://www.foodsafetynews.com/files/2025/02/timeline-chronic-wasting-disease-40x21.png 40w, https://www.foodsafetynews.com/files/2025/02/timeline-chronic-wasting-disease-80x42.png 80w, https://www.foodsafetynews.com/files/2025/02/timeline-chronic-wasting-disease-160x85.png 160w, https://www.foodsafetynews.com/files/2025/02/timeline-chronic-wasting-disease-1100x583.png 1100w, https://www.foodsafetynews.com/files/2025/02/timeline-chronic-wasting-disease-550x291.png 550w, https://www.foodsafetynews.com/files/2025/02/timeline-chronic-wasting-disease-367x194.png 367w, https://www.foodsafetynews.com/files/2025/02/timeline-chronic-wasting-disease-734x389.png 734w, https://www.foodsafetynews.com/files/2025/02/timeline-chronic-wasting-disease-275x146.png 275w, https://www.foodsafetynews.com/files/2025/02/timeline-chronic-wasting-disease-825x437.png 825w, https://www.foodsafetynews.com/files/2025/02/timeline-chronic-wasting-disease-220x117.png 220w, https://www.foodsafetynews.com/files/2025/02/timeline-chronic-wasting-disease-440x233.png 440w, https://www.foodsafetynews.com/files/2025/02/timeline-chronic-wasting-disease-660x350.png 660w, https://www.foodsafetynews.com/files/2025/02/timeline-chronic-wasting-disease-880x466.png 880w, https://www.foodsafetynews.com/files/2025/02/timeline-chronic-wasting-disease-184x97.png 184w, https://www.foodsafetynews.com/files/2025/02/timeline-chronic-wasting-disease-917x486.png 917w, https://www.foodsafetynews.com/files/2025/02/timeline-chronic-wasting-disease-138x73.png 138w, https://www.foodsafetynews.com/files/2025/02/timeline-chronic-wasting-disease-413x219.png 413w, https://www.foodsafetynews.com/files/2025/02/timeline-chronic-wasting-disease-688x364.png 688w, https://www.foodsafetynews.com/files/2025/02/timeline-chronic-wasting-disease-963x510.png 963w, https://www.foodsafetynews.com/files/2025/02/timeline-chronic-wasting-disease-123x65.png 123w, https://www.foodsafetynews.com/files/2025/02/timeline-chronic-wasting-disease-110x58.png 110w, https://www.foodsafetynews.com/files/2025/02/timeline-chronic-wasting-disease-330x175.png 330w, https://www.foodsafetynews.com/files/2025/02/timeline-chronic-wasting-disease-300x159.png 300w, https://www.foodsafetynews.com/files/2025/02/timeline-chronic-wasting-disease-600x318.png 600w, https://www.foodsafetynews.com/files/2025/02/timeline-chronic-wasting-disease-207x110.png 207w, https://www.foodsafetynews.com/files/2025/02/timeline-chronic-wasting-disease-344x182.png 344w, https://www.foodsafetynews.com/files/2025/02/timeline-chronic-wasting-disease-55x29.png 55w, https://www.foodsafetynews.com/files/2025/02/timeline-chronic-wasting-disease-71x38.png 71w, https://www.foodsafetynews.com/files/2025/02/timeline-chronic-wasting-disease-102x54.png 102w, https://www.foodsafetynews.com/files/2025/02/timeline-chronic-wasting-disease.png 1850w" sizes="(max-width: 656px) 100vw, 656px"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;figcaption class="wp-element-caption"&gt;Click on graphic to enlarge.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;p&gt;This is a disease doesn’t stay put. It has been found in South Korea; in free-ranging reindeer, moose and red deer in Norway; in free-ranging moose in Finland; and in free-ranging moose Sweden.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Caused by malformed proteins called prions, it can be confirmed through testing of lymph nodes or brain tissue, at the base of the skull. The lymph nodes of the deer that tested positive in Eastern Washington in July were submitted to the Washington Animal Disease Laboratory in Pullman at Washington State University.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Much smaller than bacteria, prions are single proteins that cannot be destroyed by typical “kill strategies” such as extreme heat or ultraviolet light.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;There is no vaccine or cure for this disease. It is spread through urine, feces, saliva, blood, semen, deer parts, and especially via live deer. Not only that, plants and roots can bind, uptake and transport infectious prions. And plants infected with the prions were able to transmit the disease when animals were fed the contaminated plants.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;This is a disease that has baffled scientists for decades. Where did it come from, and why is it spreading across the landscape?&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“”Our biggest challenge is to try to minimize its spread.” said Melia T. Devivo, the Washington State Fish and Wildlife Department’s lead for its CWD program,&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How do you know if an animal has CWD&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Drastic weight loss, stumbling and lack of coordination, drooling, excessive thirst or urination, drooping ears and lack of fear of people are signs that an animal is infected with CWD. No wonder that some people refer to the infected animals as “zombie deer.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;But Devivo said that because it takes so long — sometimes several years — for the disease to become apparent in an animal, some animals with CWD look healthy. It’s a year-round disease — not seasonal.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Because CWD moves slowly through a population, and because it kills individual deer slowly, its impact is not dramatic or rapid, which is why some hunters believe CWD is not a serious problem.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;However, CWD will gradually grow in prevalence if it is not actively managed, and it will eventually reduce populations.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“CWD is the biggest threat to the future of deer hunting,” says the Theodore Roosevelt Conservation Partnership &lt;a href="https://www.trcp.org/chronic-wasting-disease/?gad_source=1&amp;amp;gbraid=0AAAAADq_fn0JJJB1eul-lmXJQWXTk1JDu&amp;amp;gclid=EAIaIQobChMI9vbQ0PbfiwMVm9bCBB0-1jFPEAAYASAAEgLRN_D_BwE)"&gt;on its website&lt;/a&gt;  Go to the website to watch how fast the disease has spread across the United States since 1968.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Where is it?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.usgs.gov/media/images/distribution-chronic-wasting-disease-north-america-0)"&gt;Go here&lt;/a&gt; to see the regions in the U.S. where CWD has been confirmed. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Deer and other cervids — members of the deer family — killed in those regions need to be tested and also butchered according to state rules.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What about food safety?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;While no cases of transmission to humans have been reported, the Centers for Disease Control recommends that you do not consume meat from a CWD positive deer. And the National Deer Association encourages all hunters to adhere to the agency’s  guidelines regarding the handling or consumption of venison from CWD positive deer.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;According to CDC, the high-risk parts include the brain, eyes, backbone and spleen.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;That’s why it’s important to bone out your harvest to avoid moving sensitive parts of the deer that could carry CWD.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Boots on the ground: How hunters can help&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://deerassociation.com/cwd/"&gt;Go here&lt;/a&gt; for some advice from the National Deer Association about how hunters can help prevent the spread of CWD.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;        •       Know if you hunt in a CWD management zone where the disease has been found or will be traveling to hunt in a CWD zone. This is basic, crucial knowledge that helps you learn and follow regulations and guidelines designed to prevent the spread of CWD out of these zones.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;  •     If you hunt in a CWD zone, submit all harvested deer to the state wildlife agency for CWD testing (and wait for satisfactory results before consuming the venison). Testing helps the agency keep tabs on the disease’s prevalence and location, which is crucial information for protecting the deer resource and hunting.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;        •       If you hunt in a CWD zone, dispose of deer carcasses inside the zone following the recommendations of that state’s wildlife agency. Leave the zone only with boned-out meat, antlers connected to clean skull plates, clean hides, or clean jawbones/teeth. Most states now ban the importation of whole deer carcasses and are enforcing these laws.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;        •       If you kill a deer that tests positive for CWD, that’s a good thing. You removed an infected deer from the woods, which helps fight the disease. Don’t let it get you down. Collect your replacement tag from the state wildlife agency, keep hunting, and keep testing the deer you harvest.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;        •       If you do not hunt in a CWD zone, but your state wildlife agency asks you to voluntarily submit deer for CWD testing, respond to the call for help. Submit your deer for testing. Discovering new CWD outbreaks early is critical to reducing the impact.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;        •       Report sick deer immediately to your state wildlife agency. Whether you see or harvest a deer that appears unhealthy, the state wildlife agency may want to examine and test the deer. Early detection of CWD is very important, so don’t hesitate to report sick deer.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;        •       Harvest an appropriate number of does to maintain balance between deer density and forage availability where you hunt. Diseases that spread deer-to-deer like CWD move more slowly across the landscape in healthy deer densities.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Devivo said that CWD is most prevalent in buck deer simply because buck deer have a larger home range than do does, and they have more contact with other deer because of breeding and fighting with other bucks.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;        •       Connect with your state wildlife agency for information, even if you don’t hunt in or near a CWD zone. Sign up for the agency’s e-newsletter, follow them on social media, and attend public hearings whenever offered. Stay informed about all wildlife issues in your state, including deer health and hunting regulations.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What about ‘captive’ cervid farms&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Sometimes called “deer farms,’  captive cervid facilities are located on privately owned property. There are more than 10,000 captive-cervid breeding and shooting facilities in North America.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;According to a study from Texas A&amp;amp;M University, they are “perhaps the fastest growing industry in rural America.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The industry includes raising native or exotic cervids sold for such things as antlers, meat, breeding and even urine, which is used as an attractant. In some cases artificial breeding is used to produce larger cervids and antlers, which bring in good prices.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;When it comes to CWD, what’s particularly troubling is that these operations often transport the animals to locations across North America, thus raising the risk of spreading the disease to other locations. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Then, too, since they’re often raised in dense populations, there’s more risk of CWD spreading should an animal have it. And even though the animals are fenced in, they sometimes “escape” and come into contact with wild cervids. There’s also the possible problem of “fence-to-fence” contact between captive and wild cervids.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The annual estimated economic impact of the cervid industry in Minnesota by 2012 was $17 million, with an estimated 1,287 jobs supported by this industry.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;However, on the flip size of the coin, economic losses associated with CWD’s impact on the captive cervid industry for places like Alberta, Canada, range from $12 million (for prevention measures like improving fencing) to hundreds of millions (for compensation by the government for depopulation).&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“The impact of CWD on the captive cervid industry is not a future problem but a growing and ongoing reality,” says the report. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://wildlife.org/wp-content/uploads/2014/05/captive-cervid-breeding.pdf"&gt;Go here&lt;/a&gt; for more information about captive cervid farms.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;(To sign up for a free subscription to Food Safety News,&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.foodsafetynews.com/subscribe/#.VtSWqcdln_R"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;click&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;here)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;


			
			
		&lt;/div&gt;
  
		&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Food Safety News</author><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 05:02:58 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMieEFVX3lxTE0xSm5ybTV5ZldVYm5NbjZVVUVVX254VTdnQ1UtMFVEOTYyS3BuWlhWeWR0RHhhM0M5U29sRVFZVEQwNVItdG1UaEhkNThpZ00xcEk3Rjg3NWZJZXptX3hVRWRLTVNPY0F2QktxNE9PSHJaYVNZUzh2Zw</guid></item><item><title>RFK Jr, noted vaccine sceptic, backs measles jab amid deadly US outbreak - Al Jazeera English</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMirwFBVV95cUxNT1dtUW1GUU05RHF1bWxhOExzMk5QeDhNWVE2V1BBVUlEQ2g3MzdmNV9DV0NubHdSOWlWMHhqUHhmRW9PVEN5TjZ5SHA5cnBpX21ISzdQMm56R09tWkZNS19YaVQyQ1JmZmpJV3gtSHNWajlZV3JzRUNhejNCRUdoXzRTWlJTN3htUUxENnVsWUp1R2JfZm1sa1FYZVdtZmxFRUxGeUhZX3FLSE15ODFR0gG0AUFVX3lxTE9XTVY3aGtqVjNaUEJDWlZ1RWJaTDgtRUY2Y1dnRDByTl94aWliZFdHRmxKMEpFRExZUENNR3N3LXIxUkl4U0FMbnRuWWw0enNyMTh0dTV0WW0tQmN1OVV6QnRIaFNoTm1yZ2p0TXRvOEVVVUpJVzI1ZDN0LUx3LW5zWWsxTERJZ09KTDl2dHJDeGIxZXpkZ0xyRnV5Vkl0eC1qVGM2ZVBaZXdTa1lRWWlXS21vRQ?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;header class="article-header"&gt;&lt;h1&gt;RFK Jr, noted vaccine sceptic, backs measles jab amid deadly US outbreak&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;p class="article__subhead"&gt;&lt;em&gt;US health secretary says he is ‘deeply concerned’ about outbreak in Texas.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/header&gt;&lt;div class="wysiwyg wysiwyg--all-content" aria-live="polite" aria-atomic="true"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Robert F Kennedy Jr, the top health official in the United States who is known for his scepticism of vaccines, has backed the measles jab amid &lt;a href="/news/2025/2/27/us-reports-first-measles-death-since-2015"&gt;a deadly outbreak of the infectious disease&lt;/a&gt; in Texas.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In an opinion piece published by Fox News on Sunday, Kennedy said he was “deeply concerned” about the spread of the disease despite earlier suggesting that it was “not unusual”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="more-on"&gt;&lt;h2 class="more-on__heading"&gt;Recommended Stories &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;span class="screen-reader-text"&gt;list of 4 items&lt;/span&gt;&lt;article class="more-on__article"&gt;&lt;span class="screen-reader-text"&gt;list 1 of 4&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;article class="more-on__article"&gt;&lt;span class="screen-reader-text"&gt;list 2 of 4&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;article class="more-on__article"&gt;&lt;span class="screen-reader-text"&gt;list 3 of 4&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;article class="more-on__article"&gt;&lt;span class="screen-reader-text"&gt;list 4 of 4&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;span class="screen-reader-text"&gt;end of list&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Vaccines not only protect individual children from measles, but also contribute to community immunity, protecting those who are unable to be vaccinated due to medical reasons,” Kennedy wrote, though he said the decision to vaccinate is “a personal one”.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The US secretary of health and human services said that before the introduction of the MMR vaccine, “virtually every child” in the US contracted measles.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“For example, in the United States, from 1953 to 1962, on average there were 530,217 confirmed cases and 440 deaths, a case fatality rate of 1 in 1,205 cases,” he wrote.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;US authorities last month reported the first measles death in the country in a decade after an unvaccinated school-aged child was hospitalised with the disease in northwest Texas.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As of Friday, 146 cases had been identified in the state since late January, according to the Texas Department of State Health Services.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Health officials have said the cases have been concentrated in a community of Mennonites, a Christian sect that arose out of the radical factions of the 16th-century Reformation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kennedy, who has &lt;a href="/news/2025/1/29/rfk-jrs-view-on-vaccines-comes-under-fire-at-contentious-us-senate-hearing"&gt;promoted scientifically discredited research&lt;/a&gt; linking vaccines to autism, attracted criticism last month when he appeared to downplay the outbreak by pointing out there had been several outbreaks already this year.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Measles can be highly dangerous for people who are not vaccinated, including young infants who are not typically eligible for immunisation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;About one in five unvaccinated individuals in the US who gets measles is hospitalised, while about one out of every 20 children with the disease gets pneumonia, according to the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Al Jazeera English</author><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 04:39:17 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMirwFBVV95cUxNT1dtUW1GUU05RHF1bWxhOExzMk5QeDhNWVE2V1BBVUlEQ2g3MzdmNV9DV0NubHdSOWlWMHhqUHhmRW9PVEN5TjZ5SHA5cnBpX21ISzdQMm56R09tWkZNS19YaVQyQ1JmZmpJV3gtSHNWajlZV3JzRUNhejNCRUdoXzRTWlJTN3htUUxENnVsWUp1R2JfZm1sa1FYZVdtZmxFRUxGeUhZX3FLSE15ODFR0gG0AUFVX3lxTE9XTVY3aGtqVjNaUEJDWlZ1RWJaTDgtRUY2Y1dnRDByTl94aWliZFdHRmxKMEpFRExZUENNR3N3LXIxUkl4U0FMbnRuWWw0enNyMTh0dTV0WW0tQmN1OVV6QnRIaFNoTm1yZ2p0TXRvOEVVVUpJVzI1ZDN0LUx3LW5zWWsxTERJZ09KTDl2dHJDeGIxZXpkZ0xyRnV5Vkl0eC1qVGM2ZVBaZXdTa1lRWWlXS21vRQ</guid></item><item><title>The rising alarm about the dangers of legalized marijuana - Deseret News</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMijAFBVV95cUxOeERTVHM3ZEkxeVprWDQwZzlWVmRkOHA1RDN1YzNGY1VWOXlKSi1lTGxmZDJHYVdBaldudjAxNlZkM2NoSzhvcjlfQ3k2QjRXdElaR2VzZk5ncHVGVTk1R1BjQzJvREVTNkRvRVUwdmxnVlc2Mld5QlV5VHVFaEs0ZDllXzl4MjVUZmJhdw?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="dn-article-body mt-4"&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;Miriam was vomiting uncontrollably on a summer morning in 2022 when she arrived at a Utah hospital. She was diagnosed with a condition she had never heard of.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;This was her third ER trip with cannabinoid hyperemesis syndrome (CHS) in as many years. The first time she vomited for 12 hours, the second for 36 hours. This time, the worst and last, the intense pain lasted five days, during which, she was later told, she had hallucinatory conversations and threatened to leap from a fourth story window.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;Miriam, 45, who asked for professional reasons to use only her first name, had a legal marijuana prescription to treat both PTSD, acquired from years of driving an ambulance, and chronic pain from an auto accident.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;This was all true, but the real reason she needed cannabis that summer was that her mother was dying of a rare blood infection, and she had just been diagnosed with thyroid cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;She needed emotional help. And help was at hand.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;Having used marijuana off and on since high school, Miriam had a high tolerance for THC, the drug’s main psychotropic compound. But after a single drag on a 95 percent pure THC vape pen purchased at a local medical dispensary, it felt like her body was in a vice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;“Every nerve was going off,” Miriam told me. “I hurt physically everywhere. If I had to choose between doing that again and being eaten by a bear, I would choose the bear.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 id="The-race-to-legalize-marijuana" class="dn-article-body__h3"&gt;The race to legalize marijuana&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;CHS is rare but becoming less so. The key risk factors are long-term, frequent and heavy marijuana use. Symptoms begin with nausea, followed in later episodes, often separated by a year or more, by cyclical vomiting, dehydration, and emergency room visits.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;The New York Times estimated last year that 6 million Americans may have CHS symptoms from using marijuana. The syndrome’s rates have risen as more Americans consume higher-potency cannabis with greater frequency. Over recent decades breeding has dramatically increased THC content in the plant itself, while purified THC products are now ubiquitous.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;At the federal level, marijuana remains a Schedule 1 illegal drug, alongside heroin, LSD and a few others. But at the state level, the race to legalization in recent years has been dizzying. Several states and territories have significantly liberalized marijuana access. According to the National Conference of State Legislatures, as of January, 39 states allow medical marijuana, with 24 of those having fully legalized weed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;And yet, amid this enthusiasm, prominent health researchers are sounding alarms. And CHS is just one of several emerging concerns. While few experts now advocate a full return to prohibition, many do worry that the accelerating pace of easy access and heightened potency are outstripping scientific evidence on the safety of long-term marijuana use — and, when used as medicine, its efficacy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;In particular, many experts point to the long-term effects on the developing minds and bodies of adolescents and young adults, calling out overlooked risks of regular marijuana use to developing brains and bodies in their 20s.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;“We allowed people to vote whether or not cannabis is a medicine,” noted Yasmin Hurd, a neurobiologist at the Mount Sinai Medical Center in New York City. “Now we’re asking everybody in the country to be their own doctor with cannabis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;“That has never been done with any other medicine.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;Recent polls show that 88 percent of Americans favor legal medical use of cannabis, and 60 percent full legalization.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 id="What-science-says" class="dn-article-body__h3"&gt;What science says&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;In 2023, the National Survey on Drug Use and Health found that nearly 44 million Americans used marijuana in the past month. By comparison, the same report cites 135 million daily alcohol users. “Far more people drink,” noted one study, “but high-frequency drinking is less common. In 2022, the median drinker reported drinking on 4–5 days in the past month, versus 15–16 days in the past month for cannabis.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;Among those daily or nearly-daily users are many who look to cannabis for help with assorted ailments. In 2018, the International Cannabis Policy Study found that 27 percent of North Americans between 16 and 65 had used cannabis to help with pain, sleep, migraines, anxiety, depression and PTSD. Conditions that qualify under Utah’s medical cannabis law include HIV, Alzheimer’s, ALS, cancer, Crohn’s disease, epilepsy, multiple sclerosis and PTSD.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;Whether all these medical hopes could withstand random controlled trials is the key unanswered question. For now, the evidence is mostly weak or nonexistent. On treating PTSD with cannabis, for example, the American Psychiatric Association actually issued a &lt;a href="https://www.psychiatry.org/getattachment/0b3cc852-bc22-45ce-b9dc-9b98747889e7/Position-Cannabis-for-PTSD.pdf#:~:text=APA%20Position:%20Because%20of%20the%20lack%20of,the%20treatment%20of%20post%2Dtraumatic%20stress%20disorder%20(PTSD).&amp;amp;text=The%20APA%20does%20not%20endorse%20cannabis%20for,this%20time%2C%20as%20further%20study%20is%20needed." target="_blank"&gt;&lt;u&gt;formal statement&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; opposing the use of cannabis to treat PTSD, emphasizing that “no published evidence of sufficient quality exists in the medical literature to support the practice.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;In 2017, the National Academies of Sciences, Engineering, and Medicine released an exhaustive report on cannabis science and policy that remains the most widely-cited reference. For medical uses, the National Academies study found “insufficient or no evidence.” But it did support improvements in three areas: “chronic pain,” “chemotherapy-induced nausea and vomiting,” and “spasticity associated with multiple sclerosis.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;But even the study’s chronic pain section concludes that “very little is known about the efficacy, dose, routes of administration, or side effects” and warns that the products being sold to consumers and patients bear “little resemblance to the products that are available for research.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 id="'I'd-never-had-access-to-anything-that-strong'" class="dn-article-body__h3"&gt;‘I’d never had access to anything that strong'&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;Utah’s dispensaries are home to a huge variety of THC materials. In addition to raw cannabis flower, there are vapes, liquids, concentrates, tinctures, topicals and edibles. Gummies are available in a multitude of fruit flavors. And vape cartridges come with names like “galactic gas,” “piña gluelada,” “mountain diesel” and “pappy poison.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;Utah medical cannabis law allows up to 113 grams of raw cannabis flower a month. Depending on the potency, that could be enough for seven joints a day. On top of that, the law allows 20 grams of purified THC in other forms like edibles, tinctures and vapes. That’s enough for 66 potent gummies every day. No one really could handle that much. In short, under Utah law there is nothing stopping a willing doctor from giving eager patients all the THC their body could handle and more.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;Just contemplating the plethora of delivery devices and variety of formulas and potencies on the dispensary sales floor is nearly as mind-blowing as consuming them. “I’ve been smoking pot since I was 14,” Miriam said, “but I’d never had access to anything that strong.” It was there, in her local Utah dispensary, that Miriam purchased the 95 percent pure THC vape pen that sparked her final cannabinoid hyperemesis syndrome incident.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote cite="" class="c-stack dn-article-body__pullquote " data-style-direction="vertical" data-style-justification="start" data-style-alignment="unset" data-style-inline="false" data-style-wrap="nowrap"&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;“We allowed people to vote whether or not cannabis is a medicine. Now we’re asking everybody in the country to be their own doctor with cannabis. That has never been done with any other medicine.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;Exactly how THC affects the body is still a mystery. Not until 1988 did researchers begin to map the delicate system we now call the endocannabinoid system, a network of receptors and internal cannabinoids that are active throughout the body.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;The network relies on subtle nudges to modulate stress, appetite, hormones, memory, emotions, sleep, body temperature, pain and the immune system. That sweeping portfolio may in time uncover previously unimaginable treatments for difficult conditions, says UC Irvine’s Daniele Piomelli, who since the early 1990s has been a key player in endocannabinoid system research.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;Piomelli is a neuroscientist who argues that the brain cannot be considered separately from the body. “The endocannabinoid system works in all these tissues and all these organs,” Piomelli said. And the daily use of THC in adolescence will permanently affect how the ECS works in organs that regulate health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;A flood of THC appears to slow internal cannabinoid production and attenuate receptor networks, Piomelli said. More THC is then required for a similar effect, a key marker of addiction. Those system disruptions can also lead to severe inflammation and immune and digestive problems, such as Miriam experienced with CHS.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;A 2022 study in Colorado linked cannabis to increased temporary psychosis. A recent article on the Yale School of Medicine website noted that “heavy and early use of cannabis is associated with increased risk of developing schizophrenia, bipolar disorder, depression, and anxiety.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;Neurobiologist Yasmin Hurd has done pathbreaking work on the neurological risks of adolescent THC use, but she also studies the therapeutic potential of cannabidiol for opioid addiction.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;Now a professor at the Mt. Sinai Medical Center’s Icahn School of Medicine, Hurd has been working since the early 1990s with rats, first studying cocaine, amphetamine and heroin addictions. When she turned to cannabis 20 years ago, her colleagues laughed. “Oh, that’s not a drug, you know,” they said. At the time, most people were still convinced cannabis was not truly biologically addictive.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;But she found that rats given THC as adolescents would self-administer heroin at higher rates once they were adults. At least for rats, it was now clear that the cannabis gateway to opiates is biological.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;“People aren’t laughing at me that much anymore,” she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;Hurd also found that brain scans of adult rats exposed to THC as adolescents showed attenuated neural networks. Those scans, she says, look very similar to human schizophrenia. Subsequent human studies, Hurd says, have confirmed that “adolescent exposure to cannabis does indeed change the prefrontal cortical in a manner similar to what we had shown in animals.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;Hurd also notes a Danish epidemiological study that showed a strong correlation between increased cannabis use and potency and rising schizophrenia rates. That study found much lower schizophrenia rates among those who began cannabis use after they turned 26, suggesting a link to prefrontal cortex maturation. Most experts now see the evidence linking adolescent cannabis use to heightened schizophrenia as compelling.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;Hurd makes a point of clarifying “adolescence.” Neurologically, human adolescence does not end until age 25, when the prefrontal cortex matures. Women mature a bit earlier and men a bit later. At 21, legal young adults are still neurological adolescents, and will be for years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;In a finding Hurd fairly describes as scary, her lab also discovered that rats given THC as adolescents can pass epigenetic damage to the second and third generation. Descendants struggled to manage stress and were more prone to self-administer heroin.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;But Hurd is not only framing problems; she is also looking for solutions. She began studying cannabidiol (CBD) long before it became popular. Like THC, cannabidiol is an important compound in the cannabis plant, but it has very different effects. The balance of CBD and THC is often considered critical in therapeutic uses.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;“We found that CBD actually did the opposite to THC,” she said. “Animals exposed to CBD reduced their heroin seeking.” Hurd is now a co-principal investigator in advanced clinical trials, with results so far confirming that CBD can be used to effectively reduce opiate craving.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;When she began researching THC’s impact on adolescent brains, Hurd says the cannabis industry marked her as an enemy. Once she began researching cannabidiol therapies, the industry decided she might be OK. But she has never cared about what they think. “Follow the data,” she tells her research team. “No matter what the results are, the data tells us.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote cite="" class="c-stack dn-article-body__pullquote " data-style-direction="vertical" data-style-justification="start" data-style-alignment="unset" data-style-inline="false" data-style-wrap="nowrap"&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;“People should not be using it when they’re young and their brains are still developing.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;Following data is easier said than done. Everybody is using different kinds of medical cannabis for dozens of different conditions, said Ryan Vandrey, a psychiatry professor at the Johns Hopkins medical school, “but they’re all doing it different, making it very hard to integrate the data.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;Databases demand consistent inputs. To make that possible, Vandrey and his colleagues at Johns Hopkins recently got a $10 million grant for a five-year project to create a standardized assessment and collect large quantities of observational data that will, they hope, be followed by good clinical trials.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;“If you were to ask me which health conditions should be studied with a large clinical trial,” Vandrey told me, “and what the product would be, I couldn’t tell you.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 id="'It-was-not-an-easy-decision'" class="dn-article-body__h3"&gt;‘It was not an easy decision’&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;The stories Vandrey needs are in the files of general practitioners like Dr. Matt McIff. About 100 of McIff’s patients currently use medical cannabis, mostly for chronic pain. However, he opposes recreational legalization — or even casual medical legalization where the difference gets blurred.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;McIff illustrates his approach with two cases from his practice. Fittingly, they serve as bookends to Yasmin Hurd’s dual research tracks: CBD for opioid addiction and adolescent THC risks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;The first case is a carpenter with chronic pain from a work injury who disclosed that he had for years struggled with opiate painkiller addiction but was now sober, implying that he white-knuckled his recovery — a rare and difficult feat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;With his curiosity piqued, McIff asked directly if the patient had used cannabis to overcome opiate cravings. Of course, he had. “After I assured him it was OK,” McIff said, “his eyes got really big and he teared up. He was so relieved to have his experience legitimized.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;The patient still uses a moderate cannabis dose for sleep and pain, a careful balance of THC and cannabidiol. But he is opiate-free, married with two children, and runs a business with 10 employees.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;On the flip side, McIff tells of a 17-year-old patient who had self-medicated for his anxiety with cannabis obtained from friends. McIff walked the mother and son through the risks of adolescent cannabis — CHS, addiction risks, cognitive dysfunction and harms to the developing brain and body.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;Finally, he suggested that teens who use cannabis for anxiety may shortchange their emotional development. The stress and confusion in youth, he said, is sometimes just part of learning life skills under pressure. Early cannabis use that masks stress may not only damage neural networks but also undercut psychological growth.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;“If you are 17 and feeling stressed and you haven’t developed emotional skills,” McIff told me, “cannabis becomes a substitute.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;McIff is an outspoken advocate of supervised medical cannabis, but also an outspoken opponent of recreational legalization. In his view, the very respect he has for the drug’s potency pushes back against its unsupervised casual use for entertainment or self-medication.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;McIff’s reticence on legalization makes him a bit of an outlier. Despite layer upon layer of health concerns, none of the other experts I spoke with favored continued prohibition.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;For example, Christopher Andrews, a gastroenterologist in Calgary, Canada, and an expert on cannabinoid hyperemesis syndrome, was philosophical when I asked about Canada’s permissive 18- to 21-year-old limit for recreational cannabis, given the developmental realities of the human body noted above.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;“People should not be using it when they’re young and their brains are still developing,” Andrews said. But he was sympathetic to Canadian policymakers, who feared the black-market realities of trying to enforce prohibition until a later age.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;“It was not an easy decision,” Andrews said. “That’s for sure.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;Rather than going back to a policy of blanket prohibition, most researchers I spoke with, like Andrews, are focused on doing the long-delayed science required to better quantify both the perils and promise of cannabis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote cite="" class="c-stack dn-article-body__pullquote " data-style-direction="vertical" data-style-justification="start" data-style-alignment="unset" data-style-inline="false" data-style-wrap="nowrap"&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;“Follow the data. No matter what the results are, the data tells us.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;Not all doctors who prescribe cannabis are as careful as McIff. Miriam, for example, got her prescription from a doctor she had never previously met, located in a cannabis medical clinic in the same building as the dispensary. “You sit down at a desk with the doctor. They ask you a few questions, and then they write you a prescription and you walk out the door,” Miriam said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;No one probed her underlying needs, checked on current therapies, explored alternatives — or even taught her how to balance THC and cannabidiol. Miriam finds it alarming that neither the doctor nor the dispensary staff warned her of CHS — a foreseeable risk, however rare, that she would have recognized in her own profile if it had been described.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;Now with 18 months of recovery behind her, Miriam makes a surprising admission. She’s glad she was forced to quit. Cold turkey recovery, she says, made her realize she had been using not just for pain and PTSD, and not just to grieve her current loss, but also to bury unresolved emotional issues from her youth. “I used pot to avoid dealing with my stuff,” she said. “It was convenient that it was legal.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;After her crisis, Miriam spent three months at home on bed rest. With little else to do, she joined remote group therapy sessions twice a day. At first her engagement was perfunctory, even petulant. Uncovering old hurts and grieving new losses without her chemical crutch was wrenching. But the payoff was worth it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;“Having to grieve my mom and grieve having cancer 100 percent sober was the best thing that ever happened to me,” she said. “I have less pain than I’ve ever had in my life. I have less anxiety. And I’m so glad that I can’t smoke pot.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;&lt;i&gt;This story appears in the March 2025 issue of&lt;/i&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.deseret.com/magazine/"&gt;&lt;i&gt; Deseret Magazine&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;i&gt;.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;a href="https://pages.deseret.com/subscribe?utm_source=deseret&amp;amp;utm_medium=deseret_com&amp;amp;utm_campaign=learn_more_subscribe_footers"&gt;&lt;i&gt; Learn more about how to subscribe&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;i&gt;.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Deseret News</author><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijAFBVV95cUxOeERTVHM3ZEkxeVprWDQwZzlWVmRkOHA1RDN1YzNGY1VWOXlKSi1lTGxmZDJHYVdBaldudjAxNlZkM2NoSzhvcjlfQ3k2QjRXdElaR2VzZk5ncHVGVTk1R1BjQzJvREVTNkRvRVUwdmxnVlc2Mld5QlV5VHVFaEs0ZDllXzl4MjVUZmJhdw</guid></item><item><title>Montgomery County reports measles case linked to international travel - 69News WFMZ-TV</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMimgJBVV95cUxNVVVMWnNlRTNkMG5pVnNnOGlZczJidTdibkFZS1A5d0RPdVFaYjVFQThkTHM0Wk5icThvbG9kWnhsRmhNeFNha25pQnZNSzA2LThoOFgyMHJ0Uzc2WFpEelhIQkNnTmlRZnpaRXhUQm05aUExcUc4SDJMVXJURy1jbldJbUtIWTFJdTJta29fRWVyTzNvWmRZVGxNS2txWm8xTnBLaHB4OUdyeHhFZ2JpQzZkS096SzdPTTZoQV9XY0x3Tjd0RWVERjZYNmtMNFNMemxhaUdrX2ZMU1lRTkVqOXQtTjBUeWNXTHZyWlo2Skd4VkUxUG5VWlczSW9MVmt3bXNWelJYaGtOVWhSZUltS3RFNHQxTkY1WEE?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="article-body" itemprop="articleBody" class="asset-content  subscriber-premium" false&gt;
                                &lt;meta itemprop="isAccessibleForFree" content="true"&gt;
                                
                                
                                &lt;p&gt;MONTGOMERY CO., Pa. - "They took the appropriate precautions, they did the appropriate testing," said Dr. Lorraine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to the county, people may have been exposed on a China Airlines shuttle bus departing JFK Airport, arriving in North Philadelphia February 25th into the 26th.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In addition to the Children's Hospital on the 26th, the county said people may also have been exposed at True North Pediatrics Associates of Plymouth in Plymouth Meeting on the same date.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The good news is that the vaccine is highly effective against measles," said Dr. Lorraine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He said droplets can linger for two hours in a space after someone with the virus leaves.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr. Lorraine said the county maintains fairly good vaccination rates.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="tncms-region-article_instory_middle" class="tncms-region hidden-print"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He spoke about what symptoms come along with measles&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Typically, we'll see pretty high fevers and all the concomitant symptoms that would be associated with that, it can cause seizures if it becomes significantly elevated, cough, shortness of breath. These are all very, very common," said Dr. Lorraine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He said in Texas there is a spread within a population that is specifically unvaccinated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Our situation is definitely different. This is essentially a one-off. It was a case of a child who was too young to be vaccinated traveled to an area where measles happens to be endemic and happened to unfortunately contract the disease," said Dr. Lorraine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr. Lorraine said if you suspect you have measles, to seek medical attention and to let the facility you are going to know you are coming.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He said the best defense is to be vaccinated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="tncms-region-article_instory_bottom" class="tncms-region hidden-print"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
                                
                                
                            &lt;/div&gt;

                            

                            
    


                            
    


                            
                                &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>69News WFMZ-TV</author><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 03:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimgJBVV95cUxNVVVMWnNlRTNkMG5pVnNnOGlZczJidTdibkFZS1A5d0RPdVFaYjVFQThkTHM0Wk5icThvbG9kWnhsRmhNeFNha25pQnZNSzA2LThoOFgyMHJ0Uzc2WFpEelhIQkNnTmlRZnpaRXhUQm05aUExcUc4SDJMVXJURy1jbldJbUtIWTFJdTJta29fRWVyTzNvWmRZVGxNS2txWm8xTnBLaHB4OUdyeHhFZ2JpQzZkS096SzdPTTZoQV9XY0x3Tjd0RWVERjZYNmtMNFNMemxhaUdrX2ZMU1lRTkVqOXQtTjBUeWNXTHZyWlo2Skd4VkUxUG5VWlczSW9MVmt3bXNWelJYaGtOVWhSZUltS3RFNHQxTkY1WEE</guid></item><item><title>Cancer family 'financially broken' by wait for benefits - BBC.com</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiWkFVX3lxTE1iLWxVOHp3ajFvNXFER3dPc092UEZlRWFNNmM2aF92SHN4ZzZqTWlJUkIzaDdBZEg1dFJ0di1SMnNYVmhQWkx6U1RzcFRGcDdtZXR6OFVSNGdjQdIBX0FVX3lxTE56QVN5RnU3aUV5TzZiZkdmcjBMajhSVFQzUkJkZUlfTVN5UlZYOER6c1RwSUVWRElJaVpWTC02eHQ2ZDlaUU02WDRMWEMydVdKbU5yNU0taW9LRTcxX09B?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article&gt;&lt;p data-component="headline-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 eeiVGB"&gt;&lt;h1 class="sc-518485e5-0 itISwu"&gt;Cancer family 'financially broken' by benefits wait&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 ejjhCR"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="hero-image" class="sc-a34861b-1 jxzoZC"&gt;&lt;img src="/bbcx/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-a34861b-0 cOpVbP hide-when-no-script"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/653c/live/04638850-f5f1-11ef-bd6e-cd71c2e1454a.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/653c/live/04638850-f5f1-11ef-bd6e-cd71c2e1454a.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/653c/live/04638850-f5f1-11ef-bd6e-cd71c2e1454a.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/653c/live/04638850-f5f1-11ef-bd6e-cd71c2e1454a.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/653c/live/04638850-f5f1-11ef-bd6e-cd71c2e1454a.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/653c/live/04638850-f5f1-11ef-bd6e-cd71c2e1454a.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/653c/live/04638850-f5f1-11ef-bd6e-cd71c2e1454a.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/653c/live/04638850-f5f1-11ef-bd6e-cd71c2e1454a.jpg.webp" loading="eager" alt="Kerry Bolton Oliver sitting on a hospital bed holding a sick bowl" class="sc-a34861b-0 efFcac"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-a34861b-2 hesJxn"&gt;Kerry Bolton&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 bdPeAJ"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-8353772e-0 iUqqeb"&gt;Oliver Hercombe's family said they had been "financially broken" by the additional living costs since his cancer diagnosis&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 dlWCEZ"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;Families of children and young people with cancer are struggling financially for several months waiting for benefits to help cover extra costs caused by the illness, according to a charity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;Young Lives vs Cancer says families need "immediate" help with additional living costs, which amount to £700 a month on average - and is calling for quicker access to the funds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;One family has said they were left "financially broken" by the extra living costs after their 16-year-old son Oliver's leg had to be amputated because he had a rare type of cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;The government says it is committed to giving people access to benefits in a "timely manner", but acknowledges that "waits are too high".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 eeiVGB"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-518485e5-0 DkKTF"&gt;'If I don't have electricity, he can't walk'&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 dlWCEZ"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;Kerry Bolton, from Solihull, said she had to wait five months before a decision was made on her benefits application after her son Oliver was diagnosed with cancer, aged 16.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;"The hospital is an hour away from us and I don't drive. It was costing us £48 a day for us to travel in taxis there and back."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;Oliver later underwent a leg amputation, meaning his family had to buy new clothes to fit him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;They also faced higher electricity bills to charge his prosthetic leg, Ms Bolton said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;"Ollie's leg needs electricity...if I don't have electricity, he can't walk."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;Ms Bolton said she also had to use more energy to heat her home to keep Oliver warm, because of his immunosuppression treatment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 jFCfG"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-a34861b-1 jxzoZC"&gt;&lt;img src="/bbcx/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-a34861b-0 cOpVbP hide-when-no-script"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/53da/live/39d806f0-f5fb-11ef-a576-211c964a64b2.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/53da/live/39d806f0-f5fb-11ef-a576-211c964a64b2.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/53da/live/39d806f0-f5fb-11ef-a576-211c964a64b2.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/53da/live/39d806f0-f5fb-11ef-a576-211c964a64b2.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/53da/live/39d806f0-f5fb-11ef-a576-211c964a64b2.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/53da/live/39d806f0-f5fb-11ef-a576-211c964a64b2.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/53da/live/39d806f0-f5fb-11ef-a576-211c964a64b2.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/53da/live/39d806f0-f5fb-11ef-a576-211c964a64b2.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Kerry Bolton Oliver showing his prosthetic leg" class="sc-a34861b-0 efFcac"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-a34861b-2 hesJxn"&gt;Kerry Bolton&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 bdPeAJ"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-8353772e-0 iUqqeb"&gt;Oliver's prosthetic leg needs to be charged regularly, which has increased the family's energy bill, his mother says &lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 dlWCEZ"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;During a child's cancer treatment, families may need to travel to distant appointments, buy special food, use more electricity and heating, pay for childcare for siblings, and stay in hotels.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;Under UK law, cancer patients may be entitled to benefits to help with costs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;However, patients are not eligible for financial support until they have been ill for three months.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;They then face a further wait of four months on average for their application to be assessed, according to Young Lives vs Cancer, which has interviewed hundreds of patients and put out a new report.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;The charity is calling for families to qualify for benefits immediately following a diagnosis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 jFCfG"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-a34861b-1 jxzoZC"&gt;&lt;img src="/bbcx/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-a34861b-0 cOpVbP hide-when-no-script"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/c250/live/a7fa0df0-f5f5-11ef-bd6e-cd71c2e1454a.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/c250/live/a7fa0df0-f5f5-11ef-bd6e-cd71c2e1454a.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/c250/live/a7fa0df0-f5f5-11ef-bd6e-cd71c2e1454a.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/c250/live/a7fa0df0-f5f5-11ef-bd6e-cd71c2e1454a.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/c250/live/a7fa0df0-f5f5-11ef-bd6e-cd71c2e1454a.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/c250/live/a7fa0df0-f5f5-11ef-bd6e-cd71c2e1454a.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/c250/live/a7fa0df0-f5f5-11ef-bd6e-cd71c2e1454a.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/c250/live/a7fa0df0-f5f5-11ef-bd6e-cd71c2e1454a.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Danielle Roberts Jasmine wearing a head cover " class="sc-a34861b-0 efFcac"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-a34861b-2 hesJxn"&gt;Danielle Roberts&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 bdPeAJ"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-8353772e-0 iUqqeb"&gt;Nine-year-old Jasmine's family had to make long car journeys for her treatment&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 dlWCEZ"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;Danielle Roberts, from North Wales, told the BBC that she experienced financial "strain" as soon as her nine-year-old daughter Jasmine was diagnosed with cancer last year, but she did not receive any benefits for eight months.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;"We were just thrown into this world where...our child's got cancer and we don't know if she's going to survive, along with dealing with the financial impact.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;"You've still got all these bills to pay on top of going back and forward to hospital, which was an hour and 15 minutes away, extra food, accommodation".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;Ms Roberts said having to take long periods off work added to the financial strain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;"My income was dramatically reduced because it's hard to work when your child is in hospital... and you don't want to work, you should be able to spend time with your child when they're poorly."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 eeiVGB"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-518485e5-0 DkKTF"&gt;Form filling&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 dlWCEZ"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;"What we're seeing is heartbreaking," Young People vs Cancer's chief executive Rachel Kirby-Rider told the BBC.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;"People don't have that disposable income, they don't have that money in savings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;"Having to wait seven months for disability benefits is driving a lot of families into debt and impacting families at a time they just want to concentrate on getting their child well." &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;The charity is also concerned about the application process, as the 50-page forms were "tricky, long and complex", asking families for detailed descriptions about their child's needs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;The process should be made "simple and efficient", it says, by using medical evidence alone to make applications.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;Ms Roberts said she struggled to find the "head space" to complete the application form when her daughter Jasmine was ill.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;"They asked so many questions and you've got to send added proof... you don't want to have to think about that really as well as 'is my child going to be OK?'.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;"It's something that shouldn't have to be done when you're going through that traumatic time."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;A Department for Work and Pensions spokesperson said: "We are committed to ensuring people can access financial support through Personal Independence Payment and Disability Living Allowance for children in a timely manner.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;"But we recognise waits are too high, and we have increased the number of staff to respond to the increase in claim volumes."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BBC.com</author><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 02:47:12 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiWkFVX3lxTE1iLWxVOHp3ajFvNXFER3dPc092UEZlRWFNNmM2aF92SHN4ZzZqTWlJUkIzaDdBZEg1dFJ0di1SMnNYVmhQWkx6U1RzcFRGcDdtZXR6OFVSNGdjQdIBX0FVX3lxTE56QVN5RnU3aUV5TzZiZkdmcjBMajhSVFQzUkJkZUlfTVN5UlZYOER6c1RwSUVWRElJaVpWTC02eHQ2ZDlaUU02WDRMWEMydVdKbU5yNU0taW9LRTcxX09B</guid></item><item><title>RFK Jr says Texas measles outbreak a ‘call to action’ - The Hill</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMinwFBVV95cUxNZmlCRzVrQjhOVG9GZXZCRGpaR1BGWEd3Z2dPUFlBTURVZ0lqRU11RVB4TDNtRUlwUmVlVVNTRzVEd1hjVUNFVjRyeHVtU3BHenpVMG40dmhiTFhybkhUTFFMR3B1UGFpQ004czJHb3VXYnA3SXQ2UDAtU0ZWUURmTXZ1VkpHYU9RZUJxMTNKNWZTNGJuWEt1RkNaUEpDRTDSAaQBQVVfeXFMTWRia2tUWHg4UjRXdHhjNUY5SDVvNWIxNEQtQmpRZWdBZ05lY2R1R01reHpsXzJEQnV0YlNMNl9xVUxoZUd6Q3ZaYkFUOW9UT3ptbEtqcEVfQS12dHlYcDZZUnBiNG0zZEpQNWlyRm9qTEZ1a0xaUXdNTXlqZ1FtRjZrMVM2aE40S1R5U1ZGdzY3bzZtWkVuc3hoSkZPQ01xYnRaU2Q?oc=5</link><description>&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;
    
    
    &lt;noscript&gt;
      
    &lt;/noscript&gt;
  &lt;/body&gt;
</description><author>The Hill</author><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 02:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMinwFBVV95cUxNZmlCRzVrQjhOVG9GZXZCRGpaR1BGWEd3Z2dPUFlBTURVZ0lqRU11RVB4TDNtRUlwUmVlVVNTRzVEd1hjVUNFVjRyeHVtU3BHenpVMG40dmhiTFhybkhUTFFMR3B1UGFpQ004czJHb3VXYnA3SXQ2UDAtU0ZWUURmTXZ1VkpHYU9RZUJxMTNKNWZTNGJuWEt1RkNaUEpDRTDSAaQBQVVfeXFMTWRia2tUWHg4UjRXdHhjNUY5SDVvNWIxNEQtQmpRZWdBZ05lY2R1R01reHpsXzJEQnV0YlNMNl9xVUxoZUd6Q3ZaYkFUOW9UT3ptbEtqcEVfQS12dHlYcDZZUnBiNG0zZEpQNWlyRm9qTEZ1a0xaUXdNTXlqZ1FtRjZrMVM2aE40S1R5U1ZGdzY3bzZtWkVuc3hoSkZPQ01xYnRaU2Q</guid></item><item><title>UK death rate 'reaches record low' - BBC.com</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiWkFVX3lxTFBqS1V5aFFsZ05ER3NMa0lPYnZUNjZFLTUzWkE5RzdUVVRYVGphNU1mMDUyZDI3TnlQY0lCaEdpUlM3b2ttOE1DVDE5NG1FdU5PaUx1WlJ2MjJGUdIBX0FVX3lxTFBhNnk5d0lhcjFNMktBQ1BudFlhQVR5a3Y2ZmZCZGJRcllocktMR0s2blo5bXJDeFl3d1I4LXhlZ0lOc0NQZnNTMjJEbDZJOXlWZ2NfTGxPd3d6STJISWxV?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article&gt;&lt;p data-component="headline-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 eeiVGB"&gt;&lt;h1 class="sc-518485e5-0 itISwu"&gt;UK death rate 'reaches record low'&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="byline-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 dlWCEZ"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="byline-new" class="sc-b42e7a8f-0 haItSe"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="byline-new-contributors" class="sc-b42e7a8f-12 fcCDwR"&gt;&lt;div class="sc-b42e7a8f-5 evAEAB"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;span class="sc-b42e7a8f-7 kItaYD"&gt;Christine Jeavans&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="sc-b42e7a8f-8 bTSIhT"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Data journalist, BBC Verify&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 ejjhCR"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="hero-image" class="sc-a34861b-1 jxzoZC"&gt;&lt;img src="/bbcx/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-a34861b-0 cOpVbP hide-when-no-script"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/ca50/live/75b03d10-f514-11ef-a276-596f7e6218f8.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/ca50/live/75b03d10-f514-11ef-a276-596f7e6218f8.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/ca50/live/75b03d10-f514-11ef-a276-596f7e6218f8.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/ca50/live/75b03d10-f514-11ef-a276-596f7e6218f8.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/ca50/live/75b03d10-f514-11ef-a276-596f7e6218f8.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/ca50/live/75b03d10-f514-11ef-a276-596f7e6218f8.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/ca50/live/75b03d10-f514-11ef-a276-596f7e6218f8.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/ca50/live/75b03d10-f514-11ef-a276-596f7e6218f8.jpg.webp" loading="eager" alt="Getty Images An older man carries a young boy on his shoulders during a walk outside. The relationship is one of grandfather and grandson. " class="sc-a34861b-0 efFcac"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-a34861b-2 hesJxn"&gt;Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 bdPeAJ"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-8353772e-0 iUqqeb"&gt;Improvements in death rates largely reflect better health at older age groups&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 dlWCEZ"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;The UK death rate reached a record low last year, according to exclusive analysis carried out for BBC News.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;Mortality experts looked at death certificates registered in 2024 and found that deaths per head of the population had returned to pre-pandemic levels and were slightly below the previous record in 2019.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;However, the new figure puts the UK back on its long-term trend of only gradual improvement.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;The research was carried out by analysts from the Continuous Mortality Investigation (CMI) at the Institute and Faculty of Actuaries.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 eeiVGB"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-518485e5-0 DkKTF"&gt;What's been happening to death rates?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 dlWCEZ"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;"This is five years of basically flat mortality improvement, it's pretty poor by historical standards," said Stuart McDonald from the CMI.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;There was also a "concerning" rise in the death rate at young working ages, he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;A Department of Health spokesperson said the government was "shifting focus from sickness to prevention".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;The registered death rate in the UK steadily halved from 1974 to 2011 largely driven by improvements in tackling heart disease, including smoking prevention and medical advances.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="embed-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 jVHuOl"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 dlWCEZ"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;From 2011 to 2019 the improvements drastically slowed, then changed direction during Covid as thousands more people died than normal. The first post-pandemic year of 2022 also saw &lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/health-64209221" class="sc-c9299ecf-0 beIoQm"&gt;high numbers of extra deaths&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;To calculate the record low 2024 UK figure of 989 deaths per 100,000 people, analysts at the CMI used provisional weekly death registration figures for the four nations of the UK.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;"Clearly, it's very good news that our mortality rate is lower in 2024 than it was," says Dr Veena Raleigh, epidemiologist at health think tank &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.kingsfund.org.uk/" class="sc-c9299ecf-0 beIoQm"&gt;The King's Fund&lt;/a&gt;. "But if you look at the broader canvas then it's not so good."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;Although similar countries also experienced a slowdown since 2011, the UK's has been more severe and our life expectancy is at the "bottom of the pack of comparable countries," she says, adding that nations such as Spain returned to pre-pandemic levels by 2023.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 eeiVGB"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-518485e5-0 DkKTF"&gt;Causes and risk factors&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 dlWCEZ"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;Researchers point to a variety of reasons behind the slowdown since 2011. Some of the "low hanging fruit" of improvements in heart disease and cancer, such as the cut in smoking rates, had already happened, making further gains harder.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;At the same time, the UK saw rising risk factors, including obesity, poor diet and low levels of exercise, against a backdrop of widening social inequality and pressure on the NHS.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;Some academics argue that austerity cuts to public services after the 2008 financial crash had a strong impact on life expectancy, while others say it's not possible to prove this directly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;Dementia and Alzheimer's disease is the leading cause of death in England and Wales, according to the &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.ons.gov.uk/peoplepopulationandcommunity/birthsdeathsandmarriages/deaths/bulletins/deathsregistrationsummarytables/2023" class="sc-c9299ecf-0 beIoQm"&gt;latest official figures&lt;/a&gt;. Heart disease, lung disease, strokes, lung cancer also feature highly, along with flu in some years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;"Cardiovascular disease remains a leading killer in the UK," said Prof Bryan Williams OBE, chief scientific and medical officer at the British Heart Foundation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;"The plateau we have seen in reducing the number of deaths... is a serious cause for concern, made worse by the impact of the pandemic on an already overstretched health service."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;He added that early deaths from cardiovascular disease had grown in the most deprived areas of England and called for "urgent government action" in its prevention, detection and treatment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 eeiVGB"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-518485e5-0 DkKTF"&gt;Deaths at younger ages&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 dlWCEZ"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;Overall death rates are largely a reflection of older people's health as more than three-quarters of UK deaths happen over the age of 70.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;So the main trend is driven by what is happening to people in this age group.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;But the CMI found "really significant differences" at younger ages says Stuart McDonald, with a "concerning" upward trend in mortality among 20-44-year-olds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;"For this age group, death rates have actually been going up slightly, even before the pandemic. If we go back to 2011 we can see a slight increase in death rates year-on-year."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 dlWCEZ"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;Death numbers among this age group are much lower than at older ages and the causes tend to be different. Fewer than 20,000 people aged 20-44 die in the UK each year, about 3% of all deaths.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;"External and substance-related causes are most important because often that's what people die of in this age group," says Antonino Polizzi, researcher at the &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.demography.ox.ac.uk/" class="sc-c9299ecf-0 beIoQm"&gt;Leverhulme Centre for Demographic Science&lt;/a&gt; at the University of Oxford.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;"Things like drug overdoses, alcohol-related deaths, accidents, homicides and suicides."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;The UK, particularly Scotland, has seen a rise in drug-related death rates, he says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;"These causes are usually improving for other Western European countries so we are seeing a divergent effect."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;Commenting on the overall trends at all age groups, a Department of Health and Social Care spokesperson said: "We inherited an NHS that was broken and we are determined to fix it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;"Through our Plan for Change we are shifting focus from sickness to prevention and targeting the drivers of ill health and catching the biggest killers earlier.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;"We are creating the first smoke free generation, stopping junk food ads being targeted at children and improving detection of diseases such as cancer and cardiovascular disease."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 eeiVGB"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-518485e5-0 DkKTF"&gt;About the data&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BBC.com</author><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 00:47:26 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiWkFVX3lxTFBqS1V5aFFsZ05ER3NMa0lPYnZUNjZFLTUzWkE5RzdUVVRYVGphNU1mMDUyZDI3TnlQY0lCaEdpUlM3b2ttOE1DVDE5NG1FdU5PaUx1WlJ2MjJGUdIBX0FVX3lxTFBhNnk5d0lhcjFNMktBQ1BudFlhQVR5a3Y2ZmZCZGJRcllocktMR0s2blo5bXJDeFl3d1I4LXhlZ0lOc0NQZnNTMjJEbDZJOXlWZ2NfTGxPd3d6STJISWxV</guid></item><item><title>9 reasons to have black coffee in the morning - The Times of India</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMi3AFBVV95cUxPVEQzU2hYZUQtWlNfZ29VckdTZnpOX29Eb3NxNjRzQVJyOHFWckItbXlWRzU4dnp1dmdIZWtmcDRWM0YzS2lMTmRmX3VlcG5kTFphVEFfWEZTRllLRHdsU0F4Zm9nalpWbzQwakVmRnQ5ZktPWFJNeFQ5cTQxQnZSOFNVWmdzaU4tOHA5ZXp4M2VVRnlPMXBWdEd2azNNNlJlRWJEaVcyNTZ4cDZaNHNUZkVUbmp0MkkyWG5oZ2NBVXN1aHptT2hQMmpKSjFHTWZZNFBIUjlPaWxnV0dt?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;amp-story-grid-layer class="recircular" id="rcontent" template="vertical"&gt;&lt;div class="letterbox"&gt;&lt;p class="mid-heading"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;You may also like&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="rc3 pa"&gt;How Varun Chakravarthy worked on his phy...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="rc5 pa"&gt;10 rules of intermittent fasting for hea...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/amp-story-grid-layer&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Times of India</author><pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 00:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi3AFBVV95cUxPVEQzU2hYZUQtWlNfZ29VckdTZnpOX29Eb3NxNjRzQVJyOHFWckItbXlWRzU4dnp1dmdIZWtmcDRWM0YzS2lMTmRmX3VlcG5kTFphVEFfWEZTRllLRHdsU0F4Zm9nalpWbzQwakVmRnQ5ZktPWFJNeFQ5cTQxQnZSOFNVWmdzaU4tOHA5ZXp4M2VVRnlPMXBWdEd2azNNNlJlRWJEaVcyNTZ4cDZaNHNUZkVUbmp0MkkyWG5oZ2NBVXN1aHptT2hQMmpKSjFHTWZZNFBIUjlPaWxnV0dt</guid></item><item><title>Human Skin Can Taste Things, And Scientists Just Figured Out Why - ScienceAlert</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMilwFBVV95cUxQZjkta29nQzhXUDIwSGd6Q09CZ0VSOTNFM1RCcUZDbDZBVE1rZ0tTdzlvQUltdlNWNU9LaGg1d2tGY1JmSjdUc2FSbTlyXzBHX2pHaUZvQ19LNHVWR1hYMlFWeWNBbm9CR1lzajZERXUyd1JVa3NOZlNiSmhzTGtDdlV5ZkZYMnp1WFUxWk1wRmpHQjRyb1g4?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Ever set off too many of the bitter taste receptors on your tongue? You probably spat out whatever it was in your mouth, and that's our best guess for why we even have them: to stop us from ingesting things that might be harmful.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our skin cells have the same receptors, which serve a&lt;span&gt; similar purpose on a cellular level: to detect bitter substances. &lt;/span&gt;New research led by Okayama University of Science biologists builds on our knowledge of the type-2 taste receptors (TAS2Rs) found in the skin's keratinocytes, finding their role is also to keep potentially harmful materials from sticking around and causing damage.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Once thought to be confined to the tongue, TAS2Rs are actually spread much further throughout the body. They line your colon, your stomach, and your upper airways.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;A &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://karger.com/spp/article-abstract/28/3/137/295760/Expression-and-Functional-Activity-of-the-Bitter?redirectedFrom=fulltext"&gt;2015 paper&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; discovered them not just lurking but bristling with activity in the keratinized epithelial cells of human skin. &lt;/span&gt;The new research gets into the question of what exactly they are doing there.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lab-grown human keratinocytes were fed the quintessential 'bitter pill,' &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Phenylthiocarbamide"&gt;phenylthiocarbamide&lt;/a&gt; (PTC), which has been used in all sorts of studies around the genetics of bitter taste.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On detecting and binding with the PTC, the receptors triggered production of a fleet of ABC transporters to shuttle the bitter compound across the membranes and back out of the cell.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_153454" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-153454" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/02/fba21469-fig-0007-m.jpg" alt="diagram showing how bitter substances activate receptors which trigger production of abcb1, which helps excrete the substance. " class="wp-image-153454 size-full" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/02/fba21469-fig-0007-m.jpg 2128w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/02/fba21469-fig-0007-m-642x269.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/02/fba21469-fig-0007-m-990x415.jpg 990w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/02/fba21469-fig-0007-m-768x322.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/02/fba21469-fig-0007-m-1536x644.jpg 1536w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/02/fba21469-fig-0007-m-2048x858.jpg 2048w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/02/fba21469-fig-0007-m-600x252.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 2128px) 100vw, 2128px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-153454" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Schematic model of the excretion of bitter substances by the activation of the intracellular TAS2Rs. (Mori et al., &lt;em&gt;FASEB BioAdvances&lt;/em&gt;, 2025)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;To determine whether this newly-installed exit was functional, the team administered a visible tracer dye which could be rapidly excreted from the cell via a specific ABC transporter. When the team treated the cells with a substance called verapmil which is known to inhibit the transporter, the tracer had no way out, allowing it to accumulate.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The researchers think this chain of events set off by the TAS2Rs protects the cell from being damaged by potentially toxic bitter compounds, a premise that runs in line with theories about &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1093/chemse/bjp092"&gt;why we can taste 'bitter'&lt;/a&gt; at all.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When it comes to taste on the tongue, the jury is still out on whether bitterness actually helps us detect harmful substances. &lt;a href="https://iubmb.onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/iub.1694"&gt;Studies have found&lt;/a&gt; this flavor profile may not be such a helpful indicator of toxicity as we once thought, with many popular foods and drinks featuring a bitter flavour profile, and many toxic substances lacking it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But this latest study shows that among skin cells, at least, the receptors might have some benefit in surviving exposure to toxins. Cells that were given a toxic level of antihistamine &lt;span&gt;had much better survival rates when their bitter receptors had been fired up prior. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"A&lt;span&gt;ctivation of TAS2Rs by bitter compounds, such as PTC and saccharin, enhances ABCB1 production, leading to the prevention of diphenhydramin-induced cell death via excretion of these compounds," the authors &lt;a href="https://faseb.onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1096/fba.2024-00074"&gt;report&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Verapamil also reversed this protective effect.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"&lt;span&gt;Altogether, harmless activators of TAS2Rs may be promising drugs that enhance the excretion of toxic substances from the human skin," the authors &lt;a href="https://faseb.onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1096/fba.2024-00074"&gt;suggest&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/how-does-caffeine-wake-you-up" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73115" data-postid="153408" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;Coffee&lt;/a&gt; scrub, anyone?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This research was published in &lt;a href="https://faseb.onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1096/fba.2024-00074"&gt;&lt;em&gt;FASEB BioAdvances&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 23:55:18 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilwFBVV95cUxQZjkta29nQzhXUDIwSGd6Q09CZ0VSOTNFM1RCcUZDbDZBVE1rZ0tTdzlvQUltdlNWNU9LaGg1d2tGY1JmSjdUc2FSbTlyXzBHX2pHaUZvQ19LNHVWR1hYMlFWeWNBbm9CR1lzajZERXUyd1JVa3NOZlNiSmhzTGtDdlV5ZkZYMnp1WFUxWk1wRmpHQjRyb1g4</guid></item><item><title>The US Is Withdrawing From Global Health at a Dangerous Time - Bloomberg</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiuAFBVV95cUxOc1ZIc1FZRWFDOE5GMFJuN3FKM0tzX21LaG9vTFlhbzVSdHVjUXJjZ2ZEVW5iQ1J1eWZlRW0xLUhPYVctRUZjb2kyRUZ5ZmQxQlFJRFAyOVV1ZWxUS0dFbTJVSUxuMGs5Vnk1NkRtQ1RiNFZGTHdKODczb1ZxM3BOSGVGa0U4bFJ0RUs5TTNwc1EydTVyLWpUYVZpUG9BM3hVdS1ucWdyUUstaWJHbWVFM0VJNUZldm9R?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="body-content"&gt;&lt;p class="media-ui-Paragraph_text-SqIsdNjh0t0-" data-component="paragraph"&gt;To keep an eye on some of the world’s most dangerous infectious diseases, scientists rely on reports from the &lt;a href="https://www.who.int/europe/initiatives/measles-and-rubella-laboratory-network" title="Global Measles and Rubella Laboratory Network" target="_blank" rel="noopener" class="media-ui-Link_link-tVkXhPLPofs-" data-component="link"&gt;Global Measles and Rubella Laboratory Network&lt;/a&gt;. Known affectionately as Gremlin, it’s a grouping of more than 700 international labs that test about 500,000 patient samples annually. Gremlin monitors the prevalence of a huge range of pathogens in addition to those in its full name, including Covid-19, RSV, dengue, yellow fever and Ebola. And it does so on a remarkably modest budget: just $8 million a year, or less than 10% of the price tag for a single &lt;a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2024-04-15/cost-of-sustaining-lockheed-s-f-35-jet-now-forecast-to-exceed-1-5-trillion" title="Cost of Sustaining Lockheed’s F-35 Jet Now Forecast to Exceed $1.5 Trillion" target="_blank" rel="noopener" class="media-ui-Link_link-tVkXhPLPofs-" data-component="link"&gt;F-35 fighter jet&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="media-ui-Paragraph_text-SqIsdNjh0t0-" data-component="paragraph"&gt;Yet the program, which is managed by the &lt;a href="https://www.who.int/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" class="media-ui-Link_link-tVkXhPLPofs-" data-component="link"&gt;World Health Organization&lt;/a&gt;, is suddenly on the brink of extinction. Gremlin depends on money from the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention, the flagship US public-health agency. Since its establishment in 1946, the Atlanta-based CDC has worked on the front lines of every significant infectious disease outbreak, and if any of the threats that Gremlin tracks become a major problem, the agency will be expected to play the same role again. But shortly after President Donald Trump’s inauguration on Jan. 20, the lab network’s staff learned its &lt;a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2025-02-26/as-measles-cases-surge-in-texas-who-s-global-control-program-risks-collapse" title="As Measles Cases Surge in Texas, WHO’s Global Control Program Risks Collapse" target="_blank" rel="noopener" class="media-ui-Link_link-tVkXhPLPofs-" data-component="link"&gt;future was in doubt&lt;/a&gt;, because the US had pulled its funding, prompting an urgent scramble to find alternative donors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Bloomberg</author><pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 22:00:11 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiuAFBVV95cUxOc1ZIc1FZRWFDOE5GMFJuN3FKM0tzX21LaG9vTFlhbzVSdHVjUXJjZ2ZEVW5iQ1J1eWZlRW0xLUhPYVctRUZjb2kyRUZ5ZmQxQlFJRFAyOVV1ZWxUS0dFbTJVSUxuMGs5Vnk1NkRtQ1RiNFZGTHdKODczb1ZxM3BOSGVGa0U4bFJ0RUs5TTNwc1EydTVyLWpUYVZpUG9BM3hVdS1ucWdyUUstaWJHbWVFM0VJNUZldm9R</guid></item><item><title>Measles confirmed in unvaccinated Montgomery County child; others may have been exposed - WHYY</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMie0FVX3lxTE9SSnNNeHFXMkNYSHFqSDZtLVllTlV6MVlPU0ZPY2FjQTJ5bjROTVhQekJzamtOQmFFRjhQcTl0Rkl0cXlPeWcyWFNJZnV5T0RXNENIbUVZNnZmOGNZd2FSTVljRF9kbmpkNjE2OVdtWGhZWVR0Y2pOdDRvONIBgAFBVV95cUxQQ29sVzhDUzN5TFgzX2l2cDE3UzU4SE9mOHpEeXV3U3ZWdDA4d2YwSGU0NzVPblFvRGVFb24zNDJ1ZTBOTlBqakE4MkNpNnRRU0NtOTB5T0VyZUFVMk1vdk1ZN2F3OTVJZi1OZTRwUkdYT2Q0aWRpUUhzRWJEVkpPaQ?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="flexible-content-container wysiwyg-styles"&gt;
                                                                                                                                                                                          &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This story originally appeared on &lt;a href="https://6abc.com/post/measles-confirmed-unvaccinated-montgomery-county-child-members-public-may-have-been-exposed/15969940/"&gt;6abc&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Health officials in Montgomery County, Pennsylvania have confirmed a case of &lt;a href="https://6abc.com/tag/measles/" data-testid="prism-linkbase"&gt;measles&lt;/a&gt; in a child, and say it’s possible members of the public were exposed.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Office of Public Health said Sunday that the case involved an unvaccinated child who lives in the county. The child’s hometown was not released.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Officials said contact tracing is now underway and people who may have been exposed are being contacted.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Members of the public may have been exposed at the following times and locations:
  &lt;/p&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;Feb. 25–26, 2025&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;China Airlines Airport Shuttle Bus
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Departing JFK Airport Terminal 4, arriving at North Philadelphia, Pho Ha Saigon, 575 Adams Ave., Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 19120&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;From Feb. 25 at 9:30 p.m. to Feb. 26 at 3:15 a.m.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Feb. 26, 2025&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;True North Pediatrics Associates of Plymouth
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3031 Walton Rd., #C101, Plymouth Meeting, Pennsylvania, 19462&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;11:45. a.m. – 2:15 p.m.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;CHOP King of Prussia Campus Emergency Department
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;550 S. Goddard Boulevard, King of Prussia, Pennsylvania, 19406&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;12:52 p.m. – 3:02 p.m.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>WHYY</author><pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 21:49:48 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMie0FVX3lxTE9SSnNNeHFXMkNYSHFqSDZtLVllTlV6MVlPU0ZPY2FjQTJ5bjROTVhQekJzamtOQmFFRjhQcTl0Rkl0cXlPeWcyWFNJZnV5T0RXNENIbUVZNnZmOGNZd2FSTVljRF9kbmpkNjE2OVdtWGhZWVR0Y2pOdDRvONIBgAFBVV95cUxQQ29sVzhDUzN5TFgzX2l2cDE3UzU4SE9mOHpEeXV3U3ZWdDA4d2YwSGU0NzVPblFvRGVFb24zNDJ1ZTBOTlBqakE4MkNpNnRRU0NtOTB5T0VyZUFVMk1vdk1ZN2F3OTVJZi1OZTRwUkdYT2Q0aWRpUUhzRWJEVkpPaQ</guid></item><item><title>Measles outbreak continues to spike with nearly 150 reported cases - The Hill</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMihgFBVV95cUxPMFBfVGFub3lxM1FMX3lqVWFBX2pfbXVtTXJzS1RPZ0s5czI3NjlnYXM1ejJfTmllRlEyVDA0MW55SVl4OF8yVUZDZGdNc0dlVHdiYlkyWENyQ3hNQkJ4bTR2VEVscnFXYlhDYlFSZ244Y1Fsck1Cb2RDa21sNy1taG9PQk80dw?oc=5</link><description>&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;
    
    
    &lt;noscript&gt;
      
    &lt;/noscript&gt;
  &lt;/body&gt;
</description><author>The Hill</author><pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 21:11:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihgFBVV95cUxPMFBfVGFub3lxM1FMX3lqVWFBX2pfbXVtTXJzS1RPZ0s5czI3NjlnYXM1ejJfTmllRlEyVDA0MW55SVl4OF8yVUZDZGdNc0dlVHdiYlkyWENyQ3hNQkJ4bTR2VEVscnFXYlhDYlFSZ244Y1Fsck1Cb2RDa21sNy1taG9PQk80dw</guid></item><item><title>Measles outbreak continues to spike with nearly 150 reported cases - The Hill</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMihgFBVV95cUxPMFBfVGFub3lxM1FMX3lqVWFBX2pfbXVtTXJzS1RPZ0s5czI3NjlnYXM1ejJfTmllRlEyVDA0MW55SVl4OF8yVUZDZGdNc0dlVHdiYlkyWENyQ3hNQkJ4bTR2VEVscnFXYlhDYlFSZ244Y1Fsck1Cb2RDa21sNy1taG9PQk80d9IBiwFBVV95cUxQdV9iSnNOa3JZX1E0NWhSMTNfZGdNRGdTZ2pkZGxIcW51RWlwS0NsWGJNNUJwQUdtUDEzakdRNTNQcEE1TGNudmxiOURlc3JQWFN0UHdYRlB0TFBkU3FkaWdKbTVmRzJfUGxqSkRCWEpFck9PUnZ5ejRTVW82WnNlN090b19BQmw2bGhv?oc=5</link><description>&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;
    
    
    &lt;noscript&gt;
      
    &lt;/noscript&gt;
  &lt;/body&gt;
</description><author>The Hill</author><pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 21:11:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihgFBVV95cUxPMFBfVGFub3lxM1FMX3lqVWFBX2pfbXVtTXJzS1RPZ0s5czI3NjlnYXM1ejJfTmllRlEyVDA0MW55SVl4OF8yVUZDZGdNc0dlVHdiYlkyWENyQ3hNQkJ4bTR2VEVscnFXYlhDYlFSZ244Y1Fsck1Cb2RDa21sNy1taG9PQk80d9IBiwFBVV95cUxQdV9iSnNOa3JZX1E0NWhSMTNfZGdNRGdTZ2pkZGxIcW51RWlwS0NsWGJNNUJwQUdtUDEzakdRNTNQcEE1TGNudmxiOURlc3JQWFN0UHdYRlB0TFBkU3FkaWdKbTVmRzJfUGxqSkRCWEpFck9PUnZ5ejRTVW82WnNlN090b19BQmw2bGhv</guid></item><item><title>Measles case confirmed in unvaccinated child in Montgomery County - 69News WFMZ-TV</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMilAJBVV95cUxQTHVPOWlMcDNiVFBzTUtGaFNISU5QTGgzYl80TnNORFAydmUzWUI3WklNd1I0UHN6aVFYaFhVUG1LNEQ5b0xUMHItUU0xdVJwcUUwSUVRUDFWemM0N0lCYWpPb19VRjNjSDZ5OEZpTGp5d252THgxcWJTSUdEM2txbnAwVTJ2S0dFclRfbERha25YRVdsaWtNTUplellmbERPM0VMSjNkaDdkRUVhYmZNVVQyc0twU1Z0WkZJYXpRMEIwdGxYX3ZsdHVMSU04d01tQ0I1dTR2bldZN0hIOFN0ZmNxYjJlb3ZnZmNlNC1oNVZvTFFwWkJtYXJwRXZqMUdqSEdJcjFUNDg0ZEVzTjczVE9HbzM?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="article-body" itemprop="articleBody" class="asset-content  subscriber-premium" false&gt;
                                &lt;meta itemprop="isAccessibleForFree" content="true"&gt;
                                
                                
                                &lt;p&gt;NORRISTOWN, Pa. - The Montgomery County Department of Health and Human Services (HHS) Office of Public Health (OPH) have confirmed a case of measles in an unvaccinated Montgomery County child. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;OPH disease investigators are completing contact tracing in coordination with the health care systems listed below and the child's guardians, according to the press release.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Officials say that identified individuals are in the process of being contacted and notified of potential exposure to measles and assessed for vaccination status and risk for infection. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The following locations were visited by the child with a confirmed case of measles during their infectious period. People who were at any of these locations during the identified time periods may have been exposed:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;February 25-26, 2025&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;China Airlines Airport Shuttle Bus&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Departing JFK Airport Terminal 4, arriving at North Philadelphia, Pho Ha Saigon, 757 Adams Avenue, Philadelphia, PA 19120&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;From February 25 at 9:30 p.m. to February 26 at 3:15 a.m.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;February 26, 2025&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="tncms-region-article_instory_middle" class="tncms-region hidden-print"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;True North Pediatrics Associates of Plymouth&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;3031 Walton Rd., #C101, Plymouth Meeting, PA 19462&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;11:45. a.m. - 2:15 p.m.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;February 26, 2025&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;CHOP King of Prussia Campus Emergency Department&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;550 S. Goddard Boulevard, King of Prussia, PA 19406&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;12:52 p.m. - 3:02 p.m.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Officials say that additional details regarding possible exposure during and after air travel will be provided as soon as they are available.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Measles virus can remain in the air and on surfaces for up to two hours after an infected person leaves the area. If someone breathes in the contaminated air or touches an infected surface and then touches their eyes, nose, or mouth, they can become infected. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="tncms-region-article_instory_bottom" class="tncms-region hidden-print"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
                                
                                
                            &lt;/div&gt;

                            

                            
    


                            
    


                            
                                &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>69News WFMZ-TV</author><pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 21:03:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilAJBVV95cUxQTHVPOWlMcDNiVFBzTUtGaFNISU5QTGgzYl80TnNORFAydmUzWUI3WklNd1I0UHN6aVFYaFhVUG1LNEQ5b0xUMHItUU0xdVJwcUUwSUVRUDFWemM0N0lCYWpPb19VRjNjSDZ5OEZpTGp5d252THgxcWJTSUdEM2txbnAwVTJ2S0dFclRfbERha25YRVdsaWtNTUplellmbERPM0VMSjNkaDdkRUVhYmZNVVQyc0twU1Z0WkZJYXpRMEIwdGxYX3ZsdHVMSU04d01tQ0I1dTR2bldZN0hIOFN0ZmNxYjJlb3ZnZmNlNC1oNVZvTFFwWkJtYXJwRXZqMUdqSEdJcjFUNDg0ZEVzTjczVE9HbzM</guid></item><item><title>Federal Officials Underplaying Measles Vaccination, Experts Say - The New York Times</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMihwFBVV95cUxQRlhNa1BCdjRoYzB2VGZ6eWwySkdlQjV4NGxMeXA3WTBxeElFMW5lRXF5dzNfcmhpQ0xLX0hPX0RpUExPV25veU9lREQtUV9fVTBVSkg4aU1NaWM4cWZORnQ1c1pzRTVrQ0I1V21FYVZkbzBYYURaRlhPa2VlVzFJU1hkZ0VialE?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="css-s99gbd StoryBodyCompanionColumn" data-testid="companionColumn-0"&gt;&lt;div class="css-53u6y8"&gt;&lt;p class="css-at9mc1 evys1bk0"&gt;In a first test of the Trump administration’s ability to respond to an infectious disease emergency, its top health official has shied away from one of the government’s most important tools, experts said on Sunday: loudly and directly encouraging parents to get their children vaccinated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="css-at9mc1 evys1bk0"&gt;Robert F. Kennedy Jr., the health secretary, was widely criticized as &lt;a class="css-yywogo" href="https://www.nytimes.com/2025/02/26/us/texas-measles-outbreak-death.html" title=""&gt;minimizing the measles outbreak&lt;/a&gt; in West Texas at a cabinet meeting on Wednesday. In a social media post on &lt;a class="css-yywogo" href="https://x.com/SecKennedy/status/1895585297351799198" title="" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;Friday&lt;/a&gt;, he took a new tact, saying that the outbreak was a “top priority” for his department, Health and Human Services.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="css-at9mc1 evys1bk0"&gt;He noted various ways in which the department is aiding Texas, among them by funding the state’s immunization program and updating advice that doctors give children vitamin A. But on neither occasion did Mr. Kennedy himself advise Americans to make sure their children got the shots.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="css-at9mc1 evys1bk0"&gt;The Centers for Disease Control and Prevention, part of H.H.S., did not send its first substantive notice about the outbreak until Thursday, almost a month after the first cases in Texas were reported.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="css-s99gbd StoryBodyCompanionColumn" data-testid="companionColumn-1"&gt;&lt;div class="css-53u6y8"&gt;&lt;p class="css-at9mc1 evys1bk0"&gt;“They’ve been shouting with a whisper,” said Dr. Michael Osterholm, who is an epidemiologist at the University of Minnesota and a former health department official.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="css-at9mc1 evys1bk0"&gt;“I fear that their hands have been tied,” he added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="css-at9mc1 evys1bk0"&gt;C.D.C. officials did not immediately respond to a request for comment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="css-1336jj"&gt;&lt;div class="css-121kum4"&gt;&lt;p class="css-171quhb"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="css-asuuk5"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;div class="css-7axq9l" data-testid="optimistic-truncator-noscript"&gt;&lt;svg viewbox="0 0 24 24" aria-hidden="true" class="css-1b5b8u1"&gt;&lt;path fill="currentColor" fill-rule="evenodd" d="M2.5 12a9.5 9.5 0 1 1 19 0 9.5 9.5 0 0 1-19 0Zm8.5 1.75v-7.5h2v7.5h-2Zm0 2v2h2v-2h-2Z" clip-rule="evenodd"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;div data-testid="optimistic-truncator-noscript-message" class="css-6yo1no"&gt;&lt;p class="css-3kpklk"&gt;We are having trouble retrieving the article content.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="css-3kpklk"&gt;Please enable JavaScript in your browser settings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;div class="css-1dv1kvn" id="optimistic-truncator-a11y" tabindex="-1"&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thank you for your patience while we verify access. If you are in Reader mode please exit and &lt;a href="https://myaccount.nytimes.com/auth/login?response_type=cookie&amp;amp;client_id=vi&amp;amp;redirect_uri=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.nytimes.com%2F2025%2F03%2F02%2Fhealth%2Fmeasles-vaccination-texas-kennedy.html&amp;amp;asset=opttrunc"&gt;log into&lt;/a&gt; your Times account, or &lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/subscription?campaignId=89WYR&amp;amp;redirect_uri=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.nytimes.com%2F2025%2F03%2F02%2Fhealth%2Fmeasles-vaccination-texas-kennedy.html"&gt;subscribe&lt;/a&gt; for all of The Times.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="css-1g71tqy"&gt;&lt;svg viewbox="0 0 24 24" aria-hidden="true" class="css-63woee" data-testid="optimistic-truncator-spinner"&gt;&lt;g fill="currentColor"&gt;&lt;path d="M11.28 22.8a.72.72 0 1 0 1.44 0v-6.72a.72.72 0 1 0-1.44 0v6.72Z" opacity=".37"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="M17.766 21.16a.72.72 0 1 0 1.165-.846l-3.95-5.436a.72.72 0 1 0-1.165.846l3.95 5.437Z" opacity=".26"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="M1.506 14.653a.72.72 0 0 0 .445 1.37l6.391-2.078a.72.72 0 1 0-.445-1.369l-6.39 2.077Z" opacity=".61"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="M5.07 20.314a.72.72 0 0 0 1.164.847l3.95-5.437a.72.72 0 1 0-1.165-.846l-3.95 5.436Z" opacity=".48"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="M22.049 16.022a.72.72 0 0 0 .445-1.37l-6.391-2.076a.72.72 0 1 0-.445 1.37l6.39 2.076Z" opacity=".17"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="M22.494 9.347a.72.72 0 1 0-.445-1.37l-6.391 2.078a.72.72 0 1 0 .445 1.369l6.39-2.077Z" opacity=".09"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="M6.234 2.84a.72.72 0 0 0-1.165.846l3.95 5.436a.72.72 0 0 0 1.165-.846l-3.95-5.437Z" opacity=".87"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="M1.951 7.978a.72.72 0 1 0-.445 1.37l6.391 2.076a.72.72 0 1 0 .445-1.37l-6.39-2.076Z" opacity=".74"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="M18.93 3.686a.72.72 0 0 0-1.164-.847l-3.95 5.437a.72.72 0 0 0 1.165.846l3.95-5.436Z" opacity=".02"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="M12.72 1.2a.72.72 0 1 0-1.44 0v6.72a.72.72 0 0 0 1.44 0V1.2Z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/g&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;div data-testid="optimistic-truncator-message" class="css-6yo1no"&gt;&lt;p class="css-3kpklk"&gt;Thank you for your patience while we verify access.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="css-3kpklk"&gt;Already a subscriber? &lt;a data-testid="log-in-link" class="css-z5ryv4" href="https://myaccount.nytimes.com/auth/login?response_type=cookie&amp;amp;client_id=vi&amp;amp;redirect_uri=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.nytimes.com%2F2025%2F03%2F02%2Fhealth%2Fmeasles-vaccination-texas-kennedy.html&amp;amp;asset=opttrunc"&gt;Log in&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="css-3kpklk"&gt;Want all of The Times? &lt;a data-testid="subscribe-link" class="css-z5ryv4" href="https://www.nytimes.com/subscription?campaignId=89WYR&amp;amp;redirect_uri=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.nytimes.com%2F2025%2F03%2F02%2Fhealth%2Fmeasles-vaccination-texas-kennedy.html"&gt;Subscribe&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The New York Times</author><pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 20:48:38 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihwFBVV95cUxQRlhNa1BCdjRoYzB2VGZ6eWwySkdlQjV4NGxMeXA3WTBxeElFMW5lRXF5dzNfcmhpQ0xLX0hPX0RpUExPV25veU9lREQtUV9fVTBVSkg4aU1NaWM4cWZORnQ1c1pzRTVrQ0I1V21FYVZkbzBYYURaRlhPa2VlVzFJU1hkZ0VialE</guid></item><item><title>Tree pollen count surges, starting possibly hellish allergy season - Chron</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMimgFBVV95cUxOS3V2M1hmaWMxT0o3WUJsb3RpWWJqanRNcXZDYUZPbTJyMUVXRUNjM19RbGpBNVFRblh1c2tnMWJRYjl4UHdCU1lPVzBBMkhLM3BHTWptRWF2NjZWcHVNN185MEpYTWVTNGR1Yk9PTUFjcFZNX2lzM2tza05YaGlVRmZNV0w4QWRsZEx2emNGbFlRU1FjdW12eC13?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;The beginning of March means &lt;a href="https://www.chron.com/sports/astros/article/cam-smith-home-run-video-spring-training-20187567.php" data-link="native" target="_blank" rel="noopener" class=""&gt;Spring Training baseball&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.chron.com/culture/houston-rodeo/" data-link="native" target="_blank" rel="noopener" class=""&gt;Rodeo season and&lt;/a&gt;, unfortunately, seasonal allergy flare-ups. Peak tree pollen season is starting in Houston, ensuring plenty of folks will begin suffering from rhinitis once again.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to the Houston Health Department, &lt;a href="https://www.houstonhealth.org/services/pollen-mold/houston-pollen-mold-count-friday-february-282025" data-link="native" target="_blank" rel="noopener" class=""&gt;Friday's tree pollen count was 2,541&lt;/a&gt;, an extremely high number and the first time this year the count has exceeded 2,000. The HHD measures tree pollen with the &lt;a href="https://burkard.co.uk/product/7-day-recording-volumetric-spore-trap/" data-link="native" target="_blank" rel="noopener" class=""&gt;Burkard Spore Trap&lt;/a&gt;, an instrument that collects air samples from the roof of its laboratory at the Texas Medical Center.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Meanwhile, IQVIA, which manufactures a pollen count tool called Rotorod, maintains a &lt;a href="https://www.pollen.com/map/tx" data-link="native" target="_blank" rel="noopener" class=""&gt;nationalallergy map&lt;/a&gt;. It's not surprising that IQVIA's map shows a &lt;a href="https://www.pollen.com/forecast/current/pollen/77002" data-link="native" target="_blank" rel="noopener" class=""&gt;high pollen count for the Houston area&lt;/a&gt;, as well. In fact, much of Texas and the Gulf Coast is seeing high allergy risks, according to the IQVIA map. The Asthma and Allergy Foundation of America, w&lt;a href="https://aafa.org/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/aafa-2024-allergy-capitals-report.pdf" data-link="native" target="_blank" rel="noopener" class=""&gt;hich annually ranks the most challenging places to live nationwide&lt;/a&gt; with pollen allergies, has Houston 14th overall among U.S. cities. Only Dallas is ranked higher in Texas, coming in fourth place.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Spring in Houston means tree pollen falling off ash, birch, cottonwood, maple, mesquite, mulberry, oak, pecan and pine trees, &lt;a href="https://www.bcm.edu/news/an-early-start-to-spring-allergies" data-link="native" target="_blank" rel="noopener" class=""&gt;according to Baylor College of Medicine&lt;/a&gt;. Cedar pollen can also be a nuisance, which is what occurred Friday, according to HHD's data. Elm and oak trees increased their pollen shedding, as well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Moreover, people visiting the Houston Livestock Show &amp;amp; Rodeo could experience even greater allergy issues thanks to all the animals you may be in close contact with during a visit to NRG Center.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You're outdoors and you're exposed to a lot of novel allergens that you don't traditionally get on a normal Houston day," &lt;a href="https://www.chron.com/culture/houston-rodeo/article/treating-houston-rodeo-allergies-18693409.php" data-link="native" target="_blank" rel="noopener" class=""&gt;Kelsey-Seybold Clinic allergist-immunologist Albert Wu told Chron in 2024&lt;/a&gt;. "That can be anything from a variety of different animals, swine, cattle, horse, geese, or roosters."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;The AAFA &lt;a href="https://aafa.org/allergies/types-of-allergies/pollen-allergy/" data-link="native" target="_blank" rel="noopener" class=""&gt;says the best way&lt;/a&gt; to prevent an allergic reaction to pollen is to reducing exposure. That means limiting outdoor activities, keeping windows closed during peak pollen times, cover your hair, nose, eyes and mouth while outside; and clean bedding and blinds often.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Pollen counts are highest in the mornings, so it's generally a good idea to keep windows and doors closed as much as possible during this time,"&lt;a href="https://www.houstonmethodist.org/blog/articles/2022/apr/5-tips-for-avoiding-seasonal-allergy-symptoms/" data-link="native" target="_blank" rel="noopener" class=""&gt; Dr. Omar Ahmed of Houston Methodist said in 2022&lt;/a&gt;. "They're also higher on some days than others, and you'll want to be most stringent with your avoidance techniques on days and weeks when pollen counts are high."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Chron</author><pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 19:37:32 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimgFBVV95cUxOS3V2M1hmaWMxT0o3WUJsb3RpWWJqanRNcXZDYUZPbTJyMUVXRUNjM19RbGpBNVFRblh1c2tnMWJRYjl4UHdCU1lPVzBBMkhLM3BHTWptRWF2NjZWcHVNN185MEpYTWVTNGR1Yk9PTUFjcFZNX2lzM2tza05YaGlVRmZNV0w4QWRsZEx2emNGbFlRU1FjdW12eC13</guid></item><item><title>Cholera resurgence hampers progress in South and East Africa, study finds - The Washington Post</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMijwFBVV95cUxOdHRYX19Ua0NldVphZ2thaHhOWm9kVlc1UEFQdmZTY1FocTR1OU5uNHl4LXRBZVdvSEp2LXJKN0d5MUJ2S2twOUlRc0pPXzVhU1kwZUFKOTZxemhUSE1PWHVidTM1bzFlWFFuOFRJQkY1d182dng3aHRtYVpyQ29CZ1BJSjBlUWdZNk8wejBiTQ?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="meteredContent grid-center"&gt;&lt;div class="teaser-content"&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-testid="drop-cap-letter" data-apitype="text" data-contentid="ELWQGFNR6FD7FOYIC7AOOI4NRA" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Southern and eastern African countries are facing a resurgence of cholera, threatening worldwide progress toward eliminating the disease, a recent analysis warns.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-testid="drop-cap-letter" data-apitype="text" data-contentid="BKZTEQDIR5GKPBS42YZHPJNLTI" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;The &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1136/bmjgh-2024-016168" target="_blank"&gt;study&lt;/a&gt;, published in the journal BMJ Global Health in January, assessed cholera elimination attempts in the World Health Organization’s African region between 2018 and 2022. Since 2021, the region has faced “an acute upsurge” in cholera, the authors write.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-subscribe-cta" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-testid="drop-cap-letter" data-apitype="text" data-contentid="WH3JJSEDA5F43CQT6VXOUX4EKM" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Out of 27 African countries participating in the study, just three — Ethiopia, Kenya and Zambia — were on track to meet the region’s goal of eliminating cholera by 2030, the study found. While the region was on track with efforts such as mapping hot spots and setting up surveillance systems, the researchers found, it lags on milestones involving increased funding for cholera control and elimination.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-testid="drop-cap-letter" data-apitype="text" data-contentid="ZMGF7HNYP5H5ZFZEEIOKH2GWG4" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Insufficient water, sanitation and hygiene efforts and fragile health-care systems are to blame, the researchers write — and climate change, war and poverty are making things worse. Overall, the researchers found, the region had progressed by just 53 percent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-topic-follow-interstitial" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-testid="drop-cap-letter" data-apitype="text" data-contentid="FANVINFOBZBKLGMTENJKM2UBA4" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;One issue is that some countries treat cholera outbreaks as an emergency instead of investing in long-term infrastructure to combat the disease, the researchers write. The region needs “sustainable and predictable” funding to meet its goals, they note. The researchers called for increased funding to the region, including a possible U.N. cholera fund.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-testid="drop-cap-letter" data-apitype="text" data-contentid="M3CJ7MZYRJCVRFDQIIAYN5JHRQ" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Meanwhile, the &lt;a href="https://www.who.int/news-room/fact-sheets/detail/cholera" target="_blank"&gt;outbreak&lt;/a&gt; of the waterborne disease, which can cause fatal diarrhea, continues. Cholera is most prevalent in places that lack sanitation due to poverty, poor infrastructure, war and weak health systems. Though it’s easy to treat and there are vaccines available, outbreaks have &lt;a href="https://www.who.int/news-room/fact-sheets/detail/cholera" target="_blank"&gt;risen&lt;/a&gt; worldwide in recent years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-testid="drop-cap-letter" data-apitype="text" data-contentid="CKAICIK2MVE6XJCRGXHFZGPGSY" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;In a recent &lt;a href="https://www.who.int/publications/m/item/multi-country-cholera-outbreak--external-situation-report--22---24-january-2025" target="_blank"&gt;report&lt;/a&gt;, the WHO documented more than 800,000 cases of cholera and 5,805 deaths in 2024.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-testid="drop-cap-letter" data-apitype="text" data-contentid="TCHK2JSGNRFTBJKDLU3MHVNUR4" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;According to the organization’s &lt;a href="https://www.who.int/publications/m/item/multi-country-cholera-outbreak--external-situation-report--23--20-february-2025" target="_blank"&gt;most recent data release&lt;/a&gt;, 19 countries nationwide had cholera cases in January, led by South Sudan and the Democratic Republic of the Congo in the Africa region and Afghanistan, Yemen and Sudan in the Eastern Mediterranean.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-header" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;h5 class="wpds-c-vXjlY wpds-c-vXjlY-bALvEi-isCenteredLayout-false" data-qa="article-header" data-contentid="COKY34CHNBB4JFZ6PCIJ6Z3ZPY" data-apitype="header" level="6" id="COKY34CHNBB4JFZ6PCIJ6Z3ZPY"&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 19:02:49 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijwFBVV95cUxOdHRYX19Ua0NldVphZ2thaHhOWm9kVlc1UEFQdmZTY1FocTR1OU5uNHl4LXRBZVdvSEp2LXJKN0d5MUJ2S2twOUlRc0pPXzVhU1kwZUFKOTZxemhUSE1PWHVidTM1bzFlWFFuOFRJQkY1d182dng3aHRtYVpyQ29CZ1BJSjBlUWdZNk8wejBiTQ</guid></item><item><title>Lifesaving drug successfully lowers cholesterol levels and body weight - The Brighter Side of News</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMisAFBVV95cUxQR3MwNUtJRmdwOTdPa0Q3VWRSZ3RSX2ROYldlLUZnX1hjaFpUckMtN3lhRXRpZTd6YTBkcURNTmxKNDdZalJ0bU1VTmZHYWNmcy1nandwaTQxYzNLdXRfQkJqWmt3QTFkd1g5Q0FzNEJOVWpFRFRXNXE3YU1xRlY3blczd29uRERtaDI2N3ZIZGZDd1hERi15YXJ2N2h6a0pqeHk1dkNoMm5COTcyVXoxXw?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="MuiBox-root css-a9h2n1" data-id="page-content" data-og-area="article-blocks"&gt;&lt;div class="MuiTypography-root MuiTypography-paragraph paragraph css-50tlrn" data-og-block-area="article-blocks" data-og-block-nth="1" data-og-block-type="core/paragraph" data-rawhtml="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;More than 100 million Americans struggle with obesity and related metabolic disorders, a staggering number with widespread consequences. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="MuiTypography-root MuiTypography-paragraph paragraph css-50tlrn" data-og-block-area="article-blocks" data-og-block-nth="2" data-og-block-type="core/paragraph" data-rawhtml="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We were really excited about this work," says S. Thai Thayumanavan, a biomedical engineer and chemist at the &lt;a href="https://www.umass.edu/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;University of Massachusetts Amherst&lt;/a&gt;. This technique takes on greater significance when viewed against the broader health crisis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="MuiTypography-root MuiTypography-paragraph paragraph css-50tlrn" data-og-block-area="article-blocks" data-og-block-nth="3" data-og-block-type="core/paragraph" data-rawhtml="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;At the heart of this breakthrough is a tiny yet powerful tool—nanogels. These microscopic carriers hold a synthetic thyroid hormone drug known as a &lt;a href="https://www.thebrighterside.news/post/dna-based-nanotransporters-revolutionize-cancer-treatment/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;thyromimetic&lt;/a&gt;. While thyroid hormones are vital for liver metabolism, their systemic use often leads to severe side effects, making them an unreliable treatment option.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="MuiTypography-root MuiTypography-paragraph paragraph css-50tlrn" data-og-block-area="article-blocks" data-og-block-nth="4" data-og-block-type="core/paragraph" data-rawhtml="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rather than administering the hormone throughout the body, researchers designed nanogels to deliver it precisely where it's needed. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure class="image MuiBox-root css-0" data-og-block-area="article-blocks" data-og-block-nth="1" data-og-block-type="core/image"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="MuiTypography-root MuiTypography-caption css-1wisz3b" data-rawhtml="1"&gt;A graphic depicting how the drug targets the liver. (CREDIT: Creative Commons) &lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div class="MuiTypography-root MuiTypography-paragraph paragraph css-50tlrn" data-og-block-area="article-blocks" data-og-block-nth="5" data-og-block-type="core/paragraph" data-rawhtml="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We came up with a very simple approach, using our unique invention—nanogels that we can direct selectively to different targets," Thayumanavan explains. "They were custom-designed for hepatocyte delivery in the liver." This precision avoids the harmful effects associated with traditional treatments.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="MuiTypography-root MuiTypography-paragraph paragraph css-50tlrn" data-og-block-area="article-blocks" data-og-block-nth="6" data-og-block-type="core/paragraph" data-rawhtml="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;The results were striking. Mice given the treatment lost all the excess weight they had gained, with no harmful side effects. "The treated mice completely lost their gained weight, and we did not see any untoward side effects," Thayumanavan reports.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="MuiTypography-root MuiTypography-paragraph paragraph css-50tlrn" data-og-block-area="article-blocks" data-og-block-nth="7" data-og-block-type="core/paragraph" data-rawhtml="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;But the benefits went beyond weight loss. Despite remaining on a high-fat diet, the mice showed improved cholesterol levels and significantly reduced &lt;a href="https://www.thebrighterside.news/post/the-first-successful-in-patient-trial-of-liver-dialysis-has-been-completed/"&gt;liver inflammation&lt;/a&gt;. The findings suggest a deeper metabolic shift rather than just a temporary fix.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="MuiTypography-root MuiTypography-paragraph paragraph css-50tlrn" data-og-block-area="article-blocks" data-og-block-nth="8" data-og-block-type="core/paragraph" data-rawhtml="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We found that we are activating the reverse cholesterol transport pathway, which lowers cholesterol," Thayumanavan explains. This discovery points to a potential long-term solution for obesity-related conditions, offering hope for safer and more effective metabolic treatments.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="MuiTypography-root MuiTypography-paragraph paragraph css-50tlrn" data-og-block-area="article-blocks" data-og-block-nth="9" data-og-block-type="core/paragraph" data-rawhtml="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;He further theorizes, "We believe that activation of fat oxidation and an &lt;a href="https://www.thebrighterside.news/post/waist-not-want-not-new-discovery-on-belly-fat-and-diabetic-risk-connection/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;increase in metabolic rate&lt;/a&gt; are causing the loss in weight, but more work needs to be done to prove that point."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="MuiTypography-root MuiTypography-paragraph paragraph css-50tlrn" data-og-block-area="article-blocks" data-og-block-nth="10" data-og-block-type="core/paragraph" data-rawhtml="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Delving into the mechanics, once these nanogels permeate the hepatocytes, the liver cell environment disintegrates the bonds within the nanogel, releasing axitirome. This drug subsequently latches onto &lt;a href="https://www.thebrighterside.news/post/blood-proteins-could-be-the-key-to-a-long-and-healthy-life-study-finds/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;proteins&lt;/a&gt; pivotal for gene expression regulation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="MuiTypography-root MuiTypography-paragraph paragraph css-50tlrn" data-og-block-area="article-blocks" data-og-block-nth="11" data-og-block-type="core/paragraph" data-rawhtml="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;The apparent effectiveness of the ANG-delivered axitirome, which reversed weight gain without disrupting thyroid hormone levels, indicates a promising avenue for thyromimetics in addressing &lt;a href="https://www.thebrighterside.news/post/breakthrough-drug-fights-obesity-and-diabetes-by-transforming-bad-fats-into-good-fats/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;metabolic diseases like obesity&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure class="image MuiBox-root css-0" data-og-block-area="article-blocks" data-og-block-nth="2" data-og-block-type="core/image"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="MuiTypography-root MuiTypography-caption css-1wisz3b" data-rawhtml="1"&gt;A scanning electron micrograph of a section through a vein in the liver, showing red blood cells surrounded by hepatocytes (green). (CREDIT: PNAS Nexus) &lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div class="MuiTypography-root MuiTypography-paragraph paragraph css-50tlrn" data-og-block-area="article-blocks" data-og-block-nth="12" data-og-block-type="core/paragraph" data-rawhtml="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;An interesting observation emerged: mice on axitirome retained their appetite for high-calorie food. This is in stark contrast to human subjects using other &lt;a href="https://www.thebrighterside.news/post/groundbreaking-weight-loss-drug-could-be-stronger-than-ozempic-and-as-powerful-as-surgery/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;weight loss drugs&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="MuiTypography-root MuiTypography-paragraph paragraph css-50tlrn" data-og-block-area="article-blocks" data-og-block-nth="13" data-og-block-type="core/paragraph" data-rawhtml="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;"There is a significant amount of development work to be conducted between mice and humans," Thayumanavan cautions, "but we are hoping it will eventually become a drug."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="MuiTypography-root MuiTypography-paragraph paragraph css-50tlrn" data-og-block-area="article-blocks" data-og-block-nth="14" data-og-block-type="core/paragraph" data-rawhtml="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Driven by the promise of the nanogel technology his lab birthed, Thayumanavan has launched a startup, Cyta Therapeutics. Their primary mission? To spearhead cutting-edge delivery platforms ensuring drugs are dispatched to their intended bodily destinations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure class="image MuiBox-root css-0" data-og-block-area="article-blocks" data-og-block-nth="3" data-og-block-type="core/image"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="MuiTypography-root MuiTypography-caption css-1wisz3b" data-rawhtml="1"&gt;In vivo lipid-regulating effects of CGS-ANG in GAN diet-induced disease model. A) Schematic illustration of protocol for fully developed disease establishment in C57BL/6J mice and therapeutic study of CGS-ANG. (CREDIT: PNAS Nexus) &lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div class="MuiTypography-root MuiTypography-paragraph paragraph css-50tlrn" data-og-block-area="article-blocks" data-og-block-nth="15" data-og-block-type="core/paragraph" data-rawhtml="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;The exciting potential of this discovery cannot be understated. It not only offers a beacon of hope for those grappling with obesity and associated disorders but also paves the way for further advancements in drug delivery, potentially revolutionizing the treatment of metabolic diseases.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h3 class="MuiTypography-root MuiTypography-h3 heading css-i66mep" data-og-block-area="article-blocks" data-og-block-nth="1" data-og-block-type="core/heading" data-rawhtml="1" id="other_health_benefits_for_thyromimetics"&gt;Other Health Benefits for Thyromimetics&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;div class="MuiTypography-root MuiTypography-paragraph paragraph css-50tlrn" data-og-block-area="article-blocks" data-og-block-nth="16" data-og-block-type="core/paragraph" data-rawhtml="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thyromimetics are drugs that mimic the effects of thyroid hormones, primarily triiodothyronine (T3), by activating thyroid hormone receptors (THRs). They are being explored for various therapeutic applications due to their ability to regulate metabolism, cholesterol levels, and other physiological functions. Here are some potential benefits of taking thyromimetics:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h4 class="MuiTypography-root MuiTypography-h4 heading css-1i7gs84" data-og-block-area="article-blocks" data-og-block-nth="2" data-og-block-type="core/heading" data-rawhtml="1" id="cholesterol_reduction_and_cardiovascular_health"&gt;Cholesterol Reduction and Cardiovascular Health&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;ul class="MuiTypography-root MuiTypography-paragraph list css-26i8l3" data-og-block-area="article-blocks" data-og-block-nth="1" data-og-block-type="core/list" data-rawhtml="1"&gt;&lt;li class="MuiTypography-root MuiTypography-body1 css-1m35scc"&gt;&lt;span class="MuiTypography-root MuiTypography-body1 css-3e5pyk"&gt;Some thyromimetics, such as Eprotirome and Resmetirom, selectively target thyroid hormone receptor beta (THR-β) in the liver. This activation helps:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;ul class="MuiTypography-root MuiTypography-paragraph list css-26i8l3" data-og-block-nth="1" data-og-block-type="core/list" data-rawhtml="1"&gt;&lt;li class="MuiTypography-root MuiTypography-body1 css-3e5pyk"&gt;Lower LDL (bad) cholesterol and triglycerides.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="MuiTypography-root MuiTypography-body1 css-3e5pyk"&gt;Increase HDL (good) cholesterol.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="MuiTypography-root MuiTypography-body1 css-3e5pyk"&gt;Reduce the risk of atherosclerosis and cardiovascular disease without significant side effects on the heart or bones.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h4 class="MuiTypography-root MuiTypography-h4 heading css-1i7gs84" data-og-block-area="article-blocks" data-og-block-nth="3" data-og-block-type="core/heading" data-rawhtml="1" id="non_alcoholic_fatty_liver_disease_nafld_and_nash_treatment"&gt;Non-Alcoholic Fatty Liver Disease (NAFLD) and NASH Treatment&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;ul class="MuiTypography-root MuiTypography-paragraph list css-26i8l3" data-og-block-area="article-blocks" data-og-block-nth="2" data-og-block-type="core/list" data-rawhtml="1"&gt;&lt;li class="MuiTypography-root MuiTypography-body1 css-3e5pyk"&gt;Thyromimetics like Resmetirom are being studied for their role in treating non-alcoholic steatohepatitis (NASH).&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="MuiTypography-root MuiTypography-body1 css-3e5pyk"&gt;They help reduce hepatic fat accumulation, inflammation, and fibrosis by improving liver metabolism.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h4 class="MuiTypography-root MuiTypography-h4 heading css-1i7gs84" data-og-block-area="article-blocks" data-og-block-nth="4" data-og-block-type="core/heading" data-rawhtml="1" id="potential_for_hypothyroidism_treatment"&gt;Potential for Hypothyroidism Treatment&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;ul class="MuiTypography-root MuiTypography-paragraph list css-26i8l3" data-og-block-area="article-blocks" data-og-block-nth="3" data-og-block-type="core/list" data-rawhtml="1"&gt;&lt;li class="MuiTypography-root MuiTypography-body1 css-3e5pyk"&gt;Some thyromimetics are being investigated as alternatives or adjuncts to levothyroxine (T4) therapy in hypothyroid patients, particularly those who do not fully respond to T4 alone.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h4 class="MuiTypography-root MuiTypography-h4 heading css-1i7gs84" data-og-block-area="article-blocks" data-og-block-nth="5" data-og-block-type="core/heading" data-rawhtml="1" id="neuroprotective_effects"&gt;Neuroprotective Effects&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;ul class="MuiTypography-root MuiTypography-paragraph list css-26i8l3" data-og-block-area="article-blocks" data-og-block-nth="4" data-og-block-type="core/list" data-rawhtml="1"&gt;&lt;li class="MuiTypography-root MuiTypography-body1 css-3e5pyk"&gt;Research suggests thyromimetics may play a role in protecting neurons and supporting brain health.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="MuiTypography-root MuiTypography-body1 css-3e5pyk"&gt;They are being explored for potential benefits in neurodegenerative diseases, such as Alzheimer’s and Parkinson’s, by modulating brain metabolism.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h4 class="MuiTypography-root MuiTypography-h4 heading css-1i7gs84" data-og-block-area="article-blocks" data-og-block-nth="6" data-og-block-type="core/heading" data-rawhtml="1" id="muscle_and_bone_health"&gt;Muscle and Bone Health&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;ul class="MuiTypography-root MuiTypography-paragraph list css-26i8l3" data-og-block-area="article-blocks" data-og-block-nth="5" data-og-block-type="core/list" data-rawhtml="1"&gt;&lt;li class="MuiTypography-root MuiTypography-body1 css-3e5pyk"&gt;Thyroid hormones influence muscle strength and bone density.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="MuiTypography-root MuiTypography-body1 css-3e5pyk"&gt;Selective thyromimetics that avoid excessive THR-α activation (which can cause muscle breakdown and bone loss) may provide benefits for conditions like sarcopenia (age-related muscle loss).&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h3 class="MuiTypography-root MuiTypography-h3 heading css-i66mep" data-og-block-area="article-blocks" data-og-block-nth="7" data-og-block-type="core/heading" data-rawhtml="1" id="caution_and_side_effects"&gt;Caution and Side Effects&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;div class="MuiTypography-root MuiTypography-paragraph paragraph css-50tlrn" data-og-block-area="article-blocks" data-og-block-nth="17" data-og-block-type="core/paragraph" data-rawhtml="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;While thyromimetics have promising benefits, excessive activation of thyroid receptors can cause tachycardia, muscle wasting, osteoporosis, and hyperthyroid-like symptoms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="MuiTypography-root MuiTypography-paragraph paragraph css-50tlrn" data-og-block-area="article-blocks" data-og-block-nth="18" data-og-block-type="core/paragraph" data-rawhtml="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;The key is selectivity, with newer drugs targeting THR-β more than THR-α to avoid these side effects.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="MuiTypography-root MuiTypography-paragraph paragraph css-50tlrn" data-og-block-area="article-blocks" data-og-block-nth="19" data-og-block-type="core/paragraph" data-rawhtml="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thyromimetics are currently under investigation for their therapeutic potential, especially for cardiovascular and liver diseases. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;hr class="MuiDivider-root MuiDivider-fullWidth css-1pbb6nf" data-og-block-area="article-blocks" data-og-block-nth="1" data-og-block-type="core/separator" id=""&gt;&lt;hr class="MuiDivider-root MuiDivider-fullWidth css-1pbb6nf" data-og-block-area="article-blocks" data-og-block-nth="2" data-og-block-type="core/separator" id=""&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Brighter Side of News</author><pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 17:09:55 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMisAFBVV95cUxQR3MwNUtJRmdwOTdPa0Q3VWRSZ3RSX2ROYldlLUZnX1hjaFpUckMtN3lhRXRpZTd6YTBkcURNTmxKNDdZalJ0bU1VTmZHYWNmcy1nandwaTQxYzNLdXRfQkJqWmt3QTFkd1g5Q0FzNEJOVWpFRFRXNXE3YU1xRlY3blczd29uRERtaDI2N3ZIZGZDd1hERi15YXJ2N2h6a0pqeHk1dkNoMm5COTcyVXoxXw</guid></item><item><title>Eating This Fruit Every Day Can Reduce Depression Risk - AOL</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMickFVX3lxTFBMSjRLSDRkY1hZdnNNaVM3U0dCM3dKcUNBS041NktmTWtFYkk4S0hudDlMUkdPQlc3d0VpNmpEc3FiejZlOE5qbXFTS3ZYM0VHOWVHREhtc2Vyd1BPd21CRzM1d0s1VXRmZURxamRjWUp1dw?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="caas-body"&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure"&gt;&lt;p class="caption-wrapper caption-aligned-with-image"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption-collapse"&gt;&lt;span class="caption"&gt;This Fruit Could Do Wonders for Your Mental Health&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="photo-credit"&gt;Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;i&gt;"Hearst Magazines and Yahoo may earn commission or revenue on some items through these links."&lt;/i&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.frontiersin.org/journals/behavioral-neuroscience/articles/10.3389/fnbeh.2023.1185522/full" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Research;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Research&lt;/a&gt; has made it clear that your &lt;a href="https://www.prevention.com/health/mental-health/a39732341/gut-brain-connection/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:gut and brain;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;gut and brain&lt;/a&gt; like to talk to each other, and even influence the health of the other. Yes, what you eat (and the bacteria that creates in your gut) can have a big impact on how you think and feel. And new research even suggests that that connection could extend to your &lt;a href="https://www.prevention.com/health/mental-health/a43893160/barriers-to-mental-health-care/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:mental health;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;mental health&lt;/a&gt; as well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A study published in the journal &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://microbiomejournal.biomedcentral.com/articles/10.1186/s40168-024-01961-3" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:BMC Microbiome;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;BMC Microbiome&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/em&gt;found a link between eating citrus and depression risk, suggesting that you may be able to lower your risk of developing depression by doing something as simple as adding oranges into your daily diet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It's important to stress that there are a lot of factors that go into depression, and it wouldn’t be fair to suggest that just eating an orange will dramatically alter your mental health status. But, if you want to learn more about things you can do to lower your risk of &lt;a href="https://www.prevention.com/health/mental-health/a37271432/depression-myths/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:depression;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;depression&lt;/a&gt;, these findings are definitely worth paying attention to.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Here’s what the researchers found, plus what a dietitian and psychologist want you to keep in mind when interpreting the study's results.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Meet the experts&lt;/strong&gt;: Scott Keatley, RD, is co-owner of &lt;a href="https://keatleymnt.com/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Keatley Medical Nutrition Therapy;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Keatley Medical Nutrition Therapy&lt;/a&gt;; &lt;a href="https://nyulangone.org/doctors/1003153511/thea-gallagher" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Thea Gallagher;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Thea Gallagher&lt;/a&gt;, PsyD, is a clinical associate professor at NYU Langone Health and cohost of the &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://go.redirectingat.com?id=74968X1596630&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fpodcasts.apple.com%2Fus%2Fpodcast%2Fmind-in-view%2Fid1544156706&amp;amp;sref=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.prevention.com%2Fhealth%2Fa63975392%2Forange-citrus-depression-study%2F" data-i13n="elm:affiliate_link;elmt:premonetized" rel="sponsored" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Mind in View;elm:affiliate_link;elmt:premonetized;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp rapid-with-clickid etailiffa-link"&gt;Mind in View&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; podcast; &lt;a href="https://doctors.nyp.org/gail-m-saltz-md/1095-park-avenue" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Gail Saltz;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Gail Saltz&lt;/a&gt;, MD, associate professor of psychiatry at the NY Presbyterian Hospital Weill-Cornell School of Medicine&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What did the study find?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study analyzed data from nearly 32,500 women who participated in the Nurses' Health Study 2, a longitudinal study that tracked women to learn more about chronic disease risk factors. Researchers also looked at data from more than 300 men. They then used that information, along with fecal (i.e. poop) samples to learn more about the participants’ gut microbiomes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers found that when people had a daily serving of citrus, it lowered their risk of developing depression by about 20 percent. This was unique to citrus—meaning, data didn’t establish the same link with other fruits or vegetables.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When researchers drilled down even more, they found that the bacteria &lt;em&gt;Faecalibacterium prausnitzii&lt;/em&gt; (&lt;em&gt;F. prausnitzii)&lt;/em&gt;, which is found in the gut microbiome of people who eat citrus fruits, was more abundant in people who weren't depressed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“These data underscore the role of diet in the prevention of depression, and offer a plausible explanation for how the intestinal microbiome modulates the influence of citrus on mental health,” the researchers wrote in their conclusion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How does gut bacteria influence your mental health?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The bacteria in your gut, a.k.a. your gut microbiome, play a “crucial role” in your mental health by influencing the production of neurotransmitters (chemical messengers that help cells “talk” to each other), bodily inflammation, and the integrity of your gut barrier, says Scott Keatley, RD, co-owner of &lt;a href="https://keatleymnt.com/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Keatley Medical Nutrition Therapy;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Keatley Medical Nutrition Therapy&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Certain gut bacteria, like &lt;em&gt;F. prausnitzii&lt;/em&gt;, contribute to the gut-brain axis, a bi-directional communication system between the gut and the brain,” Keatley says. This particular bacteria is especially important because it can help to reduce inflammation, he explains.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Since chronic inflammation has been linked to depression, increasing &lt;em&gt;F. prausnitzii&lt;/em&gt; in the gut [by way of consuming citrus] may help regulate mood by reducing inflammatory markers,” Keatley says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Still, while the gut-brain relationship is firmly established, the way this pathway actually functions on a cellular level is still being explored. “We don’t fully understand the pathways between gut health and depression,” says &lt;a href="https://nyulangone.org/doctors/1003153511/thea-gallagher" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Thea Gallagher;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Thea Gallagher&lt;/a&gt;, PsyD, a clinical associate professor at NYU Langone Health and cohost of the &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://go.redirectingat.com?id=74968X1596630&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fpodcasts.apple.com%2Fus%2Fpodcast%2Fmind-in-view%2Fid1544156706&amp;amp;sref=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.prevention.com%2Fhealth%2Fa63975392%2Forange-citrus-depression-study%2F" data-i13n="elm:affiliate_link;elmt:premonetized" rel="sponsored" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Mind in View;elm:affiliate_link;elmt:premonetized;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp rapid-with-clickid etailiffa-link"&gt;Mind in View&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; podcast. “But we do know there’s something there.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How many oranges do you have to eat to see benefits?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This particular study found that eating one medium orange a day could help lower your risk of depression. But the researchers also lumped all citrus together. So, if you’re a grapefruit fan, you can feel good knowing that you’re also doing your mental health a solid by having a daily serving.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why is citrus so special?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;There are a few things about citrus that seem to give it extra oomph when it comes to improving mental health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The real game-changer in citrus is its high concentration of flavonoids, such as naringenin and formononetin,” Keatley says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These flavonoids help support the growth of the essential bacteria &lt;em&gt;F. prausnitzii, &lt;/em&gt;and also may regulate processes in the gut that help increase the availability of our "feel-good" neurotransmitters, serotonin and dopamine, in the body, he says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But keep in mind that the study's findings don't actually &lt;em&gt;prove&lt;/em&gt; that consuming citrus influences your mental health—they just establish a link.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study also only looks at one aspect of citrus' impact on the gut, and specifically, the bacterial link, points out &lt;a href="https://doctors.nyp.org/gail-m-saltz-md/1095-park-avenue" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Gail Saltz;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Gail Saltz&lt;/a&gt;, MD, associate professor of psychiatry at the NY Presbyterian Hospital Weill-Cornell School of Medicine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Citrus may impact the gut biome, but it also has other features, such as high vitamin C, which could figure into this story," she says.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Are there other foods that can lower depression risk?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Possibly. &lt;a href="https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jamanetworkopen/fullarticle/2809727" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Research;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Research&lt;/a&gt; has found a link between eating a lot of &lt;a href="https://www.womenshealthmag.com/food/a63592662/ultraprocessed-foods-list/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:ultra-processed foods;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;ultra-processed foods&lt;/a&gt; and a higher risk of depression, which suggests that eating whole, unprocessed foods may be better for your mental and physical health, Gallagher says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gallagher adds that focusing on fruits, vegetables, whole grains, and foods that don’t have a lot of ingredients is the “safe route” when it comes to eating for mental health. But she also suggests focusing on an &lt;a href="https://www.womenshealthmag.com/weight-loss/a30813088/80-20-diet-weight-lifting-weight-loss-success-story/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:80/20 style of eating;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;80/20 style of eating&lt;/a&gt;, where you try to eat healthy 80 percent of the time and are more lenient with what you eat for the other 20 percent of the time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Keatley also suggests consuming fermented foods like yogurt, &lt;a href="https://www.womenshealthmag.com/food/a29892608/health-benefits-of-kimchi/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:kimchi;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;kimchi&lt;/a&gt;, and kefir, which have probiotics that can help regulate neurotransmitter levels in the brain, along with nut and seeds, which provide omega-3 fatty acids that reduce inflammation and enhance gut-brain communication.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Legumes, fatty fish, and leafy green vegetables may also help, per Keatley. “Together, these foods create a diet that supports gut health, reduces systemic inflammation, and enhances neurotransmitter balance, all of which contribute to lowering the risk of depression,” he says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How does this effect compare to antidepressant medications?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Well, this study specifically looked at preventing depression. Antidepressants are usually used to &lt;em&gt;treat&lt;/em&gt; depression, Gallagher points out. So, it’s not clear, based on these findings, how eating oranges when you already have depression may impact your symptoms or treatment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But this is important: “Don’t go off your medications and start eating oranges,” Gallagher says. Saltz agrees. "I would not advise anyone based on this study to in any way consider oranges a treatment for clinical major depression," she says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Still, Gallagher calls the findings “exciting” for mental health. “This is something that you could easily implement in your diet and probably should regardless,” she says. “It’s accessible, and that’s always a good thing.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You Might Also Like&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>AOL</author><pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 16:58:30 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMickFVX3lxTFBMSjRLSDRkY1hZdnNNaVM3U0dCM3dKcUNBS041NktmTWtFYkk4S0hudDlMUkdPQlc3d0VpNmpEc3FiejZlOE5qbXFTS3ZYM0VHOWVHREhtc2Vyd1BPd21CRzM1d0s1VXRmZURxamRjWUp1dw</guid></item><item><title>Herpes Wakes Up: Scientists Discover Hidden Trigger for Cold Sore Flare-Ups - SciTechDaily</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiogFBVV95cUxPR2dqVjhiaVNkTklDdjY2UG8yTk1TMWRNT19WRmY5Y01WaHdCMl9aNE9sTHBXYVFCVHY4dC02TEpGX1g0WXZ4Mk9XNU9LSEFqVUhHcDBQMDF2S1MzZ1VwYUpoMTJ1X2VDZVg4NjBSRTFwaV85VVdoUXlIclZJWjdUOW00YjM2UXB1WlA3bEZXekdrbHlBcFNvV3YtSXhLTWNiaHc?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>SciTechDaily</author><pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 16:30:02 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiogFBVV95cUxPR2dqVjhiaVNkTklDdjY2UG8yTk1TMWRNT19WRmY5Y01WaHdCMl9aNE9sTHBXYVFCVHY4dC02TEpGX1g0WXZ4Mk9XNU9LSEFqVUhHcDBQMDF2S1MzZ1VwYUpoMTJ1X2VDZVg4NjBSRTFwaV85VVdoUXlIclZJWjdUOW00YjM2UXB1WlA3bEZXekdrbHlBcFNvV3YtSXhLTWNiaHc</guid></item><item><title>I’m a Dietitian and This Is My Favorite Healthy High-Protein Granola Bar - AOL</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMid0FVX3lxTE9Wb2tTZWJ6Mk5INmVzZ2lFbmRlMHlaOHJMOC1CMWFWQWRnelBmYm1CREVhRlhVM3lULTc4Zl9RSHpLU0pPaFo5ZUpHRlZPS19zRjlLV0IyOTVneUx3YlhMR0ZPVUlSWFAwTXRybnIzQTVodzlFM284?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="caas-body"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Reviewed by Dietitian Kelli McGrane, M.S., RD&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure"&gt;&lt;div class="caption-wrapper caption-aligned-with-image"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption-collapse"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Eating Well / Getty Images&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;As a dietitian, I’m all about convenience. After all, so many of us live such fast-paced lives that I always encourage my clients and readers to lean on nutritious foods that don’t require a ton of work to prepare. Granola bars are one great example. You can grab one to eat in the car while you drive to work or throw one in your daily carry bag to munch on if hunger strikes unexpectedly. However, granola bars can be a sneaky source of not-so-healthy things like added sugars and saturated fat. Eating too much saturated fat and &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/7869775/what-happens-to-your-body-when-you-cut-out-sugar/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:added sugar;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;added sugar&lt;/a&gt;—which most Americans do—can lead to health issues like heart disease and type 2 diabetes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That’s why I’m sharing my favorite healthy granola bar—Clif Nut Butter Bars. With these bars, you don’t have to sacrifice taste for nutrition. They’re stuffed with satisfying nut butter for a creamy treat full of heart-healthy fats, plant protein and fiber. Plus, they have far less added sugar and saturated fat than many other options out there.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/7829052/breakfast-bars/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:8 Better for You Breakfast Bars;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;8 Better for You Breakfast Bars&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Why I Love Clif Nut Butter Bars&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Great Taste&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Whoever said that healthy food can’t taste good was wrong. And let’s be real—if something doesn’t taste good, you’re probably not going to want to eat it anyway. One of the main reasons I love these Clif Nut Butter Bars is that they taste so good! They have a similar texture to classic Clif bars, but they’re smaller and they have a creamy nut butter filling. This makes them feel decadent and satisfying in a whole new way. You might even want one after dinner for dessert!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Good Source of Plant Protein&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Whether you’re reaching for a granola bar for a snack or a quick breakfast, protein is key. It helps you feel full so you’re held over until your next meal or snack. It also helps prevent blood sugar spikes so you can feel a steady rise in energy rather than a big burst and then a dramatic crash. I love that this Clif Nut Butter Bar has 7 grams of protein per serving. It’s all &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/plant-based-foods-with-more-protein-than-an-egg-8424134" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:plant-based protein;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;plant-based protein&lt;/a&gt; from peanuts and pea protein, making it vegetarian-friendly. Paired with a cup of milk (which has 8 grams of protein), it makes for an excellent high-protein post-workout snack to support muscle growth and recovery.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/7960613/are-peanuts-healthy/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Are Peanuts Healthy? Here's What a Dietitian Has to Say;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Are Peanuts Healthy? Here's What a Dietitian Has to Say&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Contain Heart-Healthy Fats&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;As I mentioned above, many granola bars are high in saturated fat—the kind that’s bad for heart health. Compared to other options, Clif Nut Butter Bars are pretty low in saturated fat, with 2.5 grams per bar. For reference, the Dietary Guidelines for Americans recommend eating no more than 22 grams of saturated fat per day if you follow a 2,000-calorie diet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What makes these bars especially great, though, is that they’re a good source of &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/surprising-nutrient-for-better-heart-health-8686588" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:heart-healthy unsaturated fats;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;heart-healthy unsaturated fats&lt;/a&gt;. That’s because they use real peanut butter and peanuts, which are rich in monounsaturated fat. This &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/7595261/whats-the-difference-between-saturated-fat-and-unsaturated-fat/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:type of fat;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;type of fat&lt;/a&gt; can help lower cholesterol levels to lower your risk of heart disease and stroke. Just like protein, it also helps slow digestion to prevent blood sugar spikes, making this a blood sugar–friendly snack.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Have a Few Grams of Fiber&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another key nutrient I look for in granola bars is fiber. Many Americans &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/7871141/what-happens-to-your-body-when-you-don-t-eat-enough-fiber/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:don’t eat nearly enough;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;don’t eat nearly enough&lt;/a&gt; of this important carb, and little adjustments can go a long way (like finding a higher-fiber granola bar!). Each Clif Nut Butter Bar has 3 grams of fiber—about 11% of the Daily Value.  There are other bars out there with even more fiber, but they tend to be higher in saturated fat and/or added sugars. I really like the overall nutritional balance of these bars. If you’re looking to add more fiber, pair the bar with a banana or a couple of Medjool dates.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Relatively Low in Added Sugars&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Compared to other granola bars, Clif Nut Butter Bars are pretty low in added sugars. Each bar has 6 grams. For reference, the Dietary Guidelines recommend eating no more than 50 grams of added sugars per day if you follow a 2,000-calorie diet. Other granola bars can have upward of 12 grams of added sugars. They may also use stevia or artificial sweeteners, which I personally don’t love the taste of. So I love that these bars have a delicious flavor without too many added sugars.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/breakfast-bar-recipes-you-ll-want-to-make-forever-8743366" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:16 Breakfast Bars You'll Want to Make Forever;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;16 Breakfast Bars You'll Want to Make Forever&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;The Bottom Line&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;When you need a granola bar to grab and go, I recommend Clif Nut Butter Bars. Compared to other granola bars, they have a good balance of fiber, healthy fat and protein, with minimal added sugars and saturated fat. Plus, they’re super tasty! I love having one of these bars as a part of a quick breakfast or an afternoon snack. They’re also great to pair with a glass of milk for a high-protein, post-workout snack.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Read the original article on &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/dietitians-favorite-healthy-high-protein-granola-bar-11686872" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:EATINGWELL;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;EATINGWELL&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>AOL</author><pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 16:24:52 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMid0FVX3lxTE9Wb2tTZWJ6Mk5INmVzZ2lFbmRlMHlaOHJMOC1CMWFWQWRnelBmYm1CREVhRlhVM3lULTc4Zl9RSHpLU0pPaFo5ZUpHRlZPS19zRjlLV0IyOTVneUx3YlhMR0ZPVUlSWFAwTXRybnIzQTVodzlFM284</guid></item><item><title>Bird flu detected in nearby Pa. county - WKBN.com</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMigwFBVV95cUxQQVUyRVlFN3FoM0pyNjZWUnVCVlZOa25mZ0lSd2FqbG9NWTdIMkJjOEVZMEdjYmZCYm9XZWxlMFh2SEtiTS1NUnRuM0tYZF9XdDhRTjk4dzlqMlRjUUJYUVpqblByTnAtVmNfdkhkVDFoWDBkUFZwTmx4eGdmZkpmTHNDUdIBiAFBVV95cUxNOVRra3RhTVFHRjFhOGpTZTNWeWNzWHpSYzVfVGxqMjQyRmlpUm1LWUlSeEswNzdKc1dBTWkxN09YTHNVc0JVcUR2V3dnZXZ5RGo2dVQ5RFl0c1RKakJUNjBQWnQwNEdBTkhtQl9mY1N2Rks5WjFmZW40Z0JfQVp4RWZLMnZZVUJm?oc=5</link><description>&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;
    
    
    &lt;noscript&gt;
      
    &lt;/noscript&gt;
  &lt;/body&gt;
</description><author>WKBN.com</author><pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 16:01:40 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigwFBVV95cUxQQVUyRVlFN3FoM0pyNjZWUnVCVlZOa25mZ0lSd2FqbG9NWTdIMkJjOEVZMEdjYmZCYm9XZWxlMFh2SEtiTS1NUnRuM0tYZF9XdDhRTjk4dzlqMlRjUUJYUVpqblByTnAtVmNfdkhkVDFoWDBkUFZwTmx4eGdmZkpmTHNDUdIBiAFBVV95cUxNOVRra3RhTVFHRjFhOGpTZTNWeWNzWHpSYzVfVGxqMjQyRmlpUm1LWUlSeEswNzdKc1dBTWkxN09YTHNVc0JVcUR2V3dnZXZ5RGo2dVQ5RFl0c1RKakJUNjBQWnQwNEdBTkhtQl9mY1N2Rks5WjFmZW40Z0JfQVp4RWZLMnZZVUJm</guid></item><item><title>Infectious Updates 3-2-2025 - Daily Kos</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMihAFBVV95cUxPYUdUbFYzeFcwY1RoNFM5VjdzNnRtNlZHajc1OWlvbU91Q2xhYS1vUGZKYk0ta3FtVkZIUXAwVzJvZ1VHcDVYY2pDNTFZUEt5VU9WWTJsRTIzSkVPY0YtenJRRHpGN0hTRGxoZTRHU2RTU3owQ3l5SEZVRUdGMzBZVXNmbWg?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="story__text"&gt;
          &lt;p&gt;Measles continues its march. And influencers who contributed to this debacle are trying to downplay its seriousness and dodge responsibility for their actions. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nationwide in the US there are 164 cases as of Wednesday, with Texas contributing 146 of those.  Expect another disturbing update soon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/measles-outbreak-texas-vaccines-kids-cases-what-know-rcna194216" target="_blank"&gt;NBC&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just in case you thought America was uniquely idiotic about infectious disease:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Australian vaccination rates &lt;/strong&gt;are down to 83%.  And last year they had 57,000 whooping cough cases. This continued in January of this year, with almost 5,000 cases in one month. They also have a few measles cases in Melbourne.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov.au/newsroom/news-and-articles/whooping-cough-still-lingers" target="_blank"&gt;Australian CDC&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The UK has a measles outbreak over 150 cases.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ontario has over 140 measles cases, which is more than the total they have had in the past 10 years &lt;em&gt;combined. &lt;/em&gt;They also have falling vaccination rates.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cbc.ca/news/canada/toronto/measles-cases-ontario-double-last-two-weeks-1.7470166" target="_blank"&gt;Doubled in the past two weeks&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The US has not used vitamin A at the WHO recommended protocol which does reduce morbidity and mortality in deficient children.  Americans hate to admit they might be deficient in anything at all, but a lot of us are.  In any case, measles actively depletes vitamin A stores, so a large loading dose can be useful in hospitalized children.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://journals.lww.com/infectdis/Fulltext/2020/07000/Vitamin_A_for_the_Management_of_Measles_in_the.2.aspx" target="_blank"&gt;LWW.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;New studies on Covid patients in France who were hospitalized show them at higher risk for death and readmission for as much as 2.5 years afterward.  This risk is highest for the first six months.&lt;a href="https://www.cidrap.umn.edu/covid-19/hospitalized-covid-patients-higher-risk-organ-related-death-readmission-25-years-data" target="_blank"&gt;CIDRAP&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;New Jersey reports its first H5N1 infections in cats.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cidrap.umn.edu/avian-influenza-bird-flu/new-jersey-reports-h5-avian-flu-cluster-cats" target="_blank"&gt;CIDRAP&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The WHO is recommending that next year’s flu vaccines use a different clade of the H3N2 subtype. This type changes more frequently than most of the other flus. Pandemic preparedness researches also pointed out a strain of H5N1 and one of H5N6 to focus on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cidrap.umn.edu/influenza-vaccines/who-advisers-swap-out-h3n2-strains-next-northern-hemisphere-flu-vaccines" target="_blank"&gt;CIDRAP&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The CDC reports that 13% of children who died of flu this year had brain damage.  Today in Morbidity and Mortality Weekly Report, researchers from the US Centers for Disease Control and Prevention (CDC) say that 13% of children who have died from seasonal flu this season had influenza-associated encephalopathy or encephalitis (IAE), a severe neurologic complication. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class="is-empty-p"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Included in these cases are four patients who had acute necrotizing encephalopathy (ANE), the most severe form of IAE, which can lead to varying degrees of brain dysfunction, inflammation, and other neurologic problems.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class="is-empty-p"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This data has not been consistently gathered so it is not known if this is worse than average.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;"Because no dedicated national surveillance for IAE or ANE exists, it is unknown if the numbers of cases this season vary from expected numbers," the authors wrote. "Health care providers should consider IAE in children with febrile illness and clinically compatible neurologic signs or symptoms, including but not limited to seizures, altered mental status, delirium, decreased level of consciousness, lethargy, hallucinations, or personality changes lasting &amp;gt;24 hours."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.cidrap.umn.edu/influenza-general/cdc-13-kids-who-died-flu-year-had-brain-damage" target="_blank"&gt;CIDRAP&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;..&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class="table-wrapper"&gt;
&lt;table align="center" class="basic-table"&gt;
	&lt;tbody&gt;
		&lt;tr&gt;
			&lt;td&gt;
			&lt;div&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.dailykos.com/groups/Infectious%20Information" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Infectious Information&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; is a DK group for collecting diaries on all things infectious, both basic educational material and breaking news updates.&lt;/p&gt;

			&lt;p&gt;Given the precarious state of public health agencies under the Orange Menace, it is my hope that the information &lt;em&gt;itself&lt;/em&gt; can be infectious, spread widely to all your contacts, in the hope of promoting self-defense from disease. Knowledge is the best inoculation against misinformation!&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;

			&lt;div&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.dailykos.com/users/strawbale" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Kosmail&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; for an invitation if you want to join and have info to contribute, or&lt;a href="https://www.dailykos.com/groups/Infectious%20Information" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;strong&gt; follow the group&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; to get these posts automatically in your activity stream.&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;
			&lt;/td&gt;
		&lt;/tr&gt;
	&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class="is-empty-p"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



        &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Daily Kos</author><pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 16:00:29 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihAFBVV95cUxPYUdUbFYzeFcwY1RoNFM5VjdzNnRtNlZHajc1OWlvbU91Q2xhYS1vUGZKYk0ta3FtVkZIUXAwVzJvZ1VHcDVYY2pDNTFZUEt5VU9WWTJsRTIzSkVPY0YtenJRRHpGN0hTRGxoZTRHU2RTU3owQ3l5SEZVRUdGMzBZVXNmbWg</guid></item><item><title>I’m a Dietitian and This Is My Favorite Healthy High-Protein Granola Bar - EatingWell</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMikgFBVV95cUxONFVwNHZld0s2UEp4aDJiTDBnM21fVXBPbm10X1pqZnhVZURKOFVGWGFuTnIyd0JseG90WjhJcE1BeEIxTWJTOWRjMndhUzB5QW1zSHFKZjFZTmxyWmtZSExaanRGQ2hBSnQ5RjlWRlVLMXJpQ2QxOTJuTmx2QTVob3pneDd1UlVrWGcxNGowdnB5Zw?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-page_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-page mntl-block structured-content" data-sc-sticky-offset="90" data-sc-ad-label-height="24" data-sc-ad-track-spacing="100" data-sc-min-track-height="250" data-sc-max-track-height="600" data-sc-breakpoint="50em" data-sc-load-immediate="4" data-sc-content-positions="[1, 1250, 1550, 1950, 2350, 2750, 3150, 3550, 3950]" data-bind-scroll-on-start="true"&gt;&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; As a dietitian, I’m all about convenience. After all, so many of us live such fast-paced lives that I always encourage my clients and readers to lean on nutritious foods that don’t require a ton of work to prepare. Granola bars are one great example. You can grab one to eat in the car while you drive to work or throw one in your daily carry bag to munch on if hunger strikes unexpectedly. However, granola bars can be a sneaky source of not-so-healthy things like added sugars and saturated fat. Eating too much saturated fat and &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/7869775/what-happens-to-your-body-when-you-cut-out-sugar/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;added sugar&lt;/a&gt;—which most Americans do—can lead to health issues like heart disease and type 2 diabetes.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="2"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="1"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_2-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_3-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; That’s why I’m sharing my favorite healthy granola bar—Clif Nut Butter Bars. With these bars, you don’t have to sacrifice taste for nutrition. They’re stuffed with satisfying nut butter for a creamy treat full of heart-healthy fats, plant protein and fiber. Plus, they have far less added sugar and saturated fat than many other options out there. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_4-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_6-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-why-i-love-clif-nut-butter-bars"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_7-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; Why I Love Clif Nut Butter Bars &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_8-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Great Taste &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_9-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Whoever said that healthy food can’t taste good was wrong. And let’s be real—if something doesn’t taste good, you’re probably not going to want to eat it anyway. One of the main reasons I love these Clif Nut Butter Bars is that they taste so good! They have a similar texture to classic Clif bars, but they’re smaller and they have a creamy nut butter filling. This makes them feel decadent and satisfying in a whole new way. You might even want one after dinner for dessert!
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_10-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_11-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Good Source of Plant Protein &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_12-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Whether you’re reaching for a granola bar for a snack or a quick breakfast, protein is key. It helps you feel full so you’re held over until your next meal or snack. It also helps prevent blood sugar spikes so you can feel a steady rise in energy rather than a big burst and then a dramatic crash. I love that this Clif Nut Butter Bar has 7 grams of protein per serving. It’s all &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/plant-based-foods-with-more-protein-than-an-egg-8424134" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;plant-based protein&lt;/a&gt; from peanuts and pea protein, making it vegetarian-friendly. Paired with a cup of milk (which has 8 grams of protein), it makes for an excellent high-protein post-workout snack to support muscle growth and recovery.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="3"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_13-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_15-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_16-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Contain Heart-Healthy Fats &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_17-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; As I mentioned above, many granola bars are high in saturated fat—the kind that’s bad for heart health. Compared to other options, Clif Nut Butter Bars are pretty low in saturated fat, with 2.5 grams per bar. For reference, the Dietary Guidelines for Americans recommend eating no more than 22 grams of saturated fat per day if you follow a 2,000-calorie diet.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_18-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_19-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; What makes these bars especially great, though, is that they’re a good source of &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/surprising-nutrient-for-better-heart-health-8686588" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;heart-healthy unsaturated fats&lt;/a&gt;. That’s because they use real peanut butter and peanuts, which are rich in monounsaturated fat. This &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/7595261/whats-the-difference-between-saturated-fat-and-unsaturated-fat/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;type of fat&lt;/a&gt; can help lower cholesterol levels to lower your risk of heart disease and stroke.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="4"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;Just like protein, it also helps slow digestion to prevent blood sugar spikes, making this a blood sugar–friendly snack.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_20-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_21-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Have a Few Grams of Fiber &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_22-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Another key nutrient I look for in granola bars is fiber. Many Americans &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/7871141/what-happens-to-your-body-when-you-don-t-eat-enough-fiber/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;don’t eat nearly enough&lt;/a&gt; of this important carb, and little adjustments can go a long way (like finding a higher-fiber granola bar!). Each Clif Nut Butter Bar has 3 grams of fiber—about 11% of the Daily Value.  There are other bars out there with even more fiber, but they tend to be higher in saturated fat and/or added sugars. I really like the overall nutritional balance of these bars. If you’re looking to add more fiber, pair the bar with a banana or a couple of Medjool dates.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_23-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_24-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Relatively Low in Added Sugars &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_25-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Compared to other granola bars, Clif Nut Butter Bars are pretty low in added sugars. Each bar has 6 grams. For reference, the Dietary Guidelines recommend eating no more than 50 grams of added sugars per day if you follow a 2,000-calorie diet.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="1"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;Other granola bars can have upward of 12 grams of added sugars. They may also use stevia or artificial sweeteners, which I personally don’t love the taste of. So I love that these bars have a delicious flavor without too many added sugars.  
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_26-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_28-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-the-bottom-line"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_29-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; The Bottom Line &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_30-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; When you need a granola bar to grab and go, I recommend Clif Nut Butter Bars. Compared to other granola bars, they have a good balance of fiber, healthy fat and protein, with minimal added sugars and saturated fat. Plus, they’re super tasty! I love having one of these bars as a part of a quick breakfast or an afternoon snack. They’re also great to pair with a glass of milk for a high-protein, post-workout snack.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>EatingWell</author><pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikgFBVV95cUxONFVwNHZld0s2UEp4aDJiTDBnM21fVXBPbm10X1pqZnhVZURKOFVGWGFuTnIyd0JseG90WjhJcE1BeEIxTWJTOWRjMndhUzB5QW1zSHFKZjFZTmxyWmtZSExaanRGQ2hBSnQ5RjlWRlVLMXJpQ2QxOTJuTmx2QTVob3pneDd1UlVrWGcxNGowdnB5Zw</guid></item></channel></rss>