<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>GNews Health</title><link>https://news.google.com/</link><description></description><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>骨关节炎患者报告膝袖缓解疼痛- BBC</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiWkFVX3lxTFBTbzVEZGowMjJTQWsxUTAxLUFNbVgxNXBocnFxQ3gwbGhUT2VkcXRaMzJuVHh3Tzh6eGFRcUx2b2lmUzYwT3dfVlpkZ2JwdDNUV3paaTBDZUhJQdIBX0FVX3lxTE4xMWxrNW85aUNScjlyV2tlYnJaQ3JmZlNrRm5GUEppbjM3NE8za0w1bjJYMnFpOU0wMXNwRTNzSFpOaExLYWgwallXQXI5aXRSNF9NVldWX0s0ckw3YkpV?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;An electronic knee sleeve is helping people with osteoarthritis to walk further and reduce pain, researchers have said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;The wearable device has been developed by a team from the University of Southampton with input from physiotherapists and surgeons.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;The sleeve uses transcutaneous electrical nerve stimulation (Tens) - with electrodes printed around the knee area, which are connected to an electronic control unit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Prof Kai Yang said participants in a trial of the device reported it could "reduce pain and stiffness".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Knee osteoarthritis - a degenerative joint disease that causes pain and stiffness - is thought to affect about five million people in the UK.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;The device is currently undergoing a 12-week clinical trial involving participants with knee osteoarthritis. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Patients use it for up to one hour at a time, five to seven days per week.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Among those taking part, Mike Coyne, 58, from Hedge End, is on the NHS waiting list for a knee replacement, having suffered with osteoarthritis for about eight years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;"With the sleeve on, I can walk a lot further and a lot quicker, without limping," he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;"It's really helped me when it comes to taking my dog Charlie for a walk – taking him out is now enjoyable exercise rather than a painful chore. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;"With the sleeve, I can get a bit of exercise – it's improved my overall health."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Prof Yang said: "The response from participants has been fantastic, with most reporting that it is helping to reduce pain and stiffness, enabling them to do more activities. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;"The device is also comfortable to wear and easy to use."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;The project is funded by the Medical Research Council. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;The research team is aiming to recruit 80 people diagnosed with knee osteoarthritis, aged between 45 and 75,  to join the trial of the knee sleeve.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BBC</author><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 06:03:23 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiWkFVX3lxTFBTbzVEZGowMjJTQWsxUTAxLUFNbVgxNXBocnFxQ3gwbGhUT2VkcXRaMzJuVHh3Tzh6eGFRcUx2b2lmUzYwT3dfVlpkZ2JwdDNUV3paaTBDZUhJQdIBX0FVX3lxTE4xMWxrNW85aUNScjlyV2tlYnJaQ3JmZlNrRm5GUEppbjM3NE8za0w1bjJYMnFpOU0wMXNwRTNzSFpOaExLYWgwallXQXI5aXRSNF9NVldWX0s0ckw3YkpV</guid></item><item><title>看起来比实际年龄年轻几十年的人几乎总是有这5种日常习惯- VegOut</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMixwFBVV95cUxQR3o5YUE4S2ZFZ0dZWG1Mb0ktU1hsZWxKanFHdm5sV3FhOEc2ZlpUeUpJcUFWeEFrVjhRckl5ak51VU5VUy1CV0VWMzMxRktFR1FrbXItbWpWRWlQTFRXNXZiTzZxU29Ic2preVRLR0tKOGFGeHhRTkxPLVViRkhoOVJWTGtzSXZiQlN4RFZFeWpEMDRGSExMU0NXNHl1Wl9Pdng3YWdULVVRU0FITzQyZnJRZHVGY1JZTHZaSElDQ2s5ckVkSnhn?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="page__content mt-4"&gt;
							&lt;p&gt;You know those people who make you do a double-take when you find out their real age? The ones who look 40 when they're pushing 60, or seem frozen at 50 while celebrating their 70th birthday?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We've all met them. And while we might assume they hit the genetic lottery, the truth is more encouraging than that.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While genetics do play a role in how we age, our daily habits have an enormous impact on whether we look and feel younger than our chronological age.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These aren't expensive treatments, invasive procedures, or extreme lifestyle overhauls we're talking about. Instead, they're consistent, often simple choices that compound over time. Small decisions made day after day that either accelerate or decelerate the aging process.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The best part? It's never too late to start incorporating these habits. Whether you're 25 or 65, your body responds to positive changes faster than you might think.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So what exactly are these age-defying habits?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;1. They prioritize quality sleep every single night&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ever notice how a bad night's sleep makes you look like you've aged five years overnight?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There's actual science behind this. As Matthew Walker, a professor of neuroscience and psychology at &lt;em&gt;UC Berkeley&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/9059444-sleep-is-the-single-most-effective-thing-we-can-do"&gt;puts it&lt;/a&gt;: "Sleep is the single most effective thing we can do to reset our brain and body health each day."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;People who look decades younger treat sleep like a non-negotiable appointment with themselves. They're not scrolling their phones until midnight or binge-watching shows until 2 AM.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Instead, they've figured out their optimal sleep schedule and stick to it religiously. Seven to nine hours isn't just a suggestion for them—it's a non-negotiable.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;2. They avoid smoking like their youth depends on it&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here's something that might sound obvious, but it's worth spelling out: smoking is basically a time machine that fast-forwards your appearance by decades.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As noted by the folks at &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.webmd.com/smoking-cessation/ss/slideshow-ways-smoking-affects-looks"&gt;WebMD&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; "Smoking changes the skin, teeth, and hair in ways that can add years to your looks". And we're not just talking about a subtle difference here—we're talking about dramatic, visible aging that's often irreversible.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I've seen before-and-after photos of identical twins where one smoked and the other didn't. The difference after just a few years is striking—deeper wrinkles, duller skin, yellowed teeth, and an overall aged appearance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The good news? Your body starts repairing itself almost immediately after you quit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;3. They move their bodies with purpose and intensity&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Want to know a secret that sounds too good to be true? Exercise might literally slow the clock on your cells.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://universe.byu.edu/2017/06/28/byu-research-suggests-exercise-reverses-cellular-aging-process1/"&gt;Research by professor Larry Tucker&lt;/a&gt; suggests that individuals who consistently engage in vigorous exercise can have cells that are as much as nine years younger than those of people who lead sedentary lives. Nine years! Let that sink in for a moment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This makes sense to me. The people I know who look decades younger have made physical activity a non-negotiable part of their routine.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This doesn't mean they're all marathon runners or gym rats. But they do something that gets their heart pumping and their body working hard on a regular basis. Maybe it's cycling, swimming, dancing, or hitting the weights—the key is consistency and intensity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;4. They protect their skin from sun damage religiously&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here's a question: what's the single biggest factor that makes someone look older than their years?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you guessed sun damage, you're spot on. As &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC6047276/"&gt;noted by experts&lt;/a&gt;, "exposure to UV radiation is the primary factor of extrinsic skin aging; it accounts for about 80% of facial aging."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I learned this lesson the hard way after years of California beach days without proper protection. The difference between the covered and uncovered parts of my body tells the whole story.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The people who look remarkably young treat sunscreen like brushing their teeth—it's just part of their daily routine. They understand that a few extra minutes of protection now saves them decades of visible aging later.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It's probably the simplest anti-aging strategy that exists, yet so many people skip it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;5. They manage stress before it manages them&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Last but not least, people who look decades younger have mastered the art of not letting life's inevitable stresses show up on their face.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Maybe they meditate, maybe they journal, maybe they have weekly therapy sessions, or maybe they've just learned to let things go faster than most of us. The method matters less than the consistency.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'm not talking about people who never experience stress—that's impossible. I'm talking about people who've learned to move through stress rather than marinate in it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They understand that holding onto tension, worry, and frustration doesn't just feel bad—it looks bad too. So they've prioritized finding ways to release it regularly rather than carrying it around like invisible baggage.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;The bottom line&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here's the thing about looking decades younger than your actual age: it's not about finding the fountain of youth or having perfect genes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It's about making choices today that your future self will thank you for tomorrow. Every night of quality sleep, every workout, every day you protect your skin—these small decisions compound into something remarkable over time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The people who look 40 at 60 didn't stumble into it accidentally. They built these habits deliberately, often starting years before they could see the results.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But here's what gives me hope: your body is constantly regenerating itself. The choices you make today start showing up faster than you might think.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So which of these habits resonates most with you? Which one feels like the easiest place to start?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Remember, you don't have to overhaul your entire life overnight. Pick one habit, make it stick, then add another. Your future self is counting on the decisions you make right now.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="vegou-quiz-after-article" id="vegou-3582961678"&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;What’s Your Plant-Powered Archetype?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ever wonder what your everyday habits say about your deeper purpose—and how they ripple out to impact the planet?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This 90-second quiz reveals the plant-powered role you’re here to play, and the tiny shift that makes it even more powerful.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;12 fun questions. Instant results. Surprisingly accurate.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;						&lt;/div&gt;
					&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>VegOut</author><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 05:42:57 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMixwFBVV95cUxQR3o5YUE4S2ZFZ0dZWG1Mb0ktU1hsZWxKanFHdm5sV3FhOEc2ZlpUeUpJcUFWeEFrVjhRckl5ak51VU5VUy1CV0VWMzMxRktFR1FrbXItbWpWRWlQTFRXNXZiTzZxU29Ic2preVRLR0tKOGFGeHhRTkxPLVViRkhoOVJWTGtzSXZiQlN4RFZFeWpEMDRGSExMU0NXNHl1Wl9Pdng3YWdULVVRU0FITzQyZnJRZHVGY1JZTHZaSElDQ2s5ckVkSnhn</guid></item><item><title>在家中使用空气净化器可能会降低心脏病发作的风险-每日邮报</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMioAFBVV95cUxOcjVPZVlsdXEyWXV1bVZ2YndJNFQ4QnRRaUlpT2Ytcm5uSDNTS1ZOMXBXZXkyQ3l5Q2JLS1dUcmM5aEpscEx5LVlJbkd6SjA2cko5QnJEU2lESk5hdGZUVXZqcVYxVTVEeGVRTzR4M2tHam0xWDBZanhnRjF4NGRra25oNndUcjNQWHZxWEhxeWREVnhtbndfTThsb1d0WXZ30gGmAUFVX3lxTE02dGVEM1J5VUpvQjFtMnhZSHYyUTZLZ1NrTjcyRHJrYTZMZ0JqT1NYN2IyRTVLT2hWM0VHYTVRcDRrZ1Nodi1nbVdVSmRWZUpiajBQZzBaTnpvQU5JQnprdzlhSlB6VmFndDg3U3duRVdRQS1lSkh5Q2pKS3Q3T2Rkc0JrLVkwVkxfM3VjVnBiTlB0emdfcDhNYVc1TDRGeC1kWS02ZFE?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="js-article-text" class="article-text wide  heading-tag-switch"&gt;
            &lt;h1 class="article-page-headline"&gt;Using an air purifier at home may slash the risk of heart attacks&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;p class="author-section byline-plain"&gt;By &lt;a href="/profile-2281/Meike-Leonard.html" class="author"&gt;MEIKE LEONARD, HEALTH REPORTER&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="byline-section"&gt;&lt;span class="article-timestamp article-timestamp-published"&gt; &lt;span class="article-timestamp-label"&gt;Published:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;time datetime="2025-08-10T01:11:26+0100"&gt; 20:11 EDT, 9 August 2025 &lt;/time&gt; &lt;/span&gt; | &lt;span class="article-timestamp article-timestamp-updated"&gt; &lt;span class="article-timestamp-label"&gt;Updated:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;time datetime="2025-08-10T01:15:48+0100"&gt; 20:15 EDT, 9 August 2025 &lt;/time&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;                  
    
                  &lt;noscript&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;     &lt;div itemprop="articleBody"&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Using an air purifier at home may reduce the risk of heart attacks, researchers suggest.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Studies have long linked air pollution to cardiovascular disease, with those most at risk tending to live near busy roads.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Particles emitted from car exhaust fumes and tyre rubber can drift into nearby homes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Once inhaled, they enter the bloodstream and have been associated with an increased risk of high blood pressure, inflammation, abnormal heart rhythms and the build-up of plaque in the arteries.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In the UK, the problem is said to be the number one environmental risk factor for heart and circulatory diseases – &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/article-5452385/Deadly-pollution-cocktail-raises-risk-cancer-heart-attacks.html"&gt;contributing to an estimated 14,000 deaths each year&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But scientists at the University of &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/connecticut/index.html" id="mol-4d6725e0-757e-11f0-b0a4-697cfff5c350"&gt;Connecticut&lt;/a&gt; say portable air purifiers could be the solution. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Researchers divided 154 adults living near highways in the US into two groups, giving one a high-efficiency particulate air (HEPA) purifier to use in their homes. The other group was given the same unit with the filter removed, leaving it unable to properly purify the air.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;After a month, the groups swapped purifiers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Using an air purifier at home may reduce the risk of heart attacks, researchers suggest&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Blood pressure measurements and questionnaires were carried out at the start and end of each period.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Participants who started the study with elevated blood pressure saw it reduce during the time using the HEPA filter, while those given the sham unit saw their blood pressure increase in the same period.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;‘This research adds to growing evidence that simple interventions, like in-home air filtration, may help improve heart health for people at risk,’ said Dr Douglas Brugge, chair of the Department of Public Health Sciences at the University of Connecticut and lead author of the study.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;According to the British Heart Foundation, 96 per cent of people in England are exposed to air pollution levels that exceed the limits set out by the World Health Organisation, while those living in deprived areas are at a significantly greater risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
            

            
            
            
            
            &lt;div class="column-content cleared"&gt;
                &lt;div class="shareArticles"&gt;
                    &lt;h3 class="social-links-title"&gt;Share or comment on this article: 
                        Using an air purifier at home may slash the risk of heart attacks&lt;/h3&gt;
                    
                
              &lt;/div&gt;
            &lt;/div&gt;
            
                        
            &lt;ad-slot position="smart_feed"&gt;&lt;/ad-slot&gt;
            &lt;p id="taboola-below-article-thumbnails" class="taboola" data-taboolaposition="thumbnail"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
                        
            
            &lt;ad-slot position="after_article"&gt;&lt;/ad-slot&gt;
&lt;p id="taboola-below-main-column" class="taboola" data-taboolaposition="afterArticle"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



            
            
             
           &lt;p id="most-watched-videos-lazy-container" data-lazy-content data-lazy-manifest-url="https://www.dailymail.co.uk/api/most-watched-videos/news/internal/?max_age_days=3&amp;amp;lazyManifest=true&amp;amp;lightbox=true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
            
            
            
            
            &lt;p class="column-content cleared"&gt;
              
            &lt;/p&gt;
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            




            
        &lt;/div&gt;
        
    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Daily Mail</author><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 04:18:13 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMioAFBVV95cUxOcjVPZVlsdXEyWXV1bVZ2YndJNFQ4QnRRaUlpT2Ytcm5uSDNTS1ZOMXBXZXkyQ3l5Q2JLS1dUcmM5aEpscEx5LVlJbkd6SjA2cko5QnJEU2lESk5hdGZUVXZqcVYxVTVEeGVRTzR4M2tHam0xWDBZanhnRjF4NGRra25oNndUcjNQWHZxWEhxeWREVnhtbndfTThsb1d0WXZ30gGmAUFVX3lxTE02dGVEM1J5VUpvQjFtMnhZSHYyUTZLZ1NrTjcyRHJrYTZMZ0JqT1NYN2IyRTVLT2hWM0VHYTVRcDRrZ1Nodi1nbVdVSmRWZUpiajBQZzBaTnpvQU5JQnprdzlhSlB6VmFndDg3U3duRVdRQS1lSkh5Q2pKS3Q3T2Rkc0JrLVkwVkxfM3VjVnBiTlB0emdfcDhNYVc1TDRGeC1kWS02ZFE</guid></item><item><title>医生认为年轻妈妈正在心脏病发作......她的肺部实际上充满了电子烟油-每日邮报</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMizwFBVV95cUxObzVUM25WNHFJZEgyTDNKZy1tRmRTNnZNRHVwU2hHR1ZNMWlianV1eXg5eGR0U1NVWWx2VjRNS2trMDZGT09STnpGUllxVHBtZG1wWnA4aG5Zb2RtcjlsVnEtNS0yamFCb2NuT1JMODVmbTRqTFQzVkxiZXJYSG0yY1hPTGJFcmpadDRoRWhLblhEQVd6OWRYR0pReV9Jb3pQU2J4X2NTVlh5M3VSMmZ1YlAtRV9iWF82TjNJNTJpV3RiNl9PaWFwWjR4Y0xQb1HSAdQBQVVfeXFMTTdxYWFWUUR2bXMxcTFWeDBncVNJWlNOVVdpWGpUc25XMzhqdFZHR2dxZkxHbzVEU0lJRjFYTEdJXzRHdTlhb25ZLVdVbEdidjlJVnB6ZjRWaUtMMU5qQ1ZJUnh2UTQxSWp5Njc2dzg1ZzNmSDZ6OGRjb1hhbmswdHFUYUtkRnFLQ2VISDZYdE94Mkw5eWw1Vnc1MmZ5ck9tZnE1UldvdmpEdXhubmo2WFJiSVNrWUZEY0ZPN1A5VnJTSHk3bElhdUx5b1JoTWYwbXBuSDM?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div itemprop="articleBody"&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;A young mother who feared she was having a heart attack actually had lungs that were filling with fluid from her vape.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Cloey Eyes, 25, from Ocala, &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/florida/index.html" id="mol-b1ad8b70-7231-11f0-a37d-b38de8e02458"&gt;Florida&lt;/a&gt;, had been vaping nonstop for two years. She became addicted to the devices when she used them to quit smoking cigarettes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The mother-of-five knew the vapes weren't the best for her lungs, but she kept puffing, believing they were a better option than her previous vice. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In July, however, she woke up in the middle of the night with 'sharp pains' in her chest, gasping for air as she struggled to breathe.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'I was terrified at the pain and I felt like I was going to die as I was scared I was going to not be able to breathe at all,' she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Eyes rushed to the emergency department, where scans quickly revealed she had&lt;span&gt;&lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/news/article-14615005/Rapid-rise-vaping-Britain-appears-stalled-users-anticipate-Government-crackdown.html"&gt; bronchiolitis obliterans, better known as 'popcorn lung'.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The condition is a rare type of lung disease, triggered by inflammation in bronchioles, the smallest airways in the lungs, which become scarred.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Doctors also found an oily substance building up in Eyes' lungs, which they said was the fluid she had breathed in from puffing on her vape. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Cloey Eyes (pictured), 25, from Florida, said she used vapes constantly in the lead-up to her hospitalization&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    
    
    &lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span&gt;'I woke up at 2:30am in the morning and my chest felt like it was having a heart attack,' Eyes said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'I had really bad pains in my chest and had to lean over. I couldn't catch my breath and I had to hit myself in the chest multiple times to be able to catch my breath.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'It was a sharp pain in my chest, but it also was a suffocating feeling.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;She said scans initially detected an 'oil pocket' in her left lung, before the same was also found in her right.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Doctors found that both lungs also had vape oil around them, though they weren't able to tell how much had collected in her body. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'It was scary to hear this,' she said. 'It's the oil from the vape and this is thickening up as you [breathe it in] and attaching itself to your lungs'.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In rare instances, vapes have been linked to lipoid pneumonia, a condition where oily substances inhaled while puffing on e-cigarettes build up in the lungs causing inflammation and damage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Patients normally suffer from a chronic cough, shortness of breath and coughing up blood or blood-tinged mucus. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Physicians say there is no good treatment for the condition. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In cases of bronchiolitis obliterans, steroids and an inhaler can reduce inflammation and help with breathing - in severe cases, a lung transplant may be required.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Those with the condition require life-long care to manage their symptoms and are advised to avoid air pollution, cigarette smoke, and people who are ill and could pass on infections.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Eyes is pictured above in the hospital while she received treatment for popcorn lung and fluid build up in the organs&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span&gt;'There isn't a good treatment for lipoid pneumonia, other than supportive care, while the lungs heal on their own,' Dr &lt;span&gt;Stephen Broderick, a lung cancer surgeon at Johns Hopkins University, &lt;a class="" rel="noreferrer noopener" target="_blank" href="https://www.hopkinsmedicine.org/health/wellness-and-prevention/what-does-vaping-do-to-your-lungs#:~:text=Vaping%2DRelated%20Lipoid%20Pneumonia,Symptoms%20of%20lipoid%20pneumonia%20include:"&gt;previously&lt;/a&gt; said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'The single most important thing you can do is identify what is causing it - in this case vaping - and eliminate it.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Eyes revealed she would use rechargeable disposable vapes, throwing them away when they 'ran out of juice'.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span&gt;She would puff on the device more than 300 times a day, and get through a 5,000-puff device every two weeks.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Although she would pick a different flavor every time, she said she would always opt for fruity varieties.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span&gt;She started smoking cigarettes in 2020 shortly before the Covid pandemic, but quit in August 2023 because she 'hated the smell'.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span&gt;That's when she started using vapes instead.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'I used the vape more than when I smoked as it was handy and right there,' she said of her addiction.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'When I was smoking, the pack [20 cigarettes] would last me four days, so I would smoke around five cigarettes a day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'I knew vaping wasn't any better than smoking, I just hated the smell of the smoke [from cigarettes] and needed to stop.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Eyes' condition was severe, and she had to stay overnight at the hospital before she was prescribed antibiotics, an inhaler and cough suppressant medications.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span&gt;The mom claimed doctors said it would take her lungs at least a year to heal completely.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Popcorn lung&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt; is linked to diacetyl, a chemical compound found in some vapes and used to make different flavors for the devices. This is breathed in and causes inflammation.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Warning signs of the condition include coughing, shortness of breath, wheezing, tiredness and night sweats.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Eyes (pictured) says she has now quit vapes, and urges others to do the same&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Several vapers have now come forward to reveal they were diagnosed with popcorn lung after using the devices, although it is not clear how many cases have been linked to the devices nationwide.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span&gt;In some cases, vapes have also been linked to heart attacks caused by the devices triggering inflammation in the blood and raising blood pressure.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Eyes has now quit vaping, and says she would 'never pick up a vape again'.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'I went cold turkey and quit vaping,' she said. 'I feel 10 times better now as I have stopped completely. My lungs feel better and I don't feel out of breath all the time...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'I would tell people to put the vape down, especially if you're a parent. You don't think it's going to happen to you. I didn't think it would [happen to me].&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Even if you don't go through the pain, the amount of chemicals going through your lungs is probably knocking about 10 years off your life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'I turned 25 last Saturday, and to think I could have lost my life from vaping is just not worth it.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;About one in 20 Americans vape, statistics suggest. The habit is much more common among those between 21 to 24 years old - 15.5 percent of the age group uses the devices.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Many become addicted and describe using them almost constantly during the day, which may raise the risks of serious complications.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Daily Mail</author><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 04:00:02 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMizwFBVV95cUxObzVUM25WNHFJZEgyTDNKZy1tRmRTNnZNRHVwU2hHR1ZNMWlianV1eXg5eGR0U1NVWWx2VjRNS2trMDZGT09STnpGUllxVHBtZG1wWnA4aG5Zb2RtcjlsVnEtNS0yamFCb2NuT1JMODVmbTRqTFQzVkxiZXJYSG0yY1hPTGJFcmpadDRoRWhLblhEQVd6OWRYR0pReV9Jb3pQU2J4X2NTVlh5M3VSMmZ1YlAtRV9iWF82TjNJNTJpV3RiNl9PaWFwWjR4Y0xQb1HSAdQBQVVfeXFMTTdxYWFWUUR2bXMxcTFWeDBncVNJWlNOVVdpWGpUc25XMzhqdFZHR2dxZkxHbzVEU0lJRjFYTEdJXzRHdTlhb25ZLVdVbEdidjlJVnB6ZjRWaUtMMU5qQ1ZJUnh2UTQxSWp5Njc2dzg1ZzNmSDZ6OGRjb1hhbmswdHFUYUtkRnFLQ2VISDZYdE94Mkw5eWw1Vnc1MmZ5ck9tZnE1UldvdmpEdXhubmo2WFJiSVNrWUZEY0ZPN1A5VnJTSHk3bElhdUx5b1JoTWYwbXBuSDM</guid></item><item><title>迈克尔道格拉斯癌症诊断： “基本本能”明星认为是什么导致了癌症及其原因-印度时报</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiugJBVV95cUxQZXRONVRZd1RSbkREaGNRT0tQd19pLTRjeXJvS0VXTG4wUS11UlNRc1ZhTE5LdjNiVmFNS2lURXVmUkYwLWdOWFgzS0hKMzJ5amxMLXRCeHdrbVlYTWtVQkp2ZmtjUFAzVVR1bU02dHY2RE9HSzctUFJUYzlfT0luTmV3RDNwREtKMjZzaHY2d2txZXdqWWMtQ0RfLWkyVHF3U1JsbEVwNGtQTllzN3Q5ZUEwcDNLeGpZSkp1SDZ1Y0phMmQzdU81RW9SYVJRYmlnV1UxazdpN1VHM2pZZ2pmdU1zYk9VUWt6VUYwMS1GZEwtV1Jrc0t0S09zWFdsaF9oUzdTUzVLZDEzNVpXNTNOOVRFYmJ0WFd0ZU51SEF5U3dSUDZEdWNacjB6aDZ1Nlo1SWg4TUFhX1NHUdIBvwJBVV95cUxOd1FOSXRSTXZYOHZnd09BQWdsdjN5OFRaZEF3N1FRZWk2SHpQMXRINHVFdkFtaGNtb1ZxbXBfdmN6RVdZZFoyQWEwTXlacGtXd2pTMDU2MUY3RGFEdVU3ejFVYU1Pc0hjblVtX2Nad3JDSkprdUVLVU1wUFhTYUxoT0UzVTJucmR0RkkwQXljNF9udVdHem9NTWktSVRVMHRHeF9ycGRfdk9RZlRBY0ZJc1lCMzJ5RVZZNFJHaVVyZjF6dlBSTVhjckJxdnZidFUzeGctWmRXQjg5bXN1dGVCdnlyR0NmM1hpSUEzcGlFdUtRTUtlUlRNNWR4SFFiVV9HOG1wQ29yMGpNVG81TTk1T2VocDRmQXRZV3NOQzRvUmV1ajdodjUwZHRaSHREVlhpRlRWT1JXMEJOeElJY1lJ?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="0"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even the ‘Basic Instinct’ star wasn’t immune, as it seems.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="2"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;In 2010, Hollywood icon &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/topic/michael-douglas" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;Michael Douglas&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; publicly revealed he was battling stage IV throat cancer. He initially thought stress, years of smoking, and heavy drinking might have played a role. However, as facts emerged, it became clear the cancer was linked to a different culprit altogether.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="8"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;What was it?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="10"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="11"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What did Michael Douglas think caused his cancer (and what it really was)&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="12"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;When diagnosed in August 2010, Douglas publicly suggested that long-term alcohol and tobacco use, along with stress, might have contributed to his cancer. He admitted that stress, especially relating to his son’s incarceration at the time, also weighed on his mind. Later, in a candid 2013 interview, the American actor and producer mentioned human papillomavirus (HPV) tied to oral sex as a possible cause. In a quite uncanny manner, parallels were drawn between him starring in films like ‘Basic Instinct’, ‘Fatal Attraction’, and so on.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="16"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;His initial symptoms, like persistent throat or ear pain, were misdiagnosed as infection, until a physician in Montreal peered deep into his throat and a tumor was spotted at the base of his tongue. A biopsy confirmed stage IV squamous cell carcinoma of the tongue, an advanced form of oral cancer, prompting immediate treatment with chemotherapy and radiation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="19"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="21"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="22"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;The real culprit: HPV, not habits&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="23"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;In 2013, Douglas made headlines when he suggested his cancer was caused by HPV, a sexually transmitted virus, possibly contracted through oral sex. He remarked: “this particular cancer is caused by HPV … which actually comes about from cunnilingus.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="25"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, his representatives clarified he was speaking broadly about HPV-linked cancers, not necessarily his own case. They added that he did not definitively state that oral sex caused his personal cancer, and emphasized that HPV is a known risk factor for oropharyngeal cancers, but not necessarily the direct cause in every case.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="28"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="29"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What is HPV and why does it matter in oral cancer&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="30"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;HPV, or Human Papillomavirus, is a common viral infection that can cause various health problems. It is primarily transmitted through sexual contact and affects the skin and mucous membranes, with over 200 identified types. While many HPV infections are harmless and resolve on their own, some types can lead to serious complications like genital warts and certain cancers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="32"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;HPV is categorized into low-risk and high-risk types. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="35"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Low-risk HPV:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; These types can cause genital warts but are not typically associated with cancer. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="38"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;High-risk HPV:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; These types can lead to various cancers, including cervical, vaginal, penile, anal, and throat cancers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="41"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;HPV is now recognized as a major risk factor for this type of cancer, particularly in the back of the throat, tonsils, and base of the tongue. While HPV infection is common, it usually clears up on its own. However, in some cases, it can persist and lead to the development of cancer years later.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="45"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;HPV-related throat cancers are becoming increasingly common. In fact, HPV now accounts for a majority of oropharyngeal cancer cases, especially among men. These cancers often strike adults who are non-smokers and non-heavy drinkers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="47"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="49"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="50"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What is squamous cell carcinoma?&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="51"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Squamous cell carcinoma (SCC) is a type of cancer that develops from squamous cells, which are flat, scale-like cells found in the skin and other tissues. It's the second most common type of skin cancer, after basal cell carcinoma, and can also occur in other areas like the lungs, head and neck, and cervix. SCC is often caused by prolonged exposure to ultraviolet (UV) radiation from the sun or tanning beds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="55"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Squamous cells are a type of epithelial cell, meaning they form the lining of surfaces throughout the body, including the skin, respiratory tract, and digestive tract. They are flat and scale-like, resembling fish scales under a microscope.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="59"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;While SCC is commonly found on sun-exposed areas of the skin like the face, scalp, and hands, it can also develop in other locations, including: &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="61"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Skin:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; This is the most common site. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="64"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Lungs:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; Lung cancer can sometimes be of the squamous cell type. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="67"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Head and neck:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; This includes cancers of the mouth, throat, and voice box. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="70"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Cervix:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; Cervical cancer can also be squamous cell carcinoma. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="74"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Other locations:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; SCC can also occur in the nasal cavity, sinuses, and tear ducts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="77"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="78"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Can HPV cause SCC?&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="79"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some types of Human Papillomavirus (HPV) can cause squamous cell carcinoma (SCC). Specifically, high-risk HPV types, like HPV-16 and HPV-18, are strongly linked to the development of certain squamous cell carcinomas, particularly in the oropharynx (the middle part of the throat). HPV infection is a significant risk factor for oropharyngeal squamous cell carcinoma (OPSCC).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="82"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="83"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Risk factors&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="84"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;SCC risk factors include excessive sun exposure, fair skin, a history of sunburns, older age, male gender, immunosuppression, and certain genetic syndromes apart from those stemming from HPV. Lifestyle factors like smoking and heavy alcohol consumption also increase the risk. Additionally, chronic wounds, exposure to radiation or arsenic, and a history of other skin cancers can be contributing factors. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="86"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Let’s take a detailed look:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="88"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Ultraviolet (UV) radiation exposure:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; Sun exposure is the most significant risk factor, particularly for cutaneous squamous cell carcinoma (cSCC). Cumulative sun damage over time, especially during youth, increases the risk. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="93"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Fair skin:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; Individuals with fair skin (Fitzpatrick skin types I-III) are more susceptible due to lower melanin levels, which offer less protection against UV radiation. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="96"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Age:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; The incidence of SCC rises with age, with most cases occurring in individuals over 50. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="99"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Gender:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; Males are generally at a higher risk of developing SCC compared to females. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="103"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Immunosuppression:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; Weakened immune systems, often due to medications or organ transplants, make individuals more vulnerable to SCC. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="106"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Genetic predisposition:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; Certain inherited conditions and genetic mutations (like TP53, CDKN2A, Ras, and NOTCH1) can increase susceptibility to SCC. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="109"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Smoking and alcohol consumption:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; Heavy smoking and excessive alcohol intake are strongly linked to SCC, particularly in the oral cavity and esophagus. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="113"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Chronic wounds and scarring:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; Persistent wounds, burns, or scars can create an environment where SCC can develop. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="116"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Arsenic exposure:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; Long-term exposure to arsenic, through drinking water or occupational settings, can increase the risk of SCC. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="119"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Actinic keratosis:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; These are precancerous skin lesions caused by sun damage and are a significant risk factor for cSCC. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="122"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Oral hygiene:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; Poor oral hygiene and dental problems can contribute to oral SCC. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="126"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Family history:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; A family history of skin cancer can increase an individual's risk of developing SCC.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="129"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="130"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Prevention and treatment&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="131"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;To prevent squamous cell carcinoma (SCC) of the skin, it's crucial to minimize sun exposure and avoid tanning beds. Regularly using sunscreen with at least SPF 30, seeking shade during peak sun hours, and wearing protective clothing like hats and long sleeves are essential steps. Annual skin exams, especially for those with risk factors like a history of sun exposure or family history of skin cancer, are also recommended.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="134"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Squamous cell skin cancer treatment options include surgery (excision, Mohs surgery), radiation therapy, and topical or systemic medications, depending on the cancer's size, location, and stage. For early-stage, small cancers, less invasive procedures like curettage and electrodesiccation, cryosurgery, or photodynamic therapy might be sufficient. For advanced cases, or when surgery is not an option, radiation therapy or medications like imiquimod or 5-fluorouracil may be used.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="136"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the case of Douglas, the actor underwent aggressive chemotherapy and radiation treatments and has been cancer-free since 2011, though he continues with regular check-ups.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="138"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="lOvcW vdo_embedd"&gt;&lt;div class="k7lcu"&gt;&lt;p class="efT4r"&gt;Sanjay Dutt on his battle with cancer: 'It all comes down to willpower and keeping the faith'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="140"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="141"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 03:50:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiugJBVV95cUxQZXRONVRZd1RSbkREaGNRT0tQd19pLTRjeXJvS0VXTG4wUS11UlNRc1ZhTE5LdjNiVmFNS2lURXVmUkYwLWdOWFgzS0hKMzJ5amxMLXRCeHdrbVlYTWtVQkp2ZmtjUFAzVVR1bU02dHY2RE9HSzctUFJUYzlfT0luTmV3RDNwREtKMjZzaHY2d2txZXdqWWMtQ0RfLWkyVHF3U1JsbEVwNGtQTllzN3Q5ZUEwcDNLeGpZSkp1SDZ1Y0phMmQzdU81RW9SYVJRYmlnV1UxazdpN1VHM2pZZ2pmdU1zYk9VUWt6VUYwMS1GZEwtV1Jrc0t0S09zWFdsaF9oUzdTUzVLZDEzNVpXNTNOOVRFYmJ0WFd0ZU51SEF5U3dSUDZEdWNacjB6aDZ1Nlo1SWg4TUFhX1NHUdIBvwJBVV95cUxOd1FOSXRSTXZYOHZnd09BQWdsdjN5OFRaZEF3N1FRZWk2SHpQMXRINHVFdkFtaGNtb1ZxbXBfdmN6RVdZZFoyQWEwTXlacGtXd2pTMDU2MUY3RGFEdVU3ejFVYU1Pc0hjblVtX2Nad3JDSkprdUVLVU1wUFhTYUxoT0UzVTJucmR0RkkwQXljNF9udVdHem9NTWktSVRVMHRHeF9ycGRfdk9RZlRBY0ZJc1lCMzJ5RVZZNFJHaVVyZjF6dlBSTVhjckJxdnZidFUzeGctWmRXQjg5bXN1dGVCdnlyR0NmM1hpSUEzcGlFdUtRTUtlUlRNNWR4SFFiVV9HOG1wQ29yMGpNVG81TTk1T2VocDRmQXRZV3NOQzRvUmV1ajdodjUwZHRaSHREVlhpRlRWT1JXMEJOeElJY1lJ</guid></item><item><title>微塑料正在渗透你的大脑。有什么影响？ - ScienceAlert</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMilgFBVV95cUxQUDI4R2pGb1pieDVNNVJtekZvTklnODR5UVZBLWhONk1rZmV6c1RocmNwcU51ZEpZdmdVNUZqR3EtTWFkaU5MWUFheXl5bkJneFUwWnNWLXhHc3I4YzZwcVBPQVVOcTVuQUktYmNGQzVQNkpIaDNSNXdvZ2RybVFUWGRhekFiUms5UzE1M1MxQ21yZTFnS0E?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Tiny shards of plastic called microplastics &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/microplastics-could-accumulate-in-our-brains-more-than-in-kidneys-and-livers"&gt;have been detected&lt;/a&gt; accumulating in human brains, but there is not yet enough evidence to say whether this is doing us harm, experts have said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These mostly invisible pieces of plastic have been found everywhere from the top of mountains to the bottom of oceans, in the air we breathe and the food we eat. They have also been discovered riddled throughout human bodies, inside lungs, hearts, placentas and even crossing the blood-brain barrier.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The increasing ubiquity of microplastics has become a key issue in efforts to hammer out the world's first plastic pollution treaty, with the latest round of UN talks being held in Geneva next week.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/microplastics-detected-infiltrating-human-brains-for-the-first-time"&gt;Microplastics Detected Infiltrating Human Brains For The First Time&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The effects that microplastics and even smaller nanoplastics have on human health is not yet fully understood, but researchers have been working to find out more in this relatively new field.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The most prominent study looking at microplastics in brains was published in the journal &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1038/s41591-024-03453-1"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Nature Medicine&lt;/em&gt; in February&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The scientists tested brain tissue from 28 people who died in 2016 and 24 who died last year in the US state of New Mexico, finding that the amount of microplastics in the samples increased over time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study made headlines around the world when the lead researcher, US toxicologist Matthew Campen, told the media that they detected the equivalent of a plastic spoon's worth of microplastics in the brains.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_170290" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-170290" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/08/spoon_microplastic_642.jpg" alt="microplastic in a metal spoon" class="wp-image-170290 size-full" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/08/spoon_microplastic_642.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/08/spoon_microplastic_642-592x415.jpg 592w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/08/spoon_microplastic_642-600x421.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-170290" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Plastic fragments in the environment break up into microscopic particles. (&lt;a href="https://www.canva.com/photos/MAGLbIZFnfc/"&gt;SivStockMedia/Canva&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Campen also told &lt;em&gt;Nature&lt;/em&gt; that he estimated the researchers could isolate around 10 grammes of plastic from a donated human brain – comparing that amount to an unused crayon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Speculation 'far beyond the evidence'&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;But other researchers have since urged caution about the small study.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"While this is an interesting finding, it should be interpreted cautiously pending independent verification," toxicologist Theodore Henry of Scotland's Heriot-Watt University told AFP.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Currently, the speculation about the potential effects of plastic particles on health go far beyond the evidence," he added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Oliver Jones, a chemistry professor at Australia's RMIT University, told AFP there was "not enough data to make firm conclusions on the occurrence of microplastics in New Mexico, let alone globally".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He also found it "rather unlikely" that brains could contain more microplastics than has been found in raw sewage – as the researchers had estimated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jones pointed out the people in the study were perfectly healthy before they died, and that the researchers acknowledged there was not enough data to show that the microplastics caused harm.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"If (and it is a big if in my view) there are microplastics in our brains, there is as yet no evidence of harm," Jones added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study also contained duplicated images, the neuroscience news website &lt;a href="https://www.thetransmitter.org/publishing/spoonful-of-plastics-in-your-brain-paper-has-duplicated-images/"&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Transmitter&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; has reported, though experts said this did not affect its main findings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;'Cannot wait for complete data'&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most of the research into the effects microplastics have on health has been observational, which means it cannot establish cause and effect.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One such study, published in the &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1056/NEJMoa2309822"&gt;&lt;em&gt;New England Journal of Medicine&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; last year, found that microplastics &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/plastic-found-inside-more-than-50-of-plaques-from-clogged-arteries"&gt;building up in blood vessels&lt;/a&gt; was linked to an increased risk of heart attack, stroke, and death in patients with a disease that clogs arteries.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_121072" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-121072" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/03/PlasticsInPlaquesUnderMicroscope.png" alt="Plastic Found Inside More Than 50% of Plaques From Clogged Arteries" class="wp-image-121072 size-full" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/03/PlasticsInPlaquesUnderMicroscope.png 913w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/03/PlasticsInPlaquesUnderMicroscope-642x297.png 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/03/PlasticsInPlaquesUnderMicroscope-898x415.png 898w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/03/PlasticsInPlaquesUnderMicroscope-768x355.png 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/03/PlasticsInPlaquesUnderMicroscope-600x277.png 600w" sizes="(max-width: 913px) 100vw, 913px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-121072" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Jagged plastic particles were seen inside macrophages and deposits of fatty tissue, removed from clogged arteries. (Marfella et al., &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1056/NEJMoa2309822"&gt;&lt;em&gt;NEJM&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, 2024)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;There have also been experiments carried out on mice, including a study in &lt;a href="https://www.science.org/doi/10.1126/sciadv.adr8243"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Science Advances&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; in January which &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/microplastics-can-block-blood-flow-in-the-brain-study-in-mice-shows"&gt;detected microplastics in their brains&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Chinese researchers said that microplastics can cause rare blood clots in the brains of mice by obstructing cells – while emphasising that the small mammals are very different to humans.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A review by the  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/what-does-the-world-health-organisation-do" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73079" data-postid="170285" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;World Health Organization&lt;/a&gt; in 2022 found that the "evidence is insufficient to determine risks to human health" from microplastics.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However many health experts have cited the precautionary principle, saying the potential threat microplastics could pose requires action.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A report on the health risks of microplastics by the Barcelona Institute for Global Health published this week ahead of the treaty talks said that "policy decisions cannot wait for complete data".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"By acting now to limit exposure, improve risk assessment methodologies, and prioritise vulnerable populations, we can address this pressing issue before it escalates into a broader public health crisis," it added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The amount of plastic the world produces has doubled since 2000 – and is expected to triple from current rates by 2060.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;© &lt;a href="terms-and-conditions"&gt;Agence France-Presse&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 02:02:52 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilgFBVV95cUxQUDI4R2pGb1pieDVNNVJtekZvTklnODR5UVZBLWhONk1rZmV6c1RocmNwcU51ZEpZdmdVNUZqR3EtTWFkaU5MWUFheXl5bkJneFUwWnNWLXhHc3I4YzZwcVBPQVVOcTVuQUktYmNGQzVQNkpIaDNSNXdvZ2RybVFUWGRhekFiUms5UzE1M1MxQ21yZTFnS0E</guid></item><item><title>怀孕期间出现高风险并发症的女性在50岁之前中风的几率可能更高-每日邮报</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiwwFBVV95cUxOSUdlSnlzR3h5eHBnZXpOUTJoS3ppdVFWcUw3M3U5VHpSODVtanNLbDBSUTBHa3NVaXJ5YmtQUmpYMmI5WmZQTGZ6NHFYOUd0SXNCbndzaThyNzgwYUptZW80SHBKeFlnMERCUnV1VEsxM2pvTGE2QjNjQU9wYXY2U2tEOGJES3FYVnI5OVVOODh6azNJeFdXMDN4WmI5T1hYYVNBOTRSYUQ2LW1VOVNIUFZ6bDZIYzJGeTZFc242cHluWTTSAcgBQVVfeXFMUHUydjNxQTBuUExiUE1DNlAyaHRzUlhrVjJXT05STFhfM0EzLTJKLXZFSV9VMU5VT3V5R1RQeHNIYXQ3RkdUMVA4TzdvZ3dDNWJvRno2NWFZQU9VWmVuM3B4VGFXWlI5VVcwdDlINVh1QVpJNlBGOG5LS1RPeUlkc3h1azRyaVFocndHQjZqaHJnRHZJNU1nUzkyc2g4Q0x0WTg2YjJ3UWcwMEUzY1l3U292VWZ6ZHNqNS1XUHdwajd1b0ktaWtYeS0?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="js-article-text" class="article-text wide  heading-tag-switch"&gt;
            &lt;h1 class="article-page-headline"&gt;Chances of a stroke before age 50 may be higher in women who have had high-risk complications in pregnancy&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;p class="author-section byline-plain"&gt;By MEIKE LEONARD FOR THE MAIL ON SUNDAY &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="byline-section"&gt;&lt;span class="article-timestamp article-timestamp-published"&gt; &lt;span class="article-timestamp-label"&gt;Published:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;time datetime="2025-08-10T00:55:08+0100"&gt; 19:55 EDT, 9 August 2025 &lt;/time&gt; &lt;/span&gt; | &lt;span class="article-timestamp article-timestamp-updated"&gt; &lt;span class="article-timestamp-label"&gt;Updated:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;time datetime="2025-08-10T00:55:55+0100"&gt; 19:55 EDT, 9 August 2025 &lt;/time&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;                  
    
                  &lt;noscript&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;     &lt;div itemprop="articleBody"&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Women who had complicated pregnancies could be more likely to have an early stroke, a study has found.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;High-risk complications during pregnancy is relatively uncommon in the UK – affecting just up to 10 per cent. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;However, figures show those who are impacted may be more likely to experience a stroke before the age of 50.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Researchers in the &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/the-netherlands/index.html" id="mol-05d70ee0-757c-11f0-90be-a54bf1196a86"&gt;Netherlands&lt;/a&gt; examined a sample of more than 1,000 women between the ages of 18 and 49, who had been pregnant at least once before. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;They looked at how often certain pregnancy complications had occurred in those who had strokes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;These included pre-eclampsia – high blood pressure during pregnancy – pre-term birth before 37 weeks, babies born small for their gestational age, gestational &lt;a target="_self" href="/health/diabetes/index.html" id="mol-329a68a0-757c-11f0-90be-a54bf1196a86"&gt;diabetes&lt;/a&gt;, miscarriage and stillbirth.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt; Women who had complicated pregnancies could be more likely to have an early stroke, a study has found. Pictured: Stroke Illustration&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Women who had a stroke were found to be more than twice as likely to have gone through at least one pregnancy complication, while those who had previously had a stillbirth were at the highest risk of stroke, estimated to be five times more likely.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Complications such as pre-eclampsia and pre-term birth were associated with strokes linked to large artery disease – often caused by a build-up of fatty deposits.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Doctors should ask about pregnancy history when assessing stroke risk,' said the study's lead author Dr Frank-Erik de Leeuw, a professor in cerebrovascular disease at Radboud University.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Our study suggests we may need to start thinking about cardiovascular prevention earlier in life – not just after menopause.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Future studies should investigate the effects of lifestyle modification aimed at reducing cardiovascular risk in women with pregnancy complications.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Previous research has shown that pregnancy itself can increase a woman's stroke risk by increasing blood volume, changing blood clotting factors and altering the elasticity of her blood vessels – with the highest risk occurring in the six weeks after delivery.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
            

            
            
            
            
            &lt;div class="column-content cleared"&gt;
                &lt;div class="shareArticles"&gt;
                    &lt;h3 class="social-links-title"&gt;Share or comment on this article: 
                        Chances of a stroke before age 50 may be higher in women who have had high-risk complications in pregnancy&lt;/h3&gt;
                    
                
              &lt;/div&gt;
            &lt;/div&gt;
            
                        
            &lt;ad-slot position="smart_feed"&gt;&lt;/ad-slot&gt;
            &lt;p id="taboola-below-article-thumbnails" class="taboola" data-taboolaposition="thumbnail"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
                        
            
            &lt;ad-slot position="after_article"&gt;&lt;/ad-slot&gt;
&lt;p id="taboola-below-main-column" class="taboola" data-taboolaposition="afterArticle"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



            
            
             
           &lt;p id="most-watched-videos-lazy-container" data-lazy-content data-lazy-manifest-url="https://www.dailymail.co.uk/api/most-watched-videos/news/internal/?max_age_days=3&amp;amp;lazyManifest=true&amp;amp;lightbox=true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
            
            
            
            
            &lt;p class="column-content cleared"&gt;
              
            &lt;/p&gt;
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            




            
        &lt;/div&gt;
        
    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Daily Mail</author><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 23:55:08 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiwwFBVV95cUxOSUdlSnlzR3h5eHBnZXpOUTJoS3ppdVFWcUw3M3U5VHpSODVtanNLbDBSUTBHa3NVaXJ5YmtQUmpYMmI5WmZQTGZ6NHFYOUd0SXNCbndzaThyNzgwYUptZW80SHBKeFlnMERCUnV1VEsxM2pvTGE2QjNjQU9wYXY2U2tEOGJES3FYVnI5OVVOODh6azNJeFdXMDN4WmI5T1hYYVNBOTRSYUQ2LW1VOVNIUFZ6bDZIYzJGeTZFc242cHluWTTSAcgBQVVfeXFMUHUydjNxQTBuUExiUE1DNlAyaHRzUlhrVjJXT05STFhfM0EzLTJKLXZFSV9VMU5VT3V5R1RQeHNIYXQ3RkdUMVA4TzdvZ3dDNWJvRno2NWFZQU9VWmVuM3B4VGFXWlI5VVcwdDlINVh1QVpJNlBGOG5LS1RPeUlkc3h1azRyaVFocndHQjZqaHJnRHZJNU1nUzkyc2g4Q0x0WTg2YjJ3UWcwMEUzY1l3U292VWZ6ZHNqNS1XUHdwajd1b0ktaWtYeS0</guid></item><item><title>神经学家揭示了为保护您的大脑和神经系统而应避免的三大食物- AOL.com</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMidEFVX3lxTFB0SjUzZkZmRGhUOUVaVmdpZEh2UVZYVEVoMUhMVFYxTC1nMzl1YjBNV1Y2QmF0RDZJMng4bzdoNzJ5aEo4RG12WkRucFdIU2FhNFNlZU9LMFNyQzlUS1VWUW5nQXRnQ0l6dEY3OXhFWk9QbGdm?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="caas-body"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Doctors recommend foods like &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/category/food-drink/food/healthy-foods" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:berries, nuts, fish;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;berries, nuts, fish&lt;/a&gt; packed with omega-3 fatty acids and even dark chocolate for neurological health. They also discourage foods high in sugar and saturated fat, which can increase the risk of stroke and dementia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But there are lesser-known foods that can also create a real headache, according to neurologists.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"While food-borne illness is often associated with gastrointestinal symptoms, some pathogens and toxins directly affect the nervous system, sometimes with severe or long-term consequences," said Dr. Mary Ann Picone, a neurologist at Holy Name Medical Center in New Jersey.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/health/eating-common-foods-could-reduce-alzheimers-risk-experts-say" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Eating These Common Foods Could Reduce Alzheimer's Risk, Experts Say;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Eating These Common Foods Could Reduce Alzheimer's Risk, Experts Say&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Because the illnesses are less common and symptoms can be slow to appear, even doctors can underestimate or miss the neurological component, Picone told Fox News Digital.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Experts say international travel and home food preparation can increase your risk of contracting them. Here are three common foods that neurologists caution could put you at risk of toxins and bugs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://foxnews.onelink.me/xLDS/mvaj7wvj" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Read On The Fox News App;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;Read On The Fox News App&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure"&gt;&lt;p class="caption-wrapper caption-aligned-with-image"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption-collapse"&gt;Improperly canned, preserved or fermented foods can provide the right conditions for botulinum toxin to form, according to the CDC.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;"If a can is bulging, cracked or severely dented, that's a red flag for botulinum contamination," Dr. Baibing Chen, a Michigan neurologist and epileptologist, said in recent videos posted on TikTok and Instagram, where he is known as &lt;a href="https://www.tiktok.com/@doctor.bing/video/7506993831796133151" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Dr. Bing.;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Dr. Bing.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Botulinum toxin is odorless and tasteless, and heating the contaminated food may not fully neutralize it, Chen warned. "When in doubt, throw it out," he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The potent neurotoxin can cause botulism, a &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/category/health/medical-research/rare-diseases" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:rare but serious illness;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;rare but serious illness&lt;/a&gt; that attacks the nerves, leading to muscle paralysis, breathing difficulty, and even death, according to the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention (CDC).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/lifestyle" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:For more Lifestyle articles, visit foxnews.com/lifestyle;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;For more Lifestyle articles, visit foxnews.com/lifestyle&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Home-canned, low-acid foods including green beans, asparagus, corn, meats, garlic and fermented fish are the most risky, Picone said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To prevent botulism, the CDC recommends refrigerating or freezing leftovers promptly after cooking, throwing away damaged or bulging cans, and following the USDA's guide to home-canning.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure"&gt;&lt;p class="caption-wrapper caption-aligned-with-image"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption-collapse"&gt;Large reef fish like barracudas can contain ciguatoxins that cause ciguatera fish poisoning in humans.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I like eating fish, but I try to avoid eating large tropical reef fish like barracuda, grouper and Amberjack because of a neurotoxin called ciguatoxin," Chen said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ciguatoxin is a neurotoxin produced by certain algae in coral reefs as a defense mechanism. It can travel up the food chain from herbivorous fish to carnivorous fish and eventually humans.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/health/death-confirmed-rare-deadly-brain-eating-amoeba-southern-lake" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Death Confirmed From Rare And Deadly 'Brain-eating Amoeba' In Southern Lake;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Death Confirmed From Rare And Deadly 'Brain-eating Amoeba' In Southern Lake&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/category/health/brain-health" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:neurological symptoms;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;neurological symptoms&lt;/a&gt; of ciguatoxin poisoning can include feelings of tingling and numbness, reverse temperature sensations where hot objects feel cold and cold objects feel hot, and vivid nightmares, Chen said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Approximately 50,000 cases of ciguatera poisoning are reported worldwide annually, according to the CDC, but the numbers may be higher because it is often misdiagnosed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure"&gt;&lt;p class="caption-wrapper caption-aligned-with-image"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption-collapse"&gt;One neurologist avoids eating large tropical fish because they can cause ciguatera poisoning.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;The toxin is heat-stable, he added, so cooking the fish won't destroy it. "This doesn't mean you can't eat fish," he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Just avoid or limit consumption of large predatory fish, avoid eating certain parts, like the liver or roe, and be aware of endemic areas."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ciguatera is common in the Pacific and Indian Oceans and the Caribbean Sea, according to the CDC.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chen said he does not eat &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/food-drink" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:under-cooked pork,;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;under-cooked pork,&lt;/a&gt; especially from unregulated sources, because of the risk of neurocysticercosis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/newsletters?cmpid=fnfirstnl" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Click Here To Sign Up For Our Lifestyle Newsletter;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;Click Here To Sign Up For Our Lifestyle Newsletter&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Neurocysticercosis occurs after a person swallows pork tapeworm eggs, according to the CDC. The larvae migrate to tissues like the brain and form cysts, which are diagnosed when found in the central nervous system.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"A little-known fact is that it's actually one of the leading causes of acquired epilepsy worldwide," Chen said of the infection. "And it's not just in developing countries, but can also be seen in developed countries in areas with poor sanitation."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure"&gt;&lt;p class="caption-wrapper caption-aligned-with-image"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption-collapse"&gt;Neurocysticercosis is a parasitic infection caused by larval cysts of the pork tapeworm.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;There are about 1,000 new &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/category/health/infectious-disease/foodborne-illness" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:hospitalizations for neurocysticercosis;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;hospitalizations for neurocysticercosis&lt;/a&gt; in the U.S. each year, according to the CDC, and cases are most frequently reported in New York, California, Texas, Oregon and Illinois.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It can be prevented by handwashing, cleaning and peeling fruits and vegetables, and only drinking &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/category/us/environment/water" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:bottled water or drinks or water boiled;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;bottled water or drinks or water boiled&lt;/a&gt; for at least one minute in countries where the supply may be unsafe.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Original article source:&lt;/em&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/food-drink/im-neurologist-i-never-eat-3-common-foods-can-harm-brain" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Neurologists reveal the top 3 foods to avoid to protect your brain and nervous system;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Neurologists reveal the top 3 foods to avoid to protect your brain and nervous system&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>AOL.com</author><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 23:47:41 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMidEFVX3lxTFB0SjUzZkZmRGhUOUVaVmdpZEh2UVZYVEVoMUhMVFYxTC1nMzl1YjBNV1Y2QmF0RDZJMng4bzdoNzJ5aEo4RG12WkRucFdIU2FhNFNlZU9LMFNyQzlUS1VWUW5nQXRnQ0l6dEY3OXhFWk9QbGdm</guid></item><item><title>哈佛大学将锂流失与阿尔茨海默病联系起来的研究为LI带来了希望-新闻日</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMif0FVX3lxTE13NEVpYm1zZDNoNE43azBrT05vREliWmdTdXpGNDJZNEFWOXZwT1RiVjN0QlN4bmJocDhRV3czdTJyTmlrTVVtdDFqa3VMUk5aNVdYdlE3WXBKRy1Za2tNajVoREpJWmpnMHFpMEs4Y0NSd1NlZkdfX0lPRTYtanc?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="continue-reading ContinueReading_continue-reading__uTArZ active ContinueReading_active__SOMMR"&gt;&lt;p&gt;A new Harvard Medical School study linking the loss of the metal lithium to Alzheimer’s disease is giving some hope to Long Island advocates, who said Friday it was a field where more breakthroughs were needed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The seven-year study could help doctors detect the disease earlier in people, provide new treatments and give scientists a better understanding of the human brain, according to researchers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study is "the most hopeful thing that we've had in a while," said Tori Cohen, executive director of the Long Island Alzheimer's and Dementia Center in Westbury. "This type of information ... I feel should be jumped on."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=""&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lauren Vlachos, executive director of the Alzheimer's Disease Resource Center in East Islip, called the finding "an exciting moment in Alzheimer's research."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The recent Harvard study showing lithium orotate reversing Alzheimer’s-like changes in mice is a major breakthrough, offering renewed hope for treatment and even prevention," she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Vlachos said it was crucial to continue funding research, but also to move such findings into clinical trials. "Discovery is only part of the equation," she said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One expert on Long Island cautioned the study was a preliminary finding and people should not go out and start taking lithium pills.&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr. Marc Gordon, chief of neurology for Northwell’s Zucker Hillside, North Shore University Hospital and Long Island Jewish Medical Center, said the study was "interesting."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I’m concerned that people are going to completely misinterpret it and think that they've got to start popping lithium carbonate and get toxic," he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study, led by Dr. Bruce A. Yankner, a professor of genetics and neurology at Harvard Medical School, found that researchers could reverse Alzheimer's in mice and restore brain functions using small amounts of the compound lithium orotate. The amount given was enough to mimic the metal’s natural level in the brain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=""&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The results of the study were reported in the scientific journal Nature on Wednesday.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The obvious impact is that because lithium orotate is dirt cheap, hopefully we will get rigorous, randomized trials testing this very, very quickly," Matt Kaeberlein, former director of the Healthy Aging and Longevity Research Institute at the University of Washington, who did not participate in the study, told The Washington Post. "And I would say that it will be an embarrassment to the Alzheimer’s clinical community if that doesn’t happen right away."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yankner, who is also the co-director of the Paul F. Glenn Center for Biology of Aging Research at Harvard, told The Post: "I do not recommend that people take lithium at this point, because it has not been validated as a treatment in humans. We always have to be cautious because things can change as you go from mice to humans."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yankner said other labs still needed to validate the findings of the study.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cohen said the fact the study was done with mice "doesn't mean that it can't be ... taken seriously" and possibly applied to humans.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=""&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alzheimer’s is a form of dementia that affects memory, thinking and behavior. More than 7 million people in the United States over the age of 65 have Alzheimer's, according to the Alzheimer's Association, a Chicago-based nonprofit which predicts that number will rise to almost 13 million by 2050.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Although there have been some recent breakthroughs in treating Alzheimer's, researchers have not discovered a medication to stop or reverse it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Patients with bipolar disorder are often prescribed lithium, and some previous research has suggested it could help with Alzheimer’s and also serve as an antiaging medication. One 2017 study in Denmark suggested that lithium found in drinking water could be associated with a lower incident of dementia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;With The Washington Post&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="byline Byline_byline__7W6Ao ux Byline_ux__K0907 bot Byline_bot__Vn8AK"&gt;&lt;p&gt;
	Bart Jones has covered religion, immigration and major breaking news at Newsday since 2000. A former foreign correspondent for The Associated Press in Venezuela, he is the author of “HUGO! The Hugo Chavez Story from Mud Hut to Perpetual Revolution.”
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Newsday</author><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 23:03:01 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMif0FVX3lxTE13NEVpYm1zZDNoNE43azBrT05vREliWmdTdXpGNDJZNEFWOXZwT1RiVjN0QlN4bmJocDhRV3czdTJyTmlrTVVtdDFqa3VMUk5aNVdYdlE3WXBKRy1Za2tNajVoREpJWmpnMHFpMEs4Y0NSd1NlZkdfX0lPRTYtanc</guid></item><item><title>新冠肺炎疫情重返美国和欧洲--《耶路撒冷邮报》</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiZ0FVX3lxTFBZTmw5OEdIbnVmNUlfSjhYaHFKRjhORm0wb1k0V2JXOEZfSUx1SUlWLWxTdHNFM2gtLUlhZVZkb1E4bmRXWi1LUG5oTW1LMUJVS2hxaVhBT0VXZlJkRWpFMnhUQnAydjg?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="menu-title" role="button" aria-expanded="false" tabindex="0"&gt;&lt;p&gt;JERUSALEM POST EN ESPANOL&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="arrow "&gt;&lt;svg xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" fill="none" viewbox="0 0 16 16"&gt;&lt;path stroke="#CB133E" stroke-linecap="round" stroke-linejoin="round" stroke-width="1.7" d="m5.335 13.333 5.333-5.334-5.333-5.333"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Jerusalem Post</author><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 22:57:41 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiZ0FVX3lxTFBZTmw5OEdIbnVmNUlfSjhYaHFKRjhORm0wb1k0V2JXOEZfSUx1SUlWLWxTdHNFM2gtLUlhZVZkb1E4bmRXWi1LUG5oTW1LMUJVS2hxaVhBT0VXZlJkRWpFMnhUQnAydjg</guid></item><item><title>抗抑郁药沃替西汀与阿尔茨海默氏症患者的认知和情绪改善有关- PsyPost</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiwwFBVV95cUxOejg4ZXZYWUtrRVNJaEJCbjY4WGpaMUQta2ZWb0RqQmhpenpsNC1LX2pTbUF1YjMzN1JBSGgxVE1zdFRYYl9UY0xmbWsyLXJCTVp0M3poMGZlaFZ2ZFBpWUFvUk1YaDFiWUhMbnY4cXJHNWtVVXFIWG5ZOXVTR2duZ3laNjhOWWt5bVExeEJpdjh0aEdPT0tQUkxNd2dRcEIzZ3FlY3I0dWhva29IOVFUMnFqQ0pWVkQxbFdhTEdONHVWRjQ?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="content-inner "&gt;&lt;p&gt;A new study published in the &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1177/13872877251340084" target="_blank"&gt;Journal of Alzheimer’s Disease&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; suggests that vortioxetine, an antidepressant with a unique multimodal mechanism, may offer greater benefits for both mood and cognitive function in people with Alzheimer’s disease who also experience depressive symptoms, compared to other commonly prescribed antidepressants. Over the course of a year, patients taking vortioxetine showed larger improvements in measures of memory, attention, and reasoning, as well as a greater reduction in depressive symptoms, than those taking escitalopram, paroxetine, or bupropion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alzheimer’s disease is a progressive neurodegenerative disorder that affects memory, thinking, and behavior. It is the most common cause of dementia in older adults, gradually impairing a person’s ability to carry out daily activities. Alongside cognitive decline, many people with Alzheimer’s also experience neuropsychiatric symptoms such as depression, anxiety, and apathy. Depression in Alzheimer’s is common and can intensify the difficulties posed by memory loss and disorientation, while also worsening quality of life for both patients and caregivers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The high prevalence of depression in Alzheimer’s has led to increased prescribing of antidepressants in this population. Yet research on how these drugs affect cognitive function has been limited and sometimes conflicting. Certain antidepressants may worsen cognition due to side effects on neurotransmitter systems, while others could potentially support brain function.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Vortioxetine is of particular interest because, beyond its action on serotonin receptors, it also influences other neurotransmitter systems involved in learning and memory. Previous studies in people with depression and in those with mild cognitive impairment have hinted at cognitive benefits, but few have directly compared vortioxetine to multiple other antidepressants in patients with Alzheimer’s.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To address this gap, researchers Eduardo Cumbo and Daniela Migliore conducted a 12-month randomized, open-label study at the Neurodegenerative Disorders Unit in Caltanissetta, Italy. The analysis focused on 108 outpatients with mild Alzheimer’s disease and depressive symptoms. Participants were randomly assigned to receive either vortioxetine (n=36) or one of three other antidepressants—escitalopram, paroxetine, or bupropion (n=72 in total)—while continuing standard Alzheimer’s treatments such as cholinesterase inhibitors or memantine. Patients were assessed at the start of the study, after six months, and after twelve months.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cognitive function was measured using several established tests. The Mini-Mental State Examination evaluated overall cognitive ability, including memory, orientation, and language. The Attentive Matrices test measured selective attention, while the Coloured Progressive Matrices assessed nonverbal reasoning and problem-solving. The Digit Span task tested verbal working memory. Depression severity was measured with the Hamilton Depression Scale and the Cornell Scale for Depression in Dementia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;By the end of the study, patients in all groups showed some improvement on cognitive tests, but gains were generally largest and most consistent in the vortioxetine group. On the Mini-Mental State Examination, vortioxetine-treated patients improved by nearly three points, a statistically significant change. They also showed significant gains in selective attention and nonverbal reasoning, while patients on other antidepressants tended to improve less, and in some cases, not significantly. Working memory scores improved slightly in the vortioxetine group but did not reach statistical significance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When comparing groups directly, vortioxetine outperformed the other antidepressants on most cognitive measures. The difference was particularly notable when compared to paroxetine, which has anticholinergic properties that can impair cognition in older adults. Escitalopram and bupropion showed moderate improvements on some attention measures, but not to the same extent as vortioxetine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study also found that depressive symptoms decreased in all groups over the 12-month period, but the reduction was more pronounced in patients taking vortioxetine. On both depression scales, the vortioxetine group’s scores dropped by about seven points from baseline—an improvement considered clinically meaningful. Between-group comparisons showed that vortioxetine’s effect on depressive symptoms was statistically superior to that of the other antidepressants.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Side effects were relatively uncommon and generally mild. Nausea and headache were the most frequently reported with vortioxetine, occurring in about 8% of patients. Two participants—one on paroxetine and one on bupropion—discontinued treatment due to side effects. No serious adverse events or deaths occurred during the study.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers note some limitations. The trial was conducted at a single site with a modest sample size, which may limit how well the findings apply to the wider Alzheimer’s population. It was also open-label, meaning patients and doctors knew which treatment was being given, which could introduce bias.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Importantly, only patients with mild Alzheimer’s were included, so the results may not extend to those with more advanced disease. The study also could not determine whether the observed cognitive improvements were due directly to vortioxetine’s pharmacological effects or indirectly through relief of depressive symptoms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Despite these caveats, the findings add to a growing body of evidence suggesting that vortioxetine may have cognitive benefits beyond its antidepressant effects. The authors suggest that larger, longer-term, and double-blind studies are needed to confirm these results and to clarify how vortioxetine’s effects on neurotransmitter systems might influence both mood and cognition in people with Alzheimer’s.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If future research confirms these findings, vortioxetine could be considered a particularly useful option for Alzheimer’s patients who experience depression—addressing not only mood symptoms but also potentially helping to preserve certain cognitive functions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study, “&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1177/13872877251340084" target="_blank"&gt;Differential effects of antidepressants on cognition in Alzheimer’s disease with depression: A sub-group analysis of an open-label, observational study&lt;/a&gt;,” was authored by Eduardo Cumbo and Daniela Migliore.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>PsyPost</author><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 20:03:45 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiwwFBVV95cUxOejg4ZXZYWUtrRVNJaEJCbjY4WGpaMUQta2ZWb0RqQmhpenpsNC1LX2pTbUF1YjMzN1JBSGgxVE1zdFRYYl9UY0xmbWsyLXJCTVp0M3poMGZlaFZ2ZFBpWUFvUk1YaDFiWUhMbnY4cXJHNWtVVXFIWG5ZOXVTR2duZ3laNjhOWWt5bVExeEJpdjh0aEdPT0tQUkxNd2dRcEIzZ3FlY3I0dWhva29IOVFUMnFqQ0pWVkQxbFdhTEdONHVWRjQ</guid></item><item><title>天然化合物组合恢复老化的脑细胞-神经科学新闻</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMickFVX3lxTE0yN1NBMDFkckF3VzhEXzQ2a3VWbjRtelBZN1NVRmcxejctRjlFTGVaRlA5YkNrTTdrQWNESF9JZXB4dFhuQVQxRXpHcklRZ0ZjMmhzd2lDYi1sYVVGZnl0MTU1bHNjR2Y1SjFLZDI1UjdNdw?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content body-color clearfix link-color-wrap"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary: &lt;/strong&gt;Scientists have identified a natural compound combination that reverses aging-related brain cell decline and removes harmful Alzheimer’s-linked proteins. The treatment, combining nicotinamide (vitamin B3) and the green tea antioxidant epigallocatechin gallate, restores guanosine triphosphate (GTP) levels—critical for neuronal energy and protein cleanup.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In aged neurons, the restored energy boosted protein clearance, reduced oxidative stress, and reactivated key cell trafficking pathways. The findings suggest a potential non-drug strategy for combating Alzheimer’s, though more work is needed to optimize delivery.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Facts&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class="wp-block-list"&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Energy Restoration:&lt;/strong&gt; Nicotinamide and green tea antioxidant revived GTP levels in aged neurons to youthful levels.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Protein Clearance Boost:&lt;/strong&gt; Treatment improved the brain’s ability to remove toxic amyloid beta aggregates.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Non-Pharmaceutical Potential:&lt;/strong&gt; Findings point to a supplement-based approach for Alzheimer’s prevention or therapy.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Source: &lt;/strong&gt;UC Irvine&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Researchers at the University of California, Irvine have identified a promising nonpharmaceutical treatment that rejuvenates aging brain cells and clears away the buildup of harmful proteins associated with Alzheimer’s disease.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a paper published recently in the journal &lt;em&gt;GeroScience&lt;/em&gt;, the UC Irvine team reports that a combination of naturally occurring compounds – nicotinamide (a form of vitamin B3) and epigallocatechin gallate (a green tea antioxidant) – can reinstate levels of guanosine triphosphate, an essential energy molecule in brain cells.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="wp-block-image size-full"&gt;&lt;picture fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" class="wp-image-112113"&gt; &lt;source type="image/webp" srcset="https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/08/suppliments-aging-brain-neuroscience.jpg.webp 1200w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/08/suppliments-aging-brain-neuroscience-300x200.jpg.webp 300w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/08/suppliments-aging-brain-neuroscience-770x514.jpg.webp 770w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/08/suppliments-aging-brain-neuroscience-1155x770.jpg.webp 1155w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/08/suppliments-aging-brain-neuroscience-370x247.jpg.webp 370w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/08/suppliments-aging-brain-neuroscience-293x196.jpg.webp 293w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/08/suppliments-aging-brain-neuroscience-150x100.jpg.webp 150w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px"&gt;&lt;/source&gt; &lt;img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" src="https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/08/suppliments-aging-brain-neuroscience.jpg" alt="This shows neurons." srcset="https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/08/suppliments-aging-brain-neuroscience.jpg 1200w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/08/suppliments-aging-brain-neuroscience-300x200.jpg 300w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/08/suppliments-aging-brain-neuroscience-770x514.jpg 770w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/08/suppliments-aging-brain-neuroscience-1155x770.jpg 1155w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/08/suppliments-aging-brain-neuroscience-370x247.jpg 370w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/08/suppliments-aging-brain-neuroscience-293x196.jpg 293w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/08/suppliments-aging-brain-neuroscience-150x100.jpg 150w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px"&gt; &lt;/picture&gt;&lt;figcaption class="wp-element-caption"&gt;“We found that restoring energy levels helps neurons regain this critical cleanup function.” Credit: Neuroscience News&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;In tests on neurons in a dish, the treatment reversed age-related cellular deficits and improved the brain cells’ ability to clear damaging amyloid protein aggregates, an Alzheimer’s hallmark.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“As people age, their brains show a decline in neuronal energy levels, which limits the ability to remove unwanted proteins and damaged components,” said lead author Gregory Brewer, adjunct professor of biomedical engineering at UC Irvine. “We found that restoring energy levels helps neurons regain this critical cleanup function.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers used a genetically encoded fluorescent sensor called GEVAL to track live guanosine triphosphate levels in neurons from aged Alzheimer’s model mice. They discovered that free GTP levels declined with age – particularly in mitochondria, the cells’ energy hubs – leading to impaired autophagy, the process by which cells eliminate damaged components.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But when aged neurons were treated for just 24 hours with nicotinamide and epigallocatechin gallate, GTP levels were restored to those typically seen in younger cells.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This revival triggered a cascade of benefits: improved energy metabolism; activation of key GTPases involved in cellular trafficking, Rab7 and Arl8b; and efficient clearance of amyloid beta aggregates. Oxidative stress, another contributor to neurodegeneration, was also reduced.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“This study highlights GTP as a previously underappreciated energy source driving vital brain functions,” Brewer said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“By supplementing the brain’s energy systems with compounds that are already available as dietary supplements, we may have a new path toward treating age-related cognitive decline and Alzheimer’s disease.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He cautioned, “More work is going to be required to find the best way to administer this treatment, since a recent clinical trial involving UC Irvine researchers showed that oral nicotinamide was not very effective because of inactivation in the bloodstream.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Brewer’s collaborators were Ricardo Santana, a UC Irvine associate specialist in biomedical engineering, and Joshua McWhirt, a UC Irvine junior specialist who’s now a Ph.D. candidate at the Medical University of South Carolina.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Funding: &lt;/strong&gt;Funding was provided by the National Institutes of Health and the UC Irvine Foundation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;About this supplements and brain aging research news&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="has-background"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Author: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#52302230373e3e1227313b7c373627" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Brian Bell&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Source: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://uci.edu" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;UC Irvine&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Contact: &lt;/strong&gt;Brian Bell – UC Irvine&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Image: &lt;/strong&gt;The image is credited to Neuroscience News&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="has-background"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Original Research: &lt;/strong&gt;Open access.&lt;br&gt;“&lt;a href="https://dx.doi.org/10.1007/s11357-025-01786-4" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Treatment of age-related decreases in GTP levels restores endocytosis and autophagy&lt;/a&gt;” by Gregory Brewer et al. &lt;em&gt;GeroScience&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr class="wp-block-separator has-text-color has-pale-cyan-blue-color has-alpha-channel-opacity has-pale-cyan-blue-background-color has-background"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Abstract&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Treatment of age-related decreases in GTP levels restores endocytosis and autophagy&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Age-related declines in neuronal bioenergetic levels may limit vesicular trafficking and autophagic clearance of damaged organelles and proteins.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Age-related ATP depletion would impact cognition dependent on ionic homeostasis, but limits on proteostasis powered by GTP are less clear.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We used neurons isolated from aged 3xTg-AD Alzheimer’s model mice and a novel genetically encoded fluorescent GTP sensor (GEVAL) to evaluate live GTP levels in situ.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We report an age-dependent reduction in ratiometric measurements of free/bound GTP levels in living hippocampal neurons. Free GTP colocalized in the mitochondria decreased with age accompanied by the accumulation of free GTP-labeled vesicular structures.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The energy dependence of autophagy was demonstrated by depletion of GTP with rapamycin stimulation, while bafilomycin inhibition of autophagy raised GTP levels.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Twenty-four-hour supplementation of aged neurons with the NAD precursor nicotinamide and the Nrf2 redox modulator EGCG restored GTP levels to youthful levels and mobilized endocytosis and lysosomal consumption for autophagy via the respective GTPases Rab7 and Arl8b.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This vesicular mobilization promoted the clearance of intraneuronal Aβ aggregates, improved viability, and lowered protein oxidative nitration in AD model neurons.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Our results reveal age- and AD-related neuronal GTP energy deficits that impair autophagy and endocytosis. GTP deficits were remediated by an external NAD precursor together with a Nrf2 redox modulator which suggests a translational path.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p class="clear"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Neuroscience News</author><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 19:53:34 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMickFVX3lxTE0yN1NBMDFkckF3VzhEXzQ2a3VWbjRtelBZN1NVRmcxejctRjlFTGVaRlA5YkNrTTdrQWNESF9JZXB4dFhuQVQxRXpHcklRZ0ZjMmhzd2lDYi1sYVVGZnl0MTU1bHNjR2Y1SjFLZDI1UjdNdw</guid></item><item><title>晚上咬牙切齿？以下是修复方法-泰晤士报</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiowFBVV95cUxNWXJ0VEczS2VYNC1NZGhkT1NsT1J2VlFPa3lwbGExV1dIWjVhUFk3Q0I0SW90NXd6R0hTZ0NobnktSWhISXV6MDR1bDJJdXpkMWZhUGpKM0ltQVBZeGFscWJoSDhpcVUxczZMT05WX3p1M0xmQzVCLXVoRU1IZGh5bzVEaWsxamZrRncwVDdtWFBGTDdLeXpLcWc4d29BZVVaZmhV?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="responsive__ArticleContent-sc-15gvuj2-8 gJBkaT"&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;&lt;span class="responsive__DropCap-sc-1pktst5-1 enuiNL"&gt;I&lt;/span&gt;f you consistently wake up with an aching jaw, you could be suffering from teeth grinding — or bruxism, to give it its medical term. One in ten people in the UK suffer from the condition, which can also cause cracked and flattened teeth, receding gums and headaches, according to the Bruxism Association dental clinic. Why do we gnash our teeth without realising (often in our sleep) and how do we stop it? &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;“The main cause is stress, hands down,” says Dr Anni Seaborne, head of general dentistry at Bupa Dental Care. If you don’t have a way to release stress, it sits in your body and can come out as clenching and grinding teeth when you’re awake or asleep. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;People with ADHD are also&lt;span class="paywall-EAB47CFD"&gt; more prone to grinding their teeth, and “some prescription medications, particularly antidepressants such as SSRIs, can also trigger or worsen bruxism,” says Dr Anjum Jahan, a cosmetic dentist who compares grinding your teeth to furrowing your brow or hunching your shoulders without realising.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="paywall-EAB47CFD"&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;Women are slightly more likely than men to grind their teeth, but it’s unclear whether this is down to higher rates of reporting or hormonal factors. “There’s some evidence hormonal contraceptives and HRT may play a role in muscle tension, although more research is needed,” Jahan says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;• &lt;a href="https://www.thetimes.com/article/jaw-clenching-how-to-stop-vn6kzzkd5" class="link__RespLink-sc-1ocvixa-0 csWvlP"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Is stress making you clench your jaw without realising? What to do&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;Other causes can include sleep apnea, consuming large amounts of stimulants such as alcohol or caffeine, and an uneven bite — a condition called malocclusion. A dentist who specialises in jaw pain should be able to tell if a misaligned bite is behind your bruxism: look for clinics that offer treatments for temporomandibular disorder (TMD) and seek second opinions. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;If malocclusion is not a factor, then there are lifestyle changes that can help you to manage bruxism. A custom-fitted night-time mouth guard made from acrylic or soft rubber can protect teeth from the wear and tear caused by grinding. “It also helps that some patients become aware of the clenching sensation, which can encourage behavioural change over time,” Jahan says. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;Some bruxism sufferers report an improvement after taking magnesium. “It is involved in muscle relaxation and nerve function,” says Dr Harpreet Sarna, chief medical officer at Vitality health insurance. A deficiency could lead to increased jaw tension, though supplements should be considered a precaution rather than a treatment. Other lifestyle factors include maintaining good sleep hygiene: try to go to bed and get up at the same time every day, limit screen time, cut out caffeine after 2pm and reduce your alcohol intake as it disrupts REM sleep, the stage when most grinding tends to happen. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;• &lt;a href="https://www.thetimes.com/article/how-to-avoid-getting-teeth-stains-dt8hk960l" class="link__RespLink-sc-1ocvixa-0 csWvlP"&gt;&lt;b&gt;How to avoid getting teeth stains&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;Jaw physiotherapy, massage and osteopathy can help to relax the muscles surrounding the temporomandibular joint, which connects the lower jaw to the skull and takes the brunt of the pressure. A more extreme option is masseter Botox, where small amounts of botulinum toxin are injected into the masseter muscles, which are responsible for chewing, weakening them and reducing clenching.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="last-paragraph" class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;If you are worried, consult a dentist. They may offer biofeedback devices: wearables containing sensors that detect clenching and train you to stop doing it using vibration, sound or mild electrical stimulation, which the brain can process even while you are asleep.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p id="paywall-portal-article-footer"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Times</author><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiowFBVV95cUxNWXJ0VEczS2VYNC1NZGhkT1NsT1J2VlFPa3lwbGExV1dIWjVhUFk3Q0I0SW90NXd6R0hTZ0NobnktSWhISXV6MDR1bDJJdXpkMWZhUGpKM0ltQVBZeGFscWJoSDhpcVUxczZMT05WX3p1M0xmQzVCLXVoRU1IZGh5bzVEaWsxamZrRncwVDdtWFBGTDdLeXpLcWc4d29BZVVaZmhV</guid></item><item><title>口交如何导致咽喉癌，迈克尔·道格拉斯分享了他被诊断时的反应- UNILAD</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMinAFBVV95cUxQSnYtUmRkT3hkSnJXWWNHbks1SWZwVllVWTlibUV4dkI4YXFlMW9IeTF0ZTVUZGFLaTRhVnlQRkp6T2JwSjJ1cC1aOXZib3o1M3dTRTZ3X2pnLU96bGhrSWhQSU00a2RrVjRUemdHWWV4a3FRTmJhYUxCQV8zbS1PdWs3US05Um0wODJvVDZGQWZPeG5NVDNjc3hpakk?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;After Michael Douglas shared how he developed throat cancer due to acts carried out in the bedroom, a study has revealed that oral sex can actually cause tumors.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;The New Jersey-born &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.unilad.com/celebrity"&gt;actor&lt;/a&gt; and film producer was &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.unilad.com/news/health/michael-douglas-throat-cancer-oral-intercourse-explained-963062-20250807"&gt;diagnosed with the devastating disease&lt;/a&gt; back in August 2010, and three years later he revealed in a bombshell interview with The Guardian that it was due to his excursions &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.unilad.com/sex-and-relationships"&gt;under the sheets&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;The celeb told the news outlet he suffered from oral discomfort for months and made various trips to medical appointments, until a friend's &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.unilad.com/health"&gt;doctor&lt;/a&gt; in Montreal examined his mouth and found the glaring problem.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="floating-video-player_container__u4D9_"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;"I will always remember the look on his face," Douglas, who is married to Catherine Zeta-Jones, said. "He said: 'We need a biopsy.' There was a walnut-size tumor at the base of my tongue that no other doctor had seen."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;What caused it was going down on his partners during sex - the &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.unilad.com/science"&gt;scientific&lt;/a&gt; word is 'cunnilingus'.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="article-image_articleImage__eyzAn"&gt;&lt;cite class="image-credit_imageCredit__YMlqS"&gt;Michael Douglas, pictured with wife Catherine Zeta-Jones, is now cancer-free (Daniele Venturelli/Getty Images for The Red Sea International Film Festival)&lt;/cite&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;"Without getting too specific, this particular cancer is caused by something called HPV [human papillomavirus], which actually comes about from cunnilingus," explained the two-time &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.unilad.com/oscars"&gt;Oscar-winner&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;He wasn't fibbing either, as one study published back in the naughties found strong evidence linking oral sex to the spread of human papillomavirus (HPV), which may lead to throat &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.unilad.com/cancer"&gt;cancer&lt;/a&gt; in both men and women.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;The research identified having multiple oral sex partners as the leading sexual behavior increasing the risk of HPV-related throat cancer, even more than smoking or alcohol use.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;Douglas himself had a pretty wild time in the 90s.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;The study involved 100 patients newly diagnosed with the disease and showed those with prior HPV infection were 32 times more likely to develop it. Risk also rose with smoking, drinking, and having over six oral sex partners.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="article-image_articleImage__eyzAn"&gt;&lt;cite class="image-credit_imageCredit__YMlqS"&gt;Throat cancer can be attributed to having multiple oral sex partners in a lifetime (Getty stock)&lt;/cite&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;In fact, those that had more than six oral sex partners in their lifetime were 8.6 times more likely to develop HPV-linked cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;However, science information officer at Cancer research &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.unilad.com/uk-news"&gt;UK&lt;/a&gt;, Dr Julie Sharp, noted that the study was rather small.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;"There is conflicting evidence about the role of HPV, and this rare type of throat cancer," she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;“As this was a small study, further research is needed to confirm these observations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;"We know that after age, the main causes of mouth cancer are smoking or chewing tobacco or betel nut, and drinking too much alcohol."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;&lt;em&gt;If you’ve been affected by any of these issues and want to speak to someone in confidence, contact the American Cancer Society on 1-800-227-2345 or via their &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" target="_blank" rel="noopener" href="https://www.cancer.org/about-us/online-help/contact-us.html#:~:text=Call%20us%20at%201%2D800%2D227%2D2345&amp;amp;text=Ask%20us%20how%20you%20can,patient%2Drelated%20programs%20or%20resources"&gt;&lt;em&gt;live chat feature&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;em&gt;available 24/7 every day of the year.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>UNILAD</author><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 15:46:57 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMinAFBVV95cUxQSnYtUmRkT3hkSnJXWWNHbks1SWZwVllVWTlibUV4dkI4YXFlMW9IeTF0ZTVUZGFLaTRhVnlQRkp6T2JwSjJ1cC1aOXZib3o1M3dTRTZ3X2pnLU96bGhrSWhQSU00a2RrVjRUemdHWWV4a3FRTmJhYUxCQV8zbS1PdWs3US05Um0wODJvVDZGQWZPeG5NVDNjc3hpakk</guid></item><item><title>​从迷迭香水到口香糖： 5种令人惊讶的磨练大脑和提高记忆力的方法-印度时报</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMikwJBVV95cUxPYUh6ZTEzQUg2d0F3c0MxSS1aa1FrVHdvUHo2WWZaUk8xdUpMVmdsRHRrNkliaVhEZk0wUVBSZkhURVQyNXNNMl9jYnJkVWV6Q1p0dFhXZEk0YnpmdGk3MzNqY0JLZVBBcF9HM1IxcGtZZ0Z5MTlrRko1WHJCd2pMalRxdFlaSUozTE5oYjBnWVAwa2g4dUNVbloxWVBjNWloYllmeU5LbldEbnZUZkZFLWRxQkhkMjlGQjRFdkJHai10NlpXbzhsWWljd1QtbzZqYUJwRjNZcURvWW9nb21CTTlWdnNJZG9lTXFNQW1PS0FwdFI0a19DYk1Ecjg5c0xUSE9jZXNwcVI1VndULTZESkxiNA?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="COQxt" data-ua-type="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;We all have those moments when we forget the purpose of us walking into that room, or spend way too much time trying to remember a name that just seems out of reach. While these moments are common, they don’t have to be permanent. Small, everyday, thoughtful changes in our daily habits can make a real difference, some of which include, rest, movement or even scent, but each remedy has the potential to support a clearer and focused mind.&lt;br&gt;Scroll down to discover memory-boosting remedies!&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 14:33:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikwJBVV95cUxPYUh6ZTEzQUg2d0F3c0MxSS1aa1FrVHdvUHo2WWZaUk8xdUpMVmdsRHRrNkliaVhEZk0wUVBSZkhURVQyNXNNMl9jYnJkVWV6Q1p0dFhXZEk0YnpmdGk3MzNqY0JLZVBBcF9HM1IxcGtZZ0Z5MTlrRko1WHJCd2pMalRxdFlaSUozTE5oYjBnWVAwa2g4dUNVbloxWVBjNWloYllmeU5LbldEbnZUZkZFLWRxQkhkMjlGQjRFdkJHai10NlpXbzhsWWljd1QtbzZqYUJwRjNZcURvWW9nb21CTTlWdnNJZG9lTXFNQW1PS0FwdFI0a19DYk1Ecjg5c0xUSE9jZXNwcVI1VndULTZESkxiNA</guid></item><item><title>人们正在分享卑鄙的健康威胁，这些威胁实际上正在摧毁你的身体- buzzfeed.com</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMif0FVX3lxTFBUbFgzUlZCaDVNRU81RFVOMjU3STR3Ny1hdTFBRTdjZXpnRnlCeVowR3RhYzlmTWM1WWowQVdhQmJ6czhVcnl1NEZ0SlpKQlNxQWN0dlpvdld6R2R1UXVNSGFyNkNCNF9XV2hBdmNoNWprT2dJV1hvSnI1cUtTS00?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="subbuzz buzz-width--standard__subbuzz buzz-type--list__subbuzz subbuzz-text
  subbuzz-index-14
  
  
  
  
  " data-keywords="cleaning" data-module="subbuzz-text"&gt;
  
  &lt;p id="138917702" class="subbuzz-anchor"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



  &lt;h2 class="subbuzz__header subbuzz__header--standard subbuzz__title "&gt;
    
      &lt;span class="subbuzz__number"&gt;12.&lt;/span&gt;
    

    
      &lt;span class="js-subbuzz__title-text"&gt;"&lt;a href="https://www.health.harvard.edu/heart-health/how-does-sleep-apnea-affect-the-heart" target="_blank"&gt;Sleep Apnea&lt;/a&gt;. People think it's just snoring and annoying, but it's WAY worse."&lt;/span&gt;
    
  &lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;"When you're asleep and have obstructed breathing, your body panics a little bit, releasing a bit of adrenaline into your bloodstream to wake you up enough to breathe. With Apnea, this can happen hundreds of times a night. Adrenaline is not good for you 300 times a night. It's great if you get surprised by a wild animal and need to run away or climb a tree, but otherwise, no good for you at all. It debilitates almost every major organ and metabolic system in your body. Long-term repeated exposure can really mess you up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you even THINK you might have a problem, get it checked out."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;–&lt;a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/AskReddit/comments/1l51rha/comment/mwe4b3y/?utm_source=share&amp;amp;utm_medium=web3x&amp;amp;utm_name=web3xcss&amp;amp;utm_term=1&amp;amp;utm_content=share_button" target="_blank"&gt;u/JetScreamerBaby&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>buzzfeed.com</author><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 14:31:03 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMif0FVX3lxTFBUbFgzUlZCaDVNRU81RFVOMjU3STR3Ny1hdTFBRTdjZXpnRnlCeVowR3RhYzlmTWM1WWowQVdhQmJ6czhVcnl1NEZ0SlpKQlNxQWN0dlpvdld6R2R1UXVNSGFyNkNCNF9XV2hBdmNoNWprT2dJV1hvSnI1cUtTS00</guid></item><item><title>甜蜜的伪装：身体用糖从免疫系统中隐藏自己的RNA - Phys.org</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMic0FVX3lxTE5KV3BOak5fd25SakVwUzNLaW1fa2o1Y0U1elJKdHpURnBJem01bmRzbFNBZlp4NHlpdFFNdDdjQUxuRkt5SEdSTl94R0c1UmM0RUlLTmZ0bkNvMEp5V3NjMW14dDFJZ3BYcUdieWdfcUpQcUk?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="mt-4 article-main"&gt;
										
&lt;div class="article-gallery lightGallery"&gt;
    &lt;div data-thumb="https://scx1.b-cdn.net/csz/news/tmb/2025/sweet-disguise-body-hi-1.jpg" data-src="https://scx2.b-cdn.net/gfx/news/hires/2025/sweet-disguise-body-hi-1.jpg" data-sub-html="Schematic. Credit: &amp;lt;i&amp;gt;Nature&amp;lt;/i&amp;gt; (2025). DOI: 10.1038/s41586-025-09310-6"&gt;
        &lt;figure class="article-img"&gt;
            &lt;img src="https://scx1.b-cdn.net/csz/news/800a/2025/sweet-disguise-body-hi-1.jpg" alt="Sweet disguise: Body hides RNA with sugar" title="Schematic. Credit: Nature (2025). DOI: 10.1038/s41586-025-09310-6"&gt;
             &lt;figcaption class="text-darken text-low-up text-truncate-js text-truncate mt-3"&gt;
                Schematic. Credit: &lt;i&gt;Nature&lt;/i&gt; (2025). DOI: 10.1038/s41586-025-09310-6
            &lt;/figcaption&gt;        &lt;/figure&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;To our immune system, naked RNA is a sign of a viral or bacterial invasion and must be attacked. But our own cells also have RNA. To ward off trouble, our cells clothe their RNA in sugars, Vijay Rathinam and colleagues at the UConn School of Medicine and Ryan Flynn at Boston Children's Hospital &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41586-025-09310-6" target="_blank"&gt;report&lt;/a&gt; in &lt;i&gt;Nature&lt;/i&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;


										      
																																	&lt;p&gt;Ribonucleic acid (RNA) is a family of large biological molecules fundamental to all forms of life, including &lt;a href="https://phys.org/tags/viruses/" rel="tag" class="textTag"&gt;viruses&lt;/a&gt;, bacteria, and animals. Viruses as diverse as measles, influenza, SARS-CoV-2, and rabies all have RNA, which is why the &lt;a href="https://phys.org/tags/immune+system/" rel="tag" class="textTag"&gt;immune system&lt;/a&gt; starts attacking when it sees RNA in the bloodstream or in other inappropriate locations. But our own cells have RNA as well, sometimes displaying it on their surface, plain for roaming immune cells to see—and yet the immune system ignores it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Recognizing RNA as a sign of infection is problematic, as every &lt;a href="https://phys.org/tags/single+cell/" rel="tag" class="textTag"&gt;single cell&lt;/a&gt; in our body has RNA," says UConn School of Medicine immunologist Vijay Rathinam. The question is, how does our immune system distinguish our own RNA from that of dangerous invaders?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Previous research led by Boston Children's Hospital and Stanford University researchers Ryan Flynn and Carolyn Bertozzi had noticed that our bodies add sugars onto RNA. These sugarcoated RNAs (also known as glycosylated RNAs, or glycoRNAs) are displayed on the &lt;a href="https://phys.org/tags/cell+surface/" rel="tag" class="textTag"&gt;cell surface&lt;/a&gt; and don't seem to provoke the immune system.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rathinam and his colleagues wondered whether the sugar was somehow shielding the glycoRNAs from the immune system. This could be a strategy the body uses to prevent our own RNA from provoking inflammation.&lt;/p&gt;

																																						&lt;p class="w-100 mb-4 ads"&gt;
    
     
&lt;ins class="adsbygoogle" data-ad-layout="in-article" data-ad-format="fluid" data-ad-client="ca-pub-0536483524803400" data-ad-slot="8188791252"&gt;&lt;/ins&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;
																																			&lt;p&gt;When Vincent Graziano, a Ph.D. student in Rathinam's lab and lead author on the paper, took glycoRNA from human cell cultures and blood, cut off the sugars, and reintroduced it into cells, the immune cells attacked it. The &lt;a href="https://phys.org/tags/immune+cells/" rel="tag" class="textTag"&gt;immune cells&lt;/a&gt; had ignored the same RNA when it was sugarcoated.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"The sugarcoating hides our own RNA from the immune system," Rathinam says.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It is particularly significant to our body because cells are often covered by glycoRNAs. When cells die and are cleaned up by the immune system, the sugarcoating of RNA prevents dead cells from unnecessarily stimulating inflammation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The findings could help when thinking about autoimmune diseases. Certain &lt;a href="https://phys.org/tags/autoimmune+diseases/" rel="tag" class="textTag"&gt;autoimmune diseases&lt;/a&gt;, such as lupus, are associated with specific RNA and dead cells setting off the immune system.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now that scientists understand the role of RNA glycosylation in deflecting immune system attention, they can check on whether that strategy is somehow going awry, and, if so, how it might be fixed.&lt;/p&gt;

																																	
																														
																				&lt;div class="article-main__more p-4"&gt;
																						&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;More information:&lt;/strong&gt;
												Vincent R. Graziano et al, RNA N-glycosylation enables immune evasion and homeostatic efferocytosis, &lt;i&gt;Nature&lt;/i&gt; (2025). &lt;a data-doi="1" href="https://dx.doi.org/10.1038/s41586-025-09310-6" target="_blank"&gt;DOI: 10.1038/s41586-025-09310-6&lt;/a&gt;
																						
																						&lt;/p&gt;
																					&lt;/div&gt;
                               														
																					
                              													                                        
										
										&lt;div class="d-none d-print-block"&gt;
											 &lt;p class="mb-4"&gt;
												&lt;strong&gt;Citation&lt;/strong&gt;:
												Sweet disguise: Body hides its own RNA from the immune system with sugar (2025, August 9)
												retrieved 10 August 2025
												from https://phys.org/news/2025-08-sweet-disguise-body-rna-immune.html
											 &lt;/p&gt;
											 &lt;p class="border text-muted p-3"&gt;
											 This document is subject to copyright. Apart from any fair dealing for the purpose of private study or research, no
											 part may be reproduced without the written permission. The content is provided for information purposes only.
											 &lt;/p&gt;
										&lt;/div&gt;
                                        
									&lt;/div&gt;
								&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Phys.org</author><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 14:30:02 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMic0FVX3lxTE5KV3BOak5fd25SakVwUzNLaW1fa2o1Y0U1elJKdHpURnBJem01bmRzbFNBZlp4NHlpdFFNdDdjQUxuRkt5SEdSTl94R0c1UmM0RUlLTmZ0bkNvMEp5V3NjMW14dDFJZ3BYcUdieWdfcUpQcUk</guid></item><item><title>为什么一些80岁的人有50岁的记忆-神经科学新闻</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMic0FVX3lxTE1tM0dyWExBbG9BaDJ6emhZNFB4NXU4eG1KMGVPR3pMRXRxdjdPVV96WWM1QTJBYmpnT3VsZlBYMzR2YXpqNE5yWFl3NEtmWlc2Z3NibHUwcEluVkhVeDNoTjl5YzR5aS1lVm1VZWhkUkVTV3M?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content body-color clearfix link-color-wrap"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary: &lt;/strong&gt;For 25 years, scientists have studied “SuperAgers”—people aged 80 and above whose memory rivals those decades younger. Research reveals that their brains either resist Alzheimer’s-related plaques and tangles or remain resilient despite having them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These individuals maintain a youthful brain structure, with a thicker cortex and unique neurons linked to memory and social skills. Insights from their biology and behavior could inspire new strategies to protect cognitive health into late life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Facts&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class="wp-block-list"&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Exceptional Memory:&lt;/strong&gt; SuperAgers score like 50–60-year-olds on memory tests despite being 80+.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Brain Structure:&lt;/strong&gt; They have thicker cortex regions and unique neurons linked to social and memory functions.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cognitive Protection:&lt;/strong&gt; Resistance or resilience to Alzheimer’s pathology helps preserve function.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Source: &lt;/strong&gt;Northwestern University&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;For 25 years, scientists at Northwestern Medicine have been studying individuals aged 80 and older — dubbed “SuperAgers” — to better understand what makes them tick. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These unique individuals, who show outstanding memory performance at a level consistent with individuals who are at least three decades younger, challenge the long-held belief that cognitive decline is an inevitable part of aging. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="wp-block-image size-full"&gt;&lt;picture fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" class="wp-image-112100"&gt; &lt;source type="image/webp" srcset="https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/08/superagers-memory-neuroscicne.jpg.webp 1200w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/08/superagers-memory-neuroscicne-300x200.jpg.webp 300w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/08/superagers-memory-neuroscicne-770x513.jpg.webp 770w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/08/superagers-memory-neuroscicne-1155x770.jpg.webp 1155w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/08/superagers-memory-neuroscicne-370x247.jpg.webp 370w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/08/superagers-memory-neuroscicne-293x195.jpg.webp 293w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/08/superagers-memory-neuroscicne-150x100.jpg.webp 150w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px"&gt;&lt;/source&gt; &lt;img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" src="https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/08/superagers-memory-neuroscicne.jpg" alt="This shows an older woman and a brain." srcset="https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/08/superagers-memory-neuroscicne.jpg 1200w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/08/superagers-memory-neuroscicne-300x200.jpg 300w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/08/superagers-memory-neuroscicne-770x513.jpg 770w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/08/superagers-memory-neuroscicne-1155x770.jpg 1155w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/08/superagers-memory-neuroscicne-370x247.jpg 370w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/08/superagers-memory-neuroscicne-293x195.jpg 293w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/08/superagers-memory-neuroscicne-150x100.jpg 150w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px"&gt; &lt;/picture&gt;&lt;figcaption class="wp-element-caption"&gt;SuperAgers score at least 9 out of 15 on a delayed word recall test — on par with individuals in their 50s and 60s. Credit: Neuroscience News&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Over the quarter-century of research, the scientists have seen some notable lifestyle and personality differences between SuperAgers and those aging typically — such as being social and gregarious — but “it’s really what we’ve found in their brains that’s been so earth-shattering for us,” said Dr. Sandra Weintraub, a professor of psychiatry and behavioral sciences and neurology at Northwestern University Feinberg School of Medicine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;By identifying biological and behavioral traits associated with SuperAging, the scientists hope to uncover new strategies to promote cognitive resilience and delay or prevent Alzheimer’s and other diseases that cause cognitive decline and dementia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Our findings show that exceptional memory in old age is not only possible but is linked to a distinct neurobiological profile. This opens the door to new interventions aimed at preserving brain health well into the later decades of life,” said Weintraub, corresponding author of a new paper summarizing the findings. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The paper will be published in a perspective piece in Alzheimer’s &amp;amp; Dementia: The Journal of the Alzheimer’s Association as part of the journal’s special issue commemorating the 40th anniversary of the National Institute on Aging’s Alzheimer’s Disease Centers Program and the 25th anniversary of the National Alzheimer Coordinating Center.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SuperAger brains are resilient, resistant &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The term “SuperAger” was coined by Dr. M. Marsel Mesulam, who founded the Mesulam Center for Cognitive Neurology and Alzheimer’s Disease at Northwestern in the late 1990s.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Since 2000, a cohort of 290 SuperAger participants has passed through the Mesulam Center’s doors, and the scientists have autopsied 77 donated SuperAger brains. Some of the brains contained amyloid and tau proteins (also known as plaques and tangles), which are known to play key roles in the progression of Alzheimer’s disease, but others didn’t develop any. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“What we realized is there are two mechanisms that lead someone to become a SuperAger,” Weintraub said. “One is resistance: they don’t make the plaques and tangles. Two is resilience: they make them, but they don’t do anything to their brains.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Other &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;key findings:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class="wp-block-list"&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Exceptional memory performance:&lt;/strong&gt; SuperAgers score at least 9 out of 15 on a delayed word recall test — on par with individuals in their 50s and 60s.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Youthful brain structure:&lt;/strong&gt; Unlike typically aging brains, SuperAgers show no significant thinning of their cortex — the outer layer of the brain — and even have a thicker anterior cingulate cortex than younger adults. This crucial region of the brain plays a significant role in integrating information related to decision-making, emotion and motivation.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Unique cellular traits:&lt;/strong&gt; SuperAgers have more von economo neurons, which are specialized cells linked to social behavior, and larger entorhinal neurons, which are critical for memory, than their typically aging peers.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sociability as a common trait:&lt;/strong&gt; Despite having diverse lifestyles and varying approaches to exercise, SuperAgers tend to be highly social and report strong interpersonal relationships.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;‘&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Brain donation can offer scientific immortality’&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At the Mesulam Center, SuperAgers are evaluated annually and may choose to donate their brains for post-mortem evaluation by Northwestern scientists.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Many of the findings from this paper stem from the examination of brain specimens of generous, dedicated SuperAgers who were followed for decades,” said co-author Dr. Tamar Gefen, associate professor of psychiatry and behavioral sciences at Feinberg, director of Feinberg’s Laboratory for Translational Neuropsychology and a neuropsychologist at the Mesulam Center.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I am constantly amazed by how brain donation can enable discovery long after death, offering a kind of scientific immortality.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.brain.northwestern.edu/join/SuperAging.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Learn more about how to join the SuperAger research registry&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The perspective piece is titled, “The First 25 Years of the Northwestern SuperAging Program.” Other Northwestern authors include Dr. Mesulam and Changiz Geula, research professor of cell and developmental biology and neuroscience at Feinberg and a member of the Mesulam Center. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;About this aging and memory research news&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="has-background"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Author: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#78130b19150d1d140b17163816170a0c100f1d0b0c1d0a16561d1c0d" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Kristin Samuelson&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Source: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://northwestern.edu" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Northwestern University&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Contact: &lt;/strong&gt;Kristin Samuelson – Northwestern University&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Image: &lt;/strong&gt;The image is credited to Neuroscience News&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="has-background"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Original Research: &lt;/strong&gt;Open access.&lt;br&gt;“&lt;a href="https://alz-journals.onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/alz.70312" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;The First 25 Years of the Northwestern SuperAging Program&lt;/a&gt;” by Sandra Weintraub et al. &lt;em&gt;Alzheimer’s &amp;amp; Dementia&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr class="wp-block-separator has-text-color has-pale-cyan-blue-color has-alpha-channel-opacity has-pale-cyan-blue-background-color has-background"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Abstract&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The First 25 Years of the Northwestern SuperAging Program&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;During late life, “average” does not mean “intact.” For example, cross-sectional data from a common word list learning test show that average delayed word recall raw score at age 80 (5/15) is approximately half that at age 56 to 66 (9/15).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cognitive and neurobiological dissolution is therefore implicitly incorporated into concepts of the aging brain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This position is being challenged through investigations on “superaging,” a term that was coined at the Northwestern Alzheimer’s Disease Research Center (ADRC) to define persons ≥ 80 years with delayed word recall raw scores &lt;em&gt;at least equal&lt;/em&gt; to those of individuals 20 to 30 years younger.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;During the first 25 years of this program we established that superagers constitute not only a neuropsychological but also a neurobiological phenotype distinctive from cognitively average age peers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;With respect to brain structure, superagers have cortical volumes no different than neurotypical adults 20 to 30 years younger in contrast to neurotypical peers who do show such age-related shrinkage; they also have a region in the cingulate gyrus that is thicker than younger neurotypical adults.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;With respect to cellular biology, superagers have fewer Alzheimer’s disease–type changes in the brain, greater size of entorhinal neurons, fewer inflammatory microglia in white matter, better preserved cholinergic innervation, and a greater density of evolutionarily progressive von Economo neurons.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the future, deeper characterization of the superaging phenotype may lead to interventions that enhance resistance and resilience to involutional changes considered part of average (i.e., “normal”) brain aging.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This line of work is helping to revise common misperceptions about the cognitive potential of senescence and has inspired investigations throughout the United States and abroad.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p class="clear"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Neuroscience News</author><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 13:03:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMic0FVX3lxTE1tM0dyWExBbG9BaDJ6emhZNFB4NXU4eG1KMGVPR3pMRXRxdjdPVV96WWM1QTJBYmpnT3VsZlBYMzR2YXpqNE5yWFl3NEtmWlc2Z3NibHUwcEluVkhVeDNoTjl5YzR5aS1lVm1VZWhkUkVTV3M</guid></item><item><title>罕见的西澳大利亚州疟疾病例促使进一步研究该地区的蚊子-西雅图时报</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMirgFBVV95cUxQbDBqNlh3ckdOUjRBNUZTNnZVcF9QMnhYdkpqM1Y3dWVGQy1yWnJZQmZwdUx0UjdUNHZLMnJKdzQwLXRJcnU4RnRSMVRBa1dFakRwbm5USDMzVmhsRGt6dF9YZWdqaUdEXzllNnRxQTZEWlZ3c2ZWTS1EanlXUi1FS3h3OS02YzI5Zjh1VEV4dVhTRHIwUE4yYWowZUFQdkQzSlN1anNfcmJxeGZRR2c?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="article-content" class="article-content entry-content"&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Local health officials are still investigating how a Pierce County woman who hadn’t traveled recently &lt;a href="https://www.seattletimes.com/seattle-news/health/malaria-possibly-contracted-in-wa-would-be-states-first-case/" class="content-link"&gt;might have contracted malaria&lt;/a&gt; — but however it happened, the situation involved an “unusual sequence of events.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The case is rare for a few reasons, said Dr. James Miller, health officer of the Tacoma-Pierce County Health Department, which &lt;a href="https://tpchd.org/news/we-are-investigating-possible-locally-acquired-case-of-malaria/" target="_blank" class="content-link external"&gt;announced the news &lt;/a&gt;Wednesday. It’s Washington state’s first locally acquired case, meaning the woman was most likely bitten here by a malaria-infected mosquito, which would have gotten malaria after biting someone else with the disease, who had traveled recently and perhaps contracted malaria abroad.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If that were the case, it would be a “very unusual sequence of events” Miller said, “which is why we’re doing this more extensive investigation for this case than we would typically for a travel-acquired malaria case.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The mosquito-borne disease does not spread from person to person, nor does it spread between mosquitoes, so risk to the general public is low, he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The patient is receiving treatment, Miller said, but declined to give more details about her condition. He noted it’s common for people with malaria to be hospitalized, as the disease can cause very serious infection.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The chance of the malaria-infected mosquito biting another person in the county is “pretty low,” Miller reiterated. “But of course, malaria is a serious disease. That’s why we’re taking this seriously and doing a full investigation.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The investigation includes, in the meantime, a plan to work with the state Department of Health to set up mosquito traps all over the county and collect data from them. It’s unlikely they’ll find the malaria-infected mosquito that bit the Pierce County patient, Miller acknowledged, but the data is useful in gauging how many other mosquitoes might be carrying the malaria parasite.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The main purpose is really just to get a sense of … the burden for the population of Anopheles mosquitoes, which is the set of species that can transmit malaria,” Miller said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Part of the investigation also looks at other patients in Washington recently diagnosed with malaria, to see if there could be any potential connections, he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the United States, malaria cases are usually linked to travel, mainly from sub-Saharan African countries, and regions of South America and Southeast Asia, &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/malaria/prevention/index.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" class="content-link external"&gt;according to the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention&lt;/a&gt;. Anopheles mosquitoes, which are in Pierce County and Washington, can transmit malaria across the U.S. if they bite someone infected with the disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The U.S. sees about 2,000 to 2,500 cases per year, and &lt;a href="https://doh.wa.gov/public-health-provider-resources/notifiable-conditions/malaria" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" class="content-link external"&gt;Washington sees 20 to 70 reports of malaria&lt;/a&gt; in travelers each year, according to the state Department of Health. In 2023, the U.S. saw its first locally acquired malaria case in 20 years. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ten cases were reported across four states — &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/mmwr/volumes/73/wr/mm7342a2.htm" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" class="content-link external"&gt;Florida, Texas, Maryland and Arkansas&lt;/a&gt; — from May to October 2023.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So far this year, 19 cases of travel-associated malaria have been reported in Washington state, according to DOH.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fortunately, Miller said, mosquito populations are starting to shrink in Pierce County and throughout the state at this point in the year. Mosquitoes like warm weather and being near water to breed, so they prefer early summer, he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When temperatures fall, populations also decline, Miller said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="userMessagingInset" class="user-messaging animate"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Still, people should try to take basic precautions to avoid getting bit, he said, including: wearing bug spray, removing standing water in yards and considering long pants or long sleeves if in a place there are mosquitoes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And if traveling to a &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/yellow-book/hcp/preparing-international-travelers/yellow-fever-vaccine-and-malaria-prevention-information-by-country.html" target="_blank" class="content-link external"&gt;country where there’s risk of malaria&lt;/a&gt;, think about precautionary measures such as taking medication before, during and after your trip.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The disease typically causes fever, chills, body aches, headaches and fatigue. Without treatment, it &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/malaria/php/surveillance-report/index.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" class="content-link external"&gt;can be fatal&lt;/a&gt;, Miller said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If people recognize these symptoms or suspect malaria, health officials recommend seeking early testing and treatment. The disease can be treated with antimalarial drugs. &lt;/p&gt;    &lt;p id="userMessagingIn-story"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        
  &lt;/div&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Seattle Times</author><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMirgFBVV95cUxQbDBqNlh3ckdOUjRBNUZTNnZVcF9QMnhYdkpqM1Y3dWVGQy1yWnJZQmZwdUx0UjdUNHZLMnJKdzQwLXRJcnU4RnRSMVRBa1dFakRwbm5USDMzVmhsRGt6dF9YZWdqaUdEXzllNnRxQTZEWlZ3c2ZWTS1EanlXUi1FS3h3OS02YzI5Zjh1VEV4dVhTRHIwUE4yYWowZUFQdkQzSlN1anNfcmJxeGZRR2c</guid></item><item><title>人民药店：疱疹病毒与阿尔茨海默病之间有联系吗？ - OregonLive.com</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMixgFBVV95cUxQb3lLVFloYWJMa3lMNHkzdW9pdllNaGxod3lGOC0wRE9Db19YTEU3YkJHaVhrMklDYjU0OHZOVGx0dWF3Ry03emlsUkZpUFpTUTAyUWJMWFVoMEhaOURvUVoyRzNTQk1KVmpObjNxUk90amVXT3ZaTEN2Q1FyWk9CZFE5b3pXcWtoNDRVUFVrMnBwb19Gc1h2WGVWWXV3Ni1sbzVBazdpY0VXUFRSSFVnT1J2clF5eWJwa25HeFVzcHIxNk1pTHfSAdoBQVVfeXFMTmJqeTdpY1RVVERZNVZoVTJDNmZXb0J4ZzRrQlNpUmdJNklDU0dsd2c0SjNoa1JVUWhQX1JMTVU1Nk1wdTJMVV9hOTI0UXZmdnBqLUVkd1BqZ1RNcTkwblZsRTh2Rk5EM3lNLWFsU0pZZTZmZURaY2tPdjJHZUszalVTZFc4RnEzb3doRnFMU2JfRE1hSGhvRjBMYTIwRHcxVkRmS1NZektXb1IzTTlYLV9fb3V4MXJaaDUtc053UF90X0hITVNvZVphRmoxdDdjTkJKTDNBbmVCVEE?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content   "&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="BWVOY24CQBDELDXQ6NXPISPPEE"&gt;Q. I had chicken pox as a child and shingles as an adult. I have gotten the Shingrix vaccine. For an occasional cold sore, I use acyclovir, but I take L-lysine daily for prevention. Has anyone studied this as an alternative prevention against Alzheimer’s disease?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-1" data-gaid="inarticle-1"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="62FT2YPZYVEHRC4PRRPGRQDXWE"&gt;As I understand it, the herpes virus might be a contributing factor. Since L-lysine is available without a prescription in the U.S., it could be an alternative to antiviral drugs for many people.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-2" data-gaid="inarticle-2"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="HYX7NPUHSFHXPMOCDNSVHZZHSA"&gt;A. The link between herpes virus infection and AD is tantalizing, but it has not yet been firmly established. What we know about L-lysine is that it can help reduce outbreaks of cold sores due to herpes (Viruses, June 2, 2023). According to the scientists, the effective dose of this dietary supplement is at least 1 gram per day. We found no studies of L-lysine being used to prevent AD.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-3" data-gaid="inarticle-3"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="5EVWBTU5L5ACFHWUICHCFAIOQA"&gt;L-lysine is an essential amino acid. Another amino acid, arginine, counteracts the antiviral action of lysine. As a result, L-lysine appears to be more effective if people reduce their intake of arginine from sources such as legumes, nuts and meat like turkey, chicken or pork.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-4" data-gaid="inarticle-4"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="RM2L4IZXVRE6DPNYFRZIXB76AI"&gt;It was smart of you to get vaccinated against shingles. The varicella zoster virus that causes both chicken pox and shingles has also been implicated in AD. Studies in Wales and Australia indicate that older people vaccinated against shingles are less likely to develop AD than their neighbors who were not vaccinated (Nature, April 2, 2025; JAMA, April 23, 2025). &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-5" data-gaid="inarticle-5"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-enter:FGETUJH3HVFI7MSM2JXJU3CXBM" data-fusion-component="FGETUJH3HVFI7MSM2JXJU3CXBM"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-exit:FGETUJH3HVFI7MSM2JXJU3CXBM" data-fusion-component="FGETUJH3HVFI7MSM2JXJU3CXBM"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-6" class="middleParagraph" data-gaid="inarticle-6"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="AW27S6DSHFCL3LRTWJSJCAN7NU"&gt;Q. I have read that there is now an epinephrine nasal spray called neffy for severe allergic reactions or even anaphylaxis. It requires a prescription and is pricey. Why not use over-the-counter Primatene Mist instead? It’s far less expensive.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-7" data-gaid="inarticle-7"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="DEXAM7NQ3FFRXIKIYALXO7OUXI"&gt;A. Anaphylaxis is a life-threatening allergic reaction. It must always be treated as a medical emergency.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-8" data-gaid="inarticle-8"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="HWGBRUAKGFH6XLTVQMY3I7NX5Q"&gt;Epinephrine auto-injectors such as EpiPen or Adrenaclick deliver a specified dose of epinephrine immediately into the bloodstream. German scientists studied Primatene Mist to see if it could be used as a substitute treatment for anaphylaxis and found it is not suitable (Journal der Deutschen Dermatologischen Gesellschaft, May 2009). &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-9" data-gaid="inarticle-9"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="JF7WMR57UVAULCBW4SMLVD74DY"&gt;On the other hand, neffy was developed specifically to immediately provide an appropriate dose of epinephrine. Experimenting with a money-saving alternative may not be wise when the outcome could be death.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-10" data-gaid="inarticle-10"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="JV6MCHOH2VEWXPLJQLBNMTAT4M"&gt;&lt;i&gt;In their column, Joe and Teresa Graedon answer letters from readers. Write to them in care of King Features, 628 Virginia Drive, Orlando, FL 32803, or email them via their website: www.PeoplesPharmacy.com. Their newest book is “Top Screwups Doctors Make and How to Avoid Them.”&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-11" data-gaid="inarticle-11"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--center skimlinks"&gt;If you purchase a product or register for an account through a link on our site, we may receive compensation.&lt;span&gt; By using this site, you consent to our &lt;a href="https://www.advancelocal.com/advancelocalUserAgreement/user-agreement.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;User Agreement&lt;/a&gt; and agree that your clicks, interactions, and personal information may be collected, recorded, and/or stored by us and social media and other third-party partners in accordance with our &lt;a href="https://www.advancelocal.com/advancelocalUserAgreement/privacy-policy.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Privacy Policy.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>OregonLive.com</author><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMixgFBVV95cUxQb3lLVFloYWJMa3lMNHkzdW9pdllNaGxod3lGOC0wRE9Db19YTEU3YkJHaVhrMklDYjU0OHZOVGx0dWF3Ry03emlsUkZpUFpTUTAyUWJMWFVoMEhaOURvUVoyRzNTQk1KVmpObjNxUk90amVXT3ZaTEN2Q1FyWk9CZFE5b3pXcWtoNDRVUFVrMnBwb19Gc1h2WGVWWXV3Ni1sbzVBazdpY0VXUFRSSFVnT1J2clF5eWJwa25HeFVzcHIxNk1pTHfSAdoBQVVfeXFMTmJqeTdpY1RVVERZNVZoVTJDNmZXb0J4ZzRrQlNpUmdJNklDU0dsd2c0SjNoa1JVUWhQX1JMTVU1Nk1wdTJMVV9hOTI0UXZmdnBqLUVkd1BqZ1RNcTkwblZsRTh2Rk5EM3lNLWFsU0pZZTZmZURaY2tPdjJHZUszalVTZFc4RnEzb3doRnFMU2JfRE1hSGhvRjBMYTIwRHcxVkRmS1NZektXb1IzTTlYLV9fb3V4MXJaaDUtc053UF90X0hITVNvZVphRmoxdDdjTkJKTDNBbmVCVEE</guid></item><item><title>肺科医生揭示了有助于改善睡眠质量的5个习惯：更换枕套，不含咖啡因等|健康-印度斯坦时报-印度斯坦时报</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMihgJBVV95cUxQSHlJbW5NZ3gzZjdFcXlxaGtzc05ZTF9vLTVPLU5kdDNjMHd2LUJ2UGNVQlZidl9maWhrTnFzYU5PZG5OOXAwcDMwX3ZwQkFKX0tkSENRSTNyMWNEbUU5RHhqS2VPck1tWGk1OEpRN1pZbzU1YWwyQWlOb0N3YlNCVjlHSG9jZWhUMUVsdE1UUmRQbFBBdk9tcl9aU2t5R3h5a3JLb2FjM19EdnBUempKeS1LZE5kUy15anFYdkplWlB6ZzkzWmtYLUxDTzRoWjVjS3JzRnZHM0ZrSEc3LVV3WW54VHlOVGM5bFIxTlNkaVkyUGtfY3dLaXk1MEFtWkVIYnlMNWFn0gGLAkFVX3lxTE9kQl9KdVJyeElYRzdWc29kSDVtSzZYaHFMMWNuT25vRzJOUDgwNjFZMXcwOTlSQlZuaHN5U2ZWVlFQS1BSQ1lyM1JKWjJCT3RMMktXZ3RidU5sSWFQR2hveThNMTJCaHJGVHhtY2xhRFc5Rnc1LVd5MUNaTjZzS1lLSExGS0tVdW9ZdGtQNlA5Uk5uSllRMHlGMTRhaF84eGd5S1RDdkhQTXM1WnRJeUt2cnVQd045NzFvRnliYnFPVUJmZTdZUE9VS0E5WDQ1Nkc4OW9hNHVtMlRzdEdlMkpfbGVPYzR5Z3JMSTd5OHZURFAyQ3VqQ3U3cHVtT2lqb0t6YWJZNTRQSWJoRQ?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="storyMainDiv" class="fullStory tfStory current videoStory story__detail storyAf101754740980914 " data-vars-storyid="101754740980914" data-story-section="lifestyle" data-story-subsection="health" data-vars-author="Adrija Dey" data-premium-story="false" data-performance-type="not-set"&gt; &lt;p class="htEchoTopPageBanner dHide"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="stickyCard"&gt; &lt;/p&gt;  &lt;h1 class="hdg1"&gt;Pulmonologist reveals 5 habits that help improve sleep quality: Change pillow cover, no caffeine and more&lt;/h1&gt;  &lt;div class="actionDiv flexElm topTime"&gt; &lt;p class="dateTime secTime storyPage"&gt;Updated on: Aug 09, 2025 06:28 pm IST &lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p class="googleFollow mHide"&gt; &lt;button class="htEchoShareBarDesk"&gt;&lt;/button&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;h2 class="sortDec"&gt;It’s not just about the number of hours, you also need good quality sleep. If your sleep is light, know the essential habits that help get better quality sleep.&lt;/h2&gt;  &lt;div class="storyDetails taboola-readmore"&gt; &lt;div class="detail " dataid="/lifestyle/health/pulmonologist-reveals-5-habits-that-help-improve-sleep-quality-change-pillow-cover-no-caffeine-heavy-meals-101754740980914.html"&gt; &lt;div class="storyParagraphFigure"&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/mind-still-buzzing-late-at-night-and-can-t-sleep-try-these-5-yoga-poses-to-help-you-unwind-and-relax-before-bed-101754576315548.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="Sleep"&gt;Sleep&lt;/a&gt; is restorative for overall wellbeing, acting as the bedrock for good health. But when sleep gets compromised, the ripple effects can be felt throughout the body and mind. This is where your habits leading up to bedtime count. Sleep is more than just clocking in the recommended eight hours; the quality also matters, substantially.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;figure class=""&gt; &lt;span class=""&gt; &lt;picture&gt; &lt;source media="(max-width:767px)" srcset="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/08/09/550x309/sleep_1754741870752_1754741870898.jpg" alt="A good and comfotable sleep necessitates cummulative of habits that " title="A good and comfotable sleep necessitates cummulative of habits that "&gt;&lt;/source&gt; &lt;img src="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/08/09/550x309/sleep_1754741870752_1754741870898.jpg" alt="A good and comfotable sleep necessitates cummulative of habits that " title="A good and comfotable sleep necessitates cummulative of habits that "&gt; &lt;/picture&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;figcaption&gt;A good and comfotable sleep necessitates cummulative of habits that&lt;/figcaption&gt; &lt;/figure&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;p id="readMoreFTUser"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Despite getting the recommended hours of sleep, if you are still tossing and turning, changing sides, flipping pillows to the cold side, or counting sheep to fall asleep, then the quality of sleep may be poor. Let's take a closer look at what may help you sleep better.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="mt-10 mb-10 htEchoRecirculationWidget"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="mt10 mb10 htEchoArticlePromo"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="predictorShow mb20" data-vars-predictor="true" data-vars-quiz="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="quizShow mb20" data-vars-minimized="false" data-vars-predictor="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;ALSO READ: &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/pumpkin-seeds-for-better-sleep-a-complete-guide-to-their-nutritional-value-and-how-to-add-to-your-diet-101740382726632.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="Pumpkin seeds for better sleep: A complete guide to their nutritional value and how to add to your diet"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pumpkin seeds for better sleep: A complete guide to their nutritional value and how to add to your diet&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Dr Waseem Ud Din, Consultant Pulmonologist at Ujala Cygnus Group of Hospitals, told HT Lifestyle about the value of sleep hygiene. He elaborated, “Sleep hygiene refers to the daily habits and environment that support deep, restorative sleep. It’s not just about getting eight hours, it’s about setting up your body and mind to sleep well. When sleep suffers, everything from focus and mood to immunity can take a hit.” Certain habits help in preparing the body and mind to achieve deep, restorative sleep.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Dr Waseem shared 5 habits that you need to make a note of if you are seeking deep sleep:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;1. Regularly changing pillow covers and bedsheets&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;  &lt;figure class="inlineIMG"&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;img data-src="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/08/09/original/pillow_1754742980992.jpg" class="lazy" src="https://images.hindustantimes.com/default/550x309.jpg" alt="Change your pillow cover to reduce skin discomfort.(Shutterstock)" title="Change your pillow cover to reduce skin discomfort.(Shutterstock)"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;figcaption&gt;Change your pillow cover to reduce skin discomfort.(Shutterstock)&lt;/figcaption&gt; &lt;/figure&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Clean your pillow cover and bedsheets every week to prevent the buildup of dust, sweat, and allergens.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;These irritants can lead to skin discomfort and sinus problems that interrupt your sleep.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Keeping your bedding fresh not only feels better but also helps create a healthier sleep environment.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h2&gt;2. Go to bed and wake up at same time&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Go to bed and wake up at the same time every day, including weekends.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;This consistent routine helps regulate your body’s internal clock and improves the quality of your sleep.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h2&gt;3. No screen before bed&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Blue light from phones, tablets, and TVs can disrupt melatonin production, making it harder to fall asleep.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Turn off screens at least one hour before going to bed.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h2&gt;4. Turn your bedroom dark&lt;/h2&gt;  &lt;figure class="inlineIMG"&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;img data-src="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/08/09/original/dark_bedd_1754743127930.jpg" class="lazy" src="https://images.hindustantimes.com/default/550x309.jpg" alt="Turn your bedroom dark for restful sleep.(Shutterstock)" title="Turn your bedroom dark for restful sleep.(Shutterstock)"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;figcaption&gt;Turn your bedroom dark for restful sleep.(Shutterstock)&lt;/figcaption&gt; &lt;/figure&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Keep your bedroom dark, cool, quiet, and clutter-free.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Using blackout curtains or white noise machines can further promote restful sleep.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h2&gt;5. Avoid caffeine or heavy meals before bed&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Caffeine can stay in your system for hours.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Heavy food may cause gut discomfort that disrupts sleep.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Opt for lighter meals earlier in the evening.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Note to readers: This article is for informational purposes only and not a substitute for professional medical advice. Always seek the advice of your doctor with any questions about a medical condition.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;    &lt;/div&gt; &lt;p class="recommendedSliderContextual" id="recommendedSliderContextual-101754740980914" data-vars-story_id="101754740980914" data-vars-story_section="lifestyle" data-vars-author="Adrija Dey" data-vars-story_headline="Pulmonologist reveals 5 habits that help improve sleep quality: Change pillow cover, no caffeine and more"&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;input type="checkbox" class="trendTopsSHow" id="trendTopsSHow-101754740980914"&gt; &lt;div class="trendTops"&gt;  &lt;div class="trendInlineSeo"&gt;&lt;p&gt; Catch every big hit, every wicket with Crick-it, a one stop destination for Live Scores, Match Stats, Quizzes, Polls &amp;amp; much more. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/cricket?utm_source=endofarticle&amp;amp;utm_medium=web&amp;amp;utm_campaign=crickitlaunch"&gt;Explore now!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Catch your daily dose of &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/fashion"&gt;Fashion&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/entertainment/music/taylor-swift"&gt;Taylor Swift&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health"&gt;Health&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/festivals"&gt;Festivals&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/travel"&gt;Travel&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/relationships"&gt;Relationship&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/recipe"&gt;Recipe&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; and all the other Latest &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle"&gt;Lifestyle News&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; on Hindustan Times Website and APPs. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;label class="moreBtn1" for="trendTopsSHow-101754740980914"&gt;&lt;/label&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;div class="followHT trendSeo__1"&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="htEchoEOALite"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;div class="bottomSeoParaEcho1"&gt; &lt;div id="bottomSeoParaEcho"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Catch every big hit, every wicket with Crick-it, a one stop destination for Live Scores, Match Stats, Quizzes, Polls &amp;amp; much more. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/cricket?utm_source=endofarticle&amp;amp;utm_medium=web&amp;amp;utm_campaign=crickitlaunch"&gt;Explore now!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Catch your daily dose of &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/fashion"&gt;Fashion&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/entertainment/music/taylor-swift"&gt;Taylor Swift&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health"&gt;Health&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/festivals"&gt;Festivals&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/travel"&gt;Travel&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/relationships"&gt;Relationship&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/recipe"&gt;Recipe&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; and all the other Latest &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle"&gt;Lifestyle News&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; on Hindustan Times Website and APPs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;div class="mb5 mt5" id="bottomBreadCrumb"&gt; &lt;div class="breadcrumbs"&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com" class="breadcrumbclick" data-vars-event-label="Home_clicked" data-vars-event-action="/" data-vars-event-cta="News"&gt;News&lt;/a&gt; &lt;span&gt;/&lt;/span&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle" class="breadcrumbclick" data-vars-event-label="Lifestyle_clicked" data-vars-event-action="/lifestyle" data-vars-event-cta="Lifestyle"&gt;Lifestyle&lt;/a&gt; &lt;span&gt;/&lt;/span&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health" class="breadcrumbclick" data-vars-event-label="Health_clicked" data-vars-event-action="/lifestyle/health" data-vars-event-cta="Health"&gt;Health&lt;/a&gt; &lt;span&gt;/&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; Pulmonologist reveals 5 habits that help improve sleep quality: Change pillow cover, no caffeine and more &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;p class="bottomSeoParaEcho pb0"&gt; &lt;label class="moreBtn" for="trendTopsSHow-101754740980914" id="spanSeeLessEcho"&gt;See Less&lt;/label&gt; &lt;/p&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;   &lt;p class="relatedStoryCricket"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="saranyuPlayer" id="saranyu-player"&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;p class="relatedStory2"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="us-ad align-center mb10 mt10"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p class="htEchoShortsEntryPoint" data-size="enlarged"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="affiliate-shop-now" id="affiliate-shop-now"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Hindustan Times</author><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 12:58:06 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihgJBVV95cUxQSHlJbW5NZ3gzZjdFcXlxaGtzc05ZTF9vLTVPLU5kdDNjMHd2LUJ2UGNVQlZidl9maWhrTnFzYU5PZG5OOXAwcDMwX3ZwQkFKX0tkSENRSTNyMWNEbUU5RHhqS2VPck1tWGk1OEpRN1pZbzU1YWwyQWlOb0N3YlNCVjlHSG9jZWhUMUVsdE1UUmRQbFBBdk9tcl9aU2t5R3h5a3JLb2FjM19EdnBUempKeS1LZE5kUy15anFYdkplWlB6ZzkzWmtYLUxDTzRoWjVjS3JzRnZHM0ZrSEc3LVV3WW54VHlOVGM5bFIxTlNkaVkyUGtfY3dLaXk1MEFtWkVIYnlMNWFn0gGLAkFVX3lxTE9kQl9KdVJyeElYRzdWc29kSDVtSzZYaHFMMWNuT25vRzJOUDgwNjFZMXcwOTlSQlZuaHN5U2ZWVlFQS1BSQ1lyM1JKWjJCT3RMMktXZ3RidU5sSWFQR2hveThNMTJCaHJGVHhtY2xhRFc5Rnc1LVd5MUNaTjZzS1lLSExGS0tVdW9ZdGtQNlA5Uk5uSllRMHlGMTRhaF84eGd5S1RDdkhQTXM1WnRJeUt2cnVQd045NzFvRnliYnFPVUJmZTdZUE9VS0E5WDQ1Nkc4OW9hNHVtMlRzdEdlMkpfbGVPYzR5Z3JMSTd5OHZURFAyQ3VqQ3U3cHVtT2lqb0t6YWJZNTRQSWJoRQ</guid></item><item><title>您的户外空气质量监视器可以为每个人带来更安全的空气-有线</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMifEFVX3lxTFBTM1BobURDOFE4c2VyN2JCV1BMZDBXYnB5YTdkN3JLNUFUYTc4ZW9uREZkTVd5M1E2aXN6UGFnWW8tREM0SzhRMHJYSkFYV1FWYUxBc191SVJ1bEhXSEhGX3VJSmZ4emdpTGRDd0xGWHZFclhhVnp0bFpob3U?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="body__inner-container"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="lead-in-text-callout"&gt;It wasn’t that&lt;/span&gt; long ago that few people were monitoring the air—not the government, not its citizens. Today, weather apps provide estimates of outdoor air quality, and the government’s own air quality monitoring website, &lt;a data-offer-url="https://www.airnow.gov/how-to-use-this-site/" class="external-link" data-event-click='{"element":"ExternalLink","outgoingURL":"https://www.airnow.gov/how-to-use-this-site/"}' href="https://www.airnow.gov/how-to-use-this-site/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;AirNow&lt;/a&gt;, has an easy-to-use zip code portal and &lt;a data-offer-url="https://fire.airnow.gov/#6/41/-98" class="external-link" data-event-click='{"element":"ExternalLink","outgoingURL":"https://fire.airnow.gov/#6/41/-98"}' href="https://fire.airnow.gov/#6/41/-98" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;fire and smoke map&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;There are real health benefits to owning an &lt;a href="https://www.wired.com/gallery/best-indoor-air-quality-monitors/#:~:text=Purifier%20for%20You-,Best%20Indoor%2DOutdoor%20Option,-PHOTOGRAPH%3A%20KAT%20MERCK"&gt;air quality monitor&lt;/a&gt;. Each US state is responsible for developing its own monitoring &lt;a href="https://www.epa.gov/amtic/state-monitoring-agency-annual-air-monitoring-plans-and-network-assessments"&gt;plan&lt;/a&gt;. Even in densely populated urban areas, outdoor air monitors owned by federal, state, and local jurisdictions might be geographically spread out, leaving monitoring gaps that don't accurately capture the air quality beyond one’s front door.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="AssetEmbedWrapper-fkZDUs kHRAYC asset-embed"&gt;&lt;p class="CaptionWrapper-jYrTxZ bkfwbX caption AssetEmbedCaption-fyuOdR eXMqGf asset-embed__caption" data-testid="caption-wrapper"&gt;&lt;span class="BaseWrap-sc-gzmcOU BaseText-eqOrNE CaptionCredit-eowWKH deqABF kpqIso kpuElq caption__credit"&gt;Photograph: Lisa Wood Shapiro&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;Outdoor air quality monitors are not just for understanding the air quality when the odor of smoke fills your home—an outdoor monitor can keep you informed. America has been in the air quality monitoring business for less than a century. In the not-so-distant past, citizens died due to unregulated and unchecked air.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Container-VgtPr ekoLDG"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;Once more, Trump’s EPA is seeking to weaken current A&lt;a data-offer-url="https://www.airnow.gov/aqi/aqi-basics/" class="external-link" data-event-click='{"element":"ExternalLink","outgoingURL":"https://www.airnow.gov/aqi/aqi-basics/"}' href="https://www.airnow.gov/aqi/aqi-basics/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;ir Quality Index&lt;/a&gt; standards, the numbers that decide what is good, moderate, or unhealthy air, along with repealing the regulations on emissions of greenhouse gases. Those actions will lead to dirtier air and less reliable data. Like &lt;a href="https://www.wired.com/story/best-disposable-face-masks-n95-kn95-kf94-surgical/"&gt;face masks&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.wired.com/gallery/best-air-purifiers/"&gt;air purifiers&lt;/a&gt;, an outdoor air quality monitor is no longer a niche appliance but an electronic canary in the modern coal mine of a bad-air world.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-testid="feature-large-callout" class="CalloutFeatureLargeWrapper-cAQNly bLNMaC"&gt;&lt;div class="UnifiedProductCardBody-hIYvDT cYxZHF product-embed" data-item='{"ctaHref":"https://cna.st/p/8uvTiuNRgn5tyRjNWiSy546tbR1Y8S6C9LTLxtHtcGyQeGaAh8S5PTWd9VconBL363nQVWYpRsmQXdXowPR3UJ7KpfBtsvn4ynkrcRMZ84y4QaxAxqSziRF8idi1dt6FzoRd6LAHxwGcJhA7ZAT5ATcHSF9tRbyhUXMLbxUUR4ygMQKd2B7odDc45QcGJTiJLBSFrgkLhQNALAP6Dhz6aSmNohd5avRw27Md7a7mve8RACQFwBLokgZJD4","dangerousDek":"","productBrand":"PurpleAir","dangerousHed":"Zen","embedSize":"feature-medium","isFirstProduct":true,"image":{"altText":"Purple Air Zen, a white air quality monitor with glowing green ring light around the edge, sitting outside on a windowsill beside potted plants","credit":"Photograph: Lisa Wood Shapiro","sources":{"sm":{"aspectRatio":"4:3","width":720,"url":"https://media.wired.com/photos/67ec4890bfa28313e182e550/4:3/w_720,c_limit/PurpleAir-Zen-Air-Quality-Monitor-Reviewer-Photo-SOURCE-Kat-Merck.-(no-border).jpg","srcset":"https://media.wired.com/photos/67ec4890bfa28313e182e550/4:3/w_120,c_limit/PurpleAir-Zen-Air-Quality-Monitor-Reviewer-Photo-SOURCE-Kat-Merck.-(no-border).jpg 120w, https://media.wired.com/photos/67ec4890bfa28313e182e550/4:3/w_240,c_limit/PurpleAir-Zen-Air-Quality-Monitor-Reviewer-Photo-SOURCE-Kat-Merck.-(no-border).jpg 240w, https://media.wired.com/photos/67ec4890bfa28313e182e550/4:3/w_320,c_limit/PurpleAir-Zen-Air-Quality-Monitor-Reviewer-Photo-SOURCE-Kat-Merck.-(no-border).jpg 320w, https://media.wired.com/photos/67ec4890bfa28313e182e550/4:3/w_640,c_limit/PurpleAir-Zen-Air-Quality-Monitor-Reviewer-Photo-SOURCE-Kat-Merck.-(no-border).jpg 640w"},"md":{"aspectRatio":"4:3","width":720,"url":"https://media.wired.com/photos/67ec4890bfa28313e182e550/4:3/w_720,c_limit/PurpleAir-Zen-Air-Quality-Monitor-Reviewer-Photo-SOURCE-Kat-Merck.-(no-border).jpg","srcset":"https://media.wired.com/photos/67ec4890bfa28313e182e550/4:3/w_120,c_limit/PurpleAir-Zen-Air-Quality-Monitor-Reviewer-Photo-SOURCE-Kat-Merck.-(no-border).jpg 120w, https://media.wired.com/photos/67ec4890bfa28313e182e550/4:3/w_240,c_limit/PurpleAir-Zen-Air-Quality-Monitor-Reviewer-Photo-SOURCE-Kat-Merck.-(no-border).jpg 240w, https://media.wired.com/photos/67ec4890bfa28313e182e550/4:3/w_320,c_limit/PurpleAir-Zen-Air-Quality-Monitor-Reviewer-Photo-SOURCE-Kat-Merck.-(no-border).jpg 320w, https://media.wired.com/photos/67ec4890bfa28313e182e550/4:3/w_640,c_limit/PurpleAir-Zen-Air-Quality-Monitor-Reviewer-Photo-SOURCE-Kat-Merck.-(no-border).jpg 640w"},"lg":{"aspectRatio":"4:3","width":748,"url":"https://media.wired.com/photos/67ec4890bfa28313e182e550/4:3/w_748,c_limit/PurpleAir-Zen-Air-Quality-Monitor-Reviewer-Photo-SOURCE-Kat-Merck.-(no-border).jpg","srcset":"https://media.wired.com/photos/67ec4890bfa28313e182e550/4:3/w_120,c_limit/PurpleAir-Zen-Air-Quality-Monitor-Reviewer-Photo-SOURCE-Kat-Merck.-(no-border).jpg 120w, https://media.wired.com/photos/67ec4890bfa28313e182e550/4:3/w_240,c_limit/PurpleAir-Zen-Air-Quality-Monitor-Reviewer-Photo-SOURCE-Kat-Merck.-(no-border).jpg 240w, https://media.wired.com/photos/67ec4890bfa28313e182e550/4:3/w_320,c_limit/PurpleAir-Zen-Air-Quality-Monitor-Reviewer-Photo-SOURCE-Kat-Merck.-(no-border).jpg 320w, https://media.wired.com/photos/67ec4890bfa28313e182e550/4:3/w_640,c_limit/PurpleAir-Zen-Air-Quality-Monitor-Reviewer-Photo-SOURCE-Kat-Merck.-(no-border).jpg 640w"},"xl":{"aspectRatio":"4:3","width":748,"url":"https://media.wired.com/photos/67ec4890bfa28313e182e550/4:3/w_748,c_limit/PurpleAir-Zen-Air-Quality-Monitor-Reviewer-Photo-SOURCE-Kat-Merck.-(no-border).jpg","srcset":"https://media.wired.com/photos/67ec4890bfa28313e182e550/4:3/w_120,c_limit/PurpleAir-Zen-Air-Quality-Monitor-Reviewer-Photo-SOURCE-Kat-Merck.-(no-border).jpg 120w, https://media.wired.com/photos/67ec4890bfa28313e182e550/4:3/w_240,c_limit/PurpleAir-Zen-Air-Quality-Monitor-Reviewer-Photo-SOURCE-Kat-Merck.-(no-border).jpg 240w, https://media.wired.com/photos/67ec4890bfa28313e182e550/4:3/w_320,c_limit/PurpleAir-Zen-Air-Quality-Monitor-Reviewer-Photo-SOURCE-Kat-Merck.-(no-border).jpg 320w, https://media.wired.com/photos/67ec4890bfa28313e182e550/4:3/w_640,c_limit/PurpleAir-Zen-Air-Quality-Monitor-Reviewer-Photo-SOURCE-Kat-Merck.-(no-border).jpg 640w"}}},"isSponsored":false,"offerRetailer":"Purpleair","offerUrl":"https://www2.purpleair.com/products/purpleair-zen","contentType":"product","productId":"677fe3511de8aa366d74938b","showOfferUrl":false,"showPriceOnButton":true,"showAffiliateDisclaimerOnFirstProduct":false,"dangerousCredit":"Photograph: Lisa Wood Shapiro","showLocalisedOffers":true,"isUpcEnabled":true,"showClampedProductDescription":true,"productDescriptionLineLength":5,"hasReadMoreFeature":false,"index":1,"hasAffiliateLinkDisabled":false,"isMobileView":false,"hasMultipleImageSupport":true,"showImageCreditText":true,"showMultipleImageCount":4,"hasProsConsFeature":false,"hasRatingFeature":false,"pros":[],"cons":[],"rating":"","shouldUseAmazonPrimeDayLiveAPIData":true,"id":"677fe3511de8aa366d74938b","brand":{"name":"PurpleAir"},"offers":[{"offerUrl":"https://www2.purpleair.com/products/purpleair-zen","price":"$299","currency":"USD","purchaseUri":"https://cna.st/p/8uvTiuNRgn5tyRjNWiSy546tbR1Y8S6C9LTLxtHtcGyQeGaAh8S5PTWd9VconBL363nQVWYpRsmQXdXowPR3UJ7KpfBtsvn4ynkrcRMZ84y4QaxAxqSziRF8idi1dt6FzoRd6LAHxwGcJhA7ZAT5ATcHSF9tRbyhUXMLbxUUR4ygMQKd2B7odDc45QcGJTiJLBSFrgkLhQNALAP6Dhz6aSmNohd5avRw27Md7a7mve8RACQFwBLokgZJD4","sellerName":"Purpleair","countryCode":"US","offerId":"677fe39418f35ad1547d9525","reducedPrice":""}],"component":"unified_product_card","total_index":1,"hasMultipleImage":false,"componentType":true,"showProsConsData":false,"videoIds":[],"offersLength":1}'&gt;&lt;div id="677fe3511de8aa366d74938b" class="UnifiedLandscapeProductCardWrapper-lpCYz hyRKMF"&gt;&lt;div class="UnifiedProductCardContainer-jfmyrc hJJXyx"&gt;&lt;div class="upcSingleImageWrapper-bMOWWA jGaikA"&gt;&lt;p class="UnifiedProductCardImageCreditText-IXcDI cYcQnj"&gt;Photograph: Lisa Wood Shapiro&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;Back in January, I woke up to find my PurpleAir Zen outdoor air quality monitor glowing bright red. This happened over several days, and I was confused because the numbers were well over 100 and yet there wasn’t an air quality alert for the area.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;The annual AQI for my &lt;a href="https://a816-dohbesp.nyc.gov/IndicatorPublic/data-explorer/air-quality/?id=2023#display=map"&gt;neighborhood&lt;/a&gt; is under 50—considered good air. For context, an AQI of 100 or more is unhealthy for sensitive groups, and an AQI of 150 is unhealthy for everyone. I mentioned the unhealthy air to a friend who reminded me that New York City recently installed a &lt;a data-offer-url="https://www.cbsnews.com/newyork/news/brooklyn-concrete-recycling-plant-dust-noise/" class="external-link" data-event-click='{"element":"ExternalLink","outgoingURL":"https://www.cbsnews.com/newyork/news/brooklyn-concrete-recycling-plant-dust-noise/"}' href="https://www.cbsnews.com/newyork/news/brooklyn-concrete-recycling-plant-dust-noise/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;concrete recycling center&lt;/a&gt; a few blocks from my home. The literal &lt;a href="https://council.nyc.gov/shahana-hanif/2025/01/20/columbia-street-waterfront-residents-demand-city-shut-down-concrete-recycling-facility-over-dust-health-concerns/"&gt;dust-up&lt;/a&gt; the center caused, including failure to inform the neighborhood about its existence, might be the culprit for the recent uptick in bad air, from the &lt;a data-offer-url="https://www.osha.gov/sites/default/files/publications/3221_Concrete.pdf" class="external-link" data-event-click='{"element":"ExternalLink","outgoingURL":"https://www.osha.gov/sites/default/files/publications/3221_Concrete.pdf"}' href="https://www.osha.gov/sites/default/files/publications/3221_Concrete.pdf" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;concrete dust&lt;/a&gt; created by the recycling center. At that point the recycling center had yet to implement irrigation to mitigate the dust plumes. The data from my outdoor monitor fed into PurpleAir’s crowdsourced real-time &lt;a data-offer-url="https://map.purpleair.com/air-quality-who-aqg?opt=%2F1%2Flp%2Fa10%2Fp600%2FcC0#7.53/44.244/-69.173" class="external-link" data-event-click='{"element":"ExternalLink","outgoingURL":"https://map.purpleair.com/air-quality-who-aqg?opt=%2F1%2Flp%2Fa10%2Fp600%2FcC0#7.53/44.244/-69.173"}' href="https://map.purpleair.com/air-quality-who-aqg?opt=%2F1%2Flp%2Fa10%2Fp600%2FcC0#7.53/44.244/-69.173" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;map&lt;/a&gt;. On the map, I could see other nearby PurpleAir monitors, and the ones closest to the concrete recycling center tended to have worse air quality.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="paywall"&gt;Invisible Danger&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;In July, after a year of mounting protests and political pressure, the city announced that it would &lt;a data-offer-url="https://www.newsbreak.com/news-12-1587832/4108408236611-cobble-hill-residents-breathe-a-sigh-of-relief-after-city-announces-closure-of-concrete-recycling-plant" class="external-link" data-event-click='{"element":"ExternalLink","outgoingURL":"https://www.newsbreak.com/news-12-1587832/4108408236611-cobble-hill-residents-breathe-a-sigh-of-relief-after-city-announces-closure-of-concrete-recycling-plant"}' href="https://www.newsbreak.com/news-12-1587832/4108408236611-cobble-hill-residents-breathe-a-sigh-of-relief-after-city-announces-closure-of-concrete-recycling-plant" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;relocate&lt;/a&gt; the concrete recycling center. What would have happened if residents hadn’t seen the dust clouds or noticed the gray film collecting on their cars? What if they couldn’t see what was all around them? &lt;a href="https://www.epa.gov/pm-pollution/particulate-matter-pm-basics#PM" target="_blank"&gt;PM 2.5&lt;/a&gt; is the invisible solids and liquids that are in the air. The tiniest form can enter the deepest parts of the lungs, passing into the bloodstream. There, they can cause a host of &lt;a href="https://www.epa.gov/pm-pollution/health-and-environmental-effects-particulate-matter-pm"&gt;illnesses&lt;/a&gt;, respiratory distress, and &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S0953620513001040"&gt;cardiovascular disease&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-testid="feature-large-callout" class="CalloutFeatureLargeWrapper-cAQNly bLNMaC"&gt;&lt;div class="UnifiedProductCardBody-hIYvDT cYxZHF product-embed" data-item='{"ctaHref":"https://cna.st/p/HqPtkHbE1vfvuLcV8bSv1rMGDSyGBfBPcqG4nui5VQJM63kkiRRJy2gzUdnnvJrEVTe6nUqHZKEQHrzALU2iVw4o9FXV8me7CoGgG8hc51M67AH9vfUoXvmfwqr2RQ4LM8SXAXBTmf2wsBYnHyzUqT5dHCV7nk1rSsHhEv6RViyKAx5M6naKtSx248is9WkYsDGZTsFnDwgfDRhGBisG2mJR7wRRMoxpTXfHbHqTPCT3cF1DxVcKGno87pK8LSgytJbhXYGn1qxpYeRgqbUVAKShveDJWgiCUEF612T2JuWZRLqVt8cByZJcpv","dangerousDek":"","productBrand":"IQAir","dangerousHed":"Outdoor Air Quality Monitor","embedSize":"feature-medium","isFirstProduct":false,"image":{"altText":"Image may contain: Adapter, Electronics, and Furniture","credit":"Photograph: Lisa Wood Shapiro","sources":{"sm":{"aspectRatio":"4:3","width":720,"url":"https://media.wired.com/photos/6876eca84a197ac30b2af8fa/4:3/w_720,c_limit/IQAir%20Air%20Visual-SOURCE-Lisa%20Wood%20Shapiro.png","srcset":"https://media.wired.com/photos/6876eca84a197ac30b2af8fa/4:3/w_120,c_limit/IQAir%20Air%20Visual-SOURCE-Lisa%20Wood%20Shapiro.png 120w, https://media.wired.com/photos/6876eca84a197ac30b2af8fa/4:3/w_240,c_limit/IQAir%20Air%20Visual-SOURCE-Lisa%20Wood%20Shapiro.png 240w, https://media.wired.com/photos/6876eca84a197ac30b2af8fa/4:3/w_320,c_limit/IQAir%20Air%20Visual-SOURCE-Lisa%20Wood%20Shapiro.png 320w, https://media.wired.com/photos/6876eca84a197ac30b2af8fa/4:3/w_640,c_limit/IQAir%20Air%20Visual-SOURCE-Lisa%20Wood%20Shapiro.png 640w"},"md":{"aspectRatio":"4:3","width":720,"url":"https://media.wired.com/photos/6876eca84a197ac30b2af8fa/4:3/w_720,c_limit/IQAir%20Air%20Visual-SOURCE-Lisa%20Wood%20Shapiro.png","srcset":"https://media.wired.com/photos/6876eca84a197ac30b2af8fa/4:3/w_120,c_limit/IQAir%20Air%20Visual-SOURCE-Lisa%20Wood%20Shapiro.png 120w, https://media.wired.com/photos/6876eca84a197ac30b2af8fa/4:3/w_240,c_limit/IQAir%20Air%20Visual-SOURCE-Lisa%20Wood%20Shapiro.png 240w, https://media.wired.com/photos/6876eca84a197ac30b2af8fa/4:3/w_320,c_limit/IQAir%20Air%20Visual-SOURCE-Lisa%20Wood%20Shapiro.png 320w, https://media.wired.com/photos/6876eca84a197ac30b2af8fa/4:3/w_640,c_limit/IQAir%20Air%20Visual-SOURCE-Lisa%20Wood%20Shapiro.png 640w"},"lg":{"aspectRatio":"4:3","width":748,"url":"https://media.wired.com/photos/6876eca84a197ac30b2af8fa/4:3/w_748,c_limit/IQAir%20Air%20Visual-SOURCE-Lisa%20Wood%20Shapiro.png","srcset":"https://media.wired.com/photos/6876eca84a197ac30b2af8fa/4:3/w_120,c_limit/IQAir%20Air%20Visual-SOURCE-Lisa%20Wood%20Shapiro.png 120w, https://media.wired.com/photos/6876eca84a197ac30b2af8fa/4:3/w_240,c_limit/IQAir%20Air%20Visual-SOURCE-Lisa%20Wood%20Shapiro.png 240w, https://media.wired.com/photos/6876eca84a197ac30b2af8fa/4:3/w_320,c_limit/IQAir%20Air%20Visual-SOURCE-Lisa%20Wood%20Shapiro.png 320w, https://media.wired.com/photos/6876eca84a197ac30b2af8fa/4:3/w_640,c_limit/IQAir%20Air%20Visual-SOURCE-Lisa%20Wood%20Shapiro.png 640w"},"xl":{"aspectRatio":"4:3","width":748,"url":"https://media.wired.com/photos/6876eca84a197ac30b2af8fa/4:3/w_748,c_limit/IQAir%20Air%20Visual-SOURCE-Lisa%20Wood%20Shapiro.png","srcset":"https://media.wired.com/photos/6876eca84a197ac30b2af8fa/4:3/w_120,c_limit/IQAir%20Air%20Visual-SOURCE-Lisa%20Wood%20Shapiro.png 120w, https://media.wired.com/photos/6876eca84a197ac30b2af8fa/4:3/w_240,c_limit/IQAir%20Air%20Visual-SOURCE-Lisa%20Wood%20Shapiro.png 240w, https://media.wired.com/photos/6876eca84a197ac30b2af8fa/4:3/w_320,c_limit/IQAir%20Air%20Visual-SOURCE-Lisa%20Wood%20Shapiro.png 320w, https://media.wired.com/photos/6876eca84a197ac30b2af8fa/4:3/w_640,c_limit/IQAir%20Air%20Visual-SOURCE-Lisa%20Wood%20Shapiro.png 640w"}}},"isSponsored":false,"offerRetailer":"Amazon","offerUrl":"https://www.amazon.com/AirVisual-Outdoor-Temperature-Humidity-Pressure/dp/B09H3RXDTZ/ref=sr_1_1?","contentType":"product","productId":"686c29a8f24ef4a6bf8a6fbc","showOfferUrl":false,"showPriceOnButton":true,"showAffiliateDisclaimerOnFirstProduct":false,"dangerousCredit":"Photograph: Lisa Wood Shapiro","showLocalisedOffers":true,"isUpcEnabled":true,"showClampedProductDescription":true,"productDescriptionLineLength":5,"hasReadMoreFeature":false,"index":2,"hasAffiliateLinkDisabled":false,"isMobileView":false,"hasMultipleImageSupport":true,"showImageCreditText":true,"showMultipleImageCount":4,"hasProsConsFeature":false,"hasRatingFeature":false,"pros":[],"cons":[],"rating":"","shouldUseAmazonPrimeDayLiveAPIData":true,"id":"686c29a8f24ef4a6bf8a6fbc","brand":{"name":"IQAir"},"offers":[{"offerUrl":"https://www.amazon.com/AirVisual-Outdoor-Temperature-Humidity-Pressure/dp/B09H3RXDTZ/ref=sr_1_1?","price":"$300","currency":"USD","purchaseUri":"https://cna.st/p/HqPtkHbE1vfvuLcV8bSv1rMGDSyGBfBPcqG4nui5VQJM63kkiRRJy2gzUdnnvJrEVTe6nUqHZKEQHrzALU2iVw4o9FXV8me7CoGgG8hc51M67AH9vfUoXvmfwqr2RQ4LM8SXAXBTmf2wsBYnHyzUqT5dHCV7nk1rSsHhEv6RViyKAx5M6naKtSx248is9WkYsDGZTsFnDwgfDRhGBisG2mJR7wRRMoxpTXfHbHqTPCT3cF1DxVcKGno87pK8LSgytJbhXYGn1qxpYeRgqbUVAKShveDJWgiCUEF612T2JuWZRLqVt8cByZJcpv","sellerName":"Amazon","countryCode":"US","offerId":"686c29d3f6550babcf093aba","reducedPrice":""}],"component":"unified_product_card","total_index":1,"hasMultipleImage":false,"componentType":true,"showProsConsData":false,"videoIds":[],"offersLength":1}'&gt;&lt;div id="686c29a8f24ef4a6bf8a6fbc" class="UnifiedLandscapeProductCardWrapper-lpCYz hyRKMF"&gt;&lt;div class="UnifiedProductCardContainer-jfmyrc hJJXyx"&gt;&lt;div class="upcSingleImageWrapper-bMOWWA jGaikA"&gt;&lt;p class="UnifiedProductCardImageCreditText-IXcDI cYcQnj"&gt;Photograph: Lisa Wood Shapiro&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="UnifiedProductCardDetailsContainer-jzIVFy dEeeEw"&gt;&lt;div class="UnifiedProductCardDetailsWrapper-ieavYi jwXcRS"&gt;&lt;div class="UnifiedProductCardDetails-dTZxUl hEAQFX"&gt;&lt;p class="BaseWrap-sc-gzmcOU BaseText-eqOrNE UnifiedProductCardBrandName-kmvqXz deqABF fmYMxY jpHfSL upc-brandName"&gt;IQAir&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="BaseWrap-sc-gzmcOU BaseText-eqOrNE UnifiedProductCardNameWrapper-fsdgKv deqABF eCPEdo izjkDw"&gt;&lt;h3 id="upc_686c29a8f24ef4a6bf8a6fbc" type="embed" class="BaseWrap-sc-gzmcOU BaseText-eqOrNE UnifiedProductCardName-jDmuEE deqABF ctbzXQ hdWBHD"&gt;Outdoor Air Quality Monitor&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;In early 2024, the Biden administration strengthened the National Ambient Air Quality Health Standards (NAAQS) for particulate matter, a move that set “the level of the primary (health-based) annual PM 2.5 standard at 9.0 micrograms per cubic meter (µg/m&lt;sup&gt;3&lt;/sup&gt;) to reflect new science on harms caused by particle pollution.” This changed the window of what is considered “good” air on the &lt;a data-offer-url="https://www.airnow.gov/aqi/aqi-basics/" class="external-link" data-event-click='{"element":"ExternalLink","outgoingURL":"https://www.airnow.gov/aqi/aqi-basics/"}' href="https://www.airnow.gov/aqi/aqi-basics/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Air Quality Index&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;Those EPA guidelines are almost double those of the World Health Organization &lt;a href="https://www.who.int/news-room/feature-stories/detail/what-are-the-who-air-quality-guidelines"&gt;guidelines&lt;/a&gt;, which are a stricter 5 PM 2.5. &lt;a href="https://www.epa.gov/newsreleases/trump-epa-announces-path-forward-national-air-quality-standards-particulate-matter#:~:text=Particulate%20Matter%20(PM2.-,5)%20to%20Aid%20Manufacturing%2C%20Small%20Businesses,tape%20holding%20back%20American%20exceptionalism."&gt;Trump’s EPA&lt;/a&gt; is reconsidering the Biden administration's PM 2.5 standards. To quote EPA administrator Zeldin, “All Americans deserve to breathe clean air while pursuing the American dream. Under President Trump, we will ensure air quality standards for particulate matter are protective of human health and the environment while we unleash the Golden Age of American prosperity.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;The Trump administration also wants to &lt;a data-offer-url="https://www.regulations.gov/document/EPA-HQ-OAR-2025-0124-0001" class="external-link" data-event-click='{"element":"ExternalLink","outgoingURL":"https://www.regulations.gov/document/EPA-HQ-OAR-2025-0124-0001"}' href="https://www.regulations.gov/document/EPA-HQ-OAR-2025-0124-0001" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;repeal greenhouse gas emissions&lt;/a&gt; regulations. According to a statement from the EPA, “The EPA is further proposing to make a finding that GHG emissions from fossil fuel-fired power plants do not contribute significantly to dangerous air pollution.” &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/B9780128229286000095"&gt;Scientific research&lt;/a&gt; states otherwise. And so, as outdoor air becomes less regulated, it has the potential to get dirtier and make &lt;a href="https://ehp.niehs.nih.gov/doi/full/10.1289/ehp.1509676"&gt;people sick&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="paywall"&gt;Too Close to Home&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;This past spring, the smell of campfire filled my home. I peered out my fourth-floor window to see my neighbor’s illegal fire pit three backyards over. I watched the colors on my PurpleAir Zen outdoor monitor change from green to yellow to crimson over the course of an hour. When I logged onto the crowd-sourced PurpleAir real-time map, I could see that my outdoor air quality was an unhealthy 160 PM 2.5 and that a few blocks away, air quality was good at under 30 PM 2.5. There’s nothing surprising about a fire pit generating air pollution, but I didn’t realize how intense and localized that air pollution could be, even though I was four stories up in a half-a-city-block-sized area. This is air quality on a microscale.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="AssetEmbedWrapper-fkZDUs kHRAYC asset-embed"&gt;&lt;p class="CaptionWrapper-jYrTxZ bkfwbX caption AssetEmbedCaption-fyuOdR eXMqGf asset-embed__caption" data-testid="caption-wrapper"&gt;&lt;span class="BaseWrap-sc-gzmcOU BaseText-eqOrNE CaptionCredit-eowWKH deqABF kpqIso kpuElq caption__credit"&gt;Photograph: Lisa Wood Shapiro&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>WIRED</author><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 12:34:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMifEFVX3lxTFBTM1BobURDOFE4c2VyN2JCV1BMZDBXYnB5YTdkN3JLNUFUYTc4ZW9uREZkTVd5M1E2aXN6UGFnWW8tREM0SzhRMHJYSkFYV1FWYUxBc191SVJ1bEhXSEhGX3VJSmZ4emdpTGRDd0xGWHZFclhhVnp0bFpob3U</guid></item><item><title>一名青少年足球运动员在脑震荡后出现了数月的症状。医生发现了一种罕见的脑部畸形。- CBS新闻</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMikgFBVV95cUxNRHFjWXNlWHhBRkZGUFVneWMxVWp1b3k3UWIwYUdjT1BjQS1xc1RsZHJOUEhwXzdZQm9ET0tYaGtzdXNtajBKR1ZmaUdXa2MySTg1WFBQckF4MV9VY3RwR19TMXF2S3d0ckROWXUzTURVdTdtZWZMQnc1Z3pkbEFuOHBaNWhGeDFvVlpzcVhYY1lSUdIBlwFBVV95cUxPaTZ4ZWU3MlNjZVRqbW1YZUMwNTJRVW45V1JYd0tXMkhZTHVHUF9QT1ZSY3kxeTJzZjIxV3RIWkhvX1BFc1V6OVJWY2FnVXJhYW1rdWFEN0FFM2dMamQwT2FySnRUQmZGMXEwTEx5dEFiNHRlOHpFUmNtbVVTSXhoXzBWNXBqNndaV2xRZ0RsMVp0Zm1HRTFz?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;section class="content__body"&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Logan Coleridge was used to taking hits in football. He'd been playing since he was 6 years old and had sustained several &lt;span class="link"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/news/football-new-helmets-reduce-concussions-cte/" target="_blank" data-invalid-url-rewritten-http=""&gt;concussions&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;. But after a helmet-to-helmet impact during his freshman year of high school in August 2023, he started having debilitating symptoms. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The New Jersey teen said he was very dizzy and had trouble balancing. His memory was "terrible," and he had a "severe" light sensitivity, he said, along with "terrible headaches." Previously a strong student, he now struggled to focus in the classroom and couldn't remember school assignments or what he read in class. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I've got concussions in my past, and it wasn't like a normal one," Logan said. "I knew it was something else." &lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="embed embed--type-image is-image embed--float-none embed--size-medium"&gt;
    
                                    
      &lt;span class="img embed__content"&gt;&lt;img src="https://assets1.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/08/01/9ab1c183-c863-4fef-b720-26be765fafa7/thumbnail/620x728/c69a1b07e8923ab60919a3028363a07e/logan-coleridge-no-9.jpg#" alt="logan-coleridge-no-9.jpg " srcset="https://assets1.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/08/01/9ab1c183-c863-4fef-b720-26be765fafa7/thumbnail/620x728/c69a1b07e8923ab60919a3028363a07e/logan-coleridge-no-9.jpg 1x, https://assets1.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/08/01/9ab1c183-c863-4fef-b720-26be765fafa7/thumbnail/1240x1456/e8bda2ae9f78307dc2d63b942d957ef0/logan-coleridge-no-9.jpg 2x" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;

      
          &lt;figcaption class="embed__caption-container"&gt;
        
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__caption"&gt;Logan Coleridge (#9) on the field.&lt;/span&gt;
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__credit"&gt;
            
                Becky and Barry Coleridge

                          &lt;/span&gt;
              &lt;/figcaption&gt;
      &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;More alarmingly, Logan wasn't getting better. Several months of physical therapy had no effect, said Becky Coleridge, Logan's mom. A neurologist who had been treating Logan since his diagnosis with abdominal migraines the year before prescribed two medications, both of which had negative side effects. An orthopedic doctor suggested looking at his neck. Other practitioners had no answers. Coleridge wanted doctors to prescribe an MRI, but wasn't able to get one. Meanwhile, Logan was missing school almost every week. Over-the-counter medications couldn't dull the headaches, and they were becoming more frequent. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In early spring 2024, Logan was able to see a concussion specialist after a particularly bad headache kept him from going to school. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The first thing he said was 'Nobody's given this kid an MRI?'" Becky Coleridge remembered. The specialist prescribed the scan, as well as an X-ray of Logan's neck. The Coleridges thought the scans might show Logan had an issue with his occipital nerve, which runs from the neck to the scalp. &lt;/p&gt;

    
&lt;p id="mpu-plus-outstream-middle" data-ad="mpu-plus-outstream-middle" class="ad-mpu-plus-outstream-middle ad-wrapper " data-ad-unit='"mpu-plus-outstream-middle"'&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The results were much harder to hear: Logan was diagnosed with an arteriovenous malformation, or AVM. It was a condition that he and his parents had never heard of before. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Everything we read was very scary," Becky Coleridge said. "At that moment, we realized the danger he had been in." &lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="embed embed--type-image is-image embed--float-none embed--size-medium"&gt;
    
                                    
      &lt;span class="img embed__content"&gt;&lt;img src="https://assets3.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/08/01/67a3229a-84a5-4eaa-b0ee-548828a778c3/thumbnail/620x710/4903f4fb42fea400e6e3336bab6777bd/img-8052.jpg#" alt="img-8052.jpg " srcset="https://assets3.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/08/01/67a3229a-84a5-4eaa-b0ee-548828a778c3/thumbnail/620x710/4903f4fb42fea400e6e3336bab6777bd/img-8052.jpg 1x, https://assets1.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/08/01/67a3229a-84a5-4eaa-b0ee-548828a778c3/thumbnail/1240x1420/109ba89cc57b1d6ef0bc305857629a82/img-8052.jpg 2x" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;

      
          &lt;figcaption class="embed__caption-container"&gt;
        
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__caption"&gt;The Coleridge family. &lt;/span&gt;
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__credit"&gt;
            
                Becky and Barry Coleridge

                          &lt;/span&gt;
              &lt;/figcaption&gt;
      &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;What is an arteriovenous malformation? &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;An AVM is an abnormal tangle of blood vessels in the brain, said Dr. Andrew Russman, head of the Cleveland Clinic's stroke program, who was not involved in Logan's care. AVMs put "a lot of pressure on the vein side" and can produce a variety of symptoms, he said. The biggest risk with an AVM is rupture, where the vessels burst and cause bleeding in the brain. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a case like Logan's, where the AVM hasn't ruptured, there can still be symptoms. Those symptoms can affect a person's motor skills, sensory and visual perception, language abilities and the way they walk, Russman said. The effects can vary depending on where in the brain the AVM has formed, Russman said. &lt;/p&gt;

    
    
&lt;p id="leader-plus-inc3" data-ad="leader-plus-inc" class="ad-leader-plus-inc ad-wrapper " data-ad-unit='["leader-plus-inc",3]'&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Coleridges had two options to treat Logan: Radiation therapy, a non-invasive technique that uses focused radiation beams to target and slowly destroy the AVM, or surgery. Radiation therapy could take too long, the family decided, and so they decided to have Logan treated by Dr. Howard Riina, a cerebrovascular neurosurgeon at NYU Langone. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="embed embed--type-image is-image embed--float-none embed--size-medium"&gt;
    
                                    
      &lt;span class="img embed__content"&gt;&lt;img src="https://assets1.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/08/01/2484440c-a91b-4cd3-8b65-e7bad875203c/thumbnail/620x629/05b2f3ec7decbc75791a5259d415896b/logan-coleridge-avm.jpg#" alt="logan-coleridge-avm.jpg " class=" lazyload" srcset="https://assets1.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/08/01/2484440c-a91b-4cd3-8b65-e7bad875203c/thumbnail/620x629/05b2f3ec7decbc75791a5259d415896b/logan-coleridge-avm.jpg 1x, https://assets2.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/08/01/2484440c-a91b-4cd3-8b65-e7bad875203c/thumbnail/1240x1258/c5f2db71a5fca39862dd28f04a104bf4/logan-coleridge-avm.jpg 2x" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;

      
          &lt;figcaption class="embed__caption-container"&gt;
        
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__caption"&gt;Logan Coleridge's AVM.&lt;/span&gt;
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__credit"&gt;
            
                Becky and Barry Coleridge / NYU Langone

                          &lt;/span&gt;
              &lt;/figcaption&gt;
      &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"He couldn't go to school. His whole life was impacted by these headaches," Riina said. "They wanted an immediate solution." &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Riina said the AVM, which was on a "headache spot" in the occipital region of the brain, was likely the root of Logan's symptoms. People are born with AVMs, Riina said, and they grow as the body grows, which can cause increased symptoms. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Obviously, you don't want to have multiple things going on in your head, but the concussion is what led to the imaging, which led to the diagnosis of the AVM, which was probably what was causing the headaches all along," he said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Raising awareness and "focusing on a new beginning" &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Logan underwent surgery on July 17, 2024, nearly a year after his symptoms began. Riina performed a craniotomy and removed the AVM. Three days later, Logan was discharged from the hospital to continue his recovery at home. Logan said it was a "lonely" way to spend his summer vacation. Even as his recovery progressed, he couldn't participate in the sports he loved. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I couldn't really do the things that I love normally doing, like exercising, playing football was a big thing for me. I was just stuck in bed, pretty much having minimal activity," Logan said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="embed embed--type-image is-image embed--float-none embed--size-medium"&gt;
    
                                    
      &lt;span class="img embed__content"&gt;&lt;img src="https://assets3.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/08/01/d487edeb-98dc-4ba1-86b0-b75d840396b9/thumbnail/620x725/255c0ebc497ada6dad8cc71e6fd24dfe/logan-coleridge-recovering-in-kimmel.jpg#" alt="logan-coleridge-recovering-in-kimmel.jpg " srcset="https://assets3.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/08/01/d487edeb-98dc-4ba1-86b0-b75d840396b9/thumbnail/620x725/255c0ebc497ada6dad8cc71e6fd24dfe/logan-coleridge-recovering-in-kimmel.jpg 1x, https://assets1.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/08/01/d487edeb-98dc-4ba1-86b0-b75d840396b9/thumbnail/1240x1450/f2a657243d12b0d1734c29b52bfd03c5/logan-coleridge-recovering-in-kimmel.jpg 2x" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;

      
          &lt;figcaption class="embed__caption-container"&gt;
        
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__caption"&gt;Logan Coleridge recovering at NYU Langone after surgery.&lt;/span&gt;
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__credit"&gt;
            
                Becky and Barry Coleridge

                          &lt;/span&gt;
              &lt;/figcaption&gt;
      &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now, Logan has only the occasional headache, and the pain can be treated with medication. He has follow-ups at NYU Langone, but Riina said everything has come back clear. The Coleridges are working to encourage early testing: Becky Coleridge said she wishes Logan had received an MRI earlier so that months of suffering and confusion could have been avoided. &lt;/p&gt;

    
    
&lt;p id="leader-plus-inc4" data-ad="leader-plus-inc" class="ad-leader-plus-inc ad-wrapper " data-ad-unit='["leader-plus-inc",4]'&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This year has been a complete turnaround, Logan said. He no longer misses school. He celebrated his 16th birthday and took driving lessons. This summer, he spent almost every day at the beach with friends. This month, he's gearing up for a return to the football field. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The whole experience was a fork in the road for me that I had to get through," Logan said. "I'm leaving that time in my life in the past and focusing on a new beginning." &lt;/p&gt;

      

                    
        
      
                  
    

    


    
      
    
  

          
  
        
      &lt;div class="content-author"&gt;
      &lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/team/kerry-breen/" class="content-author__name" data-invalid-url-rewritten-http=""&gt;Kerry  Breen&lt;/a&gt;

      &lt;div class="content-author__bio"&gt;
        &lt;div class="content-author__full-information"&gt;
          &lt;p class="content-author__text"&gt;Kerry Breen is a news editor at CBSNews.com. A graduate of New York University's Arthur L. Carter School of Journalism, she previously worked at NBC News' TODAY Digital. She covers current events, breaking news and issues including substance use.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
        &lt;/section&gt;

  
  

  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>CBS News</author><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 12:00:01 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikgFBVV95cUxNRHFjWXNlWHhBRkZGUFVneWMxVWp1b3k3UWIwYUdjT1BjQS1xc1RsZHJOUEhwXzdZQm9ET0tYaGtzdXNtajBKR1ZmaUdXa2MySTg1WFBQckF4MV9VY3RwR19TMXF2S3d0ckROWXUzTURVdTdtZWZMQnc1Z3pkbEFuOHBaNWhGeDFvVlpzcVhYY1lSUdIBlwFBVV95cUxPaTZ4ZWU3MlNjZVRqbW1YZUMwNTJRVW45V1JYd0tXMkhZTHVHUF9QT1ZSY3kxeTJzZjIxV3RIWkhvX1BFc1V6OVJWY2FnVXJhYW1rdWFEN0FFM2dMamQwT2FySnRUQmZGMXEwTEx5dEFiNHRlOHpFUmNtbVVTSXhoXzBWNXBqNndaV2xRZ0RsMVp0Zm1HRTFz</guid></item><item><title>青少年的头痛并没有消失。医生发现了一个令人惊讶的原因- yahoo.com</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMijAFBVV95cUxNM2JHWmZzeTdjUkJ2TmptVC1OMVpZcEp2X0ZKc0pQME1qZ2NKNFN6MzRqeE9lRXVqaEtfZm5YWTJXaDFNclJNQUZZRFZRTVdIU0xJV0dZNTAwcGlXcHh6V0drMkUyNmVtLVpMcEdyQnYwamFsQm9jWXh6ZFQ1Y29ISHpEYXpWSWd6OWtEaw?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="" data-article-body="true"&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Logan Coleridge was used to taking hits in football. He'd been playing since he was 6 years old and had sustained several &lt;span class="link"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/news/football-new-helmets-reduce-concussions-cte/?ftag=YHF4eb9d17" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:concussions;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;concussions&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;. But after a helmet-to-helmet impact during his freshman year of high school in August 2023, he started having debilitating symptoms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The New Jersey teen said he was very dizzy and had trouble balancing. His memory was "terrible," and he had a "severe" light sensitivity, he said, along with "terrible headaches." Previously a strong student, he now struggled to focus in the classroom and couldn't remember school assignments or what he read in class.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;"I've got concussions in my past, and it wasn't like a normal one," Logan said. "I knew it was something else."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="relative mb-4"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="relative text-sm mt-1 pr-2.5"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Logan Coleridge (#9) on the field. / Credit: Becky and Barry Coleridge&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;More alarmingly, Logan wasn't getting better. Several months of physical therapy had no effect, said Becky Coleridge, Logan's mom. A neurologist who had been treating Logan since his diagnosis with abdominal migraines the year before prescribed two medications, both of which had negative side effects. An orthopedic doctor suggested looking at his neck. Other practitioners had no answers. Coleridge wanted doctors to prescribe an MRI, but wasn't able to get one. Meanwhile, Logan was missing school almost every week. Over-the-counter medications couldn't dull the headaches, and they were becoming more frequent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;In early spring 2024, Logan was able to see a concussion specialist after a particularly bad headache kept him from going to school.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;"The first thing he said was 'Nobody's given this kid an MRI?'" Becky Coleridge remembered. The specialist prescribed the scan, as well as an X-ray of Logan's neck. The Coleridges thought the scans might show Logan had an issue with his occipital nerve, which runs from the neck to the scalp.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The results were much harder to hear: Logan was diagnosed with an arteriovenous malformation, or AVM. It was a condition that he and his parents had never heard of before.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;"Everything we read was very scary," Becky Coleridge said. "At that moment, we realized the danger he had been in."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="relative mb-4"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="relative text-sm mt-1 pr-2.5"&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Coleridge family. / Credit: Becky and Barry Coleridge&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;What is an arteriovenous malformation?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;An AVM is an abnormal tangle of blood vessels in the brain, said Dr. Andrew Russman, head of the Cleveland Clinic's stroke program, who was not involved in Logan's care. AVMs put "a lot of pressure on the vein side" and can produce a variety of symptoms, he said. The biggest risk with an AVM is rupture, where the vessels burst and cause bleeding in the brain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;In a case like Logan's, where the AVM hasn't ruptured, there can still be symptoms. Those symptoms can affect a person's motor skills, sensory and visual perception, language abilities and the way they walk, Russman said. The effects can vary depending on where in the brain the AVM has formed, Russman said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The Coleridges had two options to treat Logan: Radiation therapy, a non-invasive technique that uses focused radiation beams to target and slowly destroy the AVM, or surgery. Radiation therapy could take too long, the family decided, and so they decided to have Logan treated by Dr. Howard Riina, a cerebrovascular neurosurgeon at NYU Langone.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="relative mb-4"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="relative text-sm mt-1 pr-2.5"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Logan Coleridge's AVM. / Credit: Becky and Barry Coleridge / NYU Langone&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;"He couldn't go to school. His whole life was impacted by these headaches," Riina said. "They wanted an immediate solution."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Riina said the AVM, which was on a "headache spot" in the occipital region of the brain, was likely the root of Logan's symptoms. People are born with AVMs, Riina said, and they grow as the body grows, which can cause increased symptoms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;"Obviously, you don't want to have multiple things going on in your head, but the concussion is what led to the imaging, which led to the diagnosis of the AVM, which was probably what was causing the headaches all along," he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Raising awareness and "focusing on a new beginning"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Logan underwent surgery on July 17, 2024, nearly a year after his symptoms began. Riina performed a craniotomy and removed the AVM. Three days later, Logan was discharged from the hospital to continue his recovery at home. Logan said it was a "lonely" way to spend his summer vacation. Even as his recovery progressed, he couldn't participate in the sports he loved.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;"I couldn't really do the things that I love normally doing, like exercising, playing football was a big thing for me. I was just stuck in bed, pretty much having minimal activity," Logan said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="relative mb-4"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="relative text-sm mt-1 pr-2.5"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Logan Coleridge recovering at NYU Langone after surgery. / Credit: Becky and Barry Coleridge&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Now, Logan has only the occasional headache, and the pain can be treated with medication. He has follow-ups at NYU Langone, but Riina said everything has come back clear. The Coleridges are working to encourage early testing: Becky Coleridge said she wishes Logan had received an MRI earlier so that months of suffering and confusion could have been avoided.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;This year has been a complete turnaround, Logan said. He no longer misses school. He celebrated his 16th birthday and took driving lessons. This summer, he spent almost every day at the beach with friends. This month, he's gearing up for a return to the football field.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;"The whole experience was a fork in the road for me that I had to get through," Logan said. "I'm leaving that time in my life in the past and focusing on a new beginning."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/video/israels-security-cabinet-approves-plan-to-take-over-gaza-city-1/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Israel's Security Cabinet approves plan to take over Gaza City;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Israel's Security Cabinet approves plan to take over Gaza City&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/video/mlb-first-woman-umpires-regular-season-game/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:In an MLB first, woman umpires regular-season game;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;In an MLB first, woman umpires regular-season game&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/video/2-year-old-hairless-french-bulldog-mix-wins-ugliest-dog-contest/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:2-year-old hairless French bulldog mix wins ugliest dog contest;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;2-year-old hairless French bulldog mix wins ugliest dog contest&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>yahoo.com</author><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 12:00:01 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijAFBVV95cUxNM2JHWmZzeTdjUkJ2TmptVC1OMVpZcEp2X0ZKc0pQME1qZ2NKNFN6MzRqeE9lRXVqaEtfZm5YWTJXaDFNclJNQUZZRFZRTVdIU0xJV0dZNTAwcGlXcHh6V0drMkUyNmVtLVpMcEdyQnYwamFsQm9jWXh6ZFQ1Y29ISHpEYXpWSWd6OWtEaw</guid></item><item><title>家长建议：我找到了爸爸的Reddit账号。我希望我从来没有读过它。- Slate Magazine</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiggFBVV95cUxQZWZLamJjbE9FREFqNkhENERNWVN2N2ZxQ1hodVc0Nk9vZXdpamRPVHppR0tnbG5mZlgybGM0czNwOFpHdXBrRUY3em8tS0Y0bXYyWmwxRTlKVGU5SnpORHg5YmJsWS14LUNJRGxwOEMwUEgtZ2hJbnY4WENHUDVLcE53?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article__content" itemprop="mainEntityOfPage"&gt;
          &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="16" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cme3bjb14000owtm74fbsl4zx@published"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Care and Feeding is Slate’s parenting advice column. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Have a question for Care and Feeding? &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://forms.gle/4BXEw8Wtcd7aAyXh9"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Submit it here&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="4" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cme3bm709003m3b79i92iz2jh@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dear Care and Feeding,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="72" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cme3bky1v00123b79nm86xv6o@published"&gt;I’m a 15-year-old girl, the older of two siblings. I was using the family computer and wanted to check my Reddit, and that’s when I found out that Dad has a Reddit account too. I didn’t snoop then, but I did write down his account name and then checked it out on my phone later.&lt;br&gt;I shouldn’t have done that. I should have realized it was private because he had never mentioned it.&lt;/p&gt;



  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="107" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cme3bl3t000183b79ajj2ip3a@published"&gt;A lot of his posts were heavy. They consisted of complaints about his life, how he resents his family, and then feels guilty about feeling so resentful. How he can’t stand Mom anymore but thinks it’s important to put up a good front for us kids, and how he wishes just once his kids would come to him with something other than a problem we expected him to solve. He said some nasty things specifically about me, too, about some personal incidents I don’t want to share here, but that I had shrugged off as just normal interactions—I hadn’t realized how much I had hurt his feelings.&lt;/p&gt;

  

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="109" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cme3bl661001e3b796kznxyt2@published"&gt;I feel like I’d know the answer to the question of what to do about this (NOTHING) if that was all there was to it. It wasn’t meant for my eyes, I know. But the thing is, there’s also this undercurrent about how terrible he feels for having these thoughts and feelings and how he needs to “stay strong” for his family. It makes me really uneasy and worried about him. I had no idea he was going through any of this. I feel like I pried open his diary! I don’t know what to do now. Should I just pretend I saw nothing? Or should I tell him?&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="4" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cme3bl8xi001k3b79pfgcfptz@published"&gt;—Really Stepped Into It&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="2" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cme3blets001y3b79wm4s995v@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dear Stepped,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="123" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cme3blgn000253b79eunxdanu@published"&gt;Is there an adult you feel close to, who knows and loves your father—but who is not your mother—with whom you could talk this over? It’s really beyond the scope of what a 15-year-old should be doing for a parent for you to take responsibility for your father’s mental health—and to carry the burden of guilt you now feel for having “snooped.” Of course, if your dad put all of this on Reddit—&lt;em&gt;and&lt;/em&gt; your whole family shares one computer—he had to know, at some level, that someone (if not everyone) in the family would read it. At the very least, he was making his confessions in a public space: Reddit is not a diary, as much as it may sometimes feel like one.&lt;/p&gt;

  


  


  


  


  

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="150" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cme3bliva002c3b79igstsakc@published"&gt;I don’t know why people reveal their most private thoughts to strangers on the internet (this may be a generational blind spot of mine; I am acquainted with a number of 40-somethings who seem to share &lt;em&gt;everything&lt;/em&gt;, no matter how private, on Facebook), but I do know that writing about (what sounds like) one’s depression on a shared computer is a not-so-subtle cry for help from those who have access to it. &lt;em&gt;You&lt;/em&gt; are not the right person to help him, but his best friend or a sibling of his might be. (And for all you know, he is just using Reddit to blow off steam. Some of those 40-somethings I mentioned definitely use Facebook that way. I read their posts and become alarmed—then learn that they’re just fine, really; they were just having “a dramatic moment.” Again, I’ll acknowledge that this mystifies me. But it is apparently a thing.)&lt;/p&gt;

  


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="46" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cme3blld9002j3b791t2xtql2@published"&gt;In the meantime, can you make every effort to be kind to your dad? You might even approach him with something other than a problem for him to solve. It won’t fix him—as I say, it’s not for you to fix him—but it certainly couldn’t hurt.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="1" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cme3bln64002q3b79y13rv8i5@published"&gt;&lt;span class="slate-paragraph--tombstone"&gt;—Michelle&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  


  &lt;h3 class="subhead subhead--none" data-uri="slate.com/_components/subhead/instances/cme3blzse003c3b79919stloi@published"&gt;
&lt;p class="subhead__marker"&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
More Advice From Slate

&lt;/h3&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="109" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cme3blx8800343b79f8wj2q12@published"&gt;Up until two weeks ago, my husband “Jeff” (39) was a model family man and father to “Jenny” (8) and “Kyle” (6). About the only problem in our marriage was his insomnia, and while it was difficult to deal with him getting up 5-6 times a night, every night, it was hardly his fault. Still, after over a decade of trying to treat the insomnia with nothing working except for drugs that had side effects worse than the insomnia itself, we eventually decided on adding a bedroom annex to the home office, and Jeff sleeping there instead of with me. &lt;a href="https://slate.com/human-interest/2022/11/insomnia-sleep-apart-marriage.html"&gt;Ever since then, he’s been half-assing as a father.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;section class="newsletter-signup   " data-list="Advice" data-uri="slate.com/_components/newsletter-signup/instances/cme3bjb14000rwtm7zk2fct1u@published"&gt;


    &lt;p class="newsletter-signup__intro"&gt;
        &lt;svg class="newsletter-signup__arrow"&gt;
          &lt;use xlink:href="/media/components/newsletter-signup/sprite.svg#arrow"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;
        &lt;/svg&gt;
&lt;h1 class="newsletter-signup__headline"&gt;Never miss new Advice columns&lt;/h1&gt;
      &lt;span class="newsletter-signup__description"&gt;The latest sex, parenting, and money advice from our columnists delivered to your inbox three times a week.&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;
    



&lt;/section&gt;

  

&lt;/div&gt;

      &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Slate Magazine</author><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiggFBVV95cUxQZWZLamJjbE9FREFqNkhENERNWVN2N2ZxQ1hodVc0Nk9vZXdpamRPVHppR0tnbG5mZlgybGM0czNwOFpHdXBrRUY3em8tS0Y0bXYyWmwxRTlKVGU5SnpORHg5YmJsWS14LUNJRGxwOEMwUEgtZ2hJbnY4WENHUDVLcE53</guid></item><item><title>我每天都吃木犀壳-这是好处- VOGUE</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiYkFVX3lxTE01QkkzME0tRTU4eGt3dGRWclhuQ0lrVlZRaW5fWmdSdXZ1MHBkV19kZVpadnVZMldqVlc2UDVzTWJBZHFFWGQtdlVuQVVNb0tDTjczQXJ3S2lPMVhfZ21obUln?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="body__inner-container"&gt;&lt;p&gt;But the positive effect goes beyond the bowels: psyllium husks could help reduce the risk of diseases such as bowel cancer, &lt;a data-offer-url="https://kjim.org/journal/view.php?doi=10.3904/kjim.2019.049" class="external-link" data-event-click='{"element":"ExternalLink","outgoingURL":"https://kjim.org/journal/view.php?doi=10.3904/kjim.2019.049"}' href="https://kjim.org/journal/view.php?doi=10.3904/kjim.2019.049" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;heart disease&lt;/a&gt;, and type 2 diabetes in the long term because fiber allows sugar from food to be absorbed more slowly into the bloodstream. “If you combine psyllium husks with a protein-rich meal, this can keep blood sugar levels even more stable,” Werner says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;How to eat psyllium husks&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;When it comes to psyllium husks, less is more, especially at the beginning. In fact, Werner often sees her patients make the same mistake time and again—they either take too much at once or don’t drink enough water. “Always work up to it slowly, and take plenty of fluids,” she advises.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To that end, she recommends starting with one small spoonful a day (or less), and then slowly working your way up “day by day, and week by week.” If you notice that you don’t tolerate the psyllium husks well, simply reduce the amount. “One teaspoon to a large glass of water is a good starting point for many people,” she says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That said, Werner does have one caveat—she prefers not to pre-soak her husks, unlike me: “To be honest, I find the goo in water quite disgusting,” she laughs. Instead, she prefers to simply stir the psyllium husks into smoothies, yogurt, or &lt;a href="https://www.vogue.com/article/oatmeal-benefits" target="_blank"&gt;oatmeal&lt;/a&gt;. “I now take one to two teaspoons, sometimes even a tablespoon a day—but I’ve worked my way up to it really slowly,” she say.s&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What to look for when shopping for psyllium husks&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Werner recommends hulled psyllium husks versus whole psyllium seeds. Since they contain just the outer shell of the seed, “they are usually better tolerated and swell up more,” she explains.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She also advises buying organic quality and checking the list of ingredients: “Ideally, they should really only contain psyllium husks—no additives, no flavorings. This is often a good indicator that the products are less contaminated with harmful substances.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Have a beauty or wellness trend you're curious about? We want to know! Send&lt;/em&gt; Vogue'&lt;em&gt;s senior beauty &amp;amp; wellness editor an email at beauty@vogue.com.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Vogue</author><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiYkFVX3lxTE01QkkzME0tRTU4eGt3dGRWclhuQ0lrVlZRaW5fWmdSdXZ1MHBkV19kZVpadnVZMldqVlc2UDVzTWJBZHFFWGQtdlVuQVVNb0tDTjczQXJ3S2lPMVhfZ21obUln</guid></item><item><title>一项新的研究表明，这种令人惊讶的乳制品选择可以支持更健康的衰老-食品和葡萄酒</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMihgFBVV95cUxQbm5GQW9jU2xxdHB1WjhRNlhKTFVHWUxHYmlEWUVLM0ozcGFHNDlxanIyUTh1X3NOZTg4TUpNdzJmUWFZdzRxQXdYYWxJemtjdjUwei1jWGN1SnBvUFo4S28tX1RFd0tBVWhXSmJYSVdJUHowTG9TdnJRZzl1OHhzTlpuSnBQdw?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-page_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-page mntl-block structured-content" data-sc-sticky-offset="90" data-sc-ad-label-height="24" data-sc-ad-track-spacing="100" data-sc-min-track-height="250" data-sc-max-track-height="600" data-sc-breakpoint="50em" data-sc-load-immediate="4" data-sc-content-positions="[1, 1250, 1550, 1950, 2350, 2750, 3150, 3550, 3950]" data-bind-scroll-on-start="true"&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-block_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block foodandwine-sc-block-callout--summary mntl-sc-block-universal-callout--tips mntl-sc-block-universal-callout theme-summary callout--bordered" data-text="Key points" data-tracking-id="mntl-sc-block-callout" data-tracking-container="true"&gt;
&lt;div class="mntl-sc-block-universal-callout__body"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;A new study from researchers in China analyzed the impact of consuming different types of milk on muscle and bone health while aging.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;This study used mice to learn about the relationship between sarcopenia, age-related muscle loss, and four different dairy milks.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Findings revealed that goat milk (in particular low-fat goat milk and low-fat fortified goat milk) was more effective at supporting muscle regeneration and reducing inflammation.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_2-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; If it seems like everyone is going wild for protein these days, you're not imagining things. According to &lt;a href="https://www.cargill.com/2025/consumers-are-seeking-more-protein-for-health-and-taste-in-2025" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Cargill’s 2025 Protein Profile&lt;/a&gt;, 61% of Americans increased their protein intake in 2024. As &lt;a href="https://www.grandviewresearch.com/industry-analysis/protein-fortified-food-products-market-report" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;Grand View Research&lt;/a&gt; noted in its 2025 report, the "global protein-fortified food products market size was estimated at $66.8 billion in 2023 and is projected to reach $101.62 billion by 2030."
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_3-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_4-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; However, according to one new study, you may not need to rely solely on pricey protein-fortified foods and powders to support muscle health. Simply switching up the milk you drink every day could help.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_5-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_6-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; In July, researchers from Peking University and Hyproca Nutrition in China published their findings in the journal &lt;a href="https://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/fsn3.70540" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Food Science &amp;amp; Nutrition&lt;/a&gt;, giving greater insight into four dairy products and whether they have the potential to delay the progression of sarcopenia, or age-related muscle loss. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_7-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_8-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; "Sarcopenia, characterized by progressive loss of muscle mass and strength, poses a significant public health challenge. However, the specific role of dairy products in preventing sarcopenia is not well understood," the scientists shared. Studies like this are key to finding solutions for a problem that many of us may face. As one research overview explained, on average, 5–13% of people between 60 and 70 years of age are affected by &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC3060646/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;sarcopenia&lt;/a&gt;. For people over 80, that increases to 11–50%.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_9-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_10-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block foodandwine-sc-block-embed mntl-sc-block-universal-embed mntl-sc-block-embed--youtube"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_11-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_12-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; To figure out which dairy products can help stave off sarcopenia, the researchers fed dairy-enriched diets to mice for eight weeks. The mice were split into six groups: normal control, sarcopenia, goat whole milk, goat low-fat milk, goat fortified vitamin D, calcium low-fat milk, and bovine (cow) whole milk.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_13-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_14-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; The normal control group was given saline throughout the trial — a salt and water solution that acts as a placebo — while the other five groups received dexamethasone injections to induce sarcopenia. At the same time, four groups were fed the milk in their group name. This means that one group did have induced sarcopenia without receiving a dairy supplement, acting as a sarcopenia control group.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_15-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_16-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; The team then measured the test subjects' grip strength, weight, bone mineral density, &lt;a href="https://my.clevelandclinic.org/health/articles/24058-autophagy" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;autophagy&lt;/a&gt; (the process that allows your body to reuse and recycle damaged cells), muscle morphology (the size and shape of the muscles), metabolism, inflammation, and gut microbial health. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_17-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_19-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_20-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; They found that while all types of milk helped the mice regain muscle mass and bone strength, the fortified low-fat goat’s milk — a version with added vitamin D and calcium — was most effective. As the researchers explained, the goat milk boosted muscle-building signals in the body and lowered levels of key inflammation markers linked to muscle loss. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_21-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_22-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; They also noticed one more critical finding in the gut. All of the dairy-fed mice showed shifts in their microbiome, with increases in the beneficial bacteria Leuconostoc. However, only the goat milk-fed mice showed an increase in Lactococcus and Acinetobacter bacteria, which could help reduce inflammation and support the body's metabolism. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_23-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_24-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Need all of this boiled down to simpler terms?
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_25-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_26-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; "This study demonstrates that different types of dairy products have distinct effects on muscle metabolism, autophagy, inflammation, and gut microbiota in sarcopenia," the authors concluded. "Goat milk, particularly its low-fat and vitamin D/calcium-fortified variants, showed greater benefits in promoting muscle regeneration and reducing inflammation compared to bovine milk, highlighting the importance of dairy composition." 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_27-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_29-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_30-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; It is important to note that many commercial cow milks are fortified with Vitamins A and D, but the researchers do not provide commentary on whether this might come closer to offering the same muscle-regenerating benefits as fortified goat milk.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_31-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_32-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; This study was conducted on mice, so the hypothesis has not been proven with humans. Nevertheless, it's one reason to search for goat milk the next time you're strolling through the grocery store or seek out a farmers market to start chatting with your local goat farmer about a regular supply.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Food &amp; Wine</author><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 11:54:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihgFBVV95cUxQbm5GQW9jU2xxdHB1WjhRNlhKTFVHWUxHYmlEWUVLM0ozcGFHNDlxanIyUTh1X3NOZTg4TUpNdzJmUWFZdzRxQXdYYWxJemtjdjUwei1jWGN1SnBvUFo4S28tX1RFd0tBVWhXSmJYSVdJUHowTG9TdnJRZzl1OHhzTlpuSnBQdw</guid></item></channel></rss>