<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>GNews Health</title><link>https://news.google.com/</link><description></description><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>新的突变型流感毒株会导致严冬吗？ - BBC</title><link>https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/c2dr8gzdz1wo</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article&gt;&lt;p data-component="headline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 hNbOGD"&gt;&lt;h1 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 idLnWK"&gt;Experts say this could be the worst flu season for a decade - here's why&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="byline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="byline-new" class="sc-7bfdb3c2-0 fYJjWP"&gt;&lt;span data-testid="byline-new-contributors" class="sc-7bfdb3c2-11 ljQVMv"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="byline-new-contributors-contributor-0" class="sc-7bfdb3c2-5 xGeVU"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="sc-7bfdb3c2-7 djOqvY"&gt;James Gallagher&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-testid="byline-new-contributors-contributor-0-role-location" class="sc-7bfdb3c2-8 gvcwmG"&gt;Health and science correspondent&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 eRlINq"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="hero-image" class="sc-5340b511-1 cMIbKV"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20251105-121702-1a3e907763-web-2.33.1-3/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 gUePlo hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/d4a5/live/2d103130-bc8a-11f0-8d15-f555245abf51.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/d4a5/live/2d103130-bc8a-11f0-8d15-f555245abf51.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/d4a5/live/2d103130-bc8a-11f0-8d15-f555245abf51.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/d4a5/live/2d103130-bc8a-11f0-8d15-f555245abf51.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/d4a5/live/2d103130-bc8a-11f0-8d15-f555245abf51.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/d4a5/live/2d103130-bc8a-11f0-8d15-f555245abf51.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/d4a5/live/2d103130-bc8a-11f0-8d15-f555245abf51.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/d4a5/live/2d103130-bc8a-11f0-8d15-f555245abf51.jpg.webp" loading="eager" alt="Getty Images A woman blowing her nose and sneezing into a handkerchief during a rainy autumn day. She is wearing a yellow rain coat and a red umbrella " class="sc-5340b511-0 hLdNfA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 jVqbAn"&gt;Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Flu strikes every winter, but something seems to be different this year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;A seasonal flu virus suddenly mutated in the summer; it appears to evade some of our immunity; has kick-started a flu season more than a month early and is a type of flu that history suggests is more severe.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The NHS has now issued a "flu jab SOS" as fears grow that this will add up to a brutal winter.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;There is a lot of nuance and uncertainty, but leading flu experts have told me they would not be shocked if this was the worst flu season for a decade.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"We haven't seen a virus like this for a while, these dynamics are unusual," says Prof Nicola Lewis, the director of the World Influenza Centre at the Francis Crick Institute.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"It does concern me, absolutely," she says. "I'm not panicking, but I am worried." &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;So what's going on? And what can we do?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Scientists track the evolution of influenza viruses because they mutate constantly and the seasonal flu vaccine has to be updated each year to keep up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;This evolution happens in a rhythm known as "shift and drift". &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Most of the time the virus drifts along making minor changes and then every so often there is a sudden abrupt shift as the virus mutates substantially.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;That happened in June this year. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Seven mutations appeared in a strain of H3N2 seasonal flu and led to a "fast increase" in reports of the mutated virus, says Prof Derek Smith, the director of the centre for pathogen evolution at the University of Cambridge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 gXrNRM"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 cMIbKV"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20251105-121702-1a3e907763-web-2.33.1-3/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 gUePlo hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/37d7/live/5d4b63f0-bbd7-11f0-bd4a-49c00e3ca628.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/37d7/live/5d4b63f0-bbd7-11f0-bd4a-49c00e3ca628.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/37d7/live/5d4b63f0-bbd7-11f0-bd4a-49c00e3ca628.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/37d7/live/5d4b63f0-bbd7-11f0-bd4a-49c00e3ca628.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/37d7/live/5d4b63f0-bbd7-11f0-bd4a-49c00e3ca628.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/37d7/live/5d4b63f0-bbd7-11f0-bd4a-49c00e3ca628.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/37d7/live/5d4b63f0-bbd7-11f0-bd4a-49c00e3ca628.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/37d7/live/5d4b63f0-bbd7-11f0-bd4a-49c00e3ca628.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Getty Images 3D illustration showing spherical object representing the virus. It is covered in green and orange spikes which represent the two key proteins on the surface of a flu virus. There is one flu virus in focus in the bottom right and more in varying degrees of blur in the background. " class="sc-5340b511-0 hLdNfA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 jVqbAn"&gt;Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;H3N2 strain of influenza &lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Unusually, this happened outside flu season in the middle of the northern hemisphere's summer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"It almost certainly will sweep the world, so from that standpoint, it's something that will come up quickly," says Prof Smith.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;By September, as children went back to school, the nights drew in and the temperatures started to drop, there was an uptick in cases.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Exactly what the mutations are doing is still being explored, but they are probably helping the virus to evade some of the immunity we have built up over years of flu infections and vaccines.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The result is the virus is finding it easier to infect people and spread – that is why the flu season is so early in the UK and other countries including Japan.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;If the virus can spread more easily then it does not have to wait for more favourable wintery conditions – when we spend more time indoors with the heating on and the windows shut – to start the flu season.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"We're miles ahead," says Prof Lewis, "I think it's going to be a strong flu season".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;If you remember your R numbers from the pandemic (that is the number of people each infected person passes the virus on to), they suggest the new mutant has an edge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Seasonal flu usually has an R number of around 1.2, while the early estimate for this year is 1.4, said Prof Lewis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;So very roughly, if 100 people had flu, they would pass it to 120 in a typical year and 140 this year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 hNbOGD"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 gXmhTb"&gt;Worst flu season for a decade?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"It's highly likely it's going to be a bad flu season and it's going to happen quite soon, we're already well into it," says Prof Christophe Fraser, from the Pandemic Sciences Institute at the University of Oxford.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"There are indicators that this could be worse than some of the flu seasons we've seen in the last 10 years."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;In a typical flu season around one-in-five of us get infected, but that could be higher this year, he warns.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;But all these predictions are still clouded in uncertainty.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Some look to Australia for clues as it had the worst flu season on record this year, although it did not face the same mutated H3N2 we have. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;We know the virus is spreading very well in children in the germ-fest that is the school playground.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;But the immunity a 10-year-old has developed will be very different from that of their grandparents whose immune defences may have been shaped by six times as many flu seasons. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;So, experts will be watching closely as the virus starts infecting older age groups in the coming weeks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 hNbOGD"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 gXmhTb"&gt;'It's a nastier virus'&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;History suggests that the form of influenza we are facing this year is more severe, particularly for older people.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;There are multiple types of flu and you may have heard some of the names like H1N1 swine flu, which caused a pandemic in 2009, or H5N1 which is the current flu killing birds around the world.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The fresh mutations have happened in a group of H3N2 influenzas.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"H3 is always a hotter virus, it's a nastier virus, it's more impactful on the population," said Prof Lewis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;It is worth remembering that some of us will get flu and develop no symptoms at all, while others get a sudden fever, body aches and exhaustion, but the virus can be deadly in older and more vulnerable groups.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Last year, nearly 8,000 people died from flu, and in the 2022-23 flu season there were nearly 16,000 deaths. The NHS is already anticipating a tough flu season.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;So what can we do about it?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The clear advice is to get the seasonal flu vaccine – the NHS in England issued a "flu jab SOS" saying there were 2.4 million vaccine slots available in the next week.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 GunZh"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 cMIbKV"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20251105-121702-1a3e907763-web-2.33.1-3/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 gUePlo hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/7b14/live/6dc846d0-bbd7-11f0-bd4a-49c00e3ca628.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/7b14/live/6dc846d0-bbd7-11f0-bd4a-49c00e3ca628.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/7b14/live/6dc846d0-bbd7-11f0-bd4a-49c00e3ca628.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/7b14/live/6dc846d0-bbd7-11f0-bd4a-49c00e3ca628.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/7b14/live/6dc846d0-bbd7-11f0-bd4a-49c00e3ca628.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/7b14/live/6dc846d0-bbd7-11f0-bd4a-49c00e3ca628.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/7b14/live/6dc846d0-bbd7-11f0-bd4a-49c00e3ca628.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/7b14/live/6dc846d0-bbd7-11f0-bd4a-49c00e3ca628.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Getty Images Two people in a bland, white clinic room. One is an older man with grey hair, an incredibly intense grin on his face and his left arm is rolled up. A young woman with shoulder length brown hair, wearing a rich blue set of scrubs is standing over him. She holds a shot of flu vaccine in her medical gloved hands. " class="sc-5340b511-0 hLdNfA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 jVqbAn"&gt;Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Prof Lewis argues this is "absolutely the most important year" to get vaccinated and that "if you have been called by your GP, please get your flu vaccine as soon as possible".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;However, this year's vaccine is not a perfect match to the mutated virus. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The decision on the design of the vaccine was made in February to give enough time to produce the millions of doses necessary - and then the new mutant emerged in June.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"Some protection is better than no protection, but this year is likely to be one of the years where the amount of protection is less than it is in years when the match is better, it's not an ideal situation," said Prof Fraser.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The vaccine will still trigger the body to produce antibodies that can recognise and stick to flu.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;But the biggest benefits are anticipated to be in lessening the severity of the disease rather than stopping you get ill or slowing the spread of the virus. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Meanwhile, doctors have been sent advice reminding them that &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.cas.mhra.gov.uk/ViewandAcknowledgment/ViewAlert.aspx?AlertID=103269" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;early antiviral treatment&lt;/a&gt; reduces the risk of complications from flu.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Japan is also going through an early flu season and has closed schools to help contain outbreaks. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;These are not Covid-style lockdowns, but short-term measures the country uses to disrupt the spread of the virus.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Nobody knows for certain what will happen in the coming months.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"It might all go away by next week," says Prof Lewis, "but I don't think it will."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BBC</author><pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 00:03:44 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiWkFVX3lxTE9sR1ZHNXRKYXFIR09kN1BOTWxNVXRrZTlWLWVRazJOTTVldUpBTW1hNVpBZnU5eERxOVNQU3ViY2dJR21KcDhzLVc3dFRLS0lIaF9FMGozQUFJZ9IBX0FVX3lxTFBsN2p6M2c3aVpFYW16RWFLdnJBVThodU5PYS1xWndIbURZbzNKQ0JHWDc1VXZ4UEY2Z1NiZFo3WGhFZXdqY2NJd1p5bUJHRGV3NXVuQVFzQm42anZ4R2ZN</guid></item><item><title>喝绿茶时血压会发生什么变化- AOL.com</title><link>https://www.aol.com/articles/happens-blood-pressure-drink-green-180000726.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="caas-body"&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure align-caption-with-image"&gt;&lt;div class="no-margin"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="caption-wrapper"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption-collapse"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Design elements: Getty Images. EatingWell design.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Key Points&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul class="caas-list caas-list-bullet"&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The antioxidants in green tea support healthy blood pressure by helping blood vessels relax.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the longer term, green tea may help protect your arteries by reducing oxidative stress and inflammation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Choose regular or decaf brewed green tea over supplements or extracts for blood-pressure benefits.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;High blood pressure, or hypertension, affects nearly half of U.S. adults and increases the risk for heart disease and stroke. Blood pressure is an important indicator of &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/best-tea-for-metabolic-syndrome-8782901" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:metabolic health;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;metabolic health&lt;/a&gt; and healthy blood pressure is less than 120/80 mm Hg. The top number (systolic) measures pressure when your heart beats, while the bottom (diastolic) measures it between beats.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While lifestyle and medications play the biggest roles in managing it, small daily habits—like &lt;a class="link rapid-noclick-resp" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/drink-blood-pressure-study-11760522" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:sipping green tea;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas"&gt;sipping green tea&lt;/a&gt;—may also have an impact. We spoke with nutrition experts to find out how drinking green tea affects your blood pressure and who should avoid it, plus tips to add it to your routine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;How Green Tea Affects Blood Pressure&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;h3&gt;May Relax Blood Vessels and Improve Circulation&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Much of green tea’s heart-healthy blood pressure benefits come from antioxidant compounds called catechins—these polyphenols help blood vessels stay flexible and open. “One compound in particular, epigallocatechin gallate (EGCG), boosts nitric oxide and promotes vasodilation, helping your blood vessels relax,” says &lt;a href="https://www.nutritionbybess.com/old-about" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Bess Berger, RDN;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Bess Berger, RDN&lt;/a&gt;. When your blood vessels relax, or vasodilate, your blood pressure lowers—a short-term effect that supports smoother circulation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“While catechins are one type of tea polyphenol, the blood pressure–lowering effects of green tea are probably attributable to a combination of all of the plant compounds it contains instead of an individual few,” adds &lt;a href="https://www.drnutritionchanger.com/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Qianzhi Jiang, Ph.D., RDN;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Qianzhi Jiang, Ph.D., RDN&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Though some research suggests that green tea may lower blood pressure in both healthy individuals and those with hypertension, the results are inconsistent, and further long-term studies are needed to confirm these findings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Helps Protect Arteries from Long-Term Damage&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;While green tea may help blood vessels relax in the moment, its bigger advantage may come from how it protects them over time. The same polyphenols that give green tea its antioxidant strength appear to guard arteries against oxidative stress and low-grade inflammation—two drivers of the slow, silent damage that can increase blood pressure with age.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Green tea’s catechins support blood vessel health by reducing inflammation and improving how your vessels function,” says &lt;a href="https://www.dieteticseducation.org/about" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Devon Golem, Ph.D., RD, LDN;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Devon Golem, Ph.D., RD, LDN&lt;/a&gt;. Over time, that can translate to more supple arteries that expand and contract more easily, helping your heart pump blood efficiently. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The result isn’t an overnight change in blood pressure but a gradual, protective effect that keeps arteries healthy and resilient in the long run.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Caffeine Can Temporarily Raise Blood Pressure&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Although green tea generally has less caffeine than coffee—about 30 milligrams of caffeine in an 8-ounce cup of green tea versus 95 mg in the same serving of coffee—it’s still a stimulant that can cause a short-term increase in blood pressure. “If you’re super-sensitive to caffeine, green tea could cause a temporary bump in blood pressure right after drinking it,” says Berger. This effect typically fades within a few hours as your body metabolizes the caffeine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For most people, this short-term spike doesn’t cancel out green tea’s long-term cardiovascular benefits. Research suggests that the long-term benefits of drinking green tea likely outweigh the short-term effect caffeine may have on blood pressure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you’re prone to &lt;a class="link rapid-noclick-resp" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/what-to-do-if-you-drink-too-much-coffee-in-the-am-11758446" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:caffeine jitters;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas"&gt;caffeine jitters&lt;/a&gt;, switching to &lt;a class="link rapid-noclick-resp" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/8030655/does-green-tea-have-caffeine/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:decaf green tea;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas"&gt;decaf green tea&lt;/a&gt; can be a good option. You’ll still get many of the same beneficial antioxidants, as one review compared caffeinated and decaffeinated green tea extract supplements and found no difference in blood pressure effects.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;How Much Green Tea Should You Drink Daily?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;There’s no official guideline for how much green tea to drink for blood pressure benefits. “The majority of the studies used three to four cups of green tea daily, and greater reductions in blood pressure were observed with longer use—more than three months,” explains Jiang.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Brewing matters, too. Jiang says that most of green tea’s polyphenols are released within the first five minutes of steeping, so letting your tea sit for a few minutes can help you get the most benefit from each cup.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Overconsumption is very rare from green tea beverages,” says Jiang&lt;em&gt;.&lt;/em&gt; However, green tea extracts may lead to side effects, including nausea, abdominal discomfort and increased blood pressure. Experts agree: It’s better to drink green tea than to take supplements that contain green tea extracts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;How Green Tea Interacts with Blood Pressure Medications&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;While brewed tea in moderate amounts is generally safe, concentrated green tea extracts can interfere with how certain drugs are absorbed or metabolized. Studies show that green tea can reduce the effectiveness of &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/medications-don-t-mix-with-green-tea-11815448" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:certain blood pressure medications;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;certain blood pressure medications&lt;/a&gt;, including the beta-blocker nadolol. It may also interfere with other heart or cholesterol drugs when taken at the same time. These effects are more likely with high intakes or green tea extracts, but brewed tea can still play a role.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you take medication for blood pressure or cholesterol, it’s worth checking with your health care provider to make sure that green tea fits safely into your routine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Is Green Tea Safe for Everyone?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;For most people, a few cups of green tea a day are perfectly safe—and even beneficial—but there are some exceptions. “Caffeine can negatively affect pregnant and breastfeeding women, children and individuals with anxiety, irregular heartbeats, seizures, sleep issues and irritable bowel syndrome,” says Golem.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you’re pregnant or breastfeeding, keep total &lt;a class="link rapid-noclick-resp" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/8009784/how-much-caffeine-is-too-much/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:caffeine intake;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas"&gt;caffeine intake&lt;/a&gt; under 200 mg per day (about two cups of green tea, depending on strength), or follow your health care provider’s guidance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;People who prefer to limit their caffeine intake can still benefit from drinking decaf green tea, which contains many of the same antioxidants but with less caffeine. While it’s uncommon, concentrated green tea extracts have been linked to liver issues in sensitive individuals, so sticking to brewed tea is the safest way to enjoy its benefits.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Ways to Enjoy Green Tea&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul class="caas-list caas-list-bullet"&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Try It Iced:&lt;/strong&gt; Brew a few cups ahead and &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/recipe/249466/iced-mint-green-tea/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:chill them;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;chill them&lt;/a&gt; for a refreshing afternoon drink. Add a &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/recipe/252432/green-jasmine-mint-iced-tea-with-lemon/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:squeeze of lemon;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;squeeze of lemon&lt;/a&gt; to boost flavor and add some vitamin C.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Go for Matcha:&lt;/strong&gt; This &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/matcha-health-benefits-11705379" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:powdered form of green tea;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;powdered form of green tea&lt;/a&gt; offers a concentrated source of antioxidants and a mild caffeine lift. Whisk it into hot water for a traditional preparation, or use it in desserts—think cakes, cookies and pudding.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Skip the Sugar:&lt;/strong&gt; Opt for unsweetened tea to maximize health benefits. If you prefer a sweeter beverage, try a &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/recipe/266309/warm-honey-green-tea/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:drizzle of honey;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;drizzle of honey&lt;/a&gt; or sweetener of your choice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Infuse It with Flavor:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a class="link rapid-noclick-resp" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/recipe/252432/green-jasmine-mint-iced-tea-with-lemon/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Steep your tea with fresh herbs;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas"&gt;Steep your tea with fresh herbs&lt;/a&gt; like mint or basil, or add slices of ginger or orange for a fragrant, spa-like spin.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Get Creative in the Kitchen:&lt;/strong&gt; Green tea can also be used in cooking. Jiang notes that in Japan, green tea is sometimes poured over rice and topped with salmon and scallions—a simple dish called ochazuke that adds subtle flavor and antioxidants to your meal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Our Expert Take&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Green tea isn’t a magic fix for high blood pressure, but it can play a small role in supporting heart health—especially when enjoyed regularly as part of a healthy lifestyle. Its polyphenols can help relax blood vessels in the short term and protect them from long-term damage caused by oxidative stress and inflammation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Experts recommend getting your green tea from the cup, not a capsule. Brewed tea offers the ideal balance of beneficial compounds without the risks associated with concentrated extracts. A few cups a day—paired with other healthy habits like eating a balanced diet, staying active and managing stress—can help keep your blood pressure in a healthy range.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Read the original article on &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/green-tea-and-blood-pressure-11844020" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:EatingWell;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;EatingWell&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>AOL.com</author><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 20:03:45 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihAFBVV95cUxOdDZabzFBX2E1R0luQ3BaZjlJVnRfT2lsTVFhbmdZWW5URVBjMzlJUUdVS0RVX3F4T2xTWVJ0YUh5NkpLQmJPYm8yTVVtLTJiNWoxb2JyY1pBWUdLRXN6NDZPNnY2b2g3R29OcFYxTkJCQW1abE9PT01hMFBnVUhoZXNnaXA</guid></item><item><title>我的日常能量饮料习惯使我因严重的器官损伤而住院-每日邮报</title><link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-15236087/energy-drinks-deadly-kidney-disease.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div itemprop="articleBody"&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;A 21-year-old who had an eight-a-day energy drink habit was hospitalized after the beverages severely damaged his kidneys.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The unidentified man from Turkey rushed to his local emergency room with nausea and vomiting that had started the day before. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;He had no chronic medical problems, wasn't overweight, didn't smoke and was a 'fit healthy young man' who had never abused drugs or &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/alcohol/index.html" id="mol-481cf7d0-b440-11f0-a2ba-991f13657966"&gt;alcohol&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But blood tests revealed his creatinine, a waste product that comes from normal muscle breakdown, was about five times greater than the normal range, while his phosphorus, a mineral that helps form the structure of cell membranes and bones, was three-fold higher than average. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The concerning levels showed his kidneys were not able to properly filter the materials out of his blood, a sign of injury or organ failure. If these levels get too high, they can damage vital organs and lead to heart attack, stroke or organ failure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The man told doctors that he had been preparing to run a race for the past month and was drinking two liters (68 ounces), of unnamed 'energy drink' every day to help him stay alert. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;HIS habit had caused stage three acute kidney injury (AKI), which is considered the 'middle stage' of acute &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/health/article-15208907/heart-health-condition-affects-Americans-dont-know-it.html"&gt;kidney disease&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;A 21-year-old in Turkey suffered stage three acute kidney injury after consuming excess energy drinks (stock image&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;The unidentified man said he has been drinking two liters of an unspecified energy drink every day for a month to prepare for a race (stock image)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    
    
    &lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Roughly one in three Americans report consuming an energy drink at least once, and nine percent drink them every day. They are also especially popular among teenagers, with between 30 and 50 percent of 12- to 17-year-olds say they drink them regularly. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;About one in 10 Americans, 35million, have some form of kidney disease, and just over 800,000 are in kidney failure, according to the American Kidney Fund. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;And about nine in 10 people with the condition have no idea they have it, including one in three Americans with severely reduced kidney function. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The disease causes the kidneys to be unable to properly filter out waste and excess fluid from the blood, causing them to build up in the body, leading to high potassium, which threatens heart function, brittle bones, a weakened immune system, heart attack and stroke.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Acute kidney injuries are usually caused by slowed blood flow to the organs, damage or blocked urine flow. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;While the man in the case report had no underlying conditions, his extreme energy drink consumption likely lead to the injury, doctors &lt;a class="" rel="nofollow noreferrer noopener" target="_blank" href="https://jmedicalcasereports.biomedcentral.com/articles/10.1186/s13256-025-05614-3"&gt;wrote in a case study&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Energy drinks typically contain a mix of caffeine, B vitamins, sugar, artificial sweeteners and additives like taurine and guarana. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;An 8.4-ounce can of a popular energy drink contains 80 milligrams of caffeine, roughly the same as a cup of coffee. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;If the man was drinking eight cans, this would add up to 640 milligrams of caffeine, 46 percent more than the FDA's recommended daily limit of 400 milligrams. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Recent research suggests excessive caffeine consumption, which would be more than 500 milligrams daily, may increase the risk of developing kidney stones. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Caffeine is a stimulant that temporarily raises blood pressure, but in excess amounts, that high blood pressure can put extra strain on the kidneys. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Doctors treating the man also wrote that at least once he consumed an energy drink that contained 150 milligrams per liter of caffeine and 800 milligrams per liter of taurine, which may have made taurine that primary culprit. &lt;/p&gt;
    
    
    &lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Taurine is an non-essential amino acid found naturally in the bone marrow, brain, heart and muscles. It's also found in meat and fish and is used in certain beverages to energize cells and boost mental clarity. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Taurine is considered safe in small amounts, but higher levels have been shown to cause vomiting, upset stomach, dizziness, diarrhea and constipation. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Along with caffeine, excess taurine can lead to dehydration and high blood pressure, potentially damaging kidneys, though research is limited.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Writing in a medical journal, doctors treating the man suggested the combination of taurine and caffeine likely caused his injury. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The patient was admitted to a kidney clinic and told to stop consuming energy drinks immediately. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'The most important first step to treat [energy drink]-induced AKI is withholding it,' his doctors wrote.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;His creatinine levels gradually normalized over the course of 16 days, and he did not need dialysis or other long-term treatments.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Doctors continued following him for two years, during which his kidney function remained normal.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Daily Mail</author><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 17:49:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilwFBVV95cUxNUF9IWDdsVGJPZWJSU2JWaFVXanJ0VHZyaEItR0Y1ODJPTG44NjY3cDNCUXN5QUtENE8zZWtWOXJBdGRIeFFoUFd6TzJpTExTdzVyODJ6amttU0VWbWVVaGp2bjRMZ09sTnZvbUhIanU3WjBlOXVfR3Z0UTYtSWhPOXhIZFFfM3RQNmFtUU1nVFVweUtmUGRj0gGcAUFVX3lxTE1LTDBVOUlWdnZXY1BSZHJQOFo1Rjl5WHkzcS0tSXA4c1hGWXBEbjVVMDNVME9UQVE3TXowWEZkUDdnNWJmazRpRWc0dUxHcXY1YjM1Wl9WWFU0anYtTWRlc3FSQTEtQnlrNVdielFqZ3VyRTNuWnhFMHJobkFlZF9EanByR0VraGxqWWs4eXBZMGFfZU5leDUxazVKRw</guid></item><item><title>124岁的中国妇女分享她健康长寿的秘诀……大米、这道蔬菜汤和…… --印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/124-year-old-chinese-woman-shares-the-secret-of-her-long-healthy-life-rice-this-vegetable-soup-and-/photostory/125182871.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="COQxt" data-ua-type="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Qiu Chaishi credits her longevity to a plain meticulously kept rhythm. She makes sure to have three meals each day, and goes out for a walk after each one, and heads to bed around eight o’clock in the evening. This steady routine not only eases digestion, but also keeps her internal clock in sync. At her age, she remains impressively self‑sufficient, handling everyday tasks such as brushing her hair, tending the fire, feeding the geese, and climbing the stairs all on her own. Even a modest amount of movement keeps her muscles engaged and her body functioning, helping to prevent frailty.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Times of India</author><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 16:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilAJBVV95cUxPY0xrLXhNekZpV0NZQlJrX1JkQUVNZFNORjVTRUJHSGFKa0JNZHR0R1BsQURXejVNQkF0WTVYNHRwWVNmQnRSQnh5WTRIeHZLdkEwbjBIRDRndHZSSmdRX2diZk83djZfaFZMRHh1VV9IUXROWERTNkVsazdKcDMwOE1mZ3RvWk1vRGJhc2huZ3VVWG9KZkpTdXdpaDlJUjNpQjV1UTlMWmMzNDlXVFFqaHBYODNnZENiMmJ6NEoya25lc3VTS0VITjIyc1dsS0laRnpQLS1Tb1JFWEFqZmZZNUFGOTZmZ0tYZGRtVEk1ZEN5SGp2dmNQYzBVNHB3Z29EV05xZnpVeWhSOE94SjRKYVpsT2vSAZwCQVVfeXFMTmVCS0g4SHZyc21nZUNITV9tQmJkUWtzclFFYksyUC1zUkg1a0kwMnZOd2RyT25IbFVJU01XN3NncXdLQ0F6djdRLV90bFJSQUNjMzVhbzhhSFNPZjJ5dzgtUGNTckxkLXV5T0FYeFpabU12SkNYWnBvTWRCZmVaTmRRd0dFSk4yb2h1YzBvOFBPOXV4UlhIZlFDWlY3Mml6MWNvS09vajVwWTJDZGlfSHB4SVpnT3FKQ2ZHU1BQOVdkMVFCbTZFTHBrR1pmeFVMSE5wd21IOVJlaUFKWWRZaTViaEVVMnZnT1JxbzJGTDhRSnZHekJjNEIwUE55MHd0SDA1dkd2SmxLaWhKMWhIWjNBSmhvZ3Q1aVpNNS0</guid></item><item><title>“一劳永逸”的基因编辑治疗如何降低胆固醇--《华盛顿邮报》</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/science/2025/11/08/crispr-gene-editing-cholesterol-disease/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="GULUNR3RTBFEPB6AGZL3D325TE" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;In a cutting-edge medical experiment, a small group of people who had high cholesterol despite taking conventional drugs to lower it saw significant reductions in two major risk factors for heart disease after receiving a single gene-editing treatment at the highest dose.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 16:27:26 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilAFBVV95cUxOM2FBVXA0UE9KdTBsUEJOd19QV09aWGJCR2VhS2xDTUE0aXE0V0VTM3A0dm9pc2dnQm9ycmVGbDdFNUtjQThMMmhvWnBDQzFEYlZ3NS1UeWtlUXlHUVMwWWFpb0NlTENPTEdhb3RkVHFHMWJNY1FKbFkzekExU0xvOXpIU2JUckNLOWhBLXZxQTRUOG85</guid></item><item><title>创新生命支持系统之父Robert H. Bartlett去世，享年86岁--《纽约时报》</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/11/08/science/robert-h-bartlett-dead.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The New York Times</author><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 15:55:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiekFVX3lxTE1wN1ZHcDRRNUs5dnZBcEZnd1NTRUg2OGJTbWFqd1dDbUN2VDdUTnRiYjlrTVRyaS0tNlVxNDN4YTJ1QVc5SnZuMV80ZEhreUNUT2lkd2VLWmVPLWphRFVyRFhHNzNlNi13VnBWVDlOak9mdzVFdUZuUHNR</guid></item><item><title>股票代码：不要死于心脏病-黑客新闻</title><link>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=45857053</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Hacker News</author><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 15:53:54 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiWEFVX3lxTE5ZSDVKOTdhSjIyaW15Z18wRVdvdDdncEJqN0J2b2ZTWE9BbzQ4Nzk3ZTJ2RGtsdzdtc2dBSVl6YkprUUZnaGdaWG5HOVJISVJrWTRYekNmaTY</guid></item><item><title>咖啡会让你冲进厕所吗？佛罗里达州胃肠病学家解释为什么喝咖啡会刺激肠道运动|健康-印度斯坦时报</title><link>https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/does-coffee-make-you-rush-to-the-loo-florida-gastroenterologist-explains-why-drinking-coffee-stimulates-bowel-movements-101762614578668.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="storyMainDiv" class="fullStory tfStory current videoStory story__detail storyAf101762614578668 " data-vars-storyid="101762614578668" data-story-section="lifestyle" data-story-subsection="health" data-vars-author="Eshana Saha" data-premium-story="false" data-performance-type="not-set" data-story-title="Does coffee make you rush to the loo? Florida gastroenterologist explains why drinking coffee stimulates bowel movements"&gt; &lt;p class="htEchoTopPageBanner dHide"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="stickyCard"&gt; &lt;/p&gt;  &lt;h1 class="hdg1"&gt;Does coffee make you rush to the loo? Florida gastroenterologist explains why drinking coffee stimulates bowel movements&lt;/h1&gt;  &lt;div class="actionDiv flexElm topTime"&gt; &lt;p class="dateTime secTime storyPage"&gt;Published on: Nov 08, 2025 09:20 pm IST &lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p class="googleFollow mHide"&gt; &lt;button class="htEchoShareBarDesk"&gt;&lt;/button&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;h2 class="sortDec"&gt;Do you need to drink coffee in the morning to stimulate bowel movements? Dr Salhab explains the science behind the connection.&lt;/h2&gt;  &lt;div class="storyDetails taboola-readmore"&gt; &lt;div class="detail " dataid="/lifestyle/health/does-coffee-make-you-rush-to-the-loo-florida-gastroenterologist-explains-why-drinking-coffee-stimulates-bowel-movements-101762614578668.html"&gt; &lt;div class="storyParagraphFigure"&gt; &lt;p&gt;We’ve all experienced it: that urgent need to dash to the bathroom right after your morning &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/technology/5-coffee-makers-that-will-instantly-elevate-your-kitchen-101762250675879.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="coffee"&gt;coffee &lt;/a&gt;- or the dread of drinking coffee when you’re out and about. While it might feel like a quirky coincidence, there’s actually a scientific explanation behind it.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;figure class=""&gt; &lt;span class=""&gt; &lt;picture&gt; &lt;source media="(max-width:767px)" srcset="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/11/08/550x309/coffee_1762616795423_1762616795653.jpeg" alt="Dr Salhab explains the science behind coffee and bowel movements.(Pexel)" title="Dr Salhab explains the science behind coffee and bowel movements.(Pexel)"&gt;&lt;/source&gt; &lt;img src="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/11/08/550x309/coffee_1762616795423_1762616795653.jpeg" alt="Dr Salhab explains the science behind coffee and bowel movements.(Pexel)" title="Dr Salhab explains the science behind coffee and bowel movements.(Pexel)"&gt; &lt;/picture&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;figcaption&gt;Dr Salhab explains the science behind coffee and bowel movements.(Pexel)&lt;/figcaption&gt; &lt;/figure&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;p id="readMoreFTUser"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Also Read | &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/can-chewing-gum-ease-heartburn-florida-gastroenterologist-shares-3-easy-hacks-to-relieve-acid-reflux-without-medication-101761387796258.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="Can chewing gum ease heartburn? Florida gastroenterologist shares 3 easy hacks to relieve acid reflux without medication"&gt;Can chewing gum ease heartburn? Florida gastroenterologist shares 3 easy hacks to relieve acid reflux without medication&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="mt-10 mb-10 htEchoRecirculationWidget"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="predictorShow mb20" data-vars-predictor="true" data-vars-quiz="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="quizShow mb20" data-vars-minimized="false" data-vars-predictor="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Dr Joseph Salhab, a gastroenterologist and health content creator from Florida, specialising in &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/topic/digestion" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="digestion"&gt;digestion&lt;/a&gt;, liver, pancreas and &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/deep-cleaning-for-diwali-nutritionist-shares-7-kitchen-items-to-get-rid-of-that-are-silently-harming-your-health-101760186828101.html" data-vars-anchor-text="nutrition"&gt;nutrition&lt;/a&gt;, is explaining what makes you want to run to the loo after drinking coffee. In an Instagram video posted on November 8, the gastroenterologist highlights the role of coffee in stimulating bowel movements and shares three gentler alternatives that won’t leave you running to the loo.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Why does coffee make you need to poop?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr Salhab states, “Does coffee make you have to go poop? If it does, you're not alone. In fact, 30 to 40 percent of people who drink coffee regularly report that coffee has to make them go to the bathroom in the morning.”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;He mentions that this happens for a few reasons. He explains, “First is the caffeine content. Caffeine can stimulate movement of the colon within four minutes of ingesting it. Coffee also stimulates contraction of your &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/crash-dieting-living-sedentary-life-cause-gallbladder-stones-physician-warns-of-5-everyday-habits-that-increase-risk-101758705466730.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="gallbladder"&gt;gallbladder &lt;/a&gt;to pump digestive enzymes and bile. And this also stimulates your gastrointestinal tract to start moving.”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The gastroenterologist adds that coffee is typically served warm, and consuming warm beverages can naturally stimulate bowel movements - warm water also works the same way. He continues, “Also, the antioxidants within coffee have been shown to promote the growth of beneficial bacteria within the gut and these beneficial bacteria can also influence how often we use the restroom.”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;Gentler alternatives&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr Salhab outlines three effective ways to manage that sudden urge to run to the loo after drinking coffee.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;You can opt for beverages with lower caffeine content - such as green tea - or simply cut down your usual coffee intake to reduce its laxative effect.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Switching to a cold brew or iced coffee also helps.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;If that doesn't work, you can just switch to a decaf version, which still has plenty of &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/cardiologist-calls-matcha-tea-science-in-a-cup-shares-top-5-benefits-fat-burn-antioxidant-weight-loss-caffeine-101752815578622.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="antioxidants"&gt;antioxidants &lt;/a&gt;and health benefits, minus the sudden urge to rush to the bathroom.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Note to readers: This article is for informational purposes only and not a substitute for professional medical advice. It is based on user-generated content from social media. HT.com has not independently verified the claims and does not endorse them.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;/div&gt; &lt;p class="recommendedSliderContextual" id="recommendedSliderContextual-101762614578668" data-vars-story_id="101762614578668" data-vars-story_section="lifestyle" data-vars-author="Eshana Saha" data-vars-story_headline="Does coffee make you rush to the loo? Florida gastroenterologist explains why drinking coffee stimulates bowel movements"&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;input type="checkbox" class="trendTopsSHow" id="trendTopsSHow-101762614578668"&gt; &lt;div class="trendTops"&gt;  &lt;div class="trendInlineSeo"&gt;&lt;p&gt; Catch every big hit, every wicket with Crick-it, a one stop destination for Live Scores, Match Stats, Quizzes, Polls &amp;amp; much more. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/cricket?utm_source=endofarticle&amp;amp;utm_medium=web&amp;amp;utm_campaign=crickitlaunch"&gt;Explore now!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Catch your daily dose of &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/fashion"&gt;Fashion&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/entertainment/music/taylor-swift"&gt;Taylor Swift&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health"&gt;Health&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/festivals"&gt;Festivals&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/travel"&gt;Travel&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/relationships"&gt;Relationship&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/recipe"&gt;Recipe&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; and all the other Latest &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle"&gt;Lifestyle News&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; on Hindustan Times Website and APPs. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;label class="moreBtn1" for="trendTopsSHow-101762614578668"&gt;&lt;/label&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;div class="followHT trendSeo__1"&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;div class="bottomSeoParaEcho1"&gt; &lt;div id="bottomSeoParaEcho"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Catch every big hit, every wicket with Crick-it, a one stop destination for Live Scores, Match Stats, Quizzes, Polls &amp;amp; much more. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/cricket?utm_source=endofarticle&amp;amp;utm_medium=web&amp;amp;utm_campaign=crickitlaunch"&gt;Explore now!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Catch your daily dose of &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/fashion"&gt;Fashion&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/entertainment/music/taylor-swift"&gt;Taylor Swift&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health"&gt;Health&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/festivals"&gt;Festivals&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/travel"&gt;Travel&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/relationships"&gt;Relationship&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/recipe"&gt;Recipe&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; and all the other Latest &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle"&gt;Lifestyle News&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; on Hindustan Times Website and APPs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;div class="mb5 mt5" id="bottomBreadCrumb"&gt; &lt;div class="breadcrumbs"&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com" class="breadcrumbclick" data-vars-event-label="Home_clicked" data-vars-event-action="/" data-vars-event-cta="News"&gt;News&lt;/a&gt; &lt;span&gt;/&lt;/span&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle" class="breadcrumbclick" data-vars-event-label="Lifestyle_clicked" data-vars-event-action="/lifestyle" data-vars-event-cta="Lifestyle"&gt;Lifestyle&lt;/a&gt; &lt;span&gt;/&lt;/span&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health" class="breadcrumbclick" data-vars-event-label="Health_clicked" data-vars-event-action="/lifestyle/health" data-vars-event-cta="Health"&gt;Health&lt;/a&gt; &lt;span&gt;/&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; Does coffee make you rush to the loo? Florida gastroenterologist explains why drinking coffee stimulates bowel movements &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;p class="bottomSeoParaEcho pb0"&gt; &lt;label class="moreBtn" for="trendTopsSHow-101762614578668" id="spanSeeLessEcho"&gt;See Less&lt;/label&gt; &lt;/p&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;   &lt;p class="relatedStoryCricket"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="saranyuPlayer" id="saranyu-player"&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;p class="relatedStory2"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="us-ad align-center mb10 mt10"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p class="htEchoShortsEntryPoint" data-size="enlarged"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="affiliate-shop-now" id="affiliate-shop-now"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Hindustan Times</author><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 15:50:58 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilwJBVV95cUxOWkRYLUFid09SZzdWUWkwWGVlZmJyMFdDQ1dLVGpyU21fMjZwTXhuT1RoWllJaWxhOExOTkVYa1dfM0NNTEN0UVppUmZxdkJtQWVXTXV6V0hlZ1Q4UjNORkwwQlhILUp5b2Mxd3F5eUlQSFB5NzItV28wWE5Hek5vWXF3Vk9oZTNpajdhOXR3aE5udjQwLTY0YXBJb3JGQjhRdW0tbll1b1pPYVFRczA2anBXYmdab05UWG9hc2lERU9rYlFXdWc5blgxajNHQm92Snc5OVpGcG92Tmo3WEw4bEJ2ZEtMU0lYaVpBS3EzVVJLQlRoYjNDSDZVY21iX25DMmlablh3ZnhSTkVod3d3djMxZFFFbGPSAZwCQVVfeXFMTjA0SHdHSmpLSGNrRmpyX0tqUmVsa1gxR1VMUVUxRUdCZlNxQVpRbW5sdUlSb25mUkgtR1VWQjRGcTFVT0thVng2amtlTkJmMzRSM1NnbmhSaUVXYW9MMmhxZ3hUQUZNTVpNemZoeVlZcWR3N3JpdG9XeXhVeUJxRWZ4UnhOb0JXdnhxckhpaVluRk1weThJVHU5bUxuQXBwWDNXMTFIb3N4dEk3UGdGS21JNTY3X093aVcyWXFWZk5kd1ZXWml1cy1YZ0tNS3g1Q0JGMzN6enRUWVNvYjlCcXluNTZnZ2p3RnhBTHo4UWMwY0RtTzRWS2FwVUtCWE1ZSUNnZ1VRWnNOUTl5dHhlU2h3eHAwcUMyWklVOTg</guid></item><item><title>科学家发现可以阻止阿尔茨海默氏症的脑细胞- ScienceDaily</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/11/251108083902.htm</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p id="first" class="lead"&gt;In Alzheimer's disease, the most common cause of dementia, microglia (the brain's immune cells) play a double role. They can protect the brain by clearing harmful debris or, under certain conditions, contribute to damage and inflammation. How these cells behave can strongly influence how the disease unfolds.&lt;/p&gt;

						&lt;div id="text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Scientists from the Icahn School of Medicine at Mount Sinai, together with researchers from the Max Planck Institute for Biology and Ageing in Cologne, Germany, The Rockefeller University, The City University of New York, and other international partners, have identified a unique group of microglia that appear to protect the brain. This discovery could pave the way for new treatment strategies aimed at slowing or preventing Alzheimer's disease.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In a study published November 5 in &lt;em&gt;Nature&lt;/em&gt;, the team found that microglia with lower levels of a transcription factor called PU.1 and higher expression of a receptor known as CD28 help reduce brain inflammation. These specialized microglia also slow the buildup of amyloid plaques and the spread of toxic tau proteins, which are both major hallmarks of Alzheimer's.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PU.1 is a protein that binds to specific DNA regions, helping control which genes are activated or silenced. CD28, found on the surface of T cells, acts as a signaling receptor that supports immune cell activation and communication.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How Protective Microglia Work&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Using mouse models of Alzheimer's, as well as human brain cells and tissue samples, the researchers showed that reducing PU.1 levels encourages microglia to express immune-regulating receptors typically found in lymphoid cells. Although these protective microglia make up only a small portion of total microglia, their effect is widespread: they suppress inflammation throughout the brain and help preserve memory and survival in mice.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When the scientists removed CD28 from this specific microglial subset, inflammation worsened and plaque growth increased, confirming that CD28 plays an essential role in keeping these brain-protective cells active.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="insertion_middle"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Microglia are not simply destructive responders in Alzheimer's disease -- they can become the brain's protectors," said Anne Schaefer, MD, PhD, Professor in the Nash Family Department of Neuroscience at the Icahn School of Medicine, Co-Director of the Center for Glial Biology at The Friedman Brain Institute, Director of the Max Planck Institute for Biology of Ageing, and senior author of the paper. "This finding extends our earlier observations on the remarkable plasticity of microglia states and their important roles in diverse brain functions. It also underscores the vital importance of international collaboration in advancing scientific progress."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"It is remarkable to see that molecules long known to immunologists for their roles in B and T lymphocytes also regulate microglial activity," added Alexander Tarakhovsky, MD, PhD, Dr. Plutarch Papamarkou Professor of Immunology, Virology, and Microbiology at The Rockefeller University and co-author of the paper. "This discovery comes at a time when regulatory T cells have achieved major recognition as master regulators of immunity, highlighting a shared logic of immune regulation across cell types. It also paves the way for immunotherapeutic strategies for Alzheimer's disease."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Genetic Clues Point to Lower Alzheimer's Risk&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The research expands upon earlier genetic findings by Alison M. Goate, DPhil, Jean C. and James W. Crystal Professor of Genomics and Chair of the Department of Genetics and Genomic Sciences at the Icahn School of Medicine, founding director of the Ronald M. Loeb Center for Alzheimer's Disease at Mount Sinai, and a senior co-author of the study. Dr. Goate's prior work identified a common genetic variant in SPI1 (the gene responsible for producing PU.1) that is linked to a lower risk of developing Alzheimer's disease.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"These results provide a mechanistic explanation for why lower PU.1 levels are linked to reduced Alzheimer's disease risk," said Dr. Goate.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A New Path Toward Immunotherapy for Alzheimer's&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The discovery of the PU.1-CD28 relationship offers a new molecular framework for understanding how microglia can protect the brain. It also strengthens the idea that targeting microglial activity through immune-based therapies could alter the course of Alzheimer's disease.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This research was supported by the National Institutes of Health, European Research Council, Stavros Niarchos Foundation, Cure Alzheimer's Fund, Freedom Together Foundation, Belfer Neurodegeneration Consortium Grant, Massachusetts Life Sciences Center, Robin Chemers Neustein Postdoctoral Fellowship Award, Alfred P. Sloan Foundation, Alzheimer's Association, BrightFocus Foundation, National Multiple Sclerosis Society, and Clinical and Translational Science Awards.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

					&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceDaily</author><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 15:44:40 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMib0FVX3lxTE9vdDczaW9DN1RQQ3ItVU5TMzV2UGd3RDRqR0tiN0drZ25MT0o0WTE4bFhqWWRWRERtVkJlLVYzNUU2TVhtc25CeXFtNjR5NVZuNC1iNWtITHR2VWhvczRpc0hmNWlzQzlVME9UTkJMNA</guid></item><item><title>白发可能是您身体的癌症防御秘密- SciTechDaily</title><link>https://scitechdaily.com/gray-hair-may-be-your-bodys-secret-cancer-defense/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>SciTechDaily</author><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 15:14:06 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigAFBVV95cUxNTXd1djlOaEJ0TG9MZmdVdVhXMjQ2eHhWUDdPSzBOTXRicklsVEE4cW9EVlFoM1ZPN2ljVUlIeUFBNUJqQlhiWU85LWNqenpocHVRbDNuazZnZW41Z1d5cmZ3TS1hQ1BmRHFEOWstVWJFNVMzbzRpM2Qxb0NVSEVFTQ</guid></item><item><title>基于CRISPR的治疗在早期研究中降低胆固醇和甘油三酯- statnews.com</title><link>https://www.statnews.com/2025/11/08/crispr-therapeutics-cholesterol-lowering-gene-editing-study/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content the-content wp-block-post-content is-layout-flow wp-block-post-content-is-layout-flow"&gt;&lt;p&gt;A CRISPR-based gene editing therapy dramatically reduced levels of low-density lipoprotein, often called “bad cholesterol,” and triglycerides in patients with heart disease, a new study found.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Some researchers said that the treatment, developed by the biotech CRISPR Therapeutics and so far tested in just 15 people, pointed to a possible future where some people prevent heart attacks with one-time gene editing. But this research is also at a very early stage, and scientists expressed concerns about the potential liver toxicities of the treatment and those like it. There is also the question of how many patients would want permanent editing for common illnesses that might be treated with a shot or a pill.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The results were published in the &lt;a href="http://www.nejm.org/doi/full/10.1056/NEJMoa2511778" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;New England Journal of Medicine&lt;/a&gt; and are being presented Saturday at the annual scientific meeting of the American Heart Association in New Orleans.&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;div class="restricted-content-breaker article" aria-labelledby="restricted-story-heading" aria-describedby="restricted-story-description" checked&gt;
			&lt;div class="restricted-content-breaker-bar"&gt;
				&lt;p class="restricted-text"&gt;STAT+ Exclusive Story&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p class="restricted-login"&gt;Already have an account? &lt;a href="/login/" data-stat-login data-stat-paywall-cta="breaker login cta"&gt;Log in&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; 
			&lt;/div&gt;
			&lt;img class="restricted-content-breaker-bg" src="/wp-content/themes/stat/images/stat-plus-breaker-bg.png" alt="STAT+"&gt;
			&lt;div class="restricted-content-breaker-wrapper"&gt;
				&lt;span class="stat-paywall-archive"&gt;
					&lt;a href="https://www.statnews.com/stat-plus/"&gt;
						&lt;img class="stat-plus-logo" src="/wp-content/themes/stat/images/stat-plus-logo-white.svg" alt="STAT+"&gt;
					&lt;/a&gt;
				&lt;/span&gt;
				&lt;h2 id="restricted-story-heading"&gt;This article is exclusive to STAT+ subscribers&lt;/h2&gt;
				&lt;h3 id="restricted-story-description"&gt;Unlock this article — plus daily coverage and analysis of the biotech sector — by subscribing to STAT+.&lt;/h3&gt;
				&lt;p class="restricted-content-breaker-wrapper-cta mobile"&gt;Already have an account? &lt;a href="/login/" data-stat-login data-stat-paywall-cta="breaker login cta mobile"&gt;Log in&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;div class="restricted-content-breaker-cards"&gt;
					&lt;div class="slider-container" aria-label="Subscription plan toggle"&gt;
						&lt;button type="button" class="individual" aria-pressed="false"&gt;Individual plans&lt;/button&gt;
						&lt;p class="switch" role="switch" tabindex="0" aria-checked="false"&gt;
							&lt;button class="slider"&gt;&lt;/button&gt;
						&lt;/p&gt;
						&lt;button type="button" class="group" aria-pressed="false"&gt;Group plans&lt;/button&gt;
					&lt;/div&gt;
							

		
						&lt;/div&gt;
				&lt;a href="https://www.statnews.com/stat-plus/" class="stat-button view-all" data-stat-paywall-cta="breaker view all plans" aria-label="View All Plans"&gt;View All Plans&lt;/a&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
		
		&lt;div class="restricted-message-breaker"&gt;
			&lt;div class="restricted-content-wrapper"&gt;
								
								&lt;div class="restricted-content-message"&gt;
					&lt;p class="restricted-content-text"&gt;
						To read the rest of this story subscribe to STAT+.					&lt;/p&gt;
					&lt;a href="https://www.statnews.com/stat-plus/" class="stat-button restricted-button" data-stat-paywall-cta="breaker subscribe cta 1"&gt;Subscribe&lt;/a&gt;
									&lt;/div&gt;
								
							&lt;/div&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;

		&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>statnews.com</author><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 15:00:29 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMinAFBVV95cUxPVnFXZzNmeUg1OUM2SlBjbGJnWG9NdDdaXzBxMjZJaWVLYnhadF9BVE40X2xVcnh3Y2EwWklzNHp4WkhBOUlNRkpNWmN4YWJzaDZwWkR4WE55d0podldoMTV6TzJCRndrRUo4enRLSFdDbzBvQm11bnBJbUZQUXYyZWRZNUoyVzRzclVtbTl4RmRMQldHamVtR0ZBejk</guid></item><item><title>在一项新研究中， CRISPR基因编辑有助于降低高胆固醇- NPR</title><link>https://www.npr.org/2025/11/08/nx-s1-5587748/crispr-gene-editing-cholesterol-heart-disease</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="storytext" class="storytext storylocation linkLocation"&gt;
      &lt;div id="resg-s1-97036" class="bucketwrap image large"&gt;
            
&lt;div class="credit-caption"&gt;
    &lt;div class="caption-wrap"&gt;
        &lt;div class="caption" aria-label="Image caption"&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;
                Patients with high cholesterol often take medicine for years to manage it but a new gene-editing treatment has potential to make a difference.
                &lt;b class="credit" aria-label="Image credit"&gt;
                    
                    TEK IMAGE/Science Photo Library/Getty Images
                    
                &lt;/b&gt;
                &lt;b class="hide-caption"&gt;&lt;b&gt;hide caption&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;
            &lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;


            &lt;b class="toggle-caption"&gt;&lt;b&gt;toggle caption&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;

    &lt;span class="credit" aria-label="Image credit"&gt;
        
        TEK IMAGE/Science Photo Library/Getty Images
        
    &lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;A single infusion of an experimental gene-editing drug appears safe and effective for cutting cholesterol, possibly for life, according to a small early study released Saturday.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;The study, which involved 15 volunteers, found one infusion of a drug that uses the CRISPR gene-editing technique could safely reduce cholesterol, as well as levels of harmful triglycerides, by about half.&lt;/p&gt;   
   

   &lt;p&gt;"Rather than a lifetime worth of medicine, we have the potential to give people a cure," said Dr. &lt;a href="https://providers.clevelandclinic.org/provider/luke-laffin/4268377" target="_blank"&gt;Luke Laffin&lt;/a&gt;, a preventative cardiologist at the Cleveland Clinic who helped conduct the study. "It's very exciting."&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;The results of the study were presented Saturday at the &lt;a href="https://professional.heart.org/en/meetings/scientific-sessions" target="_blank"&gt;American Heart Association's annual meeting&lt;/a&gt; and published in &lt;a href="http://www.nejm.org/doi/full/10.1056/NEJMoa2511778" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;em&gt;The New England Journal of Medicine&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;If confirmed by future research, the approach could provide a powerful new weapon to fight &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/heart-disease/about/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;heart disease&lt;/a&gt;, the nation's leading killer, freeing people from the need to take statins and other cholesterol-lowering drugs every day.&lt;/p&gt;   
   &lt;p&gt;Laffin and others cautioned, however, that much more research is needed to confirm the findings and make sure the treatment would be safe and long-lasting.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"The idea of an inexpensive, one-and-done [treatment], so you don't have to take any of those drugs, right now that's an idea — a fantasy — because gene-editing is expensive, long-term safety is unclear," Dr. &lt;a href="https://www.scripps.edu/faculty/topol/" target="_blank"&gt;Eric Topol&lt;/a&gt;, a cardiologist at Scripps Research in California who wasn't involved in the study.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Other scientists agree.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"It's a step in the right direction," says Dr. &lt;a href="https://www.med.upenn.edu/cvi/musunuru-laboratory.html" target="_blank"&gt;Kiran Musunuru&lt;/a&gt;, scientific director of the Center for Inherited Cardiovascular Medicine at the University of Pennsylvania Perelman School of Medicine. He was not involved in the research either. &lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"It could be a very important tool," he says. "But to actually prove it's protective against cardiovascular disease you need to do more study."&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;And, Musunuru and others note that the bar for safety would be higher to use gene-editing on patients who are otherwise healthy compared to those already suffering from serious illnesses.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Doctors infuse the drug into patients' bloodstream so it can travel to the liver and disable a gene called ANGPTL3, which is involved in producing cholesterol and triglycerides. &lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"It's a knockout of the gene. It cuts it. And after that, the gene no longer functions," said Dr. &lt;a href="https://providers.clevelandclinic.org/provider/steven-nissen/4268279" target="_blank"&gt;Steven Nissen&lt;/a&gt;, another preventive cardiologist at the Cleveland Clinic involved in the research.&lt;/p&gt;   
   &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://crisprtx.com/about-us/leadership/dr.-samarth-kulkarni" target="_blank"&gt;Samarth Kulkarni&lt;/a&gt;, chief executive officer at &lt;a href="https://crisprtx.com/" target="_blank"&gt;CRISPR Therapeutics&lt;/a&gt;, which is developing the drug and sponsored the study, says the approach "could potentially impact millions of people around the world."&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;The findings are consistent with a &lt;a href="https://www.npr.org/sections/health-shots/2023/11/12/1211672034/for-the-first-time-gene-editing-provides-hints-for-lowering-cholesterol" target="_blank"&gt;similar approach&lt;/a&gt; being developed by another company, &lt;a href="https://www.vervetx.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Verve Therapeutics&lt;/a&gt; in Boston.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"The fact that we now have more clinical data that there's a 'there there' is of course tremendously encouraging," says &lt;a href="https://vcresearch.berkeley.edu/faculty/fyodor-urnov" target="_blank"&gt;Fyodor Urnov&lt;/a&gt;, who studies gene editing at the University of California, Berkeley. "Having a CRISPR medicine for heart attack would be an extraordinary win."&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Neither company has said how much the treatment might cost, but other gene-editing and gene therapies have been very expensive, costing millions per patient.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Millions of people take medicines every day to cut their cholesterol and their risk for having a heart attack or stroke. But heart disease still kills nearly 700,000 people every year in the US. One big reason: A lot of people quit taking their medicine.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"This problem of adherence — that people stop taking their medications — is huge," Nissen says.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Researchers are planning larger, longer studies to see whether a one-time gene-editing drug could safely protect people against heart attacks and strokes for a lifetime.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>NPR</author><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 14:58:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilAFBVV95cUxPblE2anJRaEV6S2l5YnZibVFOSlhoMFZRd3hfZ0Y4YUNwWTRuaXNValpnLVRmRzN4V05qdEMwU1h1VFljQmY1ZEV3LWJOZEVvRGNvUzl5dV9QQmpWSEhBMXpXQ3E2NGlFZkxqYXhKZmpCWm42UW81THRrcFVWM3JxMEtHalhiNGI2WHRPVFhUSzNnU0RD</guid></item><item><title>男子在院子里工作时感染危险疾病后发出警告： “确保人们知道” -雅虎</title><link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/articles/man-issues-warning-contracting-dangerous-140000819.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="" data-article-body="true"&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;In Canada's warmer-than-usual summer in 2025, some homeowners stayed busy with outdoor tasks. However, this also provided mosquitoes with an extended period to prey on unsuspecting humans.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Ontario resident René van den Berg spent 11 days in the hospital after contracting the West Nile virus (WNV) in September, CTV News &lt;a href="https://www.ctvnews.ca/kitchener/article/cambridge-ont-man-hospitalized-after-contracting-west-nile-virus/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:reported;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;reported&lt;/a&gt;. Experts warn that rising global temperatures can accelerate breeding cycles and increase mosquito days&lt;strong&gt;,&lt;/strong&gt; heightening the risk of getting the virus.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="mb-4 text-lg font-bold"&gt;What happened?&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Van den Berg spoke with the outlet while recovering at home, saying, "I thought mosquitoes would die off at the end of August, when temperatures get colder at night."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The backyard, where he suspected he got the bite, also didn't have stagnant water, a common breeding ground for mosquitoes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;After the headaches he first experienced on September 20 became unbearable, he sought medical help and was later diagnosed with viral meningitis due to WNV.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;WNV symptoms typically show up two to 15 days after a mosquito bite, according to the &lt;a href="https://www.regionofwaterloo.ca/Modules/News/index.aspx?newsId=1b289e95-969a-46e2-b681-a8c72fec5f0b" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Region of Waterloo Public Health;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Region of Waterloo Public Health&lt;/a&gt;. Debilitating conditions, such as those Van den Berg went through, affect less than 1% of people infected with WNV.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="mb-4 text-lg font-bold"&gt;Why is this concerning?&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The government of Canada's latest mosquito-borne disease surveillance &lt;a href="https://health-infobase.canada.ca/zoonoses/mosquito/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:lists;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;lists&lt;/a&gt; 239 human cases of West Nile virus. Of these, the highest number of cases — 149 — were from Ontario.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;West Nile virus can cause muscle aches, mild fever, and skin rash. In some cases, it can be deadly — especially for older adults and immunocompromised individuals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;a href="https://health-infobase.canada.ca/zoonoses/mosquito/annual-report.html" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:According;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;According&lt;/a&gt; to a government surveillance report, the country's last reported WNV-related deaths were two people over age 70 in 2023.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;In the U.S., senior citizens also died of WNV in Utah and &lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/texas/news/dallas-county-first-west-nile-death-2025/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Texas;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Texas&lt;/a&gt;, besides one death due to underlying medical conditions in&lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/detroit/news/wayne-county-west-nile-virus-death/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Wayne;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt; Wayne&lt;/a&gt;, Michigan, according to CBS News.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Continued warm temperatures have stretched the life cycle of mosquitoes nationwide, Bernadette Moussa, acting manager at Region of Waterloo Public Health, told CTV News.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Scientists attribute this extreme weather event to a massive heatwave in the northern Pacific Ocean, triggered by rising global temperatures, according to &lt;a href="https://www.cbc.ca/news/science/heat-wave-climate-change-pacific-blob-1.7652755" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:CBC;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;CBC&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="mb-4 text-lg font-bold"&gt;What's being done about it?&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Canadian news media show that health officials issued alerts immediately after confirmed cases in&lt;a href="https://www.cbc.ca/news/canada/toronto/toronto-west-nile-2025-1.7588524" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Toronto;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt; Toronto&lt;/a&gt;,&lt;a href="https://www.burlingtontoday.com/local-news/five-halton-residents-test-positive-for-west-nile-virus-11213898" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Halton;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt; Halton&lt;/a&gt;, and&lt;a href="https://www.ctvnews.ca/kitchener/article/first-human-case-of-west-nile-virus-confirmed-in-huron-perth/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Huron Perth;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt; Huron Perth&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Toronto General Hospital infectious diseases specialist Dr. Isaac Bogoch told CTV News, "Make sure that people are aware that it's circulating at certain times of the year and then taking steps to avoid and prevent mosquito bites to prevent transmission of this infection."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Meanwhile, Region of Waterloo Public Health shared simple ways to protect yourself, including applying repellent and wearing long-sleeved tops and pants when outside, especially at dusk and dawn. &lt;a href="https://guide.thecooldown.com/journeys/take-care-of-yourself/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Practice self-care;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Practice self-care&lt;/a&gt; by consulting a doctor to avoid serious complications.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Join our &lt;a href="https://www.thecooldown.com/future-newsletter/?recZjkgSONuR6b3fh" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:free newsletter;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;free newsletter&lt;/a&gt; for &lt;strong&gt;good news&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;useful tips&lt;/strong&gt;, and don't miss &lt;a href="https://rb.gy/ivhzmj" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:this cool list;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;this cool list&lt;/a&gt; of easy ways to help yourself while helping the planet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Yahoo</author><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilgFBVV95cUxPa1ZIWTNpVFNOY19McEJBWjZCSXJVdWpFYnFxYU1EMHRiNzJsaWM4TFRHY3N6LVFZV24yNjlSU0VLX1JMNFljQ1M3amNYbnJHU3pKOEU4dWZzRDZuU01lSTh1dnJ4eUp0RjBsWmRzaFdVeVJLbW9mb201dEZmWmoySDhYVHJlUXR5U05QbVpvMzY3ZWxfdGc</guid></item><item><title>一个女人的癌症似乎无法治愈。发现一种罕见的遗传疾病挽救了她的生命。- CBS新闻</title><link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/advanced-ovarian-cancer-molecular-genetic-testing-lynch-syndrome/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;section class="content__body"&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Diane Davis thought a diagnosis of advanced ovarian cancer was the answer she had been looking for. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For months, she had been sick. Antibiotics were no help. When she went to the emergency room, a CT scan and MRI showed no definitive answers. She bounced from specialist to specialist. A colonoscopy showed nothing. All the while, Davis had lower back pain and was so nauseous she could barely eat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I just got sicker and sicker," she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In January 2017, she found herself in the office of Dr. Christopher Darus, a gynecologic oncologist at MaineHealth Maine Medical Center. He was concerned by the multiple cases of cancer in her family history. He scheduled her for exploratory surgery for the next day and found a softball-sized ovarian tumor that had spread to other organs. At last, Davis knew what she was facing. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It was devastating, obviously, but I was relieved too, because at least now we knew," Davis said. &lt;/p&gt;

    
&lt;p id="mpu-plus-outstream-middle" data-ad="mpu-plus-outstream-middle" class="ad-mpu-plus-outstream-middle ad-wrapper " data-ad-unit='"mpu-plus-outstream-middle"'&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Darus, who removed the mass during the surgery, outlined a plan to treat the advanced ovarian cancer. Next would be chemotherapy. But after three cycles of chemo, Darus found a new mass growing in her pelvis. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It's "extremely rare, extremely ominous" for ovarian cancer to return that quickly, Darus said. Generally, women whose cancer does not return within six months have a better prognosis. Those whose cancer recurs faster typically "live less than two years," Darus explained. To make matters worse, Davis' cancer had also spread to her lymph nodes. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I did not expect, halfway through chemotherapy, to be in a worse situation than I was when I was first diagnosed," Davis said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="embed embed--type-image is-image embed--float-none embed--size-medium"&gt;
    
                                    
      &lt;span class="img embed__content"&gt;&lt;img src="https://assets3.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/11/06/e0a9ed6e-73ce-48fb-9425-4b810e8be938/thumbnail/620x741/7875e516c1a49d663d7d37e42bef2a46/diane-davis-get-your-rear-in-gear.png#" alt="diane-davis-get-your-rear-in-gear.png " srcset="https://assets3.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/11/06/e0a9ed6e-73ce-48fb-9425-4b810e8be938/thumbnail/620x741/7875e516c1a49d663d7d37e42bef2a46/diane-davis-get-your-rear-in-gear.png 1x" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;

      
          &lt;figcaption class="embed__caption-container"&gt;
        
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__caption"&gt;Diane Davis.&lt;/span&gt;
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__credit"&gt;
            
                Diane Davis

                          &lt;/span&gt;
              &lt;/figcaption&gt;
      &lt;/figure&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;"Like a ping-pong ball" &lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Darus submitted Davis' tumor for molecular testing, which identified unique biomarkers and led to her diagnosis with a condition called Lynch syndrome. The condition is "essentially a cancer syndrome," said Dr. Paul Oberstein, a medical oncologist at NYU Langone who studies it. A person with Lynch syndrome is more susceptible to different forms of cancer, including ovarian cancer. The diagnosis gave context to the Davis family's cancer history and opened the door for more treatment options. &lt;/p&gt;

    
    
&lt;p id="mpu-flex-inc3" data-ad="mpu-flex-inc" class="ad-mpu-flex-inc ad-wrapper " data-ad-unit='["mpu-flex-inc",3]'&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are at least four proteins that can be involved in Lynch syndrome, Darus said. The proteins typically help repair DNA. If one or more proteins are missing, as they are in Lynch patients, mistakes in the cells can accumulate, Darus said. That "is like having a messy room" to the immune system: The body knows something is wrong and immune cells will migrate to the area, Darus said. But the cancer can turn off those immune cells, so the body doesn't respond appropriately and the cancer begins to form. The tumors that arise in Lynch syndrome may have 50, 100 or more mutations, Oberstein said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That large number of mutations makes it easier for a person's immune system to respond to the tumor, Oberstein said. Using immunotherapy to activate a Lynch syndrome patient's immune system against those cancer cells can lead to positive outcomes in many cases, he said, though no treatment works for everyone. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;With few options, Darus started looking at drugs called checkpoint inhibitors, which "unmask" tumors and allow the immune system to attack cancer cells. After the Food and Drug Administration approved a drug called pembrolizumab for some patients in June 2017, he was able to prescribe it to Davis. She received the immunotherapy treatment every three weeks. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Within two treatments, the new mass in Davis' pelvis was gone, and the cancer on her lymph nodes was receding. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It was kind of like a ping-pong ball: You get diagnosed, and then you get sick again, and then having the immunotherapy just swung me right back to feeling good," Davis said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="embed embed--type-image is-image embed--float-none embed--size-medium"&gt;
    
                                    
      &lt;span class="img embed__content"&gt;&lt;img src="https://assets1.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/11/05/db17c684-ea43-4772-946f-5b71c6a175bf/thumbnail/620x465/c0bf78dbb6dfed73046c95ec76092d71/diane-davis-photo-1.jpg#" alt="diane-davis-photo-1.jpg " class=" lazyload" srcset="https://assets1.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/11/05/db17c684-ea43-4772-946f-5b71c6a175bf/thumbnail/620x465/c0bf78dbb6dfed73046c95ec76092d71/diane-davis-photo-1.jpg 1x, https://assets3.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/11/05/db17c684-ea43-4772-946f-5b71c6a175bf/thumbnail/1240x930/3983a33b2102d7dfae786d53e61756e3/diane-davis-photo-1.jpg 2x" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;

      
          &lt;figcaption class="embed__caption-container"&gt;
        
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__caption"&gt;Diane Davis. &lt;/span&gt;
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__credit"&gt;
            
                Diane Davis

                          &lt;/span&gt;
              &lt;/figcaption&gt;
      &lt;/figure&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;Finding new hope   &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Davis' Lynch syndrome diagnosis changed her family. Lynch syndrome is genetic, with about a 50% chance of it being passed from parent to child.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Davis was the first in her family to be diagnosed with it, but her family has traced it back to her paternal grandfather. Her father and uncle, who both passed away from cancer in their 60s, likely had it. Davis' brother and two sisters were also diagnosed with the condition. &lt;/p&gt;

    
    
&lt;p id="mpu-flex-inc4" data-ad="mpu-flex-inc" class="ad-mpu-flex-inc ad-wrapper " data-ad-unit='["mpu-flex-inc",4]'&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She encouraged her children to get a screener for it. Her son tested negative, but her daughter was positive. She immediately started early cancer screenings. A colonoscopy when Davis' daughter was 29, more than a decade earlier than most people begin receiving such tests, found a "very, very large precancerous polyp." It was removed without complication, Davis said. Today, her daughter remains in good health. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"At 29 years old, she would not have had that screenings until she had much more serious symptoms," Davis said. "So it's been really good in that respect." &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Davis stayed on the immunotherapy treatment for two years. Six years later, she is still healthy and thriving, with her cancer in complete remission. She still gets regular scans and is at higher risk of being diagnosed with other forms of cancer. Instead of dwelling on what the future may hold, she focuses on her grandkids, who visit often for activities like hiking and snowmobiling. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It's been amazing. It's getting further and further in the distance, which is really strange, because when the chemotherapy failed, I pretty much thought, 'This is it.' I didn't think the future looked very promising at that moment. I thought I had maybe six months, given the speed at which the cancer grew," Davis said. "But it was amazing. It was really, really amazing." &lt;/p&gt;

    

                    
        
  
          
  
  



  
    
    
  &lt;/section&gt;

  

  
  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>CBS News</author><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 13:00:02 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimgFBVV95cUxOaUdId0V5RVNtXzlTcV9DMGZLemtXTkoxNjE0NVVyb2Znb2w0QlNDanp3VC1CM1JSVHozZ3doZXYyaFRiallOYXMtNWo2dWptZ0h2UFlROE9FemFCdU85ZUk1SWl2V0JkdnhuZjdVNHRJZzdzNUNIVDFwQlNFRXBqV1lEa1BnT0pkUlVkQm5BZHh5S1NIQmR2MWpn0gGfAUFVX3lxTFBUUVpfbDdBSVkzWXFVdy1CRjlwLWZqQjB6TTZQTlAxM1UyQkQ4TFpZb1dva3JyUzJMejNJUm5nWG40TnBXTEc5c21ZTmlHRzFleE1hWXlzYnRjRF80UjlQMWk2ZWsybjR1TWgtdUdxQ2h3Z3dSRG9WcTM2RUJ1XzMyVGpjM1FVQXJPNVowN2RTZWprb2F5YXlWSFRqcmhuSQ</guid></item><item><title>我刚生了个孩子。这让我看到了我的父母在一个全新的、痛苦的光芒下对我做了什么。-石板</title><link>https://slate.com/advice/2025/11/parent-advice-baby-parents-health-rules.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article__content" itemprop="mainEntityOfPage"&gt;
          &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="16" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmhpeec0z004dzwm9j8r25yfx@published"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Care and Feeding is Slate’s parenting advice column. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Have a question for Care and Feeding? &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://forms.gle/4BXEw8Wtcd7aAyXh9"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Submit it here&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="4" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmhpekixi001o3b79zxebbab8@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dear Care and Feeding,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="24" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmhpego9s00123b79ageqwxbq@published"&gt;My husband and I had our son about six months ago, and I’m reconsidering letting my parents meet him over the holidays as planned.&lt;/p&gt;



  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="69" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmhphu99t000r3b79g06dgw0t@published"&gt;Both my parents smoke, and although they have agreed to wear new clothes they put on just before they meet him so that their clothing doesn’t reek of smoke, I am finding that I can’t stop thinking about health and safety issues around their smoking in my own childhood. I know that the type of get-together we’ve planned will not harm my baby. But that doesn’t ease my mind.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="84" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmhpegobp00133b79rcc2y3yx@published"&gt;The fact is that my brother has a scar on his neck from cigarette ash that burned him when he was a baby, and I was sick throughout my childhood with asthma and respiratory issues (I was even hospitalized once). I was shocked by the improvement in my health almost as soon as I moved out. The frequent pneumonia ended; I discovered I could safely enjoy exercise for the first time in my life. These days, I’m down to one inhaler I rarely need.&lt;/p&gt;

  

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="95" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmhpegodq00143b7933w99rpd@published"&gt;If there was something I was doing that hurt our son the way my parents hurt me, I’d like to believe I’d move mountains to quit. But my parents never even made a failed effort—and this is all despite the fact that two of my grandparents died of smoking-related causes, and there was certainly social pressure on them to quit. I’ve gone from, “Addiction is complicated and I love my parents, but they can’t change,” to “F these people, they put their two kids at risk.” How do I figure out what to do here?&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="2" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmhpegohv00163b79vycydd9p@published"&gt;—Anti-Smoking Mom&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="2" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmhpegok200173b79wic7mzet@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dear Mom,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="133" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmhpegom700183b79ufex8f9r@published"&gt;Having a child changes you, both in ways that are predictable (your schedule is turned upside down, as are your priorities—to name just two) and in ways that come as a complete surprise (I won’t even take a stab at an illustrative list for this: There are far too many to mention, and they may be different for everyone). One of the surprises for you is a reconsideration of your own childhood and your parents’ parenting of you. This particular category of surprise is not uncommon. There’s nothing quite like contemplating the utterly vulnerable, perfect, beloved brand-new human being in your arms to make you suddenly aware, in a way that’s impossible to brush off, of the mistakes, deep flaws, failures, and bad decisions of your own parents in your infancy and childhood.&lt;/p&gt;

  


  


  


  


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="79" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmhpegopn00193b79xg3q5v00@published"&gt;I think it’s fair to say that many revelations about one’s old childhood—like yours—do not constitute new information. Like many adults, until now you managed to compartmentalize the past—your parents’ smoking, the harm it caused you, and their failure to even attempt to quit—in a way that kept you from feeling (at least consciously) hurt, bewildered, and angry. Your son’s birth cracked that compartment open. Now the question is: What to do with that opened-up Pandora’s box of feelings?&lt;/p&gt;


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="165" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmhpegorf001a3b79fsu533c7@published"&gt;Don’t try to tamp them down (they’ll just pop back up). Once opened, the box cannot be closed. So feel your feelings, as unpleasant and destabilizing as they are right now. Talk about them to anyone you’re sure will be a good listener—compassionate, kind, and disinclined either to debate you &lt;em&gt;or&lt;/em&gt; egg you on (or to try to “fix” you). Your husband might be a good place to begin. Your brother might be too. But don’t underestimate the value of talking to good friends—people who love you but have no personal stake in the issue at hand. And, of course, if your parents are the kind of people who can be talked to frankly and openly without getting defensive or going on the attack (I won’t simply assume they’re not! I am ever-optimistic!), have a conversation with them, too. But if you find that you are &lt;em&gt;consumed&lt;/em&gt; with rage, are becoming depressed or extremely anxious, then talking to a therapist would be an excellent idea.&lt;/p&gt;

  


  


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="72" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmhpegotg001b3b79dabh7b8q@published"&gt;Once you begin to deal with the feelings about your childhood that have bubbled to the surface, you’ll be able to confront and make a decision about the issue at hand. Letting your parents meet their grandson—and, beyond that, allowing them to be in his life—does not have to be tightly entwined with how you feel about your own childhood: It can be decoupled from that, if you wish to decouple it.&lt;/p&gt;

  


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="96" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmhpegovy001c3b79xk5sdepn@published"&gt;I want to be clear. I’m not saying you &lt;em&gt;must&lt;/em&gt; introduce your baby this winter as planned. If you are still too hurt and angry to do that, put it off. Don’t force yourself to go through something that will further pain you. Make an excuse if you like. Or if you’d prefer to confront things directly, tell your parents the truth (no matter what kind of people they are), letting them know you need time to work through this, and set a tentative future date. You can always postpone that date if you need to.&lt;/p&gt;

  


  
  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="155" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmhpegoy1001d3b79ssoblrkc@published"&gt;It seems your parents are open to making an effort where their grandchild is concerned (there are plenty of grandparents who would be offended by being asked to change into new, clean clothes!), and I gather you’d be seeing them in your own home or on neutral grounds for the holidays, not in their smoky, smelly house. I would hope that they’ve committed to not smoking in his presence (if not, go ahead and lay down those ground rules). So the questions to consider are these: Do you &lt;em&gt;want&lt;/em&gt; your child to have a relationship with his grandparents, or not? Do &lt;em&gt;you&lt;/em&gt; want to continue to have a relationship with your parents, or not? If the answers to these questions are yes, you’re going to make sure both these things happen—if not now, then eventually. And if you’re uncertain about the answers to these questions … well, then, be patient with yourself. Give yourself grace.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="1" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmhpeqn8x002d3b79048sys0v@published"&gt;&lt;span class="slate-paragraph--tombstone"&gt;—Michelle&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  


  


  


  &lt;h3 class="subhead subhead--none" data-uri="slate.com/_components/subhead/instances/cmhpeqs5b002r3b79q1n43bi6@published"&gt;
&lt;p class="subhead__marker"&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
More Advice From Slate

&lt;/h3&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="95" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmhpeqpkv002k3b791oiz7sj2@published"&gt;My children (10, 8, 6, and 5) have been attending school virtually since March. Our 5-year-old misses his friends and the in-person nature of school, but has been doing very well in long-distance kindergarten. He’s always been a little bit behind (within normal parameters) for self-regulating and similar skills, but he’s not regressed too much. My mother-in-law moved in with us in August, for the foreseeable future, and my partner and I have noticed that she treats the 5-year-old differently than she did the others at the same age, &lt;a href="https://slate.com/human-interest/2020/12/mil-too-harsh-discipline-care-and-feeding.html"&gt;especially when it comes to discipline.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;section class="newsletter-signup   " data-list="Advice" data-uri="slate.com/_components/newsletter-signup/instances/cmhpeec0z004gzwm9bb3tgrij@published"&gt;


    &lt;p class="newsletter-signup__intro"&gt;
        &lt;svg class="newsletter-signup__arrow"&gt;
          &lt;use xlink:href="/media/components/newsletter-signup/sprite.svg#arrow"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;
        &lt;/svg&gt;
&lt;h1 class="newsletter-signup__headline"&gt;Never miss new Slate Advice columns&lt;/h1&gt;
      &lt;span class="newsletter-signup__description"&gt;Get the latest from Prudie and our columnists in your inbox each weekday, plus special bonus letters on Saturdays.&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;
    



&lt;/section&gt;

  

&lt;/div&gt;

      &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Slate</author><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigwFBVV95cUxOdnhpanRyV0R6Sy1WY01TQ01MTVBzdWg4NEFLbnVtb3pqVFBrd1kyWTM1ckRpeDhpMDNEZERWYTJ3S0l5VnpISDdUaE94bEwydmtscW9ndmdSR2ZtWXkzX0Q4U2d4UTE4TWc3OVY2NTU0M2hrRzd4Yk5qNWtkZHBfY2xYYw</guid></item><item><title>6种有助于降低血压的早晨饮料-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/6-morning-drinks-that-can-help-bring-down-blood-pressure/photostory/125181748.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="COQxt" data-ua-type="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hypertension, or High Blood Pressure, affects millions of people from all across the world. Known as a ‘silent killer’, Hypertension is extremely dangerous, and lead to heart attacks and strokes. Apart from diet, medication, and lifestyle changes, there are a couple of morning drinks, that if consumed regularly, can bring BP in control. However, remember that they are not a substitute for medication, but can only aid in keeping BP in check. Take a look…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 12:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi2wFBVV95cUxPVWtlUzZrU0dQaXR0MTdQaDZ4T1BuazhfRWEtQjYtNHNqWmhaVDJUT3pNdVlDUEY2Y1hCaF9SZzhGNTZzYUpJb0Q1bVBHR3RkbG91dG1LSG9CaVdtRUJ6T3VqRmJSRUJJM29kaGFSV0xoVGE2Q3hXbDA3SDJpSUdmYkFVSU5RNWZLVTAyM0xvZnpYeU1oU1kya1d6T00zOFB0U0FWY1VBN1pUQXFGQ3RzX05sd0E5OVY4Qkdjd1c4OXI5NkZELVR2LTdSV3VOSWZ2TUlQWDhUZ1dlMlnSAeMBQVVfeXFMTkVxSGRIYXNpOC1TNlc0T1AtbTFBX2E0czk5eTBNUlJOVExTdUhNeVB6SG1FdnZBLVpsXzJSQjVxek5NSERDdUZ4QzdPYjZhc3Z2akpCSXlSZG9tTUhnNExJWlhtUkQtUXRUSDZVbFg4RkZKYTRuNkpBS0JpcV9TbGoySUd2Y25Rdko2cEpjLTVDR2pBWWVwY2VRbG1tWExGNC12M1dVRjNxNEdjY0RFb3ZFQUNqR2tmTEdzNjFoaTYyZ3VBWnJ0TGVjXzJJWVg4WmZzMHVSQ3Jlb3d3ZEM4Zlp2V3M</guid></item><item><title>骆驼和美洲驼中的一种独特蛋白质可以保护大脑免受阿尔茨海默氏症的侵害- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/a-unique-protein-in-camels-and-llamas-may-protect-the-brain-from-alzheimers</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Nanoscopic proteins made from the  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/antibody" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73081" data-postid="180301" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;antibodies&lt;/a&gt; of animals like camels and llamas can penetrate into cellular spaces like no other antibodies can. Mounting evidence suggests these tiny molecules could even be put to work protecting the brain from difficult-to-treat conditions like  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/go/IaO" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73015" data-postid="180301" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;Alzheimer's&lt;/a&gt; and  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/schizophrenia" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73022" data-postid="180301" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;schizophrenia&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a new paper, a team of scientists from the Centre National de la Recherche Scientifique (CNRS) in France explains where the research has gotten us so far, and what lies ahead.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The CNRS experts believe their small size may make them ideal for reaching into and &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/new-alzheimers-treatment-clears-plaques-from-brains-of-mice-within-hours"&gt;treating the brain&lt;/a&gt; with fewer side-effects, though so far, the four nanobody therapies available have been approved only for treating other parts of the body.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/ozempic-literally-came-from-a-monster-and-its-not-alone"&gt;Ozempic Literally Came From a Monster – And It's Not Alone&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Antibody"&gt;Antibodies&lt;/a&gt; are proteins that our immune system uses to tag unwanted materials in the body –  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/virus" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73053" data-postid="180301" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;viruses&lt;/a&gt;, toxins, and the like – as trash to be removed by our biological cleanup crew.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Single-domain_antibody"&gt;Nanobodies&lt;/a&gt; are stripped-down versions of these proteins, and their sleek, stealthy build means they can squeeze between a &lt;span&gt;virus&lt;/span&gt;'s defenses to disarm its most dangerous parts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Members of the &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Camelidae"&gt;camelid family&lt;/a&gt; (including llamas, camels, and alpacas) naturally produce smaller antibodies than humans. &lt;span&gt;Scientists have further refined these in the lab to be about 10 times smaller than the common Y-shaped Immunoglobulin G antibody.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_180380" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-180380" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/gr1_lrg-4-642x336.jpg" alt="A Unique Characteristic in Camels And Llamas Could Be Used to Treat Alzheimer's" class="size-medium wp-image-180380" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/gr1_lrg-4-642x336.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/gr1_lrg-4-768x402.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/gr1_lrg-4-600x314.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/gr1_lrg-4.jpg 1200w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-180380" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Nanobodies have unique features for targeting the central nervous system. (Lafon et al., &lt;em&gt;Trends in Pharm. Sci.&lt;/em&gt;, 2025)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;While sharks are also known to produce nanobodies, it's our mammalian relatives whose biological machinery is best positioned to supplement our comparatively clunky immune systems.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nanobodies made from camelids have already shown promise in protecting humans from &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/nano-scale-multidomain-antibodies-from-camelids-used-for-universal-influenza-vaccine"&gt;influenza A and B&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/llamas-hide-a-powerful-weapon-that-can-fight-deadly-virus-strains"&gt;the gastro-causing norovirus&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/llama-blood-could-play-a-role-in-helping-people-fight-off-coronavirus-infections"&gt;COVID-19&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/a-hidden-defense-inside-llamas-could-be-the-secret-to-fighting-hiv"&gt;even HIV&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Until recently, it seemed nanobodies could not be used to treat brain disorders because human kidneys eliminate them from the bloodstream before they even get a chance to reach their target destination. It also seemed they may not readily cross the &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/scientists-think-theyre-on-the-verge-of-breaching-the-blood-brain-barrier"&gt;blood brain barrier&lt;/a&gt;: a decisive checkpoint for any drugs targeting the brain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/spark-into-space-comp"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro-642x272.jpg" alt="Win a $10,000 Space Coast Adventure Holiday" class="alignnone wp-image-177074 size-medium" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro-642x272.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro-768x326.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro-600x255.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro.jpg 844w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But newer studies have overcome these challenges, with animal model lab experiments showing that engineered nanobodies can cross the blood brain barrier to target and eliminate key markers of Alzheimer's disease thought to drive symptoms, &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1038/s41467-025-58383-4"&gt;tau&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.3390/ijms24032632"&gt;amyloid beta&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Camelid nanobodies open a new era of biologic therapies for brain disorders and revolutionize our thinking about therapeutics," &lt;a href="https://www.scimex.org/newsfeed/camels-and-llamas-could-hold-the-key-to-treating-future-brain-disorders"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; Philippe Rondard, neuropharmacologist at CNRS. "We believe they can form a new class of drugs between conventional antibodies and small molecules."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But before these drugs get anywhere near a living human brain, scientists will need to evaluate their stability, proper folding, and ensure the absence of aggregation, Rondard says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;"These are highly soluble small proteins that can enter the brain passively," &lt;a href="https://www.scimex.org/newsfeed/camels-and-llamas-could-hold-the-key-to-treating-future-brain-disorders"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; functional genomicist Pierre-André Lafon. "By contrast, small-molecule drugs that are designed to cross the blood-brain barrier are hydrophobic in nature, which limits their bioavailability, increases the risk of off-target binding, and is linked to side effects."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We also need to know more about exactly how they're crossing the blood brain barrier, and how long they hang around in the brain, to ensure proper dosage. Scientists will also need to develop clinical-grade, stable formulations that can survive long-term storage and transport, from lab to patient.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;"Our lab has already started to study these different parameters for a few brain-penetrant nanobodies and has recently shown that conditions of treatment are compatible with chronic treatment," Lafon &lt;a href="https://www.scimex.org/newsfeed/camels-and-llamas-could-hold-the-key-to-treating-future-brain-disorders"&gt;adds&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Perhaps one day we will be thanking camels for saving our precious memories – but it's still a long way off.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This research was published in &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.tips.2025.10.004"&gt;Trends in Pharmacological Sciences&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 11:52:06 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipwFBVV95cUxPajFBTlBPS0xGcWJSYllJM2tEa3VVTWNMWXFFZzBuVXB0WGVwT1Y2NlQzenREWXhyMnR4cUIyeE9EaVh6eExpZHFDWVV6SjJDZFNVQXR5MzFrLUVmQm1wOTh6Rk1MVWp3OU5HeWVIMTZ2eTdnWGJvaG1VNlFUenVfazFJbTJiNDItWTFpNlNCTk55VWViSUlSYllHeU11eGFpaGdjT2xVbw</guid></item><item><title>想活得更久吗？神经病学家建议进行一项简单的运动，从字面上“增加”大脑大小-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/want-to-live-longer-neurologist-recommends-a-simple-exercise-that-can-literally-increase-brain-size/articleshow/125085485.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr. Austin Perlmutter, a neurologist and well‑known brain‑health specialist recently revealed that a simple exercise can in fact, build new brain cells. Yes, that is true! Read on to know more…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="1"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr Perlmutter says that while exercise is one of the most powerful ways to build new brain cells, amidst that, walking is the clear winner. According to the doctor, taking walks can actually stimulate the formation of new neurons. This simple, free and no fuss activity, can bolster memory and decelerate the onset of cognitive decline. In an IG video, Dr Perlmutter laid out the data that demonstrate how walking, and other forms of movement, can reshape the brain in a new direction.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="5"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="7"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Fires up the brain&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="9"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="10"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr. Perlmutter points to research showing that taking walks can actually kick‑start the birth of new brain cells, a process scientists call neurogenesis. Key areas of the brain involved in memory particularly the hippocampus, grow larger with regular physical activity. In a landmark trial involving adults those who logged a year of walking, ended up with roughly 2 % larger hippocampus size, than the participants who stuck to stretching alone; on the other hand, the stretch‑only group even experienced a slight shrinkage. This growth matters, because the hippocampus is crucial for both forming new memories, and pulling them back when we need them. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Taking walks fortifies this brain area, helping it stay robust and fend off the impacts of aging and illnesses such as Alzheimer’s.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="17"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;How walking helps&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="19"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to Dr. Perlmutter, getting your body moving sends a burst of signals to your brain urging it to stay sharp and alert. Those cues essentially tell your brain that you’re actively engaging with your surroundings, prompting neurons to stay healthy and tightly linked. Exercise also ramps up blood flow and oxygen delivery to brain tissue improving brain activity. Not only that, constant movement nudges muscles to release a mix of signaling molecules called myokines, among which the well‑known brain‑derived neurotrophic factor (BDNF) plays a role. BDNF plays the role of a fertiliser for brain cells, nudging the creation of neurons, while bolstering the survival and performance of the ones already present.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="25"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="27"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Major boost for brain health&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="29"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Taking a stroll is one of the best ways to get the heart pumping, and the blood flowing, and it doesn't demand any fancy equipment or a gym card. According to Dr. Perlmutter, a quick dose of movement, like a regular walk, gives a boost to every system that fuels the brain-from immunity and metabolism, to neuroplasticity (the brain’s ability to adapt and rewire). Clocking in a handful of walking sessions each week, can actually increase brain matters that govern memory, cognition and emotional regulation. The best part is that walking is accessible to all, without any limitations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="33"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Reduces risk of cognitive decline&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="35"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to research highlighted by Dr. Perlmutter, taking a stroll does more than grow new cells - it also appears to slow the slide of cognitive decline. Larger brain volumes and elevated BDNF levels, have been linked to a risk of Alzheimer’s disease and other dementias. A range of studies shows that people who make walks a habit, tend to preserve memory, keener attention and more agile problem‑solving abilities, as they age. Those benefits in turn, help them stay independent longer and enjoy a steady quality of life. A steady walking routine pushes back on inflammation and other dangerous mechanisms that wear down tissue, making it a crucial non‑pharmacological approach, to brain protection.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="39"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;How to walk for brain health&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="41"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr. Perlmutter recommends a consistent routine: walk for at least thirty minutes a day most days of the week. You don’t need to be an athlete, he says: just move enough to raise your heart rate and breathe a little heavier (the rule of thumb is that you should be able to talk, but not sing) If thirty minutes feels challenging at first, break it into 2 sessions of 15 minutes each. Walking outside in a park, or garden also adds benefits like soaking up sunlight for vitamin D, and giving the mind a relaxing break. Pick routes that feel safe, so you can really enjoy your walk, and make sure that you wear the right shoes, since the wrong ones might leave you with pain, or worse, an injury. The trick is staying consistent, because that way your brain keeps soaking up those growth signals day after day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="46"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="48"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="50"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Times of India</author><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 11:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilgJBVV95cUxNWTVhZTFSZThVRzhYcWxKZW1NMmRUX2d1d19Bcnp5U0x5bUJWMDdLX1BfWDZRR0VWLTNLdEdJYWxId042TnBNMHo0V2hxcjMwQ3NjbExPM3pJaFdCRDk0MUxwUWtYUTBHTUpVYm5lVG9XNDl3N2thaTRzQV9WN2YwcUdSb0NlNTVKVHNoQUNKREQ1NVlGN2xOVXBsMFVvTzk0Ni1vRElsMVFfc0xxUFA3M3R3U1hXSVJtUVVYNS1JMTM4S3k4WmhZTW5MVGdEMnZvdDdIU2liVW16clRXS3lHNFBJQjVDOWhxYTY3UWxaVUhXVHZJOXhPUTBsb2gwRmkydVhtTzFWWUhHSjJrOGI5MGp5NzB4QQ</guid></item><item><title>糟糕的空气是您健康的最大威胁之一。以下是如何保护自己的方法-有线</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/one-of-the-biggest-threats-to-your-health-is-something-you-cant-see/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="body__inner-container"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="lead-in-text-callout"&gt;There's something invisible&lt;/span&gt; that can put us in an early grave. And I’m not talking about sentient AI, but something much more ubiquitous and real. While AI doomers predict the existential risk that artificial intelligence poses to humanity, air pollution—specifically, ultrafine particulate matter, &lt;a href="https://www.epa.gov/pm-pollution/particulate-matter-pm-basics"&gt;PM 2.5&lt;/a&gt;—has been an efficient killer for decades. Many people don't realize there are volumes of scientific evidence that link cardiovascular disease, diabetes, and brain damage to the growing list of bleak health consequences of bad air.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;According to the &lt;a href="https://www.who.int/news-room/fact-sheets/detail/ambient-(outdoor)-air-quality-and-health"&gt;World Health Organization&lt;/a&gt;, air pollution caused 4.2 million premature deaths worldwide in 2019. As &lt;a href="https://www.epa.gov/newsreleases/epa-launches-biggest-deregulatory-action-us-history"&gt;Trump's EPA&lt;/a&gt; continues to roll back standards and deregulate industries that cause air pollution, the burden of maintaining a safe breathing environment is increasingly falling on individuals. Luckily, there are some steps you can take.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="paywall"&gt;Turning Back the Clock&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;PM 2.5, produced by wildfires, automobile exhaust, power plants, and industries like mining, enters the body through the nose and mouth through the simple act of breathing. Once inside the body, PM 2.5 can enter the bloodstream and the brain. Air pollution’s impact on public health and life expectancy isn’t novel. In 1970, 22 years after the deadly &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC5922205/" target="_blank"&gt;Donora Smog Event&lt;/a&gt; that killed 20 people and sickened over 6,000 in Western Pennsylvania, the &lt;a href="https://www.epa.gov/clean-air-act-overview" target="_blank"&gt;Clean Air Act&lt;/a&gt; became federal law.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Container-VgtPr ekoLDG"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;Earlier this year, the Trump administration &lt;a href="https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/07/regulatory-relief-for-certain-stationary-sources-to-promote-american-iron-ore-processing-security/?"&gt;repealed&lt;/a&gt; the Biden administration’s new standards for air pollutants from taconite iron ore processing, exempting private sectors from complying, saying, “Preserving and enhancing domestic taconite processing capabilities … ensuring [the] resilience of American industrial supply chains.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;Taconite iron ore processing creates a &lt;a data-offer-url="https://www.leg.mn.gov/docs/2015/other/150681/PFEISref_1/Jiang%20et%20al.%20n.d.pdf" class="external-link" data-event-click='{"element":"ExternalLink","outgoingURL":"https://www.leg.mn.gov/docs/2015/other/150681/PFEISref_1/Jiang%20et%20al.%20n.d.pdf"}' href="https://www.leg.mn.gov/docs/2015/other/150681/PFEISref_1/Jiang%20et%20al.%20n.d.pdf" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;major amount of PM 2.5&lt;/a&gt;. Trump’s White House also repealed recent emissions standards for &lt;a href="https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/07/regulatory-relief-for-certain-stationary-sources-to-further-promote-american-energy/?" target="_blank"&gt;coal- and oil-fired electric utility steam&lt;/a&gt;, along with several other industries. As America’s commitment to limiting air pollution declines, there are appliances and actions you can take to keep the air you breathe healthier, both indoors and outside.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="paywall"&gt;It Can Cause Heart Disease&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;When people think of high blood pressure, air pollution might not be what they envision. More often, stress, smoking, poor diet, or genetics might come to mind, but air pollution, PM 2.5, can cause and/or contribute to hypertension. NYU cardiologist Jonathan Newman, an expert on the link between the environment and cardiovascular disease, says that “in broad strokes, air pollution can affect cardiovascular risk factors, blood sugar/diabetes, blood pressure/hypertension.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;Invisible PM 2.5 reaches the deepest part of the lungs, entering the lung’s tiny air sacs, where it passes through the barrier to enter the bloodstream. There, it can build up into plaque on the arterial walls, known as atherosclerotic cardiovascular disease. According to Newman, “Generally this occurs through direct effects of inflammation, neurohormonal effects, direct particle effects.” The interaction of PM 2.5 causes an imbalance with free radicals and antioxidants that puts stress on the body, causing inflammation and &lt;a href="https://my.clevelandclinic.org/health/articles/oxidative-stress" target="_blank"&gt;oxidative stress&lt;/a&gt; that leads to cell damage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;In other words, PM 2.5 can wreak havoc on the molecular level. The World Health Organization recommends that average annual concentrations not exceed 10 micrograms per cubic meter, with daily levels under 20 micrograms per cubic meter. Those guidelines are difficult to live by. A &lt;a href="https://www.ahajournals.org/doi/full/10.1161/ATVBAHA.120.315219" target="_blank"&gt;study&lt;/a&gt; found that “over 90 percent of the world population lives at PM 2.5 levels above World Health Organization standards.” The cheapest and easiest protection is to use a well-made N95 &lt;a href="https://www.wired.com/story/best-disposable-face-masks-n95-kn95-kf94-surgical/"&gt;face mask&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;a href="https://www.wired.com/story/best-disposable-face-masks-n95-kn95-kf94-surgical/" target="_blank"&gt;I carry an N95 mask with me&lt;/a&gt; at all times, as I cannot predict if a good-air day will turn into a bad-air night. The practice of carrying a just-in-case mask is one way to have agency over the air you breathe.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-testid="feature-large-callout" class="CalloutFeatureLargeWrapper-cAQNly bLNMaC"&gt;&lt;div class="UnifiedProductCardBody-hIYvDT cYxZHF product-embed" data-item='{"ctaHref":"https://cna.st/p/CwhBZx5kSvgnvej9URPBT4ahwv1BF2pXhALcSRSjBQUcYGBWGxKxxbVvzqy9LVghNGW2Q4VRmqJKBJMWWYGxP6ad6Lsu5nCmkmo632yt6yPQDBaaDDnaUm8YMj9CVyT8cC4BsaVyTigaDZmwnZkcNTCKmoe1wiv77cymrp5XXk8Da9WUAd1fPooxEsd6qfCHFwzvzZkk3ovupL4wc1XGG4aWNKViPZMyBNjeohZhkWotZ7fFr6WFKx88pLvMdWb2Vpbmq2SJkwNuYuJUFaWzshRSpgxteBDP9U81rdCxKFQknBNS1BW3JMMdZFzM3oCTH3AKH2yWoRP9Gis4jUXRUJ2FiQYqETh1nBzQY4wNJov4uZ5n42LtvS4jYTv3EnshE5SynStoEz1jc4JQNS5hePDaGNkVhoFmFwUbv5ZjG9oV8sFKBaxfWaBvFHVaTpSBA9GkwjMLhX17jA8HGQwqY6yj9LCi9vv5615kUXMi8rkt2yRj4caBc8PMZQGGyxMDs9Jrqas4AQ3V64Vz8m1oAGQfptqk1eJs7QVBXaUUxzrHpHnAyj7s","dangerousDek":"","productBrand":"3M","dangerousHed":"Particulate Respirator N95","embedSize":"feature-medium","isFirstProduct":false,"image":{"altText":"Image may contain: Accessories, Bag, and Handbag","credit":"Photograph: Lisa Wood Shapiro","sources":{"sm":{"aspectRatio":"4:3","width":320,"url":"https://media.wired.com/photos/6801787274dbf5e99c2111ab/4:3/w_320,c_limit/Best-N95-Masks_3M-8511-particulate-respirator_Photo-SOURCE-Lisa-Wood-Shapiro.jpg","srcset":"https://media.wired.com/photos/6801787274dbf5e99c2111ab/4:3/w_120,c_limit/Best-N95-Masks_3M-8511-particulate-respirator_Photo-SOURCE-Lisa-Wood-Shapiro.jpg 120w, https://media.wired.com/photos/6801787274dbf5e99c2111ab/4:3/w_240,c_limit/Best-N95-Masks_3M-8511-particulate-respirator_Photo-SOURCE-Lisa-Wood-Shapiro.jpg 240w, https://media.wired.com/photos/6801787274dbf5e99c2111ab/4:3/w_320,c_limit/Best-N95-Masks_3M-8511-particulate-respirator_Photo-SOURCE-Lisa-Wood-Shapiro.jpg 320w"},"md":{"aspectRatio":"4:3","width":640,"url":"https://media.wired.com/photos/6801787274dbf5e99c2111ab/4:3/w_640,c_limit/Best-N95-Masks_3M-8511-particulate-respirator_Photo-SOURCE-Lisa-Wood-Shapiro.jpg","srcset":"https://media.wired.com/photos/6801787274dbf5e99c2111ab/4:3/w_120,c_limit/Best-N95-Masks_3M-8511-particulate-respirator_Photo-SOURCE-Lisa-Wood-Shapiro.jpg 120w, https://media.wired.com/photos/6801787274dbf5e99c2111ab/4:3/w_240,c_limit/Best-N95-Masks_3M-8511-particulate-respirator_Photo-SOURCE-Lisa-Wood-Shapiro.jpg 240w, https://media.wired.com/photos/6801787274dbf5e99c2111ab/4:3/w_320,c_limit/Best-N95-Masks_3M-8511-particulate-respirator_Photo-SOURCE-Lisa-Wood-Shapiro.jpg 320w, https://media.wired.com/photos/6801787274dbf5e99c2111ab/4:3/w_640,c_limit/Best-N95-Masks_3M-8511-particulate-respirator_Photo-SOURCE-Lisa-Wood-Shapiro.jpg 640w"},"lg":{"aspectRatio":"4:3","width":640,"url":"https://media.wired.com/photos/6801787274dbf5e99c2111ab/4:3/w_640,c_limit/Best-N95-Masks_3M-8511-particulate-respirator_Photo-SOURCE-Lisa-Wood-Shapiro.jpg","srcset":"https://media.wired.com/photos/6801787274dbf5e99c2111ab/4:3/w_120,c_limit/Best-N95-Masks_3M-8511-particulate-respirator_Photo-SOURCE-Lisa-Wood-Shapiro.jpg 120w, https://media.wired.com/photos/6801787274dbf5e99c2111ab/4:3/w_240,c_limit/Best-N95-Masks_3M-8511-particulate-respirator_Photo-SOURCE-Lisa-Wood-Shapiro.jpg 240w, https://media.wired.com/photos/6801787274dbf5e99c2111ab/4:3/w_320,c_limit/Best-N95-Masks_3M-8511-particulate-respirator_Photo-SOURCE-Lisa-Wood-Shapiro.jpg 320w, https://media.wired.com/photos/6801787274dbf5e99c2111ab/4:3/w_640,c_limit/Best-N95-Masks_3M-8511-particulate-respirator_Photo-SOURCE-Lisa-Wood-Shapiro.jpg 640w"},"xl":{"aspectRatio":"4:3","width":640,"url":"https://media.wired.com/photos/6801787274dbf5e99c2111ab/4:3/w_640,c_limit/Best-N95-Masks_3M-8511-particulate-respirator_Photo-SOURCE-Lisa-Wood-Shapiro.jpg","srcset":"https://media.wired.com/photos/6801787274dbf5e99c2111ab/4:3/w_120,c_limit/Best-N95-Masks_3M-8511-particulate-respirator_Photo-SOURCE-Lisa-Wood-Shapiro.jpg 120w, https://media.wired.com/photos/6801787274dbf5e99c2111ab/4:3/w_240,c_limit/Best-N95-Masks_3M-8511-particulate-respirator_Photo-SOURCE-Lisa-Wood-Shapiro.jpg 240w, https://media.wired.com/photos/6801787274dbf5e99c2111ab/4:3/w_320,c_limit/Best-N95-Masks_3M-8511-particulate-respirator_Photo-SOURCE-Lisa-Wood-Shapiro.jpg 320w, https://media.wired.com/photos/6801787274dbf5e99c2111ab/4:3/w_640,c_limit/Best-N95-Masks_3M-8511-particulate-respirator_Photo-SOURCE-Lisa-Wood-Shapiro.jpg 640w"},"xxl":{"aspectRatio":"4:3","width":640,"url":"https://media.wired.com/photos/6801787274dbf5e99c2111ab/4:3/w_640,c_limit/Best-N95-Masks_3M-8511-particulate-respirator_Photo-SOURCE-Lisa-Wood-Shapiro.jpg","srcset":"https://media.wired.com/photos/6801787274dbf5e99c2111ab/4:3/w_120,c_limit/Best-N95-Masks_3M-8511-particulate-respirator_Photo-SOURCE-Lisa-Wood-Shapiro.jpg 120w, https://media.wired.com/photos/6801787274dbf5e99c2111ab/4:3/w_240,c_limit/Best-N95-Masks_3M-8511-particulate-respirator_Photo-SOURCE-Lisa-Wood-Shapiro.jpg 240w, https://media.wired.com/photos/6801787274dbf5e99c2111ab/4:3/w_320,c_limit/Best-N95-Masks_3M-8511-particulate-respirator_Photo-SOURCE-Lisa-Wood-Shapiro.jpg 320w, https://media.wired.com/photos/6801787274dbf5e99c2111ab/4:3/w_640,c_limit/Best-N95-Masks_3M-8511-particulate-respirator_Photo-SOURCE-Lisa-Wood-Shapiro.jpg 640w"}}},"isSponsored":false,"offerRetailer":"Amazon (10 pack)","offerUrl":"https://www.amazon.com/3M-50051138543438-Particulate-Respirator-8511/dp/B07571J7V9?th=1","contentType":"product","productId":"67f420014042c13de66136b7","showOfferUrl":false,"showPriceOnButton":true,"showAffiliateDisclaimerOnFirstProduct":false,"dangerousCredit":"Photograph: Lisa Wood Shapiro","showLocalisedOffers":true,"isUpcEnabled":true,"showClampedProductDescription":true,"productDescriptionLineLength":5,"hasReadMoreFeature":false,"index":1,"hasAffiliateLinkDisabled":false,"isMobileView":false,"hasMultipleImageSupport":true,"showImageCreditText":true,"showMultipleImageCount":4,"hasProsConsFeature":false,"hasRatingFeature":false,"pros":[],"cons":[],"rating":"","shouldUseAmazonPrimeDayLiveAPIData":false,"contentInfo":{"contentUrl":"https://www.wired.com/story/one-of-the-biggest-threats-to-your-health-is-something-you-cant-see/","contentName":"Bad Air Is One of the Biggest Threats to Your Health. Here’s How to Protect Yourself"},"enableGtmFixesIntersectionObserver":true,"enableGtmFixesUseRef":true,"textBadge":null,"seal":null,"id":"67f420014042c13de66136b7","brand":{"name":"3M"},"offers":[{"offerUrl":"https://www.amazon.com/3M-50051138543438-Particulate-Respirator-8511/dp/B07571J7V9?th=1","price":"$30","currency":"USD","purchaseUri":"https://cna.st/p/CwhBZx5kSvgnvej9URPBT4ahwv1BF2pXhALcSRSjBQUcYGBWGxKxxbVvzqy9LVghNGW2Q4VRmqJKBJMWWYGxP6ad6Lsu5nCmkmo632yt6yPQDBaaDDnaUm8YMj9CVyT8cC4BsaVyTigaDZmwnZkcNTCKmoe1wiv77cymrp5XXk8Da9WUAd1fPooxEsd6qfCHFwzvzZkk3ovupL4wc1XGG4aWNKViPZMyBNjeohZhkWotZ7fFr6WFKx88pLvMdWb2Vpbmq2SJkwNuYuJUFaWzshRSpgxteBDP9U81rdCxKFQknBNS1BW3JMMdZFzM3oCTH3AKH2yWoRP9Gis4jUXRUJ2FiQYqETh1nBzQY4wNJov4uZ5n42LtvS4jYTv3EnshE5SynStoEz1jc4JQNS5hePDaGNkVhoFmFwUbv5ZjG9oV8sFKBaxfWaBvFHVaTpSBA9GkwjMLhX17jA8HGQwqY6yj9LCi9vv5615kUXMi8rkt2yRj4caBc8PMZQGGyxMDs9Jrqas4AQ3V64Vz8m1oAGQfptqk1eJs7QVBXaUUxzrHpHnAyj7s","reducedPrice":"$23","sellerName":"Amazon (10 pack)","countryCode":"US","offerId":"67f4215e4042c13de66136b9"}],"component":"unified_product_card","total_index":1,"hasMultipleImage":false,"showProsConsData":false,"videoIds":[],"offersLength":1}'&gt;&lt;div id="67f420014042c13de66136b7" class="UnifiedLandscapeProductCardWrapper-lpCYz eTmaGM"&gt;&lt;div class="UnifiedProductCardContainer-jfmyrc hJJXyx"&gt;&lt;div class="UnifiedProductCardImageContainer-cKSUFL dayPqC"&gt;&lt;div class="upcSingleImageWrapper-bMOWWA jGaikA"&gt;&lt;p class="UnifiedProductCardImageCreditText-IXcDI cYcQnj"&gt;Photograph: Lisa Wood Shapiro&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="UnifiedProductCardDetailsContainer-jzIVFy dEeeEw"&gt;&lt;div class="UnifiedProductCardDetailsWrapper-ieavYi jwXcRS"&gt;&lt;div class="UnifiedProductCardDetails-dTZxUl hEAQFX"&gt;&lt;p class="BaseWrap-sc-gzmcOU BaseText-eqOrNE UnifiedProductCardBrandName-kmvqXz deqABF fmYMxY jpHfSL upc-brandName"&gt;3M&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="BaseWrap-sc-gzmcOU BaseText-eqOrNE UnifiedProductCardNameWrapper-fsdgKv deqABF eCPEdo izjkDw"&gt;&lt;h3 id="upc_67f420014042c13de66136b7" type="embed" class="BaseWrap-sc-gzmcOU BaseText-eqOrNE UnifiedProductCardName-jDmuEE deqABF ctbzXQ hdWBHD"&gt;Particulate Respirator N95&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h2 class="paywall"&gt;It Can Progress Diabetes&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;Newman was one of the coauthors of &lt;a data-offer-url="https://www.frontiersin.org/journals/endocrinology/articles/10.3389/fendo.2024.1321323/full" class="external-link" data-event-click='{"element":"ExternalLink","outgoingURL":"https://www.frontiersin.org/journals/endocrinology/articles/10.3389/fendo.2024.1321323/full"}' href="https://www.frontiersin.org/journals/endocrinology/articles/10.3389/fendo.2024.1321323/full" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;last year's study&lt;/a&gt; that found that “air pollution exposure has been implicated in the onset and progression of diabetes. Increased exposure to fine particulate matter air pollution (PM 2.5) is associated with increases in blood glucose and all forms of diabetes.” The findings are not new; in studies going as far back as 1967, researchers have found a link between high levels of PM 2.5 in ambient air (outdoor air) and an increase in diabetes deaths. And while there are other contributors to diabetes such as obesity and genetics, there is a link between the inflammation caused by PM 2.5 and diabetes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="paywall"&gt;It Can Impair Brain Development&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;While respiratory disease has long been studied as a negative outcome of air pollution, recent &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S0197018619305078"&gt;studies&lt;/a&gt; show that it also impacts the nervous system and brain development, linking PM 2.5 with stroke, changes in cognitive function, dementia, and psychiatric disorders. In particular, that fine and ultrafine particulate matter has an outsized impact, as it can be absorbed into the bloodstream to reach the central nervous system.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;And how does this happen? One possible and terrifying way is through the &lt;a href="https://my.clevelandclinic.org/health/body/23081-olfactory-nerve" target="_blank"&gt;olfactory nerve&lt;/a&gt;, the shortest nerve in your body, which enables us to smell. It goes from your brain to the upper inside part of your nose. To understand how something tiny like PM 2.5 can cause inflammation, a 2022 &lt;a data-offer-url="https://www.frontiersin.org/journals/molecular-neuroscience/articles/10.3389/fnmol.2022.967174/full" class="external-link" data-event-click='{"element":"ExternalLink","outgoingURL":"https://www.frontiersin.org/journals/molecular-neuroscience/articles/10.3389/fnmol.2022.967174/full"}' href="https://www.frontiersin.org/journals/molecular-neuroscience/articles/10.3389/fnmol.2022.967174/full" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;study&lt;/a&gt; reiterated, “PM 2.5 can pass through the lung-gas-blood barrier and the ‘gut-microbial-brain’ axis to cause systemic oxidative stress and inflammation, or directly enter brain tissue &lt;em&gt;via&lt;/em&gt; the olfactory nerve.” That PM 2.5 accumulates and results in oxidative stress (the free radicals and antioxidants have an imbalance), where it can “cause systemic inflammation and brain tissue damage.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>WIRED</author><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 11:06:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMinAFBVV95cUxPd1BzU1BSUXdxeWtsOXZGQ2NrWU1hRlQ3Qk0yQW9ZcThfSTlKTjdKT0prVEJiUmV4NmE4emRVOTNsUGZwdVBQTlpKY0UtX01QdWZoeGRLY0JEaVREdk52WFY4ZmxORzhnVTRtMW11a1N1SkEyWmQ2Q1p0bzZqMDNneDFxVFZzNnotbDlNejNLZmt0WGJocUJKQVhKSHY</guid></item><item><title>服用降压药的理想时间是什么时候？顶尖心脏病专家揭示令人惊讶的事实--《印度时报》</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/when-is-the-ideal-time-to-take-your-blood-pressure-medicine-top-cardiologist-reveals-surprising-fact/articleshow/125135399.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;p&gt;People who suffer from Hypertension, or high Blood Pressure, often wonder when is the right time to take their blood‑pressure medication. Dr. Levine, a New York‑based cardiologist recently answered this in a video, according to research findings and patient‑focused strategies, for effective blood‑pressure control. Let’s dig deeper…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="3"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="4"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Is the timing important&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="6"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="7"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Consistently taking one’s medication is a way to keep hypertension in check, and cut down on the odds of heart attacks, strokes and kidney disease. For years, a handful of experts have speculated that the timing of taking the medicine, be it sunrise or bedtime, might change the outcomes. Dr. Levine however, argues that the ideal timing is simply the slot that merges best with an individual’s schedule; in practice, sticking to the regimen and making it convenient, outweighs any clock‑time considerations for most drugs, says Dr Levine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="10"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;What Dr. Levine recommends&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="12"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="13"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr. Levine advises his patients to take their blood‑pressure medication at whatever time they will remember it-he often suggests leaving the bottle by the bathroom sink, and taking a dose after brushing teeth. He stresses that this habit helps avoid skipping doses, which is a far bigger concern, than taking it at a particular time of the day. Skipping a dose, even for one day, can mess up your Blood Pressure readings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; Ultimately, patients should pick a routine that best fits their lifestyle, whether that means a morning, afternoon or evening dose.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="17"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="19"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;What the data says&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="21"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Earlier investigations hinted that taking blood‑pressure pills at night might better curb the early‑morning spikes. However, latest studies, notably the TIME trial, found no meaningful difference in outcomes between morning and evening dosing. Cardiologists now agree that the crucial point is taking your medicine consistently, and not the hour on the clock. Whether you choose a morning dose, an evening dose or any time that fits your routine, the evidence shows each approach is equally safe and effective.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="25"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Medication type matters&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="27"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr. Levine notes that whenever feasible, a once‑daily dose is the right approach, rather than multiple doses. Requiring patients to take medication two or three times a day, often leads to confusion and missed pills-a problem especially common among older adults. He is particularly wary of instructions such, as "one and a half tablets twice a day", because they tend to reduce the likelihood of intake. Both his clinical experience and research findings confirm that adherence slips, as the number of doses rises, and shifting from a once‑daily to multiple doses can cut compliance by 14 %. If you have been prescribed multiple doses, talk to your doctor-he/she might be able to blend doses.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="33"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Individual preferences&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="35"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;At the end of the day, Dr. Levine stresses that physicians should personalise patient recommendations, and adjust medication seamlessly into each individual’s lifestyle, so it never slips the mind. You might decide to take your pill with breakfast right after you’ve brushed your teeth or at bedtime-just pick the slot you’re certain you won’t miss. This flexibility hands control back to the patient, that in the long run, tends to deliver stronger more durable results.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="38"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="40"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Doctor suggestion&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="42"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr Levine says that certain physicians still endorse nighttime dosing for patients whose blood pressure fails to dip after dark-called the "non‑dippers." Following your doctor’s advice is reasonable, says Dr Levine, when a medical reason exist - whether it’s to sidestep side effects, mitigate diabetes risk, or because of the medication’s properties. (for instance, diuretics generally work better when taken in the morning). Dr Levine advises that if there is any doubt, one should bring it up with their doctor; but avoid altering the regimen on your own without guidance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="46"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;The power of habit&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="48"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr Levine says that linking your medication to a habit, whether it’s brushing your teeth, grabbing breakfast or winding down for bedtime, greatly ups the odds, and you’ll actually remember to take it. Dr. Levine suggests putting the pill bottle at a place you’ll see every day. What really matters is staying consistent, and not nailing the minute on the clock. Skipping doses can push blood pressure higher, and wipe out the gains even if you otherwise regular.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="52"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="53"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Using Diuretics&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="55"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Diuretics-often called "water tablets”-work best when taken in the morning, since they prompt the kidneys to fluid, and can interrupt sleep if taken at night. Likewise, many other medicines may interact with other health conditions, foods or other prescriptions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="58"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Studies confirm that patients who follow their prescription-no matter the hour-generally achieve better blood‑pressure control, and protect their heart. Dr. Levine suggests that whenever possible, consolidating medicines into one pill, can simplify the regimen and raise adherence. If your current schedule feels confusing, talk to your doctor about adjusting it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="60"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="62"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="64"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="65"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Times of India</author><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 10:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipwJBVV95cUxON1pVbkpWRFc1NkVFRktVdm5zSWJsSW1wN093Y092a0VtTmtaeEI0djVZcGExdUpndHF5QTdMRTNNeEktd2JNaFB6dVJmb3BnMGNudHZFOWJSX1JxSDgxbHFTT1l5TFk4Ul9KLW9GQkY0YXJ5ck14Z1YySzRQM05xUFdlMUctb0wxZXlIWWRBejcyRm9oQ3d6YlZvWV9ZZTNvTFYtUWxlNnRfTlZ5dGxJQWdrbEpWVDVGY3ZleTd2SjMtQzZTcmNNb2E3QkhpWkVCSEpZbkE0WUFhYzM1OGRNZHhJSXVGWlVRUVZxUVJrdW1QWFNvWHVjczBvWXprS1JKcjRvRmFybEJGRHNUM1ZXcmlZX01PS055WTZ6N3l0ZTNnRUZUZVVn</guid></item><item><title>德克萨斯州传染病激增—家长需要了解的信息- MySA</title><link>https://www.mysanantonio.com/news/local/article/whooping-cough-texas-21140895.php</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article class="rel"&gt;&lt;figure class="rel f m0 fdc -mx20 sm:-mx40 lg:-mx56 x100vw sm:cw-80 lg:cw-112 mb32"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="mediaCaptionAria" class="f fdc g2 rel pt8 px20 sm:px0 rel"&gt;&lt;span class="photoCaption c-gray700 block ya"&gt;&lt;div data-server-side-rendered="true" class="r12zgbl0 ruduv2y"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pictured is the neonatal intensive care unit at the Women's and Children's Hospital at University Health's Med Center Campus. A San Antonio doctor with University Health and UT Health San Antonio shared what to know about the rise of whooping cough cases in Texas, including in the Alamo City. About one-third of babies younger than 12 months old with pertussis, also known as whooping cough, need treatment in a hospital.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="photoCredit c-gray600 block rel z1 mt2 mr48"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Robin Jerstad&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Texas is reporting a significant increase in cases of pertussis, or better known &lt;a href="https://www.mysanantonio.com/news/local/article/whooping-cough-san-antonio-texas-19929891.php" data-link="native" rel="noopener" target="_blank" class=""&gt;as whooping cough&lt;/a&gt;, a highly contagious respiratory illness that can lead to vomiting or pauses in breathing. Complications are most severe in infants and young children who are not fully immunized, according to health officials.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;State officials are reporting 3,500 cases through October this year, which is roughly four times the number reported for the same period last year, according to &lt;a href="https://www.dshs.texas.gov/news-alerts/health-alert-increase-pertussis-cases-texas?fbclid=IwY2xjawN5octleHRuA2FlbQIxMABicmlkETF2UkpBTjVRWTRseU1FNU1mc3J0YwZhcHBfaWQQMjIyMDM5MTc4ODIwMDg5MgABHpFSp0rdlhsDjqGKeQjiznqXMAnyhJe9ttKIK6fJulgoVmbMzGtzBMIrCmt0_aem_tCyymGYZT5TngmwBGuDteQ" data-link="native" rel="noopener" target="_blank" class=""&gt;a health alert&lt;/a&gt; from the Texas Department of State Health Services (DSHS) on Monday, November 3. This is the second consecutive year that Texas is experiencing high year-over-year increases in reported pertussis cases, and the second consecutive year DSHS has issued a health alert on the illness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="pt16 sy16 bb bt b-gray300 mb32"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="uiTextSmall f aic jcc"&gt;Article continues below this ad&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-block-type="ad" data-small-id="A300" data-large-id="Inline-1" data-unit="hnp-mysanantonio.com/article_dtc" class="f jcc mnh250px sm:mnh600px ais lg:f lg:jcc lg:mnh250px lg:pb16 lg:aic"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;In San Antonio, health officials are seeing a similar increase in whooping cough cases, according to Dr. Jason Bowling, a professor and infectious disease specialist for &lt;a href="https://uthscsa.edu/" data-link="native" rel="noopener" target="_blank" class=""&gt;UT Health San Antonio&lt;/a&gt;, the academic health center of The University of Texas at San Antonio, and with University Health. Here's what to know about the rising cases and the illness, according to Bowling.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Is there an outbreak of whooping cough now?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Whooping cough cases in Texas and the United States have been increasing, according to DSHS. There are several important factors leading to the increased reporting of pertussis cases, including waning immunity in adults and adolescents. Last year, Texas reported 1,907 cases, with more than half of them occurring in November and December. The last peak year in Texas was 2013 with 3,985 cases, the highest annual case count since 1959, according to DSHS.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="md:pt16 md:sy16 md:bb md:bt b-gray300 mb32"&gt;&lt;div class="vh y0 mb0 md:vv md:y100 md:mb16"&gt;&lt;p class="uiTextSmall f aic jcc"&gt;Article continues below this ad&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-block-type="ad" data-small-id="NTV7ARD" data-large-id="Inline-2" data-unit="hnp-mysanantonio.com/article_dtc" class="lg:f lg:jcc lg:mnh250px lg:pb16 lg:aic"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;San Antonio had a similar spike in 2024, with the majority of the cases being reported in the last three months, according to Bowling. Since then, Bowling said the trend has kind of continued through this year. He added that cases tend to be reported more in the fall and winter seasons as more and more people are going to the hospital for cold-like or flu-like symptoms, which the whooping cough has similar symptoms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;How to tell if you've got a whooping cough?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Early symptoms are similar to the common cold. One to two weeks after symptoms start, people may develop coughing fits. The cough generally gets worse and becomes more frequent as the illness continues, and can cause people to vomit or make a "whoop" sound as they breathe in between coughs. The cough could last for weeks or maybe even months, according to Bowling.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bowling said whooping cough typically happens in three stages with adults. The first stage lasts for a couple of weeks, with symptoms like a running nose, cough, and some congestion. This period is when people are the most contagious to others, Bowling said. The second phase, which happens after the first kind of two weeks, is where people start to have these prolonged coughing spells that are more consistent with what people recognize as whooping cough. In the third stage, the cough gradually improves, with a mild cough that may persist for several weeks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="pt16 sy16 bb bt b-gray300 mb32"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="uiTextSmall f aic jcc"&gt;Article continues below this ad&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-block-type="ad" data-small-id="Inline-1" data-large-id="Inline-3" data-unit="hnp-mysanantonio.com/article_dtc" class="f jcc mnh250px pb16 aic lg:f lg:jcc lg:mnh250px lg:pb16 lg:aic"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;How dangerous can whooping cough be for infants and young children?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Infants under one year old are at the greatest risk of getting whooping cough and having severe complications from it. About one-third of babies younger than 12 months old with whooping cough need treatment in a hospital. DSHS indicates that approximately 85% of whooping cough cases in Texas this year have occurred among children.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;The difference among infants is that they don't have coughing spells, and instead can sometimes stop breathing, Bowling said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;"And obviously that's an emergency. So it's particularly significant for kids who are zero to 12 months," Bowling said when discussing how the whooping cough affects infants.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="pt16 sy16 bb bt b-gray300 mb32"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="uiTextSmall f aic jcc"&gt;Article continues below this ad&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-block-type="ad" data-small-id="Inline-2" data-large-id="Inline-4" data-unit="hnp-mysanantonio.com/article_dtc" class="f jcc mnh250px pb16 aic lg:f lg:jcc lg:mnh250px lg:pb16 lg:aic"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;If children have more severe or prolonged symptoms, that's when parents and guardians should go to their physician. He said parents should look out for if they're children are having a high fever that isn't getting better, even when using fever-reducing medicines. Bowling added to also watch if symptoms are kind of significant, such as changes in breathing patterns.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;How to help prevent whooping cough?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;The best way to protect against whooping cough is vaccination. The Centers for Disease Control and Prevention recommends pertussis vaccines for people of all ages. The childhood whooping cough vaccine is given as part of a combination shot called DTaP, which protects against diphtheria, tetanus and pertussis (whooping cough).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Children typically receive the series at two months, four months and six months. Then, children get it again at the 15 to 18-month time period to provide additional protection before they go into the daycare setting. Then again, between four to six years, when they're entering kindergarten, Bowling said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="pt16 sy16 bb bt b-gray300 mb32"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="uiTextSmall f aic jcc"&gt;Article continues below this ad&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-block-type="ad" data-small-id="Inline-3" data-large-id="Inline-5" data-unit="hnp-mysanantonio.com/article_dtc" class="f jcc mnh250px pb16 aic lg:f lg:jcc lg:mnh250px lg:pb16 lg:aic"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;After being 19 years old, adults are supposed to get the Tdap booster, which is usually given to refresh protection against tetanus and diphtheria. However, it also includes the whooping cough component to help prevent the illness from spreading as immunity fades over time, Bowling said. If you aren't sure when you last had a Tdap booster, Bowling recommends talking to your provider to check your records. If it's been more than 10 years, then a doctor would likely provide them with the Tdap booster.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Health officials also recommend that pregnant women receive the Tdap to protect infants when they are most vulnerable. Vaccination during each pregnancy is important for transferring high levels of protective antibodies to the infant before birth, according to DSHS. Bowling also recommends that adults get vaccinated before meeting a newborn.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;"If you're sick, you should be mindful of that," Bowling said. "Don't go visit small children, especially babies, right until you're past your illness."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="pt16 sy16 bb bt b-gray300 mb32"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="uiTextSmall f aic jcc"&gt;Article continues below this ad&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-block-type="ad" data-small-id="Inline-4" data-large-id="Inline-6" data-unit="hnp-mysanantonio.com/article_dtc" class="f jcc mnh250px pb16 aic lg:f lg:jcc lg:mnh250px lg:pb16 lg:aic"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;For more information on whooping cough, &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/pertussis/php/surveillance/index.html#:~:text=In%202024%2C%20reported%20cases%20of,Providers%20Antibiotic%2Dresistant%20Bordetella%20pertussis" data-link="native" rel="noopener" target="_blank" class=""&gt;visit the CDC's website&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="y1px x100 abs bgn top"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="y1px x100 abs bgn"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="y1px x100 abs bgn"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="y1px x100 abs bgn"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="y1px x100 abs bgn bottom"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>MySA</author><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 10:13:30 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiAFBVV95cUxQSzhjZXNlRXV2dVZzRmU3UDJFcjdhRGxCX21fLVdtd1AzYW1DN0tTSzV3aXVNdFlsUWRiWlB1ZDVjai1DNzdFM3JOS0VILWdkdzhGcUNmYnpaN3FNeVdmZS1rdGVIbXNGUzJpcnk1clo0WVd4SVpBeTBuU2RtVklENVFEWklkbUJU</guid></item><item><title>七栋被带状疱疹覆盖的鳞片状房屋- Dezeen</title><link>https://www.dezeen.com/2025/11/08/scaly-shingles-houses-roundup/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;section class="main-article-body"&gt;
                



                
                
                &lt;p&gt;A &lt;a href="https://www.dezeen.com/tag/barns/"&gt;barn&lt;/a&gt; in rural England and a lakeside &lt;a href="https://www.dezeen.com/tag/cottages/"&gt;cottage&lt;/a&gt; in Poland feature in this roundup of &lt;a href="https://www.dezeen.com/tag/houses/"&gt;homes&lt;/a&gt; with highly textured facades, finished with scaly-looking &lt;a href="https://www.dezeen.com/tag/shingles/"&gt;shingles&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;span id="more-2266242"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="div-gpt-ad-1506076990687-0" class="ad--300---mobile"&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Shingles are a type of roof and wall cladding formed of small overlapping elements, favoured for their durable and tactile qualities.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They can be made from everything from slate to thatch, but are most commonly made from wood – a variation known as shakes – with both smooth and rough surfaces.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The examples in this roundup demonstrate how shingles, especially when made of wood, can give rise to tactile, scaly-looking facades with a naturalistic quality.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Read on for seven houses sheathed in shingles:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="div-gpt-ad-1538138464089-0" class="ad--300---mobile mobile-only"&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr&gt;&lt;figure id="preload-0" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-2251687" class="wp-caption alignnone" data-lightboximage="https://static.dezeen.com/uploads/2025/09/james-grayley-architecture-church-cottage-extension-suffolk_dezeen_2364_col_3.jpg" data-orientation="landscape"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.dezeen.com/2025/09/28/james-grayley-architecture-church-cottage/"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" class="wp-image-2251687 size-full" src="https://static.dezeen.com/uploads/2025/09/james-grayley-architecture-church-cottage-extension-suffolk_dezeen_2364_col_3-852x639.jpg" alt="Church Cottage extension by James Grayley Architecture" srcset="https://static.dezeen.com/uploads/2025/09/james-grayley-architecture-church-cottage-extension-suffolk_dezeen_2364_col_3-852x639.jpg 1x, https://static.dezeen.com/uploads/2025/09/james-grayley-architecture-church-cottage-extension-suffolk_dezeen_2364_col_3-1704x1278.jpg 2x" sizes="(max-width: 2364px) 100vw, 2364px"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-2251687" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Photo by James Retief&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.dezeen.com/2025/09/28/james-grayley-architecture-church-cottage/"&gt;Church Cottage, UK, by James Grayley Architecture&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;James Grayley Architecture opted for a shingle exterior for this extension to Church Cottage in Suffolk to complement the existing 18th-century building's &lt;a href="https://www.dezeen.com/tag/thatch/"&gt;thatched&lt;/a&gt; roof.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The shingle-covered walls were raised on a plinth of red &lt;a href="https://www.dezeen.com/tag/bricks/"&gt;bricks&lt;/a&gt; and were teamed with wooden window frames and a green roof, adding to the rustic charm of the home.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.dezeen.com/2025/09/28/james-grayley-architecture-church-cottage/"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Find out more about Church Cottage ›&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;&lt;figure id="preload-1" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-2266270" class="wp-caption alignnone" data-lightboximage="https://static.dezeen.com/uploads/2025/11/waterhouse-oyama-julia-manacas-architecte-canada.jpg" data-orientation="landscape"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.dezeen.com/2025/10/14/waterhouse-oyama-julia-manacas-architecte-canada/"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" class="wp-image-2266270 size-full" src="https://static.dezeen.com/uploads/2025/11/waterhouse-oyama-julia-manacas-architecte-canada-852x608.jpg" alt="Waterhouse, Canada, by Oyama and Julia Manaças Architecte" srcset="https://static.dezeen.com/uploads/2025/11/waterhouse-oyama-julia-manacas-architecte-canada-852x608.jpg 1x, https://static.dezeen.com/uploads/2025/11/waterhouse-oyama-julia-manacas-architecte-canada-1704x1217.jpg 2x" sizes="(max-width: 2364px) 100vw, 2364px"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-2266270" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Photo by Alex Lesage&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.dezeen.com/2025/10/14/waterhouse-oyama-julia-manacas-architecte-canada/"&gt;Waterhouse, Canada, by Oyama and Julia Manaças Architecte&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Oyama and Julia Manaças Architecte designed this 260-square-metre home to blend in with its site in a forest clearing in Quebec.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To achieve this, the studios divided it into three volumes to reduce its visual mass and unified them with walls of &lt;a href="https://www.dezeen.com/tag/cedar/"&gt;cedar&lt;/a&gt; shingles. They described this as creating "strange bodies in familiar clothing".&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.dezeen.com/2025/10/14/waterhouse-oyama-julia-manacas-architecte-canada/"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Find out more about Waterhouse ›&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;&lt;figure id="preload-2" data-lightboximage="https://static.dezeen.com/uploads/2018/01/mountain-cottage-hola-design-studio-architecture-residential-poland_dezeen_2364_col_26.jpg" data-orientation="landscape"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.dezeen.com/2018/01/29/hola-design-mountain-cottage-poland-lakeside/"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" class="alignnone wp-image-1176982 size-full" src="https://static.dezeen.com/uploads/2018/01/mountain-cottage-hola-design-studio-architecture-residential-poland_dezeen_2364_col_26-852x568.jpg" alt="Shingle-covered cottage by HOLA Design Studio" srcset="https://static.dezeen.com/uploads/2018/01/mountain-cottage-hola-design-studio-architecture-residential-poland_dezeen_2364_col_26-852x568.jpg 1x, https://static.dezeen.com/uploads/2018/01/mountain-cottage-hola-design-studio-architecture-residential-poland_dezeen_2364_col_26-1704x1136.jpg 2x" sizes="(max-width: 2364px) 100vw, 2364px"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.dezeen.com/2018/01/29/hola-design-mountain-cottage-poland-lakeside/"&gt;Mountain Cottage, Poland, by HOLA Design&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The shingles on this gabled lakeside cottage were made from black-painted &lt;a href="https://www.dezeen.com/tag/aspen/"&gt;aspen&lt;/a&gt; and arranged at different angles for a highly textured surface finish.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This material and colour palette was selected by architect HOLA Design in an effort to create "a modern version of the mountain chalet" seen nearby.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.dezeen.com/2018/01/29/hola-design-mountain-cottage-poland-lakeside/"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Find out more about Mountain Cottage ›&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;&lt;figure id="preload-3" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-2265782" class="wp-caption alignnone" data-lightboximage="https://static.dezeen.com/uploads/2025/11/wallmakers-bridge-house-india_dezeen_2364_col_30.jpg" data-orientation="landscape"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.dezeen.com/2025/11/05/wallmakers-bridge-house-india/"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" class="wp-image-2265782 size-full" src="https://static.dezeen.com/uploads/2025/11/wallmakers-bridge-house-india_dezeen_2364_col_30-852x479.jpg" alt="Bridge House by Wallmakers" srcset="https://static.dezeen.com/uploads/2025/11/wallmakers-bridge-house-india_dezeen_2364_col_30-852x479.jpg 1x, https://static.dezeen.com/uploads/2025/11/wallmakers-bridge-house-india_dezeen_2364_col_30-1704x959.jpg 2x" sizes="(max-width: 2364px) 100vw, 2364px"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-2265782" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Photo by IKSHA&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.dezeen.com/2025/11/05/wallmakers-bridge-house-india/"&gt;Bridge House, India, by Wallmakers&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Difficulties transporting equipment to the site of Bridge House – a home spanning a seven-metre-deep gorge in India – led its architecture studio, Wallmakers, to use locally available construction materials.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Among them was &lt;a href="https://www.dezeen.com/tag/grass/"&gt;grass&lt;/a&gt;, used to create a scaly coat of thatched shingles.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.dezeen.com/2025/11/05/wallmakers-bridge-house-india/"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Find out more about Bridge House ›&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;&lt;figure id="preload-4" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-2266714" class="wp-caption alignnone" data-lightboximage="https://static.dezeen.com/uploads/2025/11/five-acre-barn-blee-halligan-architects-architecture_dezeen_2364_col.jpg" data-orientation="landscape"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.dezeen.com/2017/08/17/suffolk-barn-transformed-into-five-acre-countryside-bed-breakfast-hotel-by-blee-halligan-architects/"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-2266714" src="https://static.dezeen.com/uploads/2025/11/five-acre-barn-blee-halligan-architects-architecture_dezeen_2364_col-852x568.jpg" alt="Shingle-covered house" srcset="https://static.dezeen.com/uploads/2025/11/five-acre-barn-blee-halligan-architects-architecture_dezeen_2364_col-852x568.jpg 1x, https://static.dezeen.com/uploads/2025/11/five-acre-barn-blee-halligan-architects-architecture_dezeen_2364_col-1704x1136.jpg 2x" sizes="(max-width: 2364px) 100vw, 2364px"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-2266714" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Photo by Sarah Blee&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.dezeen.com/2017/08/17/suffolk-barn-transformed-into-five-acre-countryside-bed-breakfast-hotel-by-blee-halligan-architects/"&gt;Five Acre Barn, UK, by Blee Halligan Architects&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Shingles envelop the angular form of this converted barn in the countryside in Suffolk.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They were crafted from cedar with a rough finish, chosen for the way they will turn silver over time and blend in with the wild &lt;a href="https://www.dezeen.com/tag/gardens/"&gt;garden&lt;/a&gt; setting.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.dezeen.com/2017/08/17/suffolk-barn-transformed-into-five-acre-countryside-bed-breakfast-hotel-by-blee-halligan-architects/"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Find out more about Five Acre Barn ›&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;&lt;figure id="preload-5" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-1739051" class="wp-caption alignnone" data-lightboximage="https://static.dezeen.com/uploads/2021/11/ciasa-aqua-bad-cortina-pedevilla-architects-residential-italy_dezeen_1704_col_10-1.jpg" data-orientation="landscape"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.dezeen.com/2021/11/19/ciasa-aqua-bad-cortina-pedevilla-architects-italy/"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" class="wp-image-1739051 size-full" src="https://static.dezeen.com/uploads/2021/11/ciasa-aqua-bad-cortina-pedevilla-architects-residential-italy_dezeen_1704_col_10-1-852x568.jpg" alt="Shingle-covered house in Italy" srcset="https://static.dezeen.com/uploads/2021/11/ciasa-aqua-bad-cortina-pedevilla-architects-residential-italy_dezeen_1704_col_10-1-852x568.jpg 1x, https://static.dezeen.com/uploads/2021/11/ciasa-aqua-bad-cortina-pedevilla-architects-residential-italy_dezeen_1704_col_10-1.jpg 2x" sizes="(max-width: 1704px) 100vw, 1704px"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-1739051" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Photo by Gustav Willeit&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.dezeen.com/2021/11/19/ciasa-aqua-bad-cortina-pedevilla-architects-italy/"&gt;CiAsa Aqua Bad Cortina, Italy, by Pedevilla Architects&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Pedevilla Architects' prioritised having minimal environmental impact and utilising local resources and know-how in its design of this house in South Tyrol.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Its trapezoidal form is cloaked in shingles that were made from &lt;a href="https://www.dezeen.com/tag/larch/"&gt;larch&lt;/a&gt;, sourced from trees that fell in nearby forests and were processed by local craftsmen.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.dezeen.com/2021/11/19/ciasa-aqua-bad-cortina-pedevilla-architects-italy/"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Find out more about CiAsa Aqua Bad Cortina ›&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;&lt;figure id="preload-6" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-1229371" class="wp-caption alignnone" data-lightboximage="https://static.dezeen.com/uploads/2018/06/somes-sound-house-matthew-baird-architects-maine-usa_dezeen_2364_col_3.jpg" data-orientation="landscape"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.dezeen.com/2018/06/20/matthew-baird-somes-sound-house-holiday-home-cedar-shingles-maine/"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" class="wp-image-1229371 size-full" src="https://static.dezeen.com/uploads/2018/06/somes-sound-house-matthew-baird-architects-maine-usa_dezeen_2364_col_3-852x568.jpg" alt="Somes Sound House by Matthew Baird Architects" srcset="https://static.dezeen.com/uploads/2018/06/somes-sound-house-matthew-baird-architects-maine-usa_dezeen_2364_col_3-852x568.jpg 1x, https://static.dezeen.com/uploads/2018/06/somes-sound-house-matthew-baird-architects-maine-usa_dezeen_2364_col_3-1704x1135.jpg 2x" sizes="(max-width: 2364px) 100vw, 2364px"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-1229371" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Photo by Elizabeth Felicella&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.dezeen.com/2018/06/20/matthew-baird-somes-sound-house-holiday-home-cedar-shingles-maine/"&gt;Somes Sound House, USA, by Matthew Baird Architects&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Matthew Baird Architects chose cedar shakes as the cladding material for Somes Sound House, a project designed to respect its forested surroundings in Maine.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"We were encouraged to embrace a modest expression worthy of the site and to make a structure that would sit lightly on the ground," the studio said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.dezeen.com/2018/06/20/matthew-baird-somes-sound-house-holiday-home-cedar-shingles-maine/"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Find out more about Somes Sound House ›&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

                
                
                


            &lt;/section&gt;

            
            &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Dezeen</author><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMickFVX3lxTE80U19NY1M2WHZPSkNTX2VWN21Bc1ZuMHVoUlk5VWdMcDh0Mk1keHRBMEFfYktFNzJnQnlNN1BVOFpyOFBFQndCTG81NXU3OVNySDgwZnFZekZoUmRwQzhDWkZLM180RS1WWU5sWUY4VjNtUQ</guid></item><item><title>科学家刚刚创建了一个易于使用的麸质测试，可在几分钟内完成—成本为$ 10 -食品和葡萄酒</title><link>https://www.foodandwine.com/leo-gluten-test-strip-11844086</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-page_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-page mntl-block structured-content" data-sc-sticky-offset="90" data-sc-ad-label-height="24" data-sc-ad-track-spacing="100" data-sc-min-track-height="250" data-sc-max-track-height="600" data-sc-breakpoint="50em" data-sc-load-immediate="4" data-sc-content-positions="[1, 1250, 1550, 1950, 2350, 2750, 3150, 3550, 3950]" data-bind-scroll-on-start="true"&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-block_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block foodandwine-sc-block-callout--summary mntl-sc-block-universal-callout--tips mntl-sc-block-universal-callout theme-summary callout--bordered" data-text="Key Points" data-tracking-id="mntl-sc-block-callout" data-tracking-container="true"&gt;
&lt;div class="mntl-sc-block-universal-callout__body"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;A new smartphone-assisted test called LEO helps people who avoid gluten — an estimated 1% with celiac disease and another 6% with sensitivities — quickly screen foods.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Using as little as 20 milligrams of a sample on a lateral-flow strip, LEO provides a visual result in about two minutes, with an optional app image that refines the estimate in one minute.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The system detected gliadin at 5 ppm with 98% accuracy — beating the FDA labeling threshold — and identified cross-contamination in restaurant foods labeled “gluten-free.” &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_2-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; About 1% of the United States population has celiac disease, according to the &lt;a href="https://www.chop.edu/news/signs-and-symptoms-gluten-sensitivity" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Children's Hospital of Philadelphia&lt;/a&gt;. It explained that when people with celiac disease consume foods containing gluten, it can trigger an "autoimmune response that damages the small intestine and can lead to gastrointestinal symptoms, poor growth, and long-term problems, like anemia, osteoporosis, and even lymphoma." While those with celiac certainly experience more severe symptoms, an additional 6% of the population might also have a gluten sensitivity, making them feel unwell when they consume gluten products, too. That means several million people across the country do all they can to avoid it in food and drinks. But now, scientists have developed something new to make that job a lot easier.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_3-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_4-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; In September, researchers published a paper in the &lt;a href="https://pubs.acs.org/doi/10.1021/acs.jafc.5c07872" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Journal of Agricultural and Food Chemistry &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;detailing their new gluten detection device, which could help millions of people avoid gluten with ease — and at a very low price. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_5-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_6-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; The team, which included scientists from Taipei Medical University, named their device LEO, short for Lateral flow Enhanced by Optical imaging, and it works much like a high-tech home pregnancy or COVID-19 test that includes its own smartphone app, LEOMyFood.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_7-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_8-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Here’s how the LEO test works: A diner takes a small crumb of food, as little as 20 milligrams, and places it into a small vial. They then add a few drops of liquid, similar to how one swabs their nose for at-home COVID-19 testing. Next, users put a few drops of the solution onto a test strip that detects gliadin, the gluten protein that triggers reactions in individuals with celiac disease. The test strip has three lines: one serves as a baseline, while the second and third lines detect lower and higher gluten levels, respectively. The entire process takes about two minutes. If users are unsure of the results, they can take a photo and upload it to the companion app, which provides a more detailed analysis within one minute.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_9-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_10-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block foodandwine-sc-block-embed mntl-sc-block-universal-embed "&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_11-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_12-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; In their lab tests, the team found that the LEO system accurately identified gluten levels as low as 5 ppm, meaning it outperforms the &lt;a href="https://www.fda.gov/consumers/consumer-updates/gluten-free-means-what-it-says" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Food and Drug Administration’s labeling threshold&lt;/a&gt; and detects gliadin with “98% accuracy.” 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_13-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_14-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; They also tested the strips in real-world scenarios, including evaluating everyday restaurant meals and packaged snacks. They discovered that cross-contamination often happens in restaurants, especially when food is prepared in shared fryers and mixing bowls. The LEO device also successfully detected gluten traces in restaurant foods mislabeled as “gluten-free,” including fries and salads that had likely been exposed to cross-contamination during preparation.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_15-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_17-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_18-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Here's the best news about this scientific breakthrough: It's already available for purchase. Anyone can buy a sample pack of three for $35 or a jumbo pack of 40 for $250, making each one $6.25 on the &lt;a href="https://leoverified.com/collections/gluten-free-testers" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1" rel="nofollow"&gt;LEO Verified site&lt;/a&gt;. However, the team hopes to bring these prices down eventually. “Our goal is to get it to them at the most reasonable price,” Seaton Smith, a cofounder of LEO Verification Systems, shared with &lt;a href="https://www.powelltribune.com/stories/powell-based-start-up-creates-new-convenient-way-to-test-for-gluten,166205" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="2" rel="nofollow"&gt;Powell Tribune&lt;/a&gt; earlier this year. “Because as a celiac, my breads cost twice as much as yours and tastes twice as terrible.”
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_19-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_20-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; The team noted in their study that while the strips are currently designed for gluten testing, they could be adapted with minor modifications to detect other common food allergens, such as peanuts, shellfish, and dairy, in the future. That way, everyone can enjoy a stress-free meal.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Food &amp; Wine</author><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 09:57:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiakFVX3lxTE9yZW9fRGl4dVh4VGJNZGFENlpjSW55VHhaQ1U0Z1BOd1phUUNDUDl2SndjbUVuazdwOHg3OUhVZjBkWEhBeWg4blhGUm5OLVVpZnZiTTBuV0dTbkdqUnNDeWJQY2trZWZHU0E</guid></item><item><title>逆转衰老的惊人大脑锻炼- SciTechDaily</title><link>https://scitechdaily.com/the-surprising-brain-exercise-that-reverses-aging/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>SciTechDaily</author><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 09:21:52 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigAFBVV95cUxQZ2w3T3k1WWxVajZTWmtZTzd0VDJJdDJjN0tQaUpib3lGT3M2MkxBeW8tZkhyaGhCUnJncXpYdFdYS0V0Y2hPbVpybTRkMjZzWFNldVZCWENkUmJSTzNMNldGTU44MUNxek5hUk9zTkF5WF9YTzdUZWt2VS1DWTU0dQ</guid></item><item><title>当你喝一罐可乐时发生在你身体上的一切- LADbible</title><link>https://www.ladbible.com/news/health/coca-cola-can-body-changes-health-warning-517055-20251108</link><description>&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p class="loading-bar_loader__2fNms"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;main&gt;&lt;template id="B:0"&gt;&lt;/template&gt;&lt;p class="article-page-skeleton_background__h2J4n"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/main&gt;&lt;/body&gt;</description><author>LADbible</author><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 09:11:49 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimgFBVV95cUxNZUV2cmVpRkIzbTdRUEhCSTZzOUp0QmpKZS1lZHZmd0k3SXRqcS1zRHpibTBaT2IwenI4U1RkOHJuNURPUzRybXJEeUlPRm9sQXRicFFiVDYzaEVXNTIxMDhsa3VaRFRYZGZyTzViWmVqTEp3LVBFYXR6c08weFpLOUVwRl9hYmtOSkhnU3VJRUlfdHd1NVU0U0lR</guid></item><item><title>顶级健康人物在阿勒格尼县举行疫苗接种会议-匹兹堡邮报</title><link>https://www.post-gazette.com/news/health/2025/11/08/vaccine-rates-outbreak-salk-pittsburgh/stories/202511090071</link><description>&lt;body class="pgevoke bs-grid pg-hasicomoon pg-site-pg pg-user-checkingstatus pg-requesttype-story pgevoke-pageparentsection-news pg-piano" id="readabilityBody"&gt;

		
	&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;
	
	

	
	
	
	

	

	
	
	
	
	&lt;p id="dfp-peelback" class="hidden-xs hidden-sm"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
	

	&lt;p class="pgevoke-header-placeholder"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
	
	
	&lt;div class="pgevoke-pagewrapper clearfix"&gt;
			&lt;div class="pgevoke-slidemenu"&gt;
	&lt;div class="pgevoke-slidemenu-inner"&gt;
		&lt;p class="pgevoke-slidemenu-topborder"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;p class="pgevoke-slidemenu-header pgevoke-slidemenu-header-account"&gt;ACCOUNT&lt;/p&gt;
					
			
				&lt;p class="pgevoke-slidemenu-header"&gt;SECTIONS&lt;/p&gt;
		
		&lt;p class="pgevoke-slidemenu-header"&gt;OTHER&lt;/p&gt;
		
		&lt;p class="pgevoke-slidemenu-header"&gt;CLASSIFIEDS&lt;/p&gt;
		
				&lt;p class="pgevoke-slidemenu-header"&gt;CONTACT US / FAQ&lt;/p&gt;
		
	&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;		


&lt;p class="dfp-wallpaper"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  
		
		 

					
		
	&lt;/div&gt; 

	


&lt;p id="pgevoke-apwidgetloader"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;p id="pgtarget"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;


























	




			
		
		









  
  
  








  
























	











  







&lt;p id="dfpinterstitial-content" class="mfp-hide"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="dfpinterstitialmobile-content" class="mfp-hide"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



  
      
    
  
&lt;/body&gt;
</description><author>Pittsburgh Post-Gazette</author><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 09:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMisAFBVV95cUxQNXlJd0tWMko4YktaeUFGeXllT2xmdWVHUkhWa2plWE4tQmNkRTUxS3lWcG9tbFNNNUVxS1VyVk9FWWlzSnM1VU5za2d4UkNVTG00YnVYM2xhNkxZUENEd3RxYjdGeGpsblN2dG1yU2ZZNHNJckZXbFo5aGt5Q0U2VVg4WG5nUHRfZFhZN0RYdnZ1Q1B0YklWb1cwYzBKU29WY2syM2tWVDdkSmtueFhjag</guid></item><item><title>7种富含镁的豆类和豌豆：植物对肌肉和神经的支持-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/food-news/7-magnesium-rich-beans-and-peas-plant-based-support-for-muscles-and-nerves/articleshow/125108899.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Magnesium is an essential mineral that supports a wide range of bodily functions, from regulating blood pressure and blood sugar levels to promoting healthy muscle and nerve activity. It also plays a crucial role in DNA and RNA production. Most adults require 320 to 420 milligrams of magnesium daily, which can be met through a balanced diet. Beans are among the best natural sources, providing magnesium along with protein, fiber, and other key nutrients. Incorporating magnesium-rich legumes into meals can improve energy levels, aid digestion, and support heart and bone health. The following seven legumes are particularly high in magnesium, versatile in cooking, and easy to include in everyday diets for a natural, nutritious boost.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="4"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="5"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;7 plant-based foods high in magnesium for heart, bone, and muscle health&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="6"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to a &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://ods.od.nih.gov/factsheets/Magnesium-HealthProfessional/?" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;study published in Dietary Guidelines&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, legumes, including beans, peas, and lentils, are excellent sources of magnesium, providing a significant portion of the daily recommended intake. Regular consumption of these legumes can support heart health, maintain normal blood pressure, and contribute to proper muscle and nerve function.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="10"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="lOvcW vdo_embedd"&gt;&lt;div class="k7lcu"&gt;&lt;p class="efT4r"&gt;Unable to sleep? It could be magnesium deficiency&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="12"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="13"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Black beans&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="14"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="16"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Black beans are a versatile and nutrient-dense legume. One cup of cooked black beans contains approximately 120 milligrams of magnesium, covering nearly 30% of the average adult’s daily requirement. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Along with magnesium, black beans provide protein, fiber, and iron, making them a filling and nutritious choice for meals. Combining black beans with rice can further boost magnesium intake, as rice also contains a modest amount of the mineral. Black beans can be used in soups, stews, salads, or as a protein-packed side dish. Their mild flavor and hearty texture make them suitable for a variety of culinary preparations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="22"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="23"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Edamame&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="24"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Edamame, or young soybeans, are a tasty snack and an excellent plant-based source of magnesium. Half a cup of boiled edamame provides about 99 milligrams of magnesium, roughly 12% of the recommended daily intake. In addition to magnesium, edamame contains protein, fiber, and antioxidants, making it a nutrient-dense addition to any meal. Edamame can be enjoyed on its own, lightly salted, or added to salads, stir-fries, and grain bowls. Its slightly nutty taste pairs well with a variety of dishes, offering both convenience and a healthy nutrient boost.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="28"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="29"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Peanuts&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="30"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Although commonly thought of as nuts, peanuts are technically legumes. One cup of roasted peanuts contains around 260 milligrams of magnesium, making them one of the highest legume sources of this mineral. Even a smaller serving, such as a quarter cup, can provide a significant portion of the daily requirement. Peanut butter is another convenient option, with two tablespoons offering about 49 milligrams of magnesium. Peanuts can be eaten as a snack, incorporated into sauces, or sprinkled over salads for added crunch and nutrition.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="35"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="36"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Iima beans&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="37"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lima beans, also known as butter beans, offer a well-rounded nutritional profile. One cup of cooked lima beans contains about 81 milligrams of magnesium, along with protein, fiber, and calcium. These beans are soft and creamy, making them ideal for adding to salads, stews, or succotash dishes. Lima beans are also versatile enough to serve as a main ingredient or a side, providing both texture and nutritional value to meals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="41"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="42"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Peas&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="44"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Peas are another legume that delivers a healthy dose of magnesium. One cup of green peas contains approximately 62 milligrams of magnesium, along with protein, iron, potassium, and antioxidants. Peas also offer anti-inflammatory benefits, making them a nutrient-packed addition to a balanced diet. Different varieties, such as garden peas, snap peas, and snow peas, can be used in stir-fries, soups, or as a simple steamed side dish. Their natural sweetness and tender texture make them a versatile ingredient for many meals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="49"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="50"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Cannellini beans&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="51"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cannellini beans, or white beans, are rich in magnesium, with one cup providing around 113 milligrams. They are also high in protein and fiber, making them ideal for supporting digestion and sustained energy levels. Cannellini beans can be incorporated into salads, stews, or blended into dips for vegetables or whole-grain bread. Their mild flavor allows them to absorb seasonings well, making them suitable for a wide range of recipes while boosting overall magnesium intake.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="55"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="56"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Adzuki beans&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="58"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Adzuki beans are small, red beans commonly used in Asian cuisine. One cup of cooked adzuki beans contains approximately 120 milligrams of magnesium, along with protein, fiber, and calcium. These beans have a naturally sweet, nutty flavor and can be used in both savory and sweet dishes, including soups, desserts, and pastries. Adzuki beans are highly versatile and offer a concentrated source of magnesium, making them an excellent choice for anyone looking to enhance their diet with nutrient-dense legumes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="63"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Incorporating these seven legumes into your daily meals can help meet magnesium requirements and support overall health. They provide a combination of essential minerals, protein, and fiber while remaining versatile and easy to cook. From black beans and lima beans to edamame and adzuki beans, these legumes offer convenient ways to increase magnesium intake naturally. Regular consumption of magnesium-rich legumes may aid in maintaining blood pressure, supporting heart health, improving digestion, and enhancing overall energy levels, making them an important part of a balanced diet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="65"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Also Read: &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/food-news/the-japanese-method-to-keep-vegetables-fresh-longer-a-simple-4-step-fridge-storage-process-that-really-works/articleshow/125095339.cms" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;The Japanese method to keep vegetables fresh longer: A simple 4-step fridge storage process that really works&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="68"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Times of India</author><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 06:40:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi7gFBVV95cUxOQlJLaW0tR01jZmN6MGd5UlRwQXI0WDVId0s5TXZfM0lIQlo3U2d3NUo1UVB4TmlUVk5seVdwNUJQcWc5b2dmZmxvM19hTE9SajJqdnpZN1BKWE9Fa2ZBWnc3dGRLQkwtQVYxLS1qUUFqdEQyY1NlVTNyRWNfaUhleTA2SWZrQmh0NEpKMkVCSlR1Yy1CbG9Nb2ZwZTVUa1ZONWJ0N1puemRhMkR2dFBQZTl3TzdXdzJDcVFOTmx4Z09HM3B6aDhkWENFdXB2ZmJNY2lqWFBEaUhocUFyaXA5VEwxR2s4Zmg0UzBSV2dR</guid></item><item><title>我应该吃多少蛋白质来减掉身体脂肪，但保持瘦肌肉？这位专家给出了答案- Fit&amp;Well</title><link>https://www.fitandwell.com/nutrition/how-much-protein-should-i-eat-to-lose-body-fat-but-maintain-lean-muscle-this-expert-has-the-answer</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="article-body" class="article__body "&gt;
&lt;p id="979fa198-3d51-4dec-bc42-d71b336ca033"&gt;If you’re trying to lose weight you might have heard that it’s good to eat more protein, particularly if you want to maintain lean muscle. But how much should we be eating to achieve this? And why is protein so important when it comes to dropping body fat and growing muscle?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="ad-unit-1" class="ad-unit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I spoke to Dr Lena Rebecca Larsen, a nutrition specialist at &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://morenutrition.co.uk/" target="_blank" data-url="https://morenutrition.co.uk/" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;More Nutrition&lt;/a&gt;, who explained more about how this essential macronutrient can aid weight loss. “The feeling of satiety (fullness) that protein helps promote is a major factor. This can contribute to a reduced overall calorie intake which is key for losing body fat, however, there are a number of contributory elements that influence this.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a id="elk-seasonal" data-url="" href="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p id="979fa198-3d51-4dec-bc42-d71b336ca033-2"&gt;“Firstly, from a hormonal standpoint, protein affects the release of hormones that regulate appetite. It can decrease levels of the hunger hormone ghrelin, and increase levels of the hormones GLP-1 and cholecystokinin, which signal fullness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“This feeling of fullness is also experienced due to protein as a macronutrient having a higher thermic effect of food, and so the body expends more calories during its digestion and when metabolising it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="ad-unit-2" class="ad-unit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Plus, when you eat enough protein, this will help maintain muscle mass during a calorie deficit. Where your body might otherwise start breaking down muscle tissue for energy, it is more likely to oxidize fat effectively to burn fat for energy.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a id="elk-why-protein-intake-is-important-for-weight-loss" data-url="" href="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;h2 class="article-body__section" id="section-why-protein-intake-is-important-for-weight-loss"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Why protein intake is important for weight loss &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="5b8e62d0-31cb-48d0-82d9-564bde24ea1e"&gt;“Studies have indicated that up to 25% of weight lost can come from muscle mass if protein intake is insufficient,” says Larsen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She says when you eat enough protein during your weight loss journey, you can maintain muscle mass. And because muscles burn more calories at rest compared with fat, this can also help you lose weight and avoid regaining it later.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div id="slice-container-newsletterForm-articleInbodyContent-MAQnQtPCVcX78WsfyAbDsm" class="slice-container newsletter-inbodyContent-slice newsletterForm-articleInbodyContent-MAQnQtPCVcX78WsfyAbDsm slice-container-newsletterForm"&gt;&lt;div data-hydrate="true" class="newsletter-form__wrapper newsletter-form__wrapper--inbodyContent"&gt;&lt;div class="newsletter-form__container"&gt;&lt;section class="newsletter-form__main-section"&gt;&lt;p class="newsletter-form__strapline"&gt;Start your week with achievable workout ideas, health tips and wellbeing advice in your inbox.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;As you’d expect, protein requirements vary based on lots of factors including activity levels, age and body composition. Larsen has come up with this protein formula, below, so you can work out your personalised needs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“1.6g to 2g of protein per kilogram of body weight is a formula that can be used by men and women to work out roughly how much protein you should be consuming,” she says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“For very active people (ambitious hobby sports or competitive sports) or very overweight people, this amount should also be increased to 2.4g/kg. In bodybuilding with the aim of building muscle (and gaining weight) even higher.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I’d recommend trying to split your individual protein calculation evenly across meals and snacks. Also, strength training can be incredibly beneficial if you’re looking to build or maintain lean muscle mass while losing body fat.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The table below provides a good overview, taking into account that every person is individual and that these are average values.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div id="slice-container-table-MAQnQtPCVcX78WsfyAbDsm-yPm2ZK9KaGaY3hBIrAq3yiP8Qe8ibDCb" class="slice-container table-wrapper table-MAQnQtPCVcX78WsfyAbDsm-yPm2ZK9KaGaY3hBIrAq3yiP8Qe8ibDCb slice-container-table"&gt;&lt;div class="table__instruction"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Swipe to scroll horizontally&lt;/p&gt;&lt;svg viewbox="0 0 23 30" fill="none" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"&gt;&lt;path d="M21.554 15.726a2.878 2.878 0 0 0-1.705-.374 2.881 2.881 0 0 0-1.388-3.068 2.877 2.877 0 0 0-1.992-.333 2.884 2.884 0 0 0-.1-.766 2.865 2.865 0 0 0-1.346-1.75c-.47-.27-.996-.4-1.527-.385l2.742-4.73a2.87 2.87 0 0 0 .323-.83h2.612V2.084h-2.661A2.861 2.861 0 0 0 15.18.385a2.903 2.903 0 0 0-3.952 1.055l-.373.644H2.983l1.003-1L2.99.09 1.28 1.793l-.999.995L2.99 5.484l.998-.994-1.003-.999h7.054L6.505 9.586c-.34.066-.905.186-1.523.366-1.405.41-2.321.895-2.8 1.483-.742.911-1.159 2.513-1.277 4.898l-.001.01c-.067 1.816.946 6.943.99 7.16a.688.688 0 0 0 1.35-.266c-.01-.051-1.023-5.177-.963-6.84.127-2.556.598-3.64.97-4.098.133-.163.602-.587 2.104-1.027l.206-.058-1.425 2.458a.685.685 0 0 0 .252.937c.33.19.75.077.94-.251L12.42 2.126a1.52 1.52 0 0 1 2.07-.552c.35.2.6.527.705.916.105.39.051.797-.15 1.145l-4.767 8.222a.685.685 0 0 0 .252.937c.33.19.75.077.94-.25l.794-1.368c.201-.348.529-.597.92-.702a1.508 1.508 0 0 1 1.854 1.066c.105.39.052.796-.15 1.144l-.377.652-.002.002-.898 1.55a.685.685 0 0 0 .252.938c.329.189.75.077.94-.251l.9-1.551c.201-.348.528-.597.92-.702a1.512 1.512 0 0 1 1.703 2.21l-1.223 2.11a.685.685 0 0 0 .252.938c.33.189.75.076.941-.252l.5-.862c.202-.348.529-.597.92-.702.392-.104.8-.051 1.15.15.723.416.972 1.34.554 2.06l-3.525 6.08c-.517.892-1.57 1.795-3.044 2.611-1.156.64-2.163.998-2.173 1.002a.685.685 0 0 0 .23 1.333.688.688 0 0 0 .229-.04c.18-.062 4.419-1.575 5.952-4.22l3.524-6.08a2.878 2.878 0 0 0-1.059-3.934Z" fill="#333"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="table__container"&gt;&lt;table tabindex="0" class="table__wrapper table__wrapper--inbodyContent table__wrapper--sticky table__wrapper--divider"&gt;&lt;caption class="table__caption table__caption--top table__caption--left"&gt;Recommended protein intake by activity level or goal&lt;/caption&gt;&lt;thead class="table__head"&gt;&lt;tr class="table__head__row"&gt;&lt;th class="table__head__heading table__head__heading--left" colspan="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Type of person&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th class="table__head__heading table__head__heading--left" colspan="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Objective recommended protein intake (g/kg bw/day)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th class="table__head__heading table__head__heading--left" colspan="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Literature&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/th&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/thead&gt;&lt;tbody class="table__body"&gt;&lt;tr class="table__body__row"&gt;&lt;td class="table_body__data" colspan="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Minimally active (everyday life, walks)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td class="table_body__data" colspan="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;1.6 - 2.0&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td class="table_body__data" colspan="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1039/C5FO01530H" target="_blank"&gt;Wu (2016)&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1136/bjsports-2017-097608" target="_blank"&gt;Morton, R. W., et al. (2017)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr class="table__body__row"&gt;&lt;td class="table_body__data" colspan="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Moderately active (2-3x/week training)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td class="table_body__data" colspan="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;1.8 - 2.2&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td class="table_body__data" colspan="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1186/s12970-017-0177-8" target="_blank"&gt;Jäger, et al. (2017)&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1186/1550-2783-10-53" target="_blank"&gt;Schoenfeld, et al. (2018)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr class="table__body__row"&gt;&lt;td class="table_body__data" colspan="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;In a calorie deficit (with training)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td class="table_body__data" colspan="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;2.2 - 2.4&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td class="table_body__data" colspan="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1186/1550-2783-11-20" target="_blank"&gt;Helms et al. (2014)&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1123/ijsnem.2017-0273" target="_blank"&gt;Hector &amp;amp; Phillips (2018)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr class="table__body__row"&gt;&lt;td class="table_body__data" colspan="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Weight training / bodybuilding&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td class="table_body__data" colspan="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;2.0 - 2.5&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td class="table_body__data" colspan="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1186/1550-2783-10-53" target="_blank"&gt;Schoenfeld, et al. (2018)&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1155/2016/9104792" target="_blank"&gt;Antonio, et al. (2015)&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1186/s12970-017-0177-8" target="_blank"&gt;Jäger, et al. (2017)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr class="table__body__row"&gt;&lt;td class="table_body__data" colspan="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Muscle building in diet (cutting)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td class="table_body__data" colspan="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;2.3 - 3.1&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td class="table_body__data" colspan="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1186/1550-2783-11-20" target="_blank"&gt;Helms, et al. (2014)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr class="table__body__row"&gt;&lt;td class="table_body__data" colspan="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Active ageing/prevention&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td class="table_body__data" colspan="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;≥1.6 (up to 2.2 with sarcopenic tendency)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td class="table_body__data" colspan="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1039/C5FO01530H" target="_blank"&gt;Wu (2016)&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1136/bmj.m2412" target="_blank"&gt;Naghshi, et al. (2020)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;a id="elk-should-protein-intake-differ-between-men-and-women" data-url="" href="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;h2 class="article-body__section" id="section-should-protein-intake-differ-between-men-and-women"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Should protein intake differ between men and women?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="1d2d1365-2f31-4090-a651-4b61c77563b2"&gt;Larsen says that getting enough protein is essential for both sexes for muscle building and regeneration, but also for hormone and enzyme production, immunity, tissue repair, feeling full and body composition.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“On average, women have a lower muscle mass and body weight than men, so the absolute requirement is often lower, but the relative requirement per kg of bodyweight can be the same or even slightly higher—depending on the cycle phase and phase of life, for example pregnancy, breastfeeding, menopause.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“According to current scientific recommendations, athletically active women generally need around 1.4-2.2g/kg body weight for optimal supply, depending on the training goal and intensity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But she says that protein metabolism in women is significantly influenced by the female steroid hormone progesterone, which dominates in menstruating women in the second half of the cycle (known as the luteal phase).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“During menstruation a slight increase in protein is useful, even more so in menopause because the drop in oestrogen promotes muscle breakdown (&lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://womenshealth.gov/sarcopenia" target="_blank" data-url="https://womenshealth.gov/sarcopenia" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;sarcopenia&lt;/a&gt;).”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a id="elk-how-do-i-know-if-i-m-getting-enough-protein" data-url="" href="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;h2 class="article-body__section" id="section-how-do-i-know-if-i-m-getting-enough-protein"&gt;&lt;span&gt;How do I know if I’m getting enough protein?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="68360f8d-505f-40e9-a620-f8f564497b85"&gt;“The amount of protein we need is individual to every person, as is every metabolism and the associated ability of a body to utilize it,” says Larsen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Plus, we all burn different amounts of calories depending on our basal metabolic rate (how many calories you burn at rest), age, gender, genetics, the type of sport you do and the level of exertion at which it is performed.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Larsen stresses that it’s unhelpful to compare sports—for example, comparing yoga to running—because they can be performed at different levels of intensity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Put simply, all these factors mean that no specific values are recommended in natural sciences in general, but rather a variance in which everyone must look individually to see what applies to them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“For example, do you notice that you feel fuller with 1.6g protein/kg bodyweight? Do you feel fitter? Are you performing better at sports? If not, then it may be—if there is no other reason, such as a metabolic disorder or illness—that the protein content is not yet sufficient.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Remember that the need for protein increases with age. So, a woman in her mid-50s may be surprised at how more protein is needed, even if she mainly does ‘relaxed’ sports such as walking and yoga.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a id="elk-how-to-get-more-protein-into-your-diet" data-url="" href="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;h2 class="article-body__section" id="section-how-to-get-more-protein-into-your-diet"&gt;&lt;span&gt;How to get more protein into your diet&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;div class="youtube-video youtube-facade" data-nosnippet id="kST3tC9J-CU"&gt;
&lt;div class="video-aspect-box"&gt;
&lt;div class="watch-on-iframe-kST3tC9J-CU" data-yt-video-token="kST3tC9J-CU" title="Which Foods Are High In Protein? - LiveScience - YouTube"&gt;
&lt;span class="youtube-video-title"&gt;Which Foods Are High In Protein? - LiveScience - YouTube&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;img src="https://img.youtube.com/vi/kST3tC9J-CU/maxresdefault.jpg" alt="Which Foods Are High In Protein? - LiveScience - YouTube" data-aspect-ratio="16/9" loading="lazy"&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;svg class="play-button" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 234.67 165.33"&gt;&lt;path fill="red" d="M229.763 25.817c-2.699-10.162-10.65-18.165-20.748-20.881C190.716 0 117.333 0 117.333 0S43.951 0 25.651 4.936C15.553 7.652 7.6 15.655 4.903 25.817 0 44.236 0 82.667 0 82.667s0 38.429 4.903 56.85C7.6 149.68 15.553 157.681 25.65 160.4c18.3 4.934 91.682 4.934 91.682 4.934s73.383 0 91.682-4.934c10.098-2.718 18.049-10.72 20.748-20.882 4.904-18.421 4.904-56.85 4.904-56.85s0-38.431-4.904-56.85"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path fill="#fff" d="m93.333 117.559 61.333-34.89-61.333-34.894z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;
&lt;a class="watch-on-youtube-kST3tC9J-CU" href="https://youtu.be/kST3tC9J-CU" target="_blank" data-url="https://youtu.be/kST3tC9J-CU" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;Watch On &lt;svg class="youtube-logo" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 507.9 113.39"&gt;&lt;g fill="#fff"&gt;&lt;path d="M64.792 80.99V32.396l42.082 24.297zm93.803-63.285a20.285 20.285 0 0 0-14.32-14.32C131.642 0 80.99 0 80.99 0S30.337 0 17.705 3.385a20.286 20.286 0 0 0-14.32 14.32C0 30.338 0 56.693 0 56.693S0 83.049 3.385 95.68A20.285 20.285 0 0 0 17.705 110c12.632 3.386 63.285 3.386 63.285 3.386s50.652 0 63.285-3.386a20.284 20.284 0 0 0 14.32-14.32c3.385-12.632 3.385-38.988 3.385-38.988s0-26.355-3.385-38.988m94.473 74.326c.887-2.314 1.332-6.098 1.332-11.35V58.556c0-5.097-.445-8.822-1.332-11.178-.888-2.355-2.452-3.533-4.69-3.533-2.163 0-3.69 1.178-4.577 3.533-.888 2.356-1.332 6.081-1.332 11.178V80.68c0 5.25.424 9.035 1.275 11.35.848 2.318 2.392 3.475 4.633 3.475 2.239 0 3.803-1.157 4.691-3.475zm-17.953 11.122c-3.207-2.16-5.486-5.52-6.835-10.079-1.352-4.554-2.027-10.617-2.027-18.185v-10.31c0-7.644.771-13.784 2.316-18.417 1.544-4.633 3.956-8.011 7.24-10.135 3.282-2.123 7.587-3.186 12.916-3.186 5.251 0 9.459 1.082 12.626 3.243 3.165 2.162 5.482 5.542 6.95 10.136 1.466 4.595 2.2 10.715 2.2 18.36v10.31c0 7.567-.714 13.65-2.142 18.243-1.43 4.595-3.747 7.955-6.951 10.077-3.205 2.124-7.548 3.186-13.03 3.186-5.64 0-10.06-1.082-13.263-3.243m248.053-57.981c-.81 1.005-1.352 2.646-1.621 4.923-.272 2.278-.404 5.734-.404 10.367v5.097h11.697V60.46c0-4.555-.155-8.011-.463-10.367-.309-2.355-.868-4.014-1.678-4.98-.812-.966-2.067-1.449-3.766-1.449-1.7 0-2.954.503-3.765 1.506zm-2.025 29.886v3.591c0 4.557.132 7.974.404 10.251.269 2.279.828 3.94 1.68 4.982.849 1.041 2.16 1.564 3.938 1.564 2.392 0 4.035-.927 4.923-2.781.887-1.853 1.37-4.942 1.447-9.268l13.785.812c.077.62.116 1.469.116 2.548 0 6.565-1.795 11.47-5.387 14.712-3.589 3.242-8.669 4.865-15.232 4.865-7.876 0-13.398-2.47-16.564-7.414-3.168-4.94-4.75-12.586-4.75-22.935V63.589c0-10.657 1.641-18.436 4.924-23.342 3.281-4.903 8.9-7.355 16.854-7.355 5.482 0 9.691 1.004 12.626 3.012 2.933 2.01 5 5.137 6.197 9.383 1.197 4.247 1.796 10.117 1.796 17.607v12.163h-26.757m-284.953-1.33-18.187-65.68h15.869l6.37 29.77c1.623 7.339 2.82 13.594 3.591 18.766h.464c.54-3.706 1.738-9.922 3.591-18.65l6.603-29.886h15.869l-18.417 65.68v31.51h-15.754v-31.51M322.115 34.23v71.007h-12.511l-1.39-8.688h-.347c-3.399 6.564-8.496 9.845-15.291 9.845-4.71 0-8.185-1.543-10.425-4.633-2.24-3.087-3.359-7.915-3.359-14.48V34.23h15.985v52.126c0 3.168.348 5.426 1.043 6.776.695 1.353 1.853 2.027 3.475 2.027 1.39 0 2.722-.423 3.996-1.275 1.274-.849 2.22-1.928 2.838-3.241V34.229h15.986m81.995.001v71.007h-12.511l-1.391-8.688h-.345c-3.402 6.564-8.498 9.845-15.292 9.845-4.711 0-8.186-1.543-10.426-4.633-2.24-3.087-3.358-7.915-3.358-14.48V34.23h15.985v52.126c0 3.168.347 5.426 1.041 6.776.696 1.353 1.855 2.027 3.476 2.027 1.391 0 2.723-.423 3.996-1.275 1.275-.849 2.22-1.928 2.839-3.241V34.229h15.985"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="M365.552 20.908h-15.87v84.329h-15.637v-84.33h-15.869V8.05h47.376v12.858m76.811 53.636c0 5.174-.215 9.229-.639 12.162-.424 2.937-1.139 5.021-2.143 6.255-1.004 1.236-2.357 1.854-4.053 1.854a7.404 7.404 0 0 1-3.65-.927c-1.12-.618-2.026-1.544-2.722-2.78V50.796c.54-1.93 1.467-3.513 2.78-4.749 1.313-1.234 2.74-1.853 4.285-1.853 1.623 0 2.876.637 3.766 1.91.886 1.275 1.505 3.418 1.853 6.43.348 3.011.523 7.297.523 12.857zm14.652-28.964c-.967-4.478-2.531-7.721-4.692-9.73-2.163-2.007-5.136-3.011-8.919-3.011-2.935 0-5.676.83-8.224 2.49a16.926 16.926 0 0 0-5.908 6.545h-.117l.001-37.416h-15.405v100.777h13.204l1.622-6.717h.347c1.235 2.393 3.088 4.285 5.56 5.675 2.47 1.39 5.213 2.085 8.225 2.085 5.404 0 9.382-2.491 11.931-7.471 2.548-4.982 3.823-12.76 3.823-23.341V64.23c0-7.953-.484-14.17-1.448-18.65"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/g&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p id="3cb0266a-1e98-45d1-9d22-966b561278e2"&gt;“Lean meats such as chicken or turkey breast are fantastic high-protein choices, as are fish such as salmon, tuna or cod,” says Larsen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Tofu or pea protein are strong vegan alternatives, while legumes, including lentils and beans, are also brilliant choice,s as not only are they high in protein, but they’re high in fiber, which promotes a feeling of fullness and satisfaction.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Eggs and dairy items—think cottage cheese or Greek yogurt—are also great low-fat options.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Fit&amp;Well</author><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi0AFBVV95cUxPdm9KT2FhNlZJNjVLTUF3UnBaOHg5WUplYm5seTBTQWY0SjE5QU44Q3VRYmJkZlJGcWNqV1FXbHM3NDFrVWFRbUp5bDZlUnBmUGpUcjNPVFd5U3FHV3lUWEFpZ2xPMW5MZkFnTkFWcmdweVFQbjN1UE9EUThVeTRmWGk3ZkprcjFqLVlYREtNUUttNjVVTHM4LVR4UktvQTB4a2x1bUdSRTZRNTQzdm1mNzFwRkU0RWQ4Nk5HSmZWUTlydUhwWEZtSVJNeW5Qc3Q5</guid></item><item><title>由营养师创建的7天无糖高蛋白糖尿病膳食计划- EatingWell</title><link>https://www.eatingwell.com/7-day-no-sugar-high-protein-meal-plan-for-diabetes-11846243</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="mntl-sc-block-universal-table__table-wrapper"&gt;
&lt;table class="mntl-sc-block-universal-table__table"&gt;
&lt;colgroup span="1"&gt;&lt;/colgroup&gt;
&lt;colgroup span="1"&gt;&lt;/colgroup&gt;
&lt;colgroup span="1"&gt;&lt;/colgroup&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th colspan="3" class="mntl-sc-block-universal-table__title"&gt;Meal Plan at a Glance&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th&gt;BREAKFAST/ A.M. SNACK&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th&gt;LUNCH/ P.M. SNACK&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th&gt;DINNER&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;
&lt;tbody data-check="0"&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Yogurt, blueberries &amp;amp; walnuts/ Egg &amp;amp; bell peppers&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Green salad &amp;amp; apple/ Edamame&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Salmon &amp;amp; couscous&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Spinach egg scramble/ Almonds&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Chicken orzo soup/ Kefir &amp;amp; orange&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Beef &amp;amp; broccoli&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Toast &amp;amp; nut butter/ Edamame&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Chicken orzo soup/ Yogurt &amp;amp; plum&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Lentils &amp;amp; rice&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Yogurt, blueberries &amp;amp; walnuts/ Egg &amp;amp; raspberries&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Chicken orzo soup/ Almonds &amp;amp; blackberries&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Chicken Caesar pasta salad&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Toast &amp;amp; nut butter/ Yogurt &amp;amp; raspberries&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Chicken orzo soup/ Egg&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Pasta &amp;amp; Greek salad&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Yogurt, blueberries &amp;amp; walnuts/ Edamame&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Chickpea tuna salad/ Pear&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Shrimp risotto &amp;amp; green salad&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Spinach egg scramble/ Kefir &amp;amp; blackberries&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Chickpea tuna salad/ Almonds&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Chicken fajitas&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_5-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-day-1"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_6-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Day 1 &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure id="mntl-sc-block_7-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image--no-theme no-theme figure-square figure-high-res"&gt; 
&lt;figcaption id="mntl-figure-caption_1-0" class="comp mntl-figure-caption text-utility-100 figure-article-caption"&gt; &lt;span class="figure-article-caption-text"&gt;One-Skillet Salmon with Fennel &amp;amp; Sun-Dried Tomato Couscous.&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_8-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Breakfast (337 calories) &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_9-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;li&gt; 1 cup low-fat plain Greek yogurt &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt; ⅓ cup blueberries &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt; 3 Tbsp. chopped walnuts &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_10-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_11-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Morning Snack (114 calories) &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_12-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;li&gt; 1 hard-boiled egg &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt; 1 medium bell pepper, sliced &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_13-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_14-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Lunch (407 calories) &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_16-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_17-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Afternoon Snack (100 calories) &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_19-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_20-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Dinner (543 calories) &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_22-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_23-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Daily totals:&lt;/strong&gt; 1,502 calories, 70g fat, 102g protein, 128g carbohydrate, 33g fiber, 929mg sodium&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_24-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_25-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;To make it 2,000 calories: &lt;/strong&gt;Add 1 slice sprouted-wheat toast with 1 Tbsp. almond butter at breakfast, increase to 1 cup edamame at P.M. snack and add 1 serving &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/recipe/262151/guacamole-chopped-salad/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Guacamole Chopped Salad&lt;/a&gt; at dinner.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_26-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-day-2"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_27-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Day 2 &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure id="mntl-sc-block_28-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image--no-theme no-theme figure-square figure-high-res"&gt; 
&lt;figcaption id="mntl-figure-caption_2-0" class="comp mntl-figure-caption text-utility-100 figure-article-caption"&gt; &lt;span class="figure-article-caption-text"&gt;Long-Life Noodles with Beef &amp;amp; Chinese Broccoli.&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_29-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Breakfast (295 calories) &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_31-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_32-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Morning Snack (206 calories) &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_33-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;li&gt; ¼ cup unsalted dry-roasted almonds &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_34-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_35-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Lunch (408 calories) &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_37-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_38-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Afternoon Snack (134 calories) &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_39-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;li&gt; ⅔ cup low-fat plain kefir &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt; 1 medium orange &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_40-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_41-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Dinner (448 calories) &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_43-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_44-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Daily totals:&lt;/strong&gt; 1,481 calories, 73g fat, 84 protein, 135g carbohydrate, 34g fiber, 1,833mg sodium&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_45-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_46-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;To make it 2,000 calories: &lt;/strong&gt;Add 1 serving &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/recipe/257793/berry-kefir-smoothie/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Berry-Kefir Smoothie&lt;/a&gt; to breakfast, add 1 plum to A.M. snack and increase to 1 whole avocado at lunch.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_47-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-day-3"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_48-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Day 3 &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure id="mntl-sc-block_49-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image--no-theme no-theme figure-square figure-high-res"&gt; 
&lt;figcaption id="mntl-figure-caption_3-0" class="comp mntl-figure-caption text-utility-100 figure-article-caption"&gt; &lt;span class="figure-article-caption-text"&gt;One-Pot Lentils &amp;amp; Rice with Spinach.&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_50-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Breakfast (339 calories) &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_51-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;li&gt; 2 slices sprouted-wheat toast &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt; 2 Tbsp. almond butter &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_52-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_53-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Morning Snack (200 calories) &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_55-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_56-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Lunch (408 calories) &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_58-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_59-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Afternoon Snack (155 calories) &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_60-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;li&gt; ¾ cup low-fat plain Greek yogurt &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt; 1 plum &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_61-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_62-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Dinner (403 calories) &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_64-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_65-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Daily totals:&lt;/strong&gt; 1,505 calories, 61g fat, 89g protein, 156g carbohydrate, 42g fiber, 1,884mg sodium&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_66-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_67-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;To make it 2,000 calories: &lt;/strong&gt;Add 1 large pear to A.M. snack, increase to 1 whole avocado at lunch and add 1 serving &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/recipe/262713/traditional-greek-salad/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Traditional Greek Salad&lt;/a&gt; to dinner.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_68-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-day-4"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_69-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Day 4 &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure id="mntl-sc-block_70-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image--no-theme no-theme figure-landscape figure-high-res"&gt; 
&lt;figcaption id="mntl-figure-caption_4-0" class="comp mntl-figure-caption text-utility-100 figure-article-caption"&gt; &lt;span class="figure-article-caption-text"&gt;Chicken Caesar Pasta Salad.&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_71-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Breakfast (337 calories) &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_72-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;li&gt; 1 cup low-fat plain Greek yogurt &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt; ⅓ cup blueberries &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt; 3 Tbsp. chopped walnuts &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_73-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_74-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Morning Snack (109 calories) &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_75-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;li&gt; ½ cup raspberries &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt; 1 large hard-boiled egg &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_76-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_77-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Lunch (408 calories) &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_79-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_80-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Afternoon Snack (247 calories) &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_81-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;li&gt; ¼ cup unsalted dry-roasted almonds &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt; ⅔ cup blackberries &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_82-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_83-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Dinner (383 calories) &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_85-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_86-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Daily totals:&lt;/strong&gt; 1,485 calories, 79g fat, 98g protein, 110g carbohydrate, 32g fiber, 1,400mg sodium&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_87-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_88-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;To make it 2,000 calories: &lt;/strong&gt;Add 1 slice sprouted-wheat toast with 1 Tbsp. almond butter to breakfast, increase to 2 hard-boiled eggs at A.M. snack, increase to 1 whole avocado at lunch and add 1 serving &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/recipe/247873/basic-green-salad-with-vinaigrette/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Basic Green Salad with Vinaigrette&lt;/a&gt; at dinner.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_89-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-day-5"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_90-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Day 5 &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure id="mntl-sc-block_91-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image--no-theme no-theme figure-square figure-high-res"&gt; 
&lt;figcaption id="mntl-figure-caption_5-0" class="comp mntl-figure-caption text-utility-100 figure-article-caption"&gt; &lt;span class="figure-article-caption-text"&gt;Chickpea Pasta with Mushrooms &amp;amp; Kale.&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class="figure-article-caption-owner"&gt;Greg DuPree&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_92-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Breakfast (339 calories) &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_93-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;li&gt; 2 slices sprouted-wheat toast &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt; 2 Tbsp. almond butter &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_94-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_95-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Morning Snack (140 calories) &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_96-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;li&gt; ¾ cup low-fat plain Greek yogurt &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt; ¼ cup raspberries &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_97-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_98-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Lunch (408 calories) &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_100-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_101-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Afternoon Snack (78 calories) &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_103-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_104-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Dinner (529 calories) &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_106-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_107-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Daily totals:&lt;/strong&gt; 1,494 calories, 83g fat, 84g protein, 121g carbohydrate, 33g fiber, 2,027mg sodium&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_108-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_109-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;To make it 2,000 calories: &lt;/strong&gt;Add 1 serving &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/recipe/257793/berry-kefir-smoothie/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Berry-Kefir Smoothie&lt;/a&gt; to breakfast, increase to 1 whole avocado at lunch and add 1 medium orange to P.M. snack.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_110-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-day-6"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_111-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Day 6 &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure id="mntl-sc-block_112-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image--no-theme no-theme figure-square figure-high-res"&gt; 
&lt;figcaption id="mntl-figure-caption_6-0" class="comp mntl-figure-caption text-utility-100 figure-article-caption"&gt; &lt;span class="figure-article-caption-text"&gt;Wild Rice Risotto with Shrimp &amp;amp; Spring Vegetables.&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class="figure-article-caption-owner"&gt;Dera Burreson&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_113-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Breakfast (337 calories) &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_114-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;li&gt; 1 cup low-fat plain Greek yogurt &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt; ⅓ cup blueberries &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt; 3 Tbsp. chopped walnuts &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_115-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_116-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Morning Snack (200 calories) &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_118-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_119-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Lunch (357 calories) &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_121-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_122-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Afternoon Snack (131 calories) &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_124-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_125-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Dinner (500 calories) &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_127-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_128-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Daily totals:&lt;/strong&gt; 1,524 calories, 67g fat, 100g protein, 134g carbohydrate, 30g fiber, 1,536mg sodium&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_129-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_130-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;To make it 2,000 calories: &lt;/strong&gt;Add 1 slice sprouted-wheat toast with 1 Tbsp. almond butter at breakfast, add 1 medium apple to A.M. snack and add 1/4 cup unsalted dry-roasted almonds to P.M. snack.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_131-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-day-7"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_132-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Day 7 &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure id="mntl-sc-block_133-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image--no-theme no-theme figure-square figure-high-res"&gt; 
&lt;figcaption id="mntl-figure-caption_7-0" class="comp mntl-figure-caption text-utility-100 figure-article-caption"&gt; &lt;span class="figure-article-caption-text"&gt;Sheet-Pan Poblano-&amp;amp;-Corn Chicken Fajitas.&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class="figure-article-caption-owner"&gt;Photographer / Antonis Achilleos, Prop Stylist / Christine Kelly, Food Stylist / Karen Rankin&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_134-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Breakfast (295 calories) &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_136-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_137-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Morning Snack (134 calories) &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_138-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;li&gt; 1 cup blackberries &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt; ⅔ cup low-fat plain kefir &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_139-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_140-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Lunch (357 calories) &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_142-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_143-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Afternoon Snack (206 calories) &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_144-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;li&gt; ¼ cup unsalted dry-roasted almonds &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_145-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_146-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Dinner (500 calories) &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_148-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_149-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Daily totals:&lt;/strong&gt; 1,493 calories, 81g fat, 87g protein, 112g carbohydrate, 33g fiber, 1,753mg sodium&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_150-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_151-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;To make it 2,000 calories: &lt;/strong&gt;Add 1 cup edamame, in pods, to lunch, add 1 medium orange to P.M. snack and add 1 serving &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/recipe/262151/guacamole-chopped-salad/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Guacamole Chopped Salad&lt;/a&gt; to dinner.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_152-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div id="mntl-sc-block_154-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-faq mntl-sc-block-universal-faq"&gt;&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-faqs-f4a9cd72-5653-44a9-b1fa-a5ca55d319b0"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;h2 class="mntl-sc-block-universal-faq__title"&gt;Frequently Asked Questions&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;noscript id="universal-faq-noscript_1-0" class="comp universal-faq-noscript mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block-universal-faq__content_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block-universal-faq__content mntl-accordion js-accordion"&gt;
&lt;li class="accordion__item js-accordion-item " data-ordinal="1"&gt;
&lt;p tabindex="0" class="accordion__header js-accordion-trigger" id="mntl-accordion__item_1-0-section-0"&gt;
&lt;svg class="icon icon-chevron accordion__icon"&gt;
&lt;use xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xlink:href="#icon-chevron" href="#icon-chevron"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;
&lt;/svg&gt;
&lt;span class="accordion__title"&gt;Is it OK to mix and match meals if there's one I don't like?&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="accordion__body"&gt;
&lt;div id="mntl-accordion__content_1-0" class="comp mntl-accordion__content"&gt; &lt;div class="faq-accordion__item-answer"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yes! This meal plan is meant to serve as inspiration. It doesn’t need to be followed exactly to reap the benefits. When choosing recipes, we made sure to check the calories, fiber, protein and sodium to align with the parameters of this plan and be within our sodium limits. If you’re making a recipe swap, it may be helpful to choose a recipe with similar calories, fiber, protein and sodium levels. For more inspiration, check out these &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/gallery/7889605/diabetes-friendly-recipes-for-healthy-blood-sugar/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;delicious diabetes-friendly recipes&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="accordion__item js-accordion-item " data-ordinal="2"&gt;
&lt;p tabindex="0" class="accordion__header js-accordion-trigger" id="mntl-accordion__item_2-0-section-1"&gt;
&lt;svg class="icon icon-chevron accordion__icon"&gt;
&lt;use xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xlink:href="#icon-chevron" href="#icon-chevron"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;
&lt;/svg&gt;
&lt;span class="accordion__title"&gt;Can I eat the same breakfast or lunch every day?&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="accordion__body"&gt;
&lt;div id="mntl-accordion__content_2-0" class="comp mntl-accordion__content"&gt; &lt;div class="faq-accordion__item-answer"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Definitely, it’s fine to eat the same breakfast or lunch every day. The breakfasts range from 295-339 calories while the lunches span 357-408 calories. These ranges are fairly close, though if you’re closely monitoring your calories or other nutrients, like protein, you may want to adjust a snack or two.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="accordion__item js-accordion-item " data-ordinal="3"&gt;
&lt;p tabindex="0" class="accordion__header js-accordion-trigger" id="mntl-accordion__item_3-0-section-2"&gt;
&lt;svg class="icon icon-chevron accordion__icon"&gt;
&lt;use xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xlink:href="#icon-chevron" href="#icon-chevron"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;
&lt;/svg&gt;
&lt;span class="accordion__title"&gt;Why is there not a modification for 1,200 calories?&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="accordion__body"&gt;
&lt;div id="mntl-accordion__content_3-0" class="comp mntl-accordion__content"&gt; &lt;div class="faq-accordion__item-answer"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We no longer provide modifications for 1,200-calorie days in our meal plans. The 2020-2025 Dietary Guidelines for Americans suggests that limiting calories to 1,200 per day is too low for most people to meet their nutritional needs, plus it’s unsustainable for long-term health and well-being.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="1"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="accordion__item js-accordion-item " data-ordinal="4"&gt;
&lt;p tabindex="0" class="accordion__header js-accordion-trigger" id="mntl-accordion__item_4-0-section-3"&gt;
&lt;svg class="icon icon-chevron accordion__icon"&gt;
&lt;use xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xlink:href="#icon-chevron" href="#icon-chevron"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;
&lt;/svg&gt;
&lt;span class="accordion__title"&gt;What is the difference between natural and added sugars?&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="accordion__body"&gt;
&lt;div id="mntl-accordion__content_4-0" class="comp mntl-accordion__content"&gt; &lt;div class="faq-accordion__item-answer"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Natural sugars are found in fruit, vegetables and dairy foods. Added sugars are any type of sugar that has been added during the processing of a food. This can include "natural" sources like honey, agave and maple syrup. Once these sugars are added to a food, they become an added sugar. Unlike added sugars that only provide sweetness without nutrition benefits, foods containing &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/291857/heres-why-you-should-eat-fruit-even-though-it-contains-sugar/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;natural sugars also have other nutrients&lt;/a&gt; like fiber, protein, vitamins and minerals.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;noscript id="accordion-noscript_1-0" class="comp accordion-noscript mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_155-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-tips-for-managing-blood-sugar"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_156-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Tips for Managing Blood Sugar &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_157-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Choose water and unsweetened drinks: &lt;/strong&gt;Because &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/8009374/best-and-worst-hydration-drinks-for-people-with-diabetes/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;sugar-laden drinks&lt;/a&gt; are a huge source of added sugars, opting for water, seltzer and other zero-carbohydrate drinks can have a beneficial impact on your blood sugar levels.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Exercise: &lt;/strong&gt;Moving your body in whatever way feels good is always helpful, especially if you are aiming to &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/7834958/what-you-need-to-know-about-exercise-diabetes/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;lower blood sugars&lt;/a&gt;. Exercise doesn't have to be extreme to have benefits. Research shows that &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/7998411/walking-after-meals-lower-blood-sugar-science/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="3"&gt;walking for just two minutes after each meal&lt;/a&gt; can benefit your blood sugar.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pair carbohydrates with protein or fat:&lt;/strong&gt; Pairing carbs with foods containing protein or fat helps reduce blood sugar spikes, keeps you fuller for longer and provides more stable energy.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Focus on fiber:&lt;/strong&gt; Increasing fiber, a type of carbohydrate that's not digested, has a ton of &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/287742/10-amazing-health-benefits-of-eating-more-fiber/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="4"&gt;health benefits&lt;/a&gt;, including improved blood sugar levels.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_158-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="mntl-sc-block_159-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-callout mntl-sc-block-universal-callout theme-generic" data-tracking-id="mntl-sc-block-callout" data-tracking-container="true"&gt; &lt;h3 class="mntl-sc-block-universal-callout__heading"&gt;How We Create Meal Plans&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;div class="mntl-sc-block-universal-callout__body"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Registered dietitians thoughtfully create EatingWell’s meal plans to be easy-to-follow and delicious. Each meal plan meets specific parameters depending on the health condition and/or lifestyle goal it is targeting and is analyzed for accuracy using the nutrition database, ESHA Food Processor. As nutritional needs differ from person to person, we encourage you to use these plans as inspiration and adjust as you see fit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>EatingWell</author><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijwFBVV95cUxPb1V0Qmt5c094cEtpSG9GQk5Jd1JkUTZ1WDRJTVlKRjkzTUhMUjVOZDFZLVB5U0c2aXlnS0tidl8zRDFTTVRTZHVTUVhWOGNveXBvcENrVmZ1djZteFhPZnVhY3hkNjNYUHF4cFM0dmFLMWpXWmE5VHFaMEtHVnBtMzludmN4ZTJ1enZhNU1SVQ</guid></item><item><title>日本男子心脏病发作后复苏；坚持“去上班” –医生解释为什么休息-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/japanese-man-gets-resuscitated-after-heart-attack-insists-on-going-to-work-doctor-explains-why-rest-and-recovery-is-important/articleshow/125178536.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Japanese man recently collapsed on a train platform. Thankfully, he got resuscitated, but insisted on going to work that same day! Dr Kunal Sood, MD, recently put up a video explaining that while heart attacks can be fatal, if you survive one, recovery and rest is equally important to prevent a repeat episode…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="1"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr. Kunal Sood advises that the path to post‑heart‑attack recovery should rest on measures aimed at restoring health, and enhancing overall quality of life. He blends guidance with everyday lifestyle tweaks, underscoring the need to spot warning signs early and to cultivate supportive habits. Let’s take a look…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="3"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Tune in to warning signs…&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="5"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr. Sood stresses that even the faintest alarm from the heart shouldn’t be dismissed-even tiny changes can be significant. He points out that new chest ache palpitations, accompanied by fainting, or shortness of breath, swelling in the legs, all call for medical attention. Ignoring these cues can postpone treatment, and worsen the outlook. If anything feels off, call a doctor right away.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="9"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="11"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Stay on track with your medication plan&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="13"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The medicines your doctor prescribes are meant to prevent clot formation, keep your blood pressure down, and keep the heart’s rhythm in check. Dr. Sood urges everyone to keep up with their medicines, and never miss a dose, or stop taking medicine, without talking to the doctor first.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="17"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Eat foods that keep your heart healthy&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="19"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Opt for foods that nurture your heart-colorful fruit, crunchy vegetables, whole‑grain staples, lean protein sources and beneficial fats. Dr. Sood advises cutting out processed items, an overabundance of salt, sugary treats and saturated fats. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Likewise smoking and heavy drinking should be avoided, given their tendency to damage blood vessels and elevate blood pressure. Embracing a Mediterranean‑style diet can shield the heart, and promote blood flow.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="23"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Exercise&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="25"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Moving the body gives the heart a chance to bounce back while keeping weight in check. Dr. Sood recommends low‑key options, such as a stroll, a jog, or a 20‑30 minute session on a stationary bike, each day. It’s wise to consult your doctor before starting, and to stop the routine the moment chest pain, breathlessness or dizziness surface. Over time, steady activity eases the strain on the heart, and gradually builds strength.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="29"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="31"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Sleep well, and keep rest at bay&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="33"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rest plays a key role in the healing journey. Dr. Sood advises that a good night’s sleep and a steady sleep schedule, are non‑negotiable. Engaging in calming pursuits-meditation, deep‑breathing techniques or quality time with loved ones, can bolster emotional health and keep relapse at bay.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="36"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Quit smoking&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="38"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tobacco eats away at the arteries and bumps up the risk of heart disease. Dr. Sood says quitting smoking is one of the best steps you can take to protect your heart. Even the tiniest amount of tobacco, chewing tobacco included, should be stopped, because it makes recovery harder and raises the risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="40"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Maintaining weight and blood pressure&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="42"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Carrying weight taxes the heart, and can drag out the recovery timeline. Dr. Sood suggests maintaining an ideal weight, keeping a watch on salt intake, and having blood pressure measured on a routine basis. When that surplus fat drops, the odds of another heart attack shrink.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="46"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Get a support system&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="48"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Recovering from a heart attack feels less overwhelming when friends, family or a support group step, in to help. Dr. Sood advises leaning on others, asking for assistance and sharing worries. Such emotional support can reduce stress, and sustain motivation, which is crucial for long‑term heart health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="51"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Consistent health check‑ups&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="53"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;After a heart attack, staying on schedule with visits to your doctor becomes essential. Dr. Sood underscores the importance of blood work and cardiac scans, to catch any trouble early on. Throughout recovery, physicians often lean on imaging, lab tests and a range of tools to steer treatment and keep complications at bay.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="55"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Red flags that demand urgent attention&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="57"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;An abrupt uneasy pressure in the chest that radiates toward the jaw, arm or neck.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="60"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;A manifested swelling, in the legs, or a sudden spell of breathlessness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="62"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Palpitations, those flutterings of the heart, may be accompanied by vertigo or even a sudden loss of consciousness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="64"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mental fog for days at a stretch&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="66"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr Sood says that one should never ignore these warning signs, especially if they occur after a heart attack.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="68"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 05:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiyAJBVV95cUxObkNXVF93M2Jnc3JLZjlGLThPdlR6cjBjR09uNWRYN0JzdGVBdmxDelZVdWwtTFN3TUFiaGd1LVFaLUdpOERBaTM1bm1EVlRlTUFQOGE0WEVMS0FDaGFsQWJPUm5ndWo5MmphVUM3R3Y4clV1T3BDOFd6UXBVcW81NmVYVWpuanphejRIdm5IcFMwV1NoVTR3SkRxbmVsS3plTDk1enU2a1VOZmZsZVRwcWJiZS1wYl9FcjNXLWRGWFlLMEF2VjlPV05OeDNKaUpEWGsyQnVaNGtvanlGUUJ3MEIxY2F1UWpNUVU0Q0xiZF9hUm9zdVFmRDJ3VEtyMk41RzVLZFRJNU93alBxZ3hRWHZrb3UzVER0dXhRTzkzNHFHZnBCSzNZUjl5WE9vc1N0eV9kSURDV2pJMnI4R21VdEh4NXpIVExm</guid></item><item><title>根据科学家的说法，这种病毒性护肤趋势实际上是有效的- SciTechDaily</title><link>https://scitechdaily.com/according-to-scientists-this-viral-skincare-trend-actually-works/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>SciTechDaily</author><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 04:47:24 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilAFBVV95cUxPbGZmY1g3VUhTd0FWOHJHS25heGpKQU12VEJsYlRkaVVJY3BwN2I1RWF0R2h3Q2dBdmdMYUZoUHBwcnk1aFVkcmtPajNGdWJRR25tLUl4UmtQVlZUSzBZZnZ2cDBoX3BUU3MyQWZBd19HRmVjMkNoT04ybVEyZEI0UmdsOWZxWllWUEdVZ04welFvTTd1</guid></item><item><title>一直便秘？ 5种医生批准的食物组合，帮助您自然排便-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/diet/constipated-all-the-time-5-doctor-approved-food-combinations-that-help-you-poop-naturally/photostory/125177679.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="COQxt" data-ua-type="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dr. Alka's approach is refreshingly simple. She suggests listening to one's body, sticking to a routine with these combinations, and adjusting their times according to one's needs. Start with hydration, make movement a non-negotiable, load up on fiber, and then try these soothing, fiber-rich pairings. You really don't need expensive supplements or strong medications for most cases of mild constipation; nature often provides what you need&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pairing the right fruits with soothing liquids at the right time can gently support our digestive system and help with occasional stomach-related issues, such as constipation. It is imperative to understand that these solutions are not for chronic constipation and if the issues persist, it is better to consult a medical health professional, as it could be an underlying symptom of a disease not been well diagnosed. As Dr. Alka emphasises, blending evidence-backed nutrition with traditional wisdom makes the gut happy.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Times of India</author><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 04:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijgJBVV95cUxNY0hSdUFVNUVzWG5zUEFXVlRoU0lYSlJGLU1VdVdvS3JfZVpVTTA1bjhtUUNQdE9ZaGFqWGpDODRkc2VPVHhGdG5RdDUtcFVKN2tPLWhyYXhkZjZGNmhReDJ4V2ZJMGk2d2t1VnVrdDV0dWh5dVVIeTJFNGJyaGRZODJoamtZV1ZoQ29QbUJ0QjlrZkkzeGhTNTRXZHpsUVJJaDhmc1I4SkxlSkl2VE1mZjhHRHJDRGlfZXVLVV91NUtEcXh1MTRsaXZWWVF0SU93OERuQ0pmT1RwejNYeVpqaG1EVTFKTmROSEJrYi1pdC1sRDRGclZENWVEb0NpWXh3ZFZFeGZZRV9GZTJ3RlHSAZYCQVVfeXFMT3BrTkZqUTFvbGxCcGZsSTgtOHZYRHlQYWgzX3dzQjhOZ1YxS3FIVVpFUFpnLTB3YlFjRlFUT2dKckJIMXA3cjJHbldVYlkzOTlaX0UyT2N3VTYwOVdYVHBORXRoeWVLNDJ2ZFNEcHRTNmw5d2twbjJwTDBPaEJUUENfUE1QaG9hM2xHdnlncF9sQXBZN1hGcU9TZ1k3Q0ppb2hXa0NrUWZmeTAxTUJDWmxfVGZSc1I0VWoxMVJHLVpQaXVEN2Q5N2FrYVBVS0JjMVNFVEotTTRrN0UtYUtuSmZXMVlReG9icmE5dy01WnBCQ3UzUlQtalktWjJoR0pScllNUndSWGNFRU1nTnJUQ1c2bTYwM1E</guid></item><item><title>肥胖症的发现震惊了科学家，挑战了60年的信仰-SciTechDaily</title><link>https://scitechdaily.com/obesity-discovery-stuns-scientists-challenges-60-year-old-beliefs/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>SciTechDaily</author><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 04:12:53 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilgFBVV95cUxNQjdEUGFVdDVPVUZJTGVLend2emRmX3k3N1dNQUFyS1kzZ0FfWElJeHNOVDN0NWluYWRxTk5MMmZwdEtVbDJqMXpOQzFJSlU0a1BWM0NfTWFqMUFyS1AxZ0FqY3E1dHkxTFRqOEN3azBaRDFKM0sxUlJpZzJaTHlHUnZFLVhRWGRLbXZGdGE0VTFoZlQxd2c</guid></item></channel></rss>