<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>GNews Health</title><link>https://news.google.com/</link><description></description><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>我把声音看作形状。通感赋予了我非凡的语言能力--《卫报》</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/lifeandstyle/2026/jan/10/auditory-visual-synaesthesia-languages</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body-commercial-selector article-body-viewer-selector dcr-hdpgoq"&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-15rw6c2"&gt;C&lt;/span&gt;ar journeys with my partner are a nightmare. He’s an ex-DJ so he likes to crank the music up, but for me this means seeing static images and flashes of light in my mind’s eye while I’m trying to drive. It’s hard to describe exactly what I see when I hear sound. But it’s almost like the sound waves you’d see if you watched an audio recording on a screen, or these little neurons connecting and space nebulas exploding in front of me.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;I’m 44 now and only realised I had auditory-visual synaesthesia in my 30s. What I did know was that I seemed to have an extraordinary ability for linguistics. In school I studied Japanese and did really well without trying because I could literally see the words and sounds presented as images in front of me, making them easy to remember. At university I majored in Spanish, Korean and Indonesian and it was no effort at all. I then joined the air force as an intelligence officer because I didn’t want to become a teacher or translator. I walked away from the language aptitude test thinking I’d either messed it up or that it had been the easiest thing I’d ever done in my life. No one’s ever managed to get every answer right, they said when the results came back. But I hadn’t even tried. It just came naturally.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="sign-in-gate"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="7bdf26c2-a1fe-4d86-8150-a5147c09bbf1" data-spacefinder-role="richLink" data-spacefinder-type="model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.RichLinkBlockElement" class="dcr-47fhrn"&gt;&lt;gu-island name="RichLinkComponent" priority="feature" deferuntil="idle" props='{"richLinkIndex":2,"element":{"_type":"model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.RichLinkBlockElement","prefix":"Related: ","text":"I taste words. ‘Bob’ is like a milk chocolate Easter egg on my tongue","elementId":"7bdf26c2-a1fe-4d86-8150-a5147c09bbf1","role":"richLink","url":"https://www.theguardian.com/lifeandstyle/2026/jan/02/i-taste-words-lexical-gustatory-synaesthesia"},"ajaxUrl":"https://api.nextgen.guardianapps.co.uk","format":{"design":10,"display":2,"theme":4},"isInStarRatingVariant":false}'&gt;&lt;/gu-island&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The first time I heard the word synaesthesia was when I decided to work in speech pathology after leaving the military. I started learning about autism spectrum disorder and various forms of neurodivergence, and read about this phenomenon called synaesthesia, in which stimulation of one sense leads to automatic experiences in a second sense. I didn’t make any connection to my own experiences but began reading a book about a man who could learn languages in a matter of hours. Still, I didn’t make the connection. I just thought it was interesting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;It wasn’t until I started doing speech-to-text computational linguistic work that I started really thinking about the fact that I was seeing these shapes when I heard sounds or phonemes. I found a Facebook group full of people who saw sounds too, though they all saw sounds as colours whereas mine are all black and white shapes. The only time I see colour is when I hear high-frequency sounds, which start as bright white then move through the scale of yellows to oranges to reds. I’ve always been able to pass hearing tests at ridiculously quiet decibels because I see the pure tones as different coloured flashes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="861f071e-c525-4f23-aedc-b41d0f45b783" data-spacefinder-role="showcase" data-spacefinder-type="model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.ImageBlockElement" class="dcr-5h0uf4"&gt;&lt;figcaption data-spacefinder-role="inline" class="dcr-9ktzqp"&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-1inf02i"&gt;&lt;svg viewbox="0 0 18 13"&gt;&lt;path d="M18 3.5v8l-1.5 1.5h-15l-1.5-1.5v-8l1.5-1.5h3.5l2-2h4l2 2h3.5l1.5 1.5zm-9 7.5c1.9 0 3.5-1.6 3.5-3.5s-1.6-3.5-3.5-3.5-3.5 1.6-3.5 3.5 1.6 3.5 3.5 3.5z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-1qvd3m6"&gt;‘My brain feels busy pretty much constantly thanks to the noisy world we live in.’&lt;/span&gt; Photograph: Blake Sharp-Wiggins/The Guardian&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;One day I was working as an assistant transcribing Indigenous creole languages for Wollongong University when my supervisor put me in touch with the head linguist for Apple. She was looking for someone really good with phonetics, who would be free to go to Japan for 90 days to work on a new speech-to-text project. On day one of the job I found out I’d been chosen to work on Siri.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;I spent a lot of time in headphones over those next 90 days, as they recorded Australian voices and I sat in. I loved it and I’ve loved pretty much every work-day since. I’ve done speech-to-text projects for Tom Tom GPS and Bank of America, and a lot of my day-to-day work now is as a speech pathologist, helping children and adults to communicate and swallow better.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;I’m not worried about the rise of AI because language is incredibly nuanced and robots simply aren’t good enough to pick up those subtleties. I can break down the &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/science/2024/jan/25/its-an-expression-of-identity-the-tiktoker-taking-the-western-sydney-accent-to-the-world" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;western Sydney Lebanese accent&lt;/a&gt; in an instant. I wouldn’t trust AI to do it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;My form of synaesthesia comes with its challenges. I wear a lot of earplugs to block out the sound around me, and my brain feels busy pretty much constantly thanks to the noisy world we live in. Running to music is my favourite way to switch off. It’s the only time I don’t see sound and my brain is quiet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;All of that said, I wouldn’t change my synaesthesia for a second. I could lose my sight and cut my arms off, but if I couldn’t work with words and sounds it would destroy me. I feel so lucky that I found this field of work when I did, and I’ll keep going until I’m 80 if I can. It feels like my reason for being – my &lt;em&gt;ikigai&lt;/em&gt;, they call it in Japanese. I’d do it for free if I didn’t have bills to pay.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Guardian</author><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 14:09:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilgFBVV95cUxPUFBJNmk4SUh3NkJIeEs2aVVnbWNkNWRDZ2FhMU9TU0VYYkVTSTVFQ3Ixb1pBQVpSZ24yVzI5dmdnSW1xYWlhSTl2UThYcTFyd0RGRlJVYnFycEdQbUc3TGo3THlFRDgtd2I0ekNDZGNsQ280NEE2SXp4UjIwS3Z0RzJYZWQ1WE9aenRod2VhRTFlZE5hdGc</guid></item><item><title>大量研究将99%的心脏病发作和中风与4个风险因素联系起来- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/huge-study-links-99-of-heart-attacks-and-strokes-with-4-risk-factors</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Heart attacks and strokes rarely occur without warning.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to health data from more than 9 million adults in South Korea and the US, nearly everyone who develops heart disease and suffers a major cardiovascular event has one of four major risk factors in the lead-up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These factors include high blood pressure, high cholesterol, high blood sugar levels, and tobacco smoking (past or current).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/nearly-half-of-all-heart-attacks-may-be-missed-by-current-screening-tools"&gt;Nearly Half of All Heart Attacks May Be Missed by Current Screening Tools&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Combined as a group, they preceded 99 percent of all cardiovascular events during the long-term study, which was published in 2025.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_176016" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-176016" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/mm6805a2_Heart-Attack-Awareness-VA1200x675-medium.jpg" alt="CDC Heart Attack" class="size-full wp-image-176016" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/mm6805a2_Heart-Attack-Awareness-VA1200x675-medium.jpg 635w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/mm6805a2_Heart-Attack-Awareness-VA1200x675-medium-600x337.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 635px) 100vw, 635px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-176016" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Recognizing the imminent signs of a heart attack could save lives. (&lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/mmwr/volumes/68/wr/mm6805a2.htm"&gt;CDC&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even in women under 60 – the demographic with the lowest risk of cardiovascular events – more than 95 percent of heart attacks or strokes were linked to one of these existing risk factors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/over-50-of-heart-attacks-in-younger-women-arent-from-clogged-arteries"&gt;Over 50% of Heart Attacks in Younger Women Aren't From Clogged Arteries&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/new-blood-pressure-guidelines-mean-you-may-now-have-hypertension"&gt;High blood pressure&lt;/a&gt; was the factor most commonly tied to cardiovascular events. In both the US and South Korea, more than 93 percent of individuals who experienced a heart attack, stroke, or heart failure had hypertension beforehand.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Managing this risk factor could, therefore, be key to preventing serious cardiovascular disease down the road.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We think the study shows very convincingly that exposure to one or more nonoptimal risk factors before these cardiovascular outcomes is nearly 100 percent," senior author and &lt;a href="https://news.northwestern.edu/stories/2025/09/nearly-everyone-has-at-least-one-risk-factor-before-a-heart-attack-stroke-or-heart-failure"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;cardiologist Philip Greenland from Northwestern University &lt;a href="https://news.northwestern.edu/stories/2025/09/nearly-everyone-has-at-least-one-risk-factor-before-a-heart-attack-stroke-or-heart-failure"&gt;&lt;span&gt;said&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt; in September when the research was published.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The goal now is to work harder on finding ways to control these modifiable risk factors rather than to get off track in pursuing other factors that are not easily treatable and not causal."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/newsletter?utm_source=promo_generic_health"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-642x273.jpg" alt="Subscribe to ScienceAlert's free fact-checked newsletter" class="alignnone wp-image-182810 size-medium" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-642x273.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-768x326.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-600x255.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final.jpg 850w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Greenland and his co-authors note that their results challenge &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.jacc.2023.06.045"&gt;recent claims&lt;/a&gt; that insidious cardiovascular events occurring in the absence of risk factors are increasing, suggesting that previous studies may have missed diagnoses or overlooked risk factor levels that were below the clinical diagnostic threshold.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/one-protein-is-a-better-predictor-of-heart-disease-than-cholesterol"&gt;One Protein Is a Better Predictor of Heart Disease Than Cholesterol&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In an accompanying &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.jacc.2025.08.030"&gt;&lt;span&gt;editorial&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, Duke University cardiologist Neha Pagidipati (who was not involved in the study) argues that the results show just how important it is to manage health risks before they lead to serious, potentially fatal outcomes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We can – and must – do better," she &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.jacc.2025.08.030"&gt;&lt;span&gt;writes&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study was published in the &lt;a href="https://dx.doi.org/10.1016/j.jacc.2025.07.014"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Journal of the American College of Cardiology&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;An earlier version of this article was published in October 2025.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 12:03:36 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMingFBVV95cUxObmZPSTBrUDdYUEp2UjJiRERzUlhHS0ZudGZrRjZReTBpeE0yVFJBeldncVV4RVRqOHlTS1NiVGgyYm1SbFJPTGFIZkVQNGMzM2ZESHpMbmZNTUpUcExTaTUwM25BZlJPT19ZYWd3V3VKZDBXTkVBTFdVNC1STEd0SnhoMkdocXFJZEFYZEhXVlNHeG5wNjRXeFJjNWY4QQ</guid></item><item><title>随着感染的增加，美国建立病例以保持麻疹消除状态- CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2026/01/09/health/measles-elimination-investigation</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article__content" data-editable="content" itemprop="articleBody" data-reorderable="content"&gt;
                
    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmk66pf97001q26qjg3c99cdx@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            U.S. officials are building a case that ongoing measles &lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/measles-cases-south-carolina-rise-by-nine-185-state-health-department-says-2026-01-02/" target="_blank"&gt;outbreaks in South Carolina&lt;/a&gt; and other states are unrelated to last year’s major outbreak in Texas, as it tries to retain its status of having eliminated the disease after recording the highest number of confirmed infections in three decades.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmk66q3lv00063b6srmi5munv@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            To be considered measles-free by the World Health Organization, a country must have no locally transmitted cases of the same strain for 12 months or longer.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmk66pid800003b6sxik24uoo@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Scientists studying the issue say the elimination assessment may not be ironclad as it is difficult to be certain that all cases potentially linked to the Texas outbreak have been reported.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmk66qezm000d3b6s5it2ekm5@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            A large outbreak of measles in Texas kicked off 2025 in January and spread to several states, followed by large outbreaks along the Arizona-Utah border and in South Carolina that continue to cause infections.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmk66qezm000e3b6sl7pyk34m@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            In November, the Pan American Health Organization - part of the WHO - determined that Canada had &lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/canada-has-lost-its-measles-elimination-status-says-ottawa-2025-11-10/" target="_blank"&gt;lost its measles elimination status&lt;/a&gt; after nearly three decades due to its failure to curb a year-long outbreak of the vaccine-preventable disease.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmk66qeqp000b3b6suaskfzy7@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            PAHO this year will evaluate U.S. measles data, which involves 2,065 confirmed cases, to see if it can keep the measles elimination status it has had since 2000.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmk66qlve000j3b6scr4dvlm9@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Former U.S. public health officials have described measles elimination status as a key indicator of a nation’s health.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmk66qlve000k3b6st2ptaaog@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The United States will have to prove the ongoing measles cases are not related to the Texas outbreak, and were instead brought into the country from infected travelers, said William Moss, an epidemiology professor at the Johns Hopkins Bloomberg School of Public Health.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmk66qlve000l3b6ssh6tzpwc@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            State public health officials have used traditional methods of interviewing infected individuals to identify chains of transmission, as well as comparing the viral genotype - a section of the virus’ DNA - to see if cases are related. That still may not be sufficient to link cases in a large outbreak, experts said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmk66qlhh000h3b6seq4hhuzx@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Kelly Oakeson, who leads next-generation sequencing at the Utah Public Health Laboratory, said none of the patients interviewed in Utah mentioned travel to Texas or contact with people from Texas, but many gave incomplete information.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmk66qsk6000r3b6sy69hokj0@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Based on the state’s detailed genetic analysis, however, he said the Utah strain is “different enough” from the Texas outbreak to suggest they are unrelated.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmk66qsk6000s3b6skyhndgji@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “We don’t think there is a direct link,” he said in an email, adding that the state has been working with CDC, Texas and Arizona to characterize transmission patterns.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmk66qsk6000t3b6sf9d3do7z@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            In addition, the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention has been analyzing the entire genetic code of virus samples to determine if the outbreaks are related, a newer technique that has not traditionally been used to assess measles transmission.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmk66qs7t000p3b6s7ganosrl@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Early evidence from the CDC analysis, which has not been made public, suggests the outbreaks are not related, according to two sources who have seen the data.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmk66r2o2000y3b6sdddgub0i@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            In a December 5 &lt;a href="https://x.com/HHS_Jim/status/1996961704417046752" target="_blank"&gt;post&lt;/a&gt; on X, CDC Acting Director Jim O’Neill said there was no epidemiological evidence linking the Texas outbreak and the ongoing cases in South Carolina.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmk66r2o2000z3b6shrouql19@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            A U.S. Health and Human Services spokesman confirmed that the CDC has found no epidemiological evidence linking ongoing outbreaks to Texas, but said many recent U.S. cases share the same genotype and have no known source of infection, “which could indicate ongoing domestic transmission.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

  

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmk66r2o200113b6sy15hbtpf@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Dr. Noel Brewer, an infectious disease doctor at the University of North Carolina who has seen the CDC data, said the preliminary evidence suggests that new cases in Texas stopped in July and there was a three-week gap before the Utah-Arizona outbreak began.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmk66r2o200123b6sgrrbov76@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “No cases linked the two outbreaks in any clear way,” said Brewer, who chairs an independent committee that will analyze the U.S. data and make a report to PAHO on whether it agrees with the U.S. assessment.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmk66r2o200133b6skqs69ysv@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The CDC’s inability to link the outbreaks, Brewer said, may simply reflect that the virus is circulating broadly in the United States and that it is “not possible at this time to track all of the cases.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmk66r2o200143b6secvaq8zj@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            There are many gaps in epidemiological knowledge in the U.S. outbreaks and not all cases are identified or reported, said Johns Hopkins’ Moss, so you can miss cases linking two outbreaks.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmk66r2o200153b6sgt7ygao2@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            In addition, many of the larger U.S. outbreaks are occurring in communities that don’t trust the public health system and may be less likely to report cases or participate in an investigation.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmk66r2o200163b6s353evx26@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            That could lead scientists to incorrectly conclude that two viruses are different when it was just a sampling problem, Moss said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmk66r2o200173b6sob3j505y@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Dr. Demetre Daskalakis, former CDC director of the National Center for Immunization and Respiratory Diseases who quit in August over &lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/do-no-harm-why-three-cdc-officials-left-over-vaccine-policy-2025-08-28/" target="_blank"&gt;concerns&lt;/a&gt; about U.S. vaccine policy under Health Secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr., said PAHO will make the call based on the evidence it receives.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmk66r2o200183b6sdjy9o869@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “If they don’t believe in the strength of one part of the data, and there are other compelling factors that say that the U.S. has lost elimination, it means that the U.S. has lost elimination.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

              &lt;/div&gt;
                  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>CNN</author><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 12:00:58 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMie0FVX3lxTFBVWDdyeGRhaFotMnFZUFR0SXI1OFp3X1R0d2tHVXF4R0V0d0V6cDA4NG1aMXJYUWcxd3NTU3NIT1BWd09FcU1mZFowQTR0OG5STE5NMEpSVW9rT2JrVTRpQThxZUNUTDdVQ0JLQzBiRTM1c0RTM3ItNmxObw</guid></item><item><title>科学家发现女性生育率随年龄下降的新线索--《华盛顿邮报》</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/health/2026/01/09/ivf-fertility-aging-eggs/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="QBZ6XQLA2FHBTKZQ4NA3D56O3E" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Scientists are making inroads in understanding one of the central mysteries of human reproduction: Why do women’s eggs deteriorate as they age?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="P2SYEPKC7ZBGPLH2JDMF2EFQLI" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;The broad strokes have been&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;well-known — the ticking of a woman’s biological clock increases risk of miscarriage and infertility, often caused by eggs with the wrong number of chromosomes, the structures that carry DNA.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 11:32:17 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMif0FVX3lxTE5UQXIxZlJtR1AtRUhZQ0JZT2lPZDV1U1ZneFczRmlvSDAwN3h4RVdVbHZQUXhTamZMYVhpSVBIc1F3NU5WTmRtT2JRWkhsV05ZTzdnVFBMMWNSdHNIQXVKaVY0QzJhcnJzMGJLdkJydGo4cEg4VTJMaGRxNlZ1LWM</guid></item><item><title>恢复老化关节的新突破可能有助于治疗骨关节炎- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/new-breakthrough-to-restore-aging-joints-could-help-treat-osteoarthritis</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;A study in mice by researchers from Stanford University has traced the loss of cartilage that comes with aging to a single protein, pointing to treatments that may one day restore mobility and ease discomfort in seniors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The protein 15-PGDH has previously been &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1038/d41573-025-00209-5"&gt;extensively linked to aging&lt;/a&gt;: it becomes more abundant as we get older, and interferes with the molecules that repair tissue and reduce inflammation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That led scientists to consider whether 15-PGDH might be involved in osteoarthritis, where stress on joints leads to the breakdown &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Collagen"&gt;of collagen&lt;/a&gt; in cartilage, causing inflammation and pain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/arthritis-affects-thousands-of-kids-and-one-piece-of-advice-is-crucial"&gt;Arthritis Affects Thousands of Kids, And One Piece of Advice Is Crucial&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In tests on old mice, knee cartilage that had previously worn down thickened following the introduction of a 15-PGDH inhibitor. In similar tests on young, injured mice, the inhibitor offered protection against the usual effects of injury-induced osteoarthritis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When the researchers triggered the equivalent of an anterior cruciate ligament injury in mice and subsequently applied the treatment, osteoarthritis didn't develop, as would normally be expected in these kinds of mouse models.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Previous attempts at cartilage regeneration included the use of  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/stem-cells" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73034" data-postid="187978" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;stem cells&lt;/a&gt;, a factor that was no longer necessary when 15-PGDH was inhibited. Instead, &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Chondrocyte"&gt;the chondrocyte cells&lt;/a&gt; that make and maintain cartilage were being transformed into a healthier, more useful state.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"This is a new way of regenerating adult tissue, and it has significant clinical promise for treating arthritis due to aging or injury," &lt;a href="https://news.stanford.edu/stories/2025/11/joint-cartilage-aging-osteoarthritis-therapy-research"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; microbiologist Helen Blau. "We were looking for stem cells, but they are clearly not involved. It's very exciting."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_187981" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-187981" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2026/01/MouseScans.jpg" alt="Cartilage scans" class="wp-image-187981 size-full" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2026/01/MouseScans.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2026/01/MouseScans-600x420.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-187981" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Treated aged cartilage (far right, stained red) looked much more like young, healthy cartilage (far left, stained red). (Singla et al., &lt;em&gt;Science&lt;/em&gt;, 2025)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Treated mice had a steadier gait, suggesting they were experiencing less pain, and were shown putting more weight on their injured legs – signs that the &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/humans-have-a-hidden-salamander-like-ability-to-regenerate-body-tissue"&gt;cartilage restoration&lt;/a&gt; equated improved physical health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The same experiment was also tried on human tissue samples taken from people having knee replacement surgery. Again, there were clear signs of regeneration, with the cartilage getting stiffer and showing fewer signs of inflammation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The mechanism is quite striking and really shifted our perspective about how tissue regeneration can occur," &lt;a href="https://news.stanford.edu/stories/2025/11/joint-cartilage-aging-osteoarthritis-therapy-research"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; orthopaedic scientist Nidhi Bhutani. "It's clear that a large pool of already existing cells in cartilage are changing their gene expression patterns."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"And by targeting these cells for regeneration, we may have an opportunity to have a bigger overall impact clinically."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/newsletter?utm_source=promo_generic_health"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-642x273.jpg" alt="Subscribe to ScienceAlert's free fact-checked newsletter" class="alignnone wp-image-182810 size-medium" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-642x273.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-768x326.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-600x255.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final.jpg 850w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While there's still plenty of work to do, this could eventually lead to effective treatments to roll back the damage done by arthritis or aging in general. We could be heading towards a future where hip and &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/there-s-now-an-artificial-cartilage-gel-that-s-strong-enough-to-work-on-knees"&gt;knee replacements&lt;/a&gt; are no longer needed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Besides replacing the joints affected, current treatment options for osteoarthritis are limited to pain management. Despite &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/radiation-therapy-reduces-pain-from-the-most-common-form-of-arthritis"&gt;promising research&lt;/a&gt; in recent years, we don't have anything yet that tackles the root cause of the condition.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The next steps could include a  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/clinical-trials" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73032" data-postid="187978" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;clinical trial&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1093/geroni/igaf122.3994"&gt;A previous trial&lt;/a&gt; of a 15-PGDH blocker to combat &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/protecting-your-muscle-mass-is-vital-for-healthy-aging-heres-why"&gt;muscle weakness&lt;/a&gt; didn't raise any red flags in terms of health and safety, which should speed up the process of trials for similar drugs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We are very excited about this potential breakthrough," &lt;a href="https://news.stanford.edu/stories/2025/11/joint-cartilage-aging-osteoarthritis-therapy-research"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; Blau. "Imagine regrowing existing cartilage and avoiding joint replacement."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The research has been published in &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1126/science.adx6649"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Science&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 11:03:35 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiowFBVV95cUxQZTVHMklTWmRhSmJJOVJSY29MZm10MUNCZm1VZGsyV2draEpwRE9oS0hKS3I5VlV4aExCX2ZfQ1VORDRCWWx4aktLclg4MGtqX2tLellMUVl1aHRhTWhXOHRmaVU1enBzQm15UVlJUHJCbmJJeTkwdm9RNS11OU5LcVpwTUhTemZMS3gtRGhWVXhwM255RVB5T1Btdk92ZjlvbTJr</guid></item><item><title>任何有孩子在托儿所的人都知道疾病是多么不方便。嗯，它即将变得更糟。-石板</title><link>https://slate.com/technology/2026/01/rfk-jr-day-care-illness-working-parents-vaccines.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article__content" itemprop="mainEntityOfPage"&gt;
          &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="21" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmk60wx7s000w3b7bvtghhwpu@published"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://slate.com/theslatest?utm_source=slate&amp;amp;utm_medium=article&amp;amp;utm_campaign=article_plain_text_topper&amp;amp;sailthru_source=Article-TopperText-CTA"&gt;Sign up for the Slatest&lt;/a&gt; to get the most insightful analysis, criticism, and advice out there, delivered to your inbox daily.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="125" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmk60wi1o006xbem2szmezvfz@published"&gt;This week, the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention announced &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/health/2026/01/05/childhood-vaccine-immunization-schedule-overhaul/"&gt;sweeping changes to the childhood vaccine schedule&lt;/a&gt;, removing broad recommendations for immunization against such diseases as flu, hepatitis A, rotavirus, and meningitis. Until recently, the U.S. vaccine schedule called for routine protection against 17 diseases; the changes lower that number to 11 diseases. There’s &lt;a href="https://theunbiasedscipod.substack.com/p/and-what-have-we-done?utm_source=publication-search"&gt;no new science&lt;/a&gt; that would support such a colossal change, and the American Academy of Pediatricians and public health experts alike continue to recommend the evidence-backed former schedule. The &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/health/2026/01/07/cdc-vaccine-recommendations-schedule-revisions/"&gt;unusually unilateral&lt;/a&gt; declaration comes a month after President Donald Trump &lt;a href="https://www.whitehouse.gov/fact-sheets/2025/12/fact-sheet-president-donald-j-trump-begins-process-to-align-u-s-core-childhood-vaccine-recommendations-with-best-practices-from-peer-developed-countries/"&gt;issued a memorandum&lt;/a&gt; directing the CDC and the Secretary of Health and Human Services—aka longtime anti-vaccine activist RFK Jr.—to “align U.S. core childhood vaccine recommendations with best practices from peer, developed countries.”&lt;/p&gt;

  

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="150" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmk61fvb1001v3b7bwijv9ff6@published"&gt;These “peer, developed countries” mentioned are Denmark, which recommends vaccinations for 10 diseases; Japan, which recommends 14; and Germany, which recommends 15. Fifteen! Fifteen is a lot more than America’s new number, 11, is it not? In the days since the new schedule announcement, vaccine experts have repeatedly pointed out that&lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.npr.org/2025/12/26/nx-s1-5656214/childhood-vaccination-denmark-rfk-policy"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Denmark&lt;/em&gt; is actually the outlier&lt;/a&gt; from the “peer” countries for having such a parsimonious schedule. And there’s a key difference between us and Denmark: Denmark has free universal health care. If their health care system was a road, it would be smooth, and they’re able to drive the Porsche that is fewer vaccinations, epidemiologist Katelyn Jetelina writes in her &lt;a href="https://yourlocalepidemiologist.substack.com/p/a-unilateral-change-to-childhood"&gt;Substack&lt;/a&gt;. It would be silly—and dangerous—to attempt to drive that same Porsche through the hazardous terrain that is the U.S. health care system. But that is essentially what we’re doing, she says, by adopting a vaccine schedule akin to Denmark’s.&lt;/p&gt;

  


  


  


  


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="203" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmk61fvb1001w3b7b9bbyqz78@published"&gt;Because while Denmark has reliable prenatal care, consistent follow-up, and a national health registry that essentially tracks everyone from birth to death, the U.S. … well, the U.S. has literally none of those things. What we do have are the &lt;a href="https://news.harvard.edu/gazette/story/2025/04/u-s-pregnancy-related-deaths-continuing-to-rise/"&gt;highest maternity mortality rate&lt;/a&gt; &lt;em&gt;and &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC4856058/"&gt;infant mortality rate&lt;/a&gt; among our “peer” countries. What’s more, we’re one of the only countries in the entire world that &lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2021/10/25/upshot/paid-leave-democrats.html"&gt;does not mandate any paid parental leave&lt;/a&gt;, alongside Papua New Guinea, the Marshall Islands, Tonga, and just a few others. Denmark, on the other hand, offers 24 weeks for the mother and 24 weeks for the father, plus a little more for the mother prior to the birth—nearly a &lt;a href="https://www.norden.org/en/info-norden/parental-benefit-denmark"&gt;year in total&lt;/a&gt;. That means that babies are able to stay home longer with their parents, avoiding exposure to diseases that they’re not yet vaccinated for, and that also present a higher mortality risk to infants than to even slightly older children. Americans don’t have the same opportunity. Most licensed child care centers &lt;a href="https://www.parents.com/daycare-for-infants-when-to-start-8622394#:~:text=Most%20licensed%20child%20care%20centers,the%20daycare%20center's%20policies%2C%20including:"&gt;accept babies as young as 6 weeks old&lt;/a&gt;, a choice that many parents are forced to make because they need to return to work (if they can &lt;a href="https://slate.com/human-interest/2015/10/when-child-care-costs-more-than-rent-women-stay-at-home.html"&gt;afford the child care&lt;/a&gt;, which is a &lt;a href="https://slate.com/human-interest/2017/01/theres-not-enough-child-care-in-the-u-s-for-all-the-families-that-need-it.html"&gt;whole other discussion&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;/p&gt;

  


  


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="134" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmk61fvb1001x3b7bka9fdjyn@published"&gt;Day cares are germy places. “Anytime you have a gathering of kids in close quarters, you risk sharing germs,” says Elizabeth Murray, a pediatrician in Rochester, New York. And young children, who are still developing immunity to common germs and also like to stick their fingers in their mouth and eyes, share a &lt;em&gt;lot &lt;/em&gt;of germs. Research shows that in their first three years of life, kids in day cares &lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2024-07-07/kids-who-go-to-childcare-get-sick-more-often-than-others/104053704"&gt;get sick more often&lt;/a&gt; with stomach bugs, ear infections, and upper respiratory infections than kids who are cared for at home (again, an option which, in the States, with our lean parental leave, can be very expensive for parents). The more kids there are in the child care setup, the &lt;a href="https://link.springer.com/article/10.1007/s10995-012-1125-5"&gt;higher the rate&lt;/a&gt; of illnesses. Take some vaccines away from that equation—more illnesses still.&lt;/p&gt;

  


  
  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="151" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmk61fvb2001y3b7bplgieci6@published"&gt;While states &lt;em&gt;can&lt;/em&gt; still require that kids receive certain vaccines for day care even if they’ve been dropped from the recommended CDC vaccine schedule, it stands to reason that the new recommendations may influence some states to reduce their requirements too. So far, several states including &lt;a href="https://www.news10.com/capitol/cdc-vaccine-schedule-changes/"&gt;New York&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://thebaynet.com/maryland-rejects-cdcs-new-childhood-vaccine-recommendations-will-use-aap-guidelines-instead/"&gt;Maryland&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href="https://lincolnchronicle.org/oregon-other-states-reject-trump-administrations-latest-vaccine-recommendations-for-kids/"&gt;Oregon&lt;/a&gt; have released statements that they’re rejecting the new CDC recommendations for school and day care entry requirements. It’s not yet clear what red states will do, though “we’re likely to see states going in very different directions with their own vaccine recommendations, largely along partisan lines,” says Jason Schwartz, an associate professor of public health at Yale University. A long piece in the Tallahassee Democrat titled “&lt;a href="https://www.tallahassee.com/story/news/2026/01/06/florida-vaccination-rules-children-cdc-guidelines-reduces-recommended-immunizations/88045990007/"&gt;What Florida parents should know about new CDC vaccination guidelines&lt;/a&gt;” ultimately offers little to go by: “We have reached out to the Florida Department of Health to see what its plans are,” the reporter notes.&lt;/p&gt;

  


  


  



  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="40" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmk61fvb2001z3b7bnmha974z@published"&gt;Regardless, the wild swings in guidance will inevitably cause confusion, notes Schwartz. And “the more we encounter confusion around vaccines,” he says, “the more likely it is that more kids will not receive vaccines that they otherwise could or should.”&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="171" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmk61fvb200203b7bcun3kjm9@published"&gt;What’s certain is that more kids—and families—will suffer in various ways. Even outcomes that fall short of the very &lt;em&gt;worst&lt;/em&gt; outcome can still be horrible. Murray points out rotavirus, which lost its general recommendation status with the new schedule. While it’s not a major cause of death, the virus &lt;a href="https://www.medpagetoday.com/pediatrics/vaccines/119330"&gt;comes with high costs&lt;/a&gt;: extremely brutal symptoms of diarrhea and vomiting for children, days of hospitalization, and the high medical bills that come with that. Not to mention the missed days of work—you can’t send your kid to child care when they are sick. “Boy, I definitely remember when we would admit a whole lot of children to the hospital with rotavirus,” says Murray. The vaccine, which was developed in 2006, “wiped it out. I haven’t seen rotavirus in well over a decade.” If rotavirus vaccination rates go down, that’s likely to change. Then there could soon be yet another bug to worry about when parents have to send their infants to day care so that they can head back to &lt;span class="slate-paragraph--tombstone"&gt;work.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;section class="newsletter-signup   " data-list="The Slatest" data-uri="slate.com/_components/newsletter-signup/instances/cmk60wi1o0070bem2jelg1zib@published"&gt;


    &lt;div class="newsletter-signup__intro newsletter-signup__intro--centered"&gt;
          &lt;img alt="" class="newsletter-signup__img" hidden data-src-light="https://dot.cdnslate.com/static/media/components/newsletter-signup/the-slatest.49f353b.png" data-src-dark="https://dot.cdnslate.com/static/media/components/newsletter-signup/the-slatest-dark.ca73d21.png"&gt;
&lt;h1 class="newsletter-signup__headline"&gt;Get the best of news and politics&lt;/h1&gt;
      &lt;span class="newsletter-signup__description"&gt;Sign up for Slate's evening newsletter.&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    



&lt;/section&gt;

  

&lt;/div&gt;

      &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Slate</author><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 10:45:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilAFBVV95cUxPbjhoZVBPUEt6TnBqS1NfeHNVRkZDeE5lcEJuNWdQaGxMLUNTOVhnRjVxZ2pBdkdfYWN5R3QzcXgtUVV1czlLcktTTVgwVmYtc2NMRFU0UVBSNW80UDdEQ09RMm52QjZjb2dlVG41MFNIZTNSOExLdTJLVC1sbF9FeWp3NVlRbGktTE9QR2MxR1VlZ3lT</guid></item><item><title>阿尔茨海默氏症疗法应该针对特定的基因，研究人员说-卫报</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/society/2026/jan/09/alzheimers-therapies-target-apoe-gene-variants-researchers-say</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body-commercial-selector article-body-viewer-selector dcr-hdpgoq"&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;New therapies for Alzheimer’s disease should target a particular gene linked to the condition, according to researchers who said most cases would never arise if its harmful effects were neutralised.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The call to action follows the arrival of the first wave of drugs that aim to treat Alzheimer’s patients by removing toxic proteins from the brain. While the drugs slow the disease down, the benefits are minor, and they &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/society/article/2024/aug/22/uk-health-regulator-rejects-lecanemab-as-treatment-for-alzheimers" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;have been rejected&lt;/a&gt; for widespread use by the UK’s National Institute for Health and Care Excellence (Nice).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="sign-in-gate"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;In searching for alternative therapies, scientists at UCL say drug developers should focus on two risk-raising variants of a gene named Apoe. Therapies designed to block the variants’ impact have “vast potential” for preventing the disease, they claim.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Dr Dylan Williams, a genetic epidemiologist at UCL, said: “Most Alzheimer’s disease cases would not arise without the contribution of just this single gene: Apoe. We need to think about it as a direct target. Almost all potential Alzheimer’s cases could benefit from Apoe-related interventions.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;More than half a million people in the UK, and more than 40 million worldwide, are living with Alzheimer’s disease, the most common form of dementia. Several genes contribute to Alzheimer’s risk and lifestyle is important too: smoking, obesity, diabetes, high blood pressure and cholesterol all make the disease more likely.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Williams and his colleagues analysed medical records from more than 450,000 people of European ancestry to calculate how much Alzheimer’s disease arose due to different variants of the Apoe gene. People inherit two copies of the gene – one from each parent – and there are three main variants: Apoe2, 3 and 4.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Scientists have long known that people with two copies of Apoe4 are high risk for Alzheimer’s, though 40% to 70% never develop the disease. The Apoe3 variant is widely considered neutral and the rare Apoe2 variant is regarded as protective.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;But Williams said we should see it another way. Compared with carrying two copies of Apoe2, both Apoe3 and Apoe4 raise the risk of Alzheimer’s, he said. Writing in the journal &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1038/s44400-025-00045-9" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;npj Dementia&lt;/a&gt;, the team calculate that without these variants, 72% to 93% of Alzheimer’s cases, and about 45% of all dementia, would not have occurred. “If interventions could eliminate the detrimental effects [of Apoe3 and 4], we could expect to prevent most Alzheimer’s disease and a large proportion of all dementia,” they write.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;That is a big if. The Apoe gene is crucial for moving cholesterol and other fats around the body and brain, so knocking it out entirely is likely to cause problems. Future therapies might edit the gene variants, or dampen down their activity, but those are neither imminent nor risk-free.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Another problem is that the vast majority of people – more than 99% in the study – carry Apoe3 or Apoe4. So preventing Alzheimer’s would mean treating nearly the entire population, possibly through invasive gene editing of the brain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The study received a mixed reception. Tim Frayling, professor of human genetics at the University of Geneva, said claiming more than 90% of Alzheimer’s would not occur without the Apoe gene’s effects was like saying more than 90% of road traffic deaths would not occur without the contribution of cars. “People should not worry if they have the risk versions of the gene, because 99.4% of us do,” he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure data-spacefinder-role="inline" data-spacefinder-type="model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.NewsletterSignupBlockElement" class="dcr-173mewl"&gt;&lt;gu-island name="EmailSignUpWrapper" priority="feature" deferuntil="visible" props="{&amp;quot;index&amp;quot;:11,&amp;quot;listId&amp;quot;:4156,&amp;quot;identityName&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;morning-briefing&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;description&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;Our morning email breaks down the key stories of the day, telling you what’s happening and why it matters&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;name&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;First Edition&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;frequency&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;Every weekday&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;successDescription&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;We'll send you First Edition every weekday&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;theme&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;news&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;idApiUrl&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;https://idapi.theguardian.com&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;hideNewsletterSignupComponentForSubscribers&amp;quot;:true}"&gt;&lt;/gu-island&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;But Tara Spires-Jones, professor of neurodegeneration at the University of Edinburgh, said understanding the risk factors that made the brain vulnerable to Alzheimer’s was “essential for developing effective treatments and prevention strategies”, adding that Apoe was one of the most important genetic risk factors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Dr Sheona Scales, of Alzheimer’s Research UK, said: “Evidence around Apoe3 contributing to Alzheimer’s and dementia risk is significant, as this has been largely thought of as having a neutral effect on risk. However, it’s important to note that not everyone with these Apoe gene variations will go on to develop dementia, as other risk factors also have an influence.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“This research raises lots of interesting questions, such as how Apoe3 and Apoe4 could drive Alzheimer’s risk, their effects in people of non-European ancestry, and whether targeting these variants could be a promising avenue for treatment and prevention of Alzheimer’s.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“Because of the complexity of Alzheimer’s risk, Apoe testing is not available on the NHS for people worried about their risk of developing Alzheimer’s in the future. If you are worried about your dementia risk, you should speak to your GP.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Guardian</author><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 10:05:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMirwFBVV95cUxNMnFnTXlQUlBPVERraFJNS29sM3I2NXY0cUVtZFFoUXprbGZiSU53R0QyRE1JWE5sS1pwMjFUUFVKRDNfQzdLQ0RjRDdUMGFlX09USFNfZHI3b1hycXpaZGtNc0d0Zjd3MkNuOXA0WFJVejhiTUdjSnViNXZHeDdQOUpvekt5SlJIVGpVS0N4VGFaRzdQbUhfaW8yckw5YzZ6Q1U0Y0VVLTZ2a2ZQcnFz</guid></item><item><title>建议卫生专业人员佩戴口罩级口罩-《卫报》</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/global-development/2026/jan/09/health-professionals-respirator-grade-masks-who-advise</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body-commercial-selector article-body-viewer-selector dcr-hdpgoq"&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Surgical face masks provide inadequate protection against flu-like illnesses including Covid, and should be replaced by respirator-level masks – worn every time doctors and nurses are face to face with a patient, according to a group of experts urging changes to &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/world-health-organization" data-link-name="in body link" data-component="auto-linked-tag"&gt;World Health Organization&lt;/a&gt; guidelines.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;There is “no rational justification remaining for prioritising or using” the surgical masks that are ubiquitous in hospitals and clinics globally, given their “inadequate protection against airborne pathogens”, they said in &lt;a href="https://whn.global/a-call-for-the-universal-use-of-respirators-in-healthcare/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;a letter to WHO chief Dr Tedros Adhanom Ghebreyesus&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="sign-in-gate"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“There is even less justification for allowing healthcare workers to wear no face covering at all,” they said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;At the height of the Covid pandemic an &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/environment/2025/sep/08/disposable-face-masks-covid-chemical-timebomb" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;estimated 129bn&lt;/a&gt; disposable face masks were being used around the world every month, by the public and healthcare workers, with surgical masks the most widely available and recommended by most health authorities.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Respirators designed to filter tiny particles – such as masks &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2021/dec/30/masks-best-covid-protection-ffp2-ffp3" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;meeting FFP2/3 standards&lt;/a&gt; in the UK or N95 in the US – should instead be standard practice for medical interactions, they said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;As additional evidence emerged over the course of the pandemic, officials in many countries &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2021/jan/21/wear-medical-grade-masks-if-you-cant-self-isolate-britons-told" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;switched to recommending those masks as more effective&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The proposals would result in fewer infections in patients and health professionals, and reduce rates of sickness, absence and burnout in the health workforce, the authors contended.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;gu-island name="InteractiveBlockComponent" priority="critical" deferuntil="idle" props='{"url":"https://interactive.guim.co.uk/uploader/embed/2021/01/facemaks-zip/giv-3902CGt23miACpMx/","scriptUrl":"https://interactive.guim.co.uk/embed/iframe-wrapper/0.1/boot.js","alt":"Diagram showing the difference between a surgical face mask and FFP respirator mask","format":{"design":0,"display":0,"theme":0},"elementId":"11ac5918-9f2f-403f-b158-8eb58d75336a","isMainMedia":false}'&gt;&lt;figure id="11ac5918-9f2f-403f-b158-8eb58d75336a" class="element element-interactive element--inline element-inline dcr-w422y2" data-alt="Diagram showing the difference between a surgical face mask and FFP respirator mask" data-testid="interactive-element-Diagram%20showing%20the%20difference%20between%20a%20surgical%20face%20mask%20and%20FFP%20respirator%20mask" data-spacefinder-role="inline"&gt;&lt;a data-name="placeholder" href="https://interactive.guim.co.uk/uploader/embed/2021/01/facemaks-zip/giv-3902CGt23miACpMx/" class="dcr-1eupayo"&gt;Diagram showing the difference between a surgical face mask and FFP respirator mask&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/gu-island&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Prof Adam Finkel of the University of Michigan School of Public &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/society/health" data-link-name="in body link" data-component="auto-linked-tag"&gt;Health&lt;/a&gt;, one of the letter’s organisers, said surgical masks were not designed to stop airborne pathogens but “invented to stop doctors and nurses from sneezing into the guts and the hearts of patients”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Surgical masks are to respirators what the typewriter was to the modern computer, said Finkel, who was chief regulatory official at the US Occupational Safety and Health Administration between 1995 and 2000: “Obsolete.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The letter came out of discussions at an &lt;a href="https://unpolitics.global/next-steps" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;online conference&lt;/a&gt; organised last year called Unpolitics, looking at the implementation of evidence-based policies. It was authored by seven clinicians and scientists, including Finkel, and has been endorsed by almost 50 senior clinicians and researchers, and more than 2,000 members of the public, including clinically vulnerable patients.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;There could be “off-ramps”, where governments or establishments decide respirators are not necessary, based on factors such as community infection rates, and ventilation or air filtration devices in a room, the letter says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;While the suggested guidance would apply only in healthcare settings, where the risk of infection is higher, it is likely to provoke controversy. Face masks &lt;a href="https://www.economist.com/britain/2020/08/08/with-face-masks-britain-imported-an-american-culture-war" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;became a culture war issue&lt;/a&gt; during the Covid pandemic.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;In December, Tory leader &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/society/2025/dec/09/nhs-leader-calls-for-revival-of-mask-wearing-amid-tidal-wave-of-flu" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;Kemi Badenoch said&lt;/a&gt; she had been “slightly traumatised by all the mask wearing that we had to do during Covid” in response to comments by an NHS leader saying people with flu symptoms “must wear” a face mask in public.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The WHO cannot mandate global policies, but the signatories argue that an update to its infection prevention and control guidelines to recommend respirators could have a profound impact.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;They also suggest that the WHO’s procurement infrastructure could help increase access to respirators even in poorer countries, with production of surgical masks phased down over time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Surgical masks are still “better than nothing”, Finkel conceded, with studies suggesting they block approximately 40% of Covid-sized particles in the air, compared with 95% for respirators.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;He says the comparative reduction in risk can be thought of like falling off a wall of four inches rather than four feet: “You can still trip and break an ankle at four inches, but you’re much better off.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Critics of the group’s arguments point to &lt;a href="https://www.cochrane.org/evidence/CD006207_do-physical-measures-such-hand-washing-or-wearing-masks-stop-or-slow-down-spread-respiratory-viruses" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;a lack of randomised controlled trials&lt;/a&gt; showing that physical measures slow the spread of respiratory viruses. Finkel and the other authors say such trials are simply not possible, for example because people in a trial will not wear masks 24/7 and could be exposed to pathogens while unmasked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Instead they say physical tests showing that respirators stop particles, conducted in laboratories, offer sufficient evidence.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="eaf47ec1-39ae-46e9-a57b-b83d49c107fe" data-spacefinder-role="inline" data-spacefinder-type="model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.ImageBlockElement" class="dcr-173mewl"&gt;&lt;figcaption data-spacefinder-role="inline" class="dcr-fd61eq"&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-1inf02i"&gt;&lt;svg viewbox="0 0 18 13"&gt;&lt;path d="M18 3.5v8l-1.5 1.5h-15l-1.5-1.5v-8l1.5-1.5h3.5l2-2h4l2 2h3.5l1.5 1.5zm-9 7.5c1.9 0 3.5-1.6 3.5-3.5s-1.6-3.5-3.5-3.5-3.5 1.6-3.5 3.5 1.6 3.5 3.5 3.5z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-1qvd3m6"&gt;FFP2 face masks being tested at Moldex-Metric, a German protective workwear manufacturer.&lt;/span&gt; Photograph: Thomas Kienzle/AFP/Getty Images&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figure id="6e178cb4-df19-43ff-ac13-09a13bc02403" data-spacefinder-role="richLink" data-spacefinder-type="model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.RichLinkBlockElement" class="dcr-47fhrn"&gt;&lt;gu-island name="RichLinkComponent" priority="feature" deferuntil="idle" props='{"richLinkIndex":21,"element":{"_type":"model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.RichLinkBlockElement","prefix":"Related: ","text":"World agrees pandemic accord for tackling outbreaks of disease","elementId":"6e178cb4-df19-43ff-ac13-09a13bc02403","role":"richLink","url":"https://www.theguardian.com/global-development/2025/may/20/world-agrees-pandemic-accord-for-tackling-outbreaks-of-disease-who-covid"},"ajaxUrl":"https://api.nextgen.guardianapps.co.uk","format":{"design":0,"display":0,"theme":0},"isInStarRatingVariant":false}'&gt;&lt;/gu-island&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The WHO has been criticised for being slow to describe Covid-19 as &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/australia-news/2025/nov/03/australia-prime-ministers-prize-for-science-lidia-morawska-covid-michael-wear-aboriginal-and-torres-strait-islander-knowledge" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;spreading via “airborne” particles&lt;/a&gt; and the letter also calls for it to revisit earlier statements and “unambiguously inform the public that it spreads via airborne respiratory particles”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Prof Trisha Greenhalgh of the University of Oxford, &lt;a href="https://journals.asm.org/doi/10.1128/cmr.00124-23" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;whose research&lt;/a&gt; is cited extensively in the letter and is one of its signatories, said: “A germ that does not get inside someone cannot make them sick. By sealing against the face, respirators force airflow to pass through them, filtering out the airborne germs. Respirators are designed to fit closely around the face and meet high filtration standards. Medical masks, in contrast, fit loosely and leak extensively.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The letter’s supporters include members of the &lt;a href="https://whn.global/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;World Health Network&lt;/a&gt;, prominent US epidemiologist Eric Feigl-Ding, and Guardian columnist George Monbiot.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;A WHO spokesperson said the letter required “careful review”. They said the organisation consulted widely with experts from different health and economic contexts when producing guidance on personal protective equipment for health workers, adding: “We are currently reviewing WHO’s Infection Prevention and Control guidelines for epidemic and pandemic-prone acute respiratory infections, based on the latest scientific evidence to ensure protection of health workers.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Guardian</author><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 09:50:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiswFBVV95cUxQM1JlU3o5Zm5nWlBPNGNicmtqbnByaEIzTWd4aGNwUHc0WUJvT0ZQcTRZdnNWc0ZhRWtZSkxwaEppQzBhQkUxWUw5Q2tQajJBVDVsTUZ3SXVGWFoyYUVzbTh2eXNvc3ZxR00wZ0JvQTlKRFU1Yld0ajBJRGpHaDRtd0h4UzB1aF9NcndlTGlPUHF1bjZhYzQ1eUNlc29tbzdWd2Y0RmZTdUNlYXdGZUdjWmRWUQ</guid></item><item><title>研究人员揭示了导致癌症发病率飙升的令人担忧的原因： “没有更多的禁忌” -雅虎</title><link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/articles/researcher-uncovers-alarming-reason-contributing-063000948.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="" data-article-body="true"&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Cigarettes, combined with air pollution and agricultural chemicals, have led to a concerning spike in cancer in Lebanon, according to one researcher.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="mb-4 text-lg font-bold"&gt;What's happening?&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Ali Mokdad led a global &lt;a href="https://www.thelancet.com/journals/lancet/article/PIIS0140-6736(25)01635-6/abstract" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:survey;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;survey&lt;/a&gt; on cancer rates, finding that his native country of Lebanon is experiencing the fastest increase in incidence and deaths. &lt;a href="https://www.npr.org/sections/goats-and-soda/2025/10/22/g-s1-94470/cancer-rates-deaths-lebanon" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:NPR summarized;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;NPR summarized&lt;/a&gt; his research, which found that the frequency of new cancer cases in the country spiked 162% from 1990 to 2023, and cancer-related deaths increased by 80% over that period.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Though pollution and agricultural chemicals are contributing to the issue, Mokdad told the news outlet that a lot of the cancer can be attributed to a strong smoking culture in the nation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;"There is no more taboo about smoking," Mokdad said. "Everybody smokes. Kids smoke in front of their parents. Yesterday, I went with some of my friends for dinner. You come home, you stink of tobacco."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="mb-4 text-lg font-bold"&gt;Why is this study important?&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;NPR noted that cancer rates are also increasing worldwide. While smoking may be the main culprit in Lebanon, we are now confronting a number of pollutants and chemicals that are increasing our risks for different types of cancers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;For instance, air pollution, which Mokdad noted is prevalent in Beirut, has been linked to a number of health problems, including respiratory issues and cancer. In fact, one new study found that women who live in more polluted areas suffer increased risks for breast cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Airborne microplastics — which can be inhaled — also put people at risk for lung cancer, per another recent paper.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="mb-4 text-lg font-bold"&gt;What's being done about cancer-causing pollutants?&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;It's tough to prevent exposure to all cancer-causing pollutants, but one positive step is to quit smoking if you currently do. The Centers for Disease Control and Prevention has &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/tobacco/campaign/tips/quit-smoking/index.html" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:resources and tips;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;resources and tips&lt;/a&gt; to help smokers kick the habit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Another thing anyone can do to reduce air pollution in our cities is to opt for carbon-free modes of transportation, such as &lt;a href="https://guide.thecooldown.com/journeys/save-money-on-transportation/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:biking;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;biking&lt;/a&gt;, e-biking, or walking. Using public transportation can also help decrease pollution.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Reducing the amount of new microplastics entering the environment will help limit our exposure. The best way to do this is to &lt;a href="https://guide.thecooldown.com/journeys/use-less-plastic/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:stop using;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;stop using&lt;/a&gt; so many single-use plastics. Some easy swaps include reusable water bottles and shopping totes, and bringing your own sturdy container to restaurants for leftovers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Get TCD's &lt;a href="https://www.thecooldown.com/newsletter/?utm_source=recV8k9A4K32ORkwb" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:free newsletters;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;free newsletters&lt;/a&gt; for easy tips to save more, waste less, and make smarter choices — and earn up to $5,000 toward clean upgrades in TCD's exclusive &lt;a href="https://links.thecooldown.com/rewards-club" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Rewards Club;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Rewards Club&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Yahoo</author><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 06:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMioAFBVV95cUxNUUd6eHRkQlI4UW9kVXlMd0dDcExoS0JZY015cGZGX1hJTWsya3NmblNjNmhBWHNNYkZjXzg5S080S3VmSEVrQVh5U0p6YkNXTTBVaUN3N0VPZ1NOOGwtUFUyejVtcUlNQkhmeGRxM2Q4cWJSR1pPQ3ZQVzF4NnJIV1E4UVlMZkhoTGZSU2IxSWl6LTFNdHAyRkNlM2JBRVlZ</guid></item><item><title>斯诺霍米什县King的潜在麻疹暴露情况提示-《西雅图时报》</title><link>https://www.seattletimes.com/seattle-news/health/visit-from-south-carolina-family-with-measles-leads-to-alert-in-wa/</link><description>&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMitwFBVV95cUxNcXFxQ2k1RUNSbmhRYVZtbDZpRGx1Y1lSejg4MkUtUno1emhNUzBaWGdnMnZQQjdqV0dpVDdtVXdlMl8xTW9JYVBxR2dFXzRuTXhXNlRlOWF5OWpVUkpCVnNNVnA0YlZyTVhhUGJfT1Z2Mkd0ZXdDM1lTUEhiRnlsNWw0TDBOX1hyQlBUaE9kZElKaU5BbWFuT0JIbDdhZDM1UWphc2VHQlJzdFJ6d1ZJcFc2X3VwVTQ?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;Potential measles exposures in King, Snohomish counties prompt alert&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Seattle Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiuwFBVV95cUxNbTlSNC1jalJ2NFlQc2thdDVfRWN1dVRobWN6dFdQLUV3dHBWWGlrdThEX2E3cHloZE94RkFJamxmamphNE53bnVQMVBsRlNpWDhzbXlZeXBVMEs1Z3g2OFpld2k1VllkU1Q0TDMtYkV6X3Z2VThfM3I4WkhhZ09tdFN3OE9RY0VBdXltSU9jOUFpbzZ6b2hTU0loYXRlQ290TkRwbWEtUUJGcWlGZy1BS1V3UW9FdmhtNFU00gHPAUFVX3lxTE1nNXA2MUJqRHpvS3J6ZG9wQkFmTjRON01WeV9GS1BXb2dQVmdNRF9mdGRpaDlidEN2YkNTNXpUcE9SdWRaV1BBT1M3bi1ZSDU3U0Z0ZGxHcC0tVjRxblR1R1QyZE1qaXYxbHFRYWJ1Z2s2cEVtR3dpd1NveXJEa0hMaTBDNm9Wci1kMTltaG1Xdk0yYWJYVnhQSnlhMllXN1dWYmNMdjE2UWVqR2UtdU1VcTBWZVEzRzlXWVZTZS01UHdVZ0pfdnl1MlRRQ3M2OA?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;Several possible measles exposures in King, Snohomish Counties&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;KIRO 7 News Seattle&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiowFBVV95cUxQWnBjaW9MZi1GZEtSV1RPMmZ6QWxMUnA3Nnlab21mQU04MWlwblExS2Z4NGxIeUFjSVJGaDRmQVFQU0FUWnh1bm51VmQ3dHl6eTZlRGFUaUJvRVlFZjQzdXFXaXk3ekFEWlI5OVNEQm1hRkVHNGx6MFh4NGVWZzJlalVNb0RZbnlVSm45d2dGV3NyNE9WenFoQlVSREQ4M3JPVmlr?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;Health officials: Three confirmed measles cases in SnoCo over holidays&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Everett Herald&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMic0FVX3lxTFBUVkJVeGZJdzcwN19EZXJ4bDdhMElheGVkcXlldkktZGUzLVlWNUIwOG9SeG01Zmo4MGdqWk9sSHJKbXdXd1RoaTRnN3luN2doWnd6ZGdySExONl9hUmFXWGNBQ2lXQ3BRZ1ozUUhGTldWNEXSAXhBVV95cUxOQ0pyY095ZGtKeS1BdlpIeGJnb1pMS3pIMkpKYUN1TmpmaEFKWWpMTnlTRnl3SGhhNmVnb0EycTllMDVMSVVkdnhsd250WE5GV0tkWmhFWHIwc29oMlQ0VF96d0xuXzRzanl3eXg4cFBWVTFVUXVCanI?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;3 measles cases confirmed in family visiting western WA for holidays&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;FOX 13 Seattle&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;</description><author>The Seattle Times</author><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 05:32:36 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMitwFBVV95cUxNcXFxQ2k1RUNSbmhRYVZtbDZpRGx1Y1lSejg4MkUtUno1emhNUzBaWGdnMnZQQjdqV0dpVDdtVXdlMl8xTW9JYVBxR2dFXzRuTXhXNlRlOWF5OWpVUkpCVnNNVnA0YlZyTVhhUGJfT1Z2Mkd0ZXdDM1lTUEhiRnlsNWw0TDBOX1hyQlBUaE9kZElKaU5BbWFuT0JIbDdhZDM1UWphc2VHQlJzdFJ6d1ZJcFc2X3VwVTQ</guid></item><item><title>大脑健康挑战：心灵和身体的医生预约-《纽约时报》</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2026/well/brain-health-doctor-appointments.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;section class="g-main svelte-19neaxa"&gt;&lt;p class="g-text  svelte-19nwvmi"&gt;Congratulations, you’ve reached the final day of the Brain Health Challenge! Today, we’re asking you to do a few things that might feel a bit out of left field — like getting your blood pressure checked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="g-wrapper  svelte-19s2qxj"&gt;   &lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="g-text  svelte-19nwvmi"&gt;No, it isn’t as fun as &lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2026/01/07/well/brain-health-games-teasers.html"&gt;playing Pips&lt;/a&gt;, but experts say it’s one of the most important things you can do for your brain. That’s because heart health and brain health are intrinsically linked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="g-text  svelte-19nwvmi"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2024/02/29/well/live/high-blood-pressure-lower.html"&gt;High blood pressure&lt;/a&gt;, in particular, can damage brain cells, and it’s a significant risk factor for stroke and dementia. When blood pressure is too high, it places stress on the walls of arteries in the brain. Over time, that added stress can cause the blood vessel walls to thicken, obstructing blood flow. In other cases, the increased pressure causes the artery walls to thin and leak blood into the brain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="g-text  svelte-19nwvmi"&gt;These changes to the blood vessels can sometimes cause a large stroke to occur. More commonly, the damage leads to micro-strokes and micro-hemorrhages, which cause fewer immediate problems and often go unnoticed. But if someone has hypertension for years or decades, these injuries can build up, and the person may start to experience cognitive impairment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="g-text  svelte-19nwvmi"&gt;High blood pressure “is known as a silent killer for lots of reasons,” said Dr. Shyam Prabhakaran, the chair of neurology at the University of Chicago. “It doesn’t cause you any symptoms until it does.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="g-text  svelte-19nwvmi"&gt;Because the damage accumulates over many years, experts say that managing blood pressure in midlife matters most for brain health. Hypertension can be addressed with medication or lifestyle changes, as directed by your doctor. But the first thing you need to do is know your numbers. If your blood pressure comes back higher than 120/80, it’s important to take it seriously, Dr. Prabhakaran said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="g-text  svelte-19nwvmi"&gt;While you’re at it, there are a few other aspects of your physical health that you should check on.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="g-text  svelte-19nwvmi"&gt;Your eyes and ears are two of them. &lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2024/08/08/well/mind/hearing-vision-dementia-risk.html"&gt;Hearing and vision loss&lt;/a&gt; have both been shown to increase the risk of dementia. Experts think that with less sensory information coming in to stimulate the brain, the regions that process hearing and vision can start to atrophy. What’s more, people with sensory loss often withdraw or are left out of social interactions, further depriving them of cognitive stimulation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="g-text  svelte-19nwvmi"&gt;Oral health can also affect your brain health. Research has found a connection between regular flossing and reduced odds of &lt;a href="https://newsroom.heart.org/news/regular-dental-flossing-may-lower-risk-of-stroke-from-blood-clots-irregular-heartbeats?preview=df8b&amp;amp;preview_mode=True"&gt;having a stroke&lt;/a&gt;. That may be because good oral health can help to reduce inflammation in the body. The bacteria that cause gum disease have also been tied to an &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32280099/"&gt;increased risk of Alzheimer’s&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="g-text  svelte-19nwvmi"&gt;And have you gotten your shingles vaccine? There is &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC11485228/"&gt;mounting evidence&lt;/a&gt; that it’s a powerful weapon for protecting against dementia. &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41586-025-08800-x"&gt;One study&lt;/a&gt; found that it lowered people’s odds of developing the condition by as much as 20 percent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="g-text  svelte-19nwvmi"&gt;To wrap up this challenge, we want you to schedule a few medical appointments that benefit your brain, as well as your body.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="g-text  svelte-19nwvmi"&gt;After five days of &lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2026/well/brain-health-mind-diet-recipes.html"&gt;feeding&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2026/well/brain-health-exercise-workout.html"&gt;exercising&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2026/01/07/well/brain-health-games-teasers.html"&gt;challenging&lt;/a&gt; your brain, you are well on your way to better cognitive health. Thanks for joining me this week, and keep up the good habits!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/section&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The New York Times</author><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 01:01:23 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiwFBVV95cUxNOGN4VzJjWTZad0wwRWVJbWF2b1V5TkF2UHJhYXlpQXJaSzgydWlDajRGR3pZV3lBNlNhZjZxdzNFZ3ZvXzJUZXNuUU5oT1Z3RVo1cTlFNXpDSHdibTN0aGN2bDFBM0dhRVVpUk8wdF9aQTNiTlp1NVpEaE54Tjh3RTdFOV92cVJuWnNn</guid></item><item><title>停止GLP-1药物触发体重恢复比结束锻炼快4倍- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/stopping-glp-1-drugs-triggers-weight-regain-4x-faster-than-ending-exercise</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;When people stop taking the new generation of weight-loss drugs, they pile back on the kilos four times faster than they would after ending diet and exercise regimes, &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1136/bmj-2025-085304"&gt;new research&lt;/a&gt; found Thursday.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But this was mostly because they lost so much weight in the first place, according to the British researchers who conducted the largest and most up-to-date review of the subject.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A new generation of appetite-suppressing, injectable drugs called GLP-1 agonists has become immensely popular in the last few years, transforming the treatment for obesity and  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/diabetes" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73018" data-postid="188244" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;diabetes&lt;/a&gt; in many countries.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/weight-comes-back-when-you-stop-taking-drugs-like-ozempic-study-finds"&gt;Weight Comes Back When You Stop Taking Drugs Like Ozempic, Study Finds&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They have been found to help people lose between 15 and 20 percent of their body weight.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"This all appears to be a good news story," said Susan Jebb, a public health nutrition scientist at Oxford University and co-author of &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1136/bmj-2025-085304"&gt;a new &lt;em&gt;BMJ&lt;/em&gt; study&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, recent data have suggested that "around half of people discontinue these medications within a year," she told a press conference.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This might be because of common side effects such as nausea or the price – these drugs can cost over $1,000 a month in the US.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_188249" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-188249" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2026/01/semaglutide_pen_box_642.jpg" alt="semaglutide pen out of a box" class="wp-image-188249 size-full" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2026/01/semaglutide_pen_box_642.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2026/01/semaglutide_pen_box_642-600x374.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-188249" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;GLP-1 agonist drugs can cost more than $1000 a month in the US. (&lt;a href="https://www.canva.com/photos/MAE_SqrtCOc/"&gt;imyskin/Getty Images/Canva&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;So the researchers reviewed 37 studies looking at ceasing different weight-loss drugs, finding that participants regained around 0.4 kilograms a month.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Six of the  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/clinical-trials" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73032" data-postid="188244" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;clinical trials&lt;/a&gt; involved semaglutide – the ingredient used in Novo Nordisk's brands Ozempic and Wegovy – and tirzepatide, used for Eli Lilly's Mounjaro and Zepbound.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While taking these two drugs, the trial participants lost an average of nearly 15 kilograms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, after stopping the medication, they regained 10 kilograms within a year, which was the longest follow-up period available for these relatively new drugs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers projected that the participants would return to their original weight in 18 months.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Measurements of heart health, including blood pressure and cholesterol levels, also returned to their original levels after 1.4 years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;People who were instead put on &lt;span&gt;programs&lt;/span&gt; that included diet and exercise – but not drugs – lost significantly less weight. However, it took an average of four years for them to regain their lost kilos.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This meant that people taking the drugs regained their weight four times faster.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_188247" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-188247" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2026/01/man_resting_after_exercise_642.jpg" alt="man resting after exercise" class="wp-image-188247 size-full" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2026/01/man_resting_after_exercise_642.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2026/01/man_resting_after_exercise_642-600x374.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-188247" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;It takes an average of four years for weight to return after quitting exercise. (&lt;a href="https://www.canva.com/photos/MAEI06fFafA/"&gt;Hispanolistic/Getty Images Signature/Canva&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;h2&gt;'Starting point, not a cure'&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Greater weight loss tends to result in faster weight regain," lead study author Sam West of Oxford University explained.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But separate analysis showed that weight gain was "consistently faster after medication, regardless of the amount of weight lost in the first place," he added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This could be because people who have learned to eat more healthily and exercise more often continue to do so even as they regain weight.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/newsletter?utm_source=promo_generic_health"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-642x273.jpg" alt="Subscribe to ScienceAlert's free fact-checked newsletter" class="alignnone wp-image-182810 size-medium" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-642x273.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-768x326.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-600x255.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final.jpg 850w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jebb emphasized that GLP-1 drugs "are a really valuable tool in obesity treatment – but obesity is a chronic relapsing condition."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"One would expect that these treatments need to be continued for life, just in the same way as blood pressure medication," Jebb said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If this were the case, it would impact how national health systems judge whether these drugs are cost-effective, the researchers emphasized.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"This new data makes it clear they are a starting point, not a cure," &lt;a href="https://www.scimex.org/newsfeed/people-who-stop-taking-weight-loss-drugs-are-losing-their-progress-in-less-than-two-years"&gt;said&lt;/a&gt; Garron Dodd, a metabolic neuroscience researcher at the University of Melbourne, not involved in the study.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Sustainable treatment will likely require combination approaches, longer-term strategies, and therapies that reshape how the brain interprets energy balance, not just how much people eat," he &lt;a href="https://www.scimex.org/newsfeed/people-who-stop-taking-weight-loss-drugs-are-losing-their-progress-in-less-than-two-years"&gt;said&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;© &lt;a href="terms-and-conditions"&gt;Agence France-Presse&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 00:38:35 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipgFBVV95cUxPZnVGVDdBUF92SC0xNlhTd3pvZGJyUVNnR3NNZkRjM2EzekNQdjdhUFdHOHc3R3FrQ1d0MG9WU0VrdzJ6Z0UxRDBXUVdmOHE3X1M5d2hHbE1TUEp6dzhPMEtUaFBRNXVfZzkwQVRDWFFrY2VtS1RFVktNZWU0NkpiTmVhRjVuTzJKQU5qenhfazh2blZCLTRjMWI1R1JWZWpYY0R0bE1n</guid></item><item><title>这些是医生现在看到的最常见的H3N2超级流感症状- AOL.com</title><link>https://www.aol.com/articles/most-common-h3n2-super-flu-212500037.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="caas-body"&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you'v&lt;em&gt;e&lt;/em&gt; been paying attention to the news lately, you likely have heard about the new strain of severe "super &lt;a href="https://parade.com/847117/parade/mythbusters-flu-facts-and-fiction/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:flu;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;flu&lt;/a&gt;" going around right now.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;"H3N2 Influenza A has undergone genetic drift this year by generating a new variant called 'subclade K,'" public health expert and infectious disease specialist &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.tylerevansmd.com/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Dr. Tyler B. Evans, MD, MS, MPH, AAHIVS, DTM&amp;amp;H, FIDSA;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Dr. Tyler B. Evans, MD, MS, MPH, AAHIVS, DTM&amp;amp;H, FIDSA&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;, tells &lt;em&gt;Parade&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;As the name suggests, the super flu is pretty &lt;a href="https://parade.com/living/scary-games" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:scary;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;scary&lt;/a&gt; and has a lot of potential to make us miserable: Several healthy children U.S. have died from the H3N2 super flu strain and complications, according to the &lt;a href="https://publications.aap.org/aapnews/news/34114/CDC-9-children-have-died-of-flu-this-season?searchresult=1?autologincheck=redirected" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:American Academy of Pediatrics;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;American Academy of Pediatrics&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;"The 2025-26 flu season is one of the strongest seasons on record with some states in the U.S. reporting high and even record numbers of hospitalizations and emergency department visits due to flu," &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.huttonhealthconsulting.com/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Dr. Brad Hutton, MPH;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Dr. Brad Hutton, MPH&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;, infectious disease epidemiologist at Hutton Health Consulting, tells &lt;em&gt;Parade&lt;/em&gt;. "More than 90% of the flu viruses recently tested and reported by labs across the nation have been type A (H3N2), most of them belonging to a new subclade K. This new subclade K represents a genetic drift with several mutations from the versions that were circulating across the globe earlier this year when decisions were made about the strains that would be used for this year's vaccine."&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;"With more infected people, more people are likely to get seriously unwell and end up in hospitals," &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.serefin.com/who-we-are/about-serefin" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Dr. Vera Kohut, MD, Hon BSc;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Dr. Vera Kohut, MD, Hon BSc&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;, medical director at Serefin Health, explains. Combine that with a high flow of people in contact with one another over the holidays, kids in close  contact in schools and daycares with variable ventilation protection, variable hand washing skills, she says, and you have a recipe for a super flu spread bigger and faster than we've seen in years.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Here's everything to know about the new severe flu variant, including the most common H3N2 super &lt;a href="https://parade.com/health/flu-symptoms-day-by-day" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:flu symptoms;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;flu symptoms&lt;/a&gt; to watch out for, how to protect yourself and the best prevention and treatment options if you do get infected.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://emojipedia.org/stethoscope" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:🩺;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;🩺&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="https://parade.com/newsletters/healthy-now-2" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:SIGN UP for Parade’s health newsletter with expert-approved tips, healthy eats, exercises, news &amp;amp; more to help you stay healthy &amp;amp; feel your best self;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SIGN UP for Parade’s health newsletter with expert-approved tips, healthy eats, exercises, news &amp;amp; more to help you stay healthy &amp;amp; feel your best self&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="https://emojipedia.org/pill" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:💊;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;💊&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What Is a 'Super Flu'?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;What makes the "super flu" variant more severe than others isn't necessarily just the virus itself. It's also that, well, doctors and scientists aren't psychics, and this mutation of the influenza virus isn't what experts predicted we'd be dealing with this flu season.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;"This strain could cause a more severe flu season because of its divergence from forecasted viruses used in this season’s flu vaccine," Dr. Evans explains. "Flu viruses can change over time, which can make it harder for our bodies and vaccines to protect us."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure align-caption-with-image"&gt;&lt;div class="no-margin"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="caption-wrapper"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption-collapse"&gt;Photo by CDC&amp;amp;sol;SCIENCE PHOTO LIBRARY on Getty Images&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;"How bad our flu season gets depends on things like which flu viruses we’ve had infections with before, which vaccines we’ve gotten in the past, which flu viruses are spreading this year and how well the &lt;a href="https://parade.com/health/how-effective-flu-shot-this-year-2024-2025" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:flu shot;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;flu shot&lt;/a&gt; works against these viruses," he adds.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Board-certified internist &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.shoshanaungerleider.com/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Dr. Shoshana Ungerleider, MD;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Dr. Shoshana Ungerleider, MD&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;, notes, "The virus has changed enough that our &lt;a href="https://parade.com/health/immune-system-trick-we-wish-we-knew-about-sooner" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:immune systems;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;immune systems&lt;/a&gt; do not recognize it as well, leading to higher rates of hospitalization, especially among older adults and young children."&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://parade.com/1255833/stephanieosmanski/how-many-people-die-from-flu-each-year/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:How Many People Die of the Flu Each Year? Doctors Break Down What Statistics Look Like—and How To Protect Yourself;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;How Many People Die of the Flu Each Year? Doctors Break Down What Statistics Look Like—and How To Protect Yourself&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Why Is This Year's Flu So Bad?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;In terms of why it's spreading so fast and so widely, experts generally agree that a few factors are at play.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Flu viruses change over time as a part of their &lt;a href="https://parade.com/1034896/marynliles/nature-quotes/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:nature;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;nature&lt;/a&gt; via minor genetic mutations. When these changes accumulate over time, new subclades are create,d and these subclades attack differently than earlier strains," &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://publichealth.nmsu.edu/about-us/faculty-directory/faculty/jagdish-khubchandani.html" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Dr. Jagdish Khubchandani, Ph.D., MPH, MBBS;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Dr. Jagdish Khubchandani, Ph.D., MPH, MBBS&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;, professor of public health at New Mexico State University, tells &lt;em&gt;Parade&lt;/em&gt;. "Since widespread immunity for such new strains is not generated in one season, we see rampant infections and complications. That's the strength of flu viruses: We chase them, but never get ahead. Over time, they learn to evade our immune systems."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.goodrx.com/about/bio/karla-robinson?srsltid=AfmBOoqpCBBkuoEw7_zEQrYBEqDcKE8CSMYx6dMjy6ecUvAAL1EuR2fe" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Dr. Karla Robinson, MD;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dr. Karla Robinson, MD&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, licensed, board-certified &lt;a href="https://parade.com/1045384/marynliles/family-quotes/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:family;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;family&lt;/a&gt; physician and medical editor at GoodRx, explains that we're already seeing a lot of signs of widespread infection.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Research from GoodRx shows Tamiflu fill rates rising earlier and more sharply than in many recent seasons, a sign that more people are seeking treatment," she says. "That means more people are getting sick, and symptoms tend to be more intense."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some of why the super flu is spreading is just the nature of the virus, but we also need to stay responsible and vigilant as a society. "People need to be at their best in terms of hygiene and sanitation practices, which has been an issue since the COVID pandemic," Dr. Khubchandani says. "Over time, people have been lax in preventive behaviors including &lt;a href="https://parade.com/health/surprising-covid-vaccine-side-effect-according-to-study-2025" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:vaccination;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;vaccination&lt;/a&gt;. My biggest worry is the conglomerate of influenza, &lt;a href="https://parade.com/health/states-with-highest-covid-flu-rsv-cases-december-2023" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:coronaviruses and others, such as RSV infections;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;coronaviruses and others, such as RSV infections&lt;/a&gt;, surging at the same time."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://parade.com/health/what-happens-when-you-dont-get-vaccines-every-year-according-to-infectious-disease-experts" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Here's What Happens When You Don't Get Some Vaccines Every Year, According to Infectious Disease Experts;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Here's What Happens When You Don't Get Some Vaccines Every Year, According to Infectious Disease Experts&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.bryant.edu/academics/faculty/hokeness-kirsten" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Dr. Kirsten Hokeness, Ph.D.,;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Dr. Kirsten Hokeness, Ph.D.,&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; professor of biological and biomedical sciences at Bryant University, explains, "The early mutation this year means the vaccine is not a very good direct match, plus vaccination rates are down. This means that the flu season has started with a vengeance and people are getting pretty sick."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What's more, the H3N2 super flu also brings complications with it for some patients, and it's those complications that make it particularly dangerous, especially for high-risk people and those with compromised immune systems or other pre-existing conditions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It is an H3N2 strain, which typically causes more severe disease and is more commonly associated with secondary bacterial pneumonias," &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.creighton.edu/campus-directory/tierney-maureen" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Dr. Maureen Tierney, MD, MSc;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Dr. Maureen Tierney, MD, MSc&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;, Associate Dean, Department Chair of Clinical Research and Public Health at Creighton University, tells &lt;em&gt;Parade&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.rwjbh.org/doctors/christopher-f-freer-do-facep-facep/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Dr. Christopher Freer, DO, FACEP;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Dr. Christopher Freer, DO, FACEP&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;, Senior Vice President of Emergency and Hospitalist Medicine at RWJBarnabas Health, explains further why it hits so hard: "This flu strain, subclade K, appears more aggressive because it triggers a stronger inflammatory response in the body. This can lead to higher fevers, more intense fatigue, and a greater risk of complications like pneumonia."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://parade.com/health/habit-to-break-to-avoid-getting-sick-according-to-doctors" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:The One Habit Doctors Are Begging You To Break ASAP if You Don't Want To Get Sick This Fall;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;The One Habit Doctors Are Begging You To Break ASAP if You Don't Want To Get Sick This Fall&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What Are Super Flu Symptoms?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you get the flu, take it seriously! Influenza is a respiratory infection. Influenza “packs a punch." It's not "just a cold"—you really are sick. "The impact of the virus on the body is severe; it causes direct damage to the respiratory tract from the nose to the lungs, compromising the body’s natural defense barriers," Dr. Kohut emphasizes. "Even in healthy individuals, the impact of the virus on the body's immune system can create changes that leave the individual susceptible to other infections—particularly bacterial infections."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Normal &lt;a href="https://parade.com/health/flu-symptoms-2025-2026" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:flu symptoms;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;flu symptoms&lt;/a&gt;, according to the &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/flu/signs-symptoms/index.html" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Centers for Disease Control and Prevention;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Centers for Disease Control and Prevention&lt;/a&gt; (CDC), include:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In terms of super flu symptoms, you can expect more severe manifestations of the above, plus some other signs that will make you feel lousy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Beyond typical flu symptoms like fever, cough and body aches, warning signs include &lt;a href="https://parade.com/health/heart-condition-with-limited-warning-signs-according-to-cardiologists" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:trouble breathing;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;trouble breathing&lt;/a&gt;, chest pain, confusion, severe weakness, persistent &lt;a href="https://parade.com/health/norovirus-symptoms-january-2025" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:vomiting;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;vomiting&lt;/a&gt; or symptoms that worsen instead of improve," Dr. Ungerleider says. "In serious cases, the flu can lead to pneumonia, heart complications, neurologic symptoms, or organ failure."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One thing to note about super flu symptoms, Dr. Tierney says, is how they start: "Symptom onset with the flu is often abrupt." This means that you're less likely to have a cough or sore throat that gets progressively worse and instead will be hit hard with symptoms suddenly, even if you felt fine the night before.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Patients should be alert for persistent high fevers, trouble breathing, chest tightness or &lt;a href="https://parade.com/health/sneaky-reasons-you-feel-exhausted-all-the-time" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:extreme exhaustion;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;extreme exhaustion&lt;/a&gt;," Dr. Freer advises. "Severe body aches, &lt;a href="https://parade.com/health/hydration-hack-that-can-dehydrate-you-according-to-dietitian" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:dehydration;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;dehydration&lt;/a&gt; and confusion, particularly in older adults, are also concerning signs. If symptoms feel severe or suddenly worsen, it is important to seek medical care."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Flu can sometimes lead to serious complications like pneumonia, &lt;a href="https://parade.com/health/common-cold-remedy-mistake-to-avoid-according-to-doctors" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:sinus;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;sinus&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href="https://parade.com/health/most-people-forget-to-wash-this-body-part" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:ear infections;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;ear infections&lt;/a&gt;, and—in rare cases—&lt;a href="https://parade.com/tag/inflammation/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:inflammation;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;inflammation&lt;/a&gt; of the heart or brain, organ failure or &lt;a href="https://parade.com/celebrities/madonna-makes-personal-admission-on-her-near-death-experience" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:sepsis;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;sepsis&lt;/a&gt; (a dangerous body-wide reaction to infection)," Dr. Robinson warns. "This strain can cause significant illness across all ages, but older adults, young children, and immunocompromised people are at the highest risk for complications. Seek medical care if you have trouble breathing, chest or abdominal pain that doesn’t go away, severe headaches or &lt;a href="https://parade.com/health/what-happens-to-your-blood-pressure-when-you-drink-water" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:dizziness;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;dizziness&lt;/a&gt;, or if your fever or cough gets better but then returns or worsens."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.nfid.org/person/robert-h-hopkins-jr-md/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Dr. Robert Hopkins, Jr., MD;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Dr. Robert Hopkins, Jr., MD&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;, Medical Director of the National Foundation for Infectious Diseases, points out that children and seniors may show symptoms you don't necessarily expect or associate with the flu, so it's extra important to monitor them closely if infected.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The very young and the elderly may not have typical flu symptoms," he says. "They may present with irritability, sleepiness or confusion, and these highest risk patients need prompt evaluation by a healthcare professional."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://parade.com/345104/jenniferlarson/what-do-i-have-cold-or-flu/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:How To Tell the Difference Between a Cold and the Flu;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;How To Tell the Difference Between a Cold and the Flu&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Does the Flu Shot Protect Against H3N2 Super Flu?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to Dr. Evans, even though the H3N2 super flu may evade some of the protection that this season's &lt;a href="https://parade.com/1165746/kimberlyzapata/flu-shot-side-effects/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:flu shot;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;flu shot&lt;/a&gt; provides, it's still your best bet to protect yourself from a severe infection.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr. Freer agrees, noting, "The goal of the flu vaccine is to prevent serious illness requiring hospitalization and adverse outcomes. If you get the flu even though you got the vaccine, that is not a failure. The flu vaccine is our best defense against serious illness and death."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While the &lt;a href="https://parade.com/health/exact-best-time-to-get-flu-shot-according-to-infecitous-disease-experts" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:best time to get your flu shot;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;best time to get your flu shot&lt;/a&gt; for 2025-2026 was last fall, if you didn't get a flu shot yet, you can still get a vaccine now, and doctors are urging you to do just that.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It is never too late to get vaccinated for the flu, and we encourage everyone to get the 2025-2026 vaccine," &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.bluebirdkids.com/providers/michael-glazier-md" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Dr. Michael Glazier, MD;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Dr. Michael Glazier, MD&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;, CMO at Bluebird Kids Health, tells us. "The flu vaccine provides the opportunity to prevent infection and spread from certain strains of the flu and it can also decrease the severity of infection."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Not only does the flu shot offer at least some protection against severe super flu infection, but it comes with a potential bonus for your &lt;a href="https://parade.com/tag/dementia/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:cognitive health;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;cognitive health&lt;/a&gt; too: A study found that &lt;a href="https://parade.com/health/flu-shot-alzheimers" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:patients who got their flu shots regularly were 40% less likely;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;patients who got their flu shots regularly were 40% less likely&lt;/a&gt; to be diagnosed with &lt;a href="https://parade.com/tag/alzheimers/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Alzheimer's disease;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Alzheimer's disease&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://parade.com/health/when-to-see-doctor-vaccine-side-effects-according-to-infectious-disease-experts" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:These Are the Actual Vaccine Side Effects You Should Worry About, According to Infectious Disease Experts;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;These Are the Actual Vaccine Side Effects You Should Worry About, According to Infectious Disease Experts&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What Are Other Ways To Protect Yourself From Super Flu?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some common-sense measures can serve as kryptonite for the super flu. "Flu prevention is about staying vigilant and acting early to minimize the severity of your symptoms," &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.nychealthandhospitals.org/doctors-day-2022/sanjiv-shah/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Dr. Sanjiv Shah, MD, MPH;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Dr. Sanjiv Shah, MD, MPH&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;, says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Getting the flu shot is the most important step," Dr. Ungerleider emphasizes. "Other effective measures include washing hands regularly, covering coughs, staying home when sick, avoiding close contact with people who are ill and using preventive antiviral medication in high risk individuals after known exposure."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Experts also recommend taking it easy. (It &lt;em&gt;is&lt;/em&gt; hibernation season, after all.) "We recommend, when possible, to rest, ensure hydration and practice good hand hygiene," Dr. Glazier stresses. "Now is not the time to overdo it and stretch oneself over multiple activities and obligations. Also, if you do not feel well, please be sure to avoid exposing high-risk family and friends (particularly infants and the elderly). When in doubt, it's ok to sit it out and defer the large family gatherings if you are sick."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr. Freer recommends avoiding touching or rubbing your face and maintaining a healthy diet as ways to help fight off infection, while Dr. Tierney suggests more precautions as well, especially if you're at a high risk for super flu complications.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Consider wearing a mask when in crowded indoor places, especially in healthcare settings," she says, adding that you may want to talk to your doctor about preventative antivirals if you know you've been exposed to flu or super flu but haven't yet shown symptoms. (Learn more about those below!)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://parade.com/health/handwashing-trick-that-cuts-germs" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:The Clever Handwashing Trick That Slashes Germs and Bacteria;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;The Clever Handwashing Trick That Slashes Germs and Bacteria&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What Are H3N2 Super Flu Treatments?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;What should you do if you &lt;em&gt;do&lt;/em&gt; get infected with H3N2 super flu (or just the regular flu)? Don't panic, because you have options!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;First, see if you can snag a prescription for antivirals from your doctor if you're a good candidate for them. "Treatment and/or prophylaxis are especially important to reduce severity, hospitalization and death among high-risk individuals: the elderly or the very young, those who are immunocompromised and those with chronic medical conditions," Dr. Tierney says. "Oseltamivir, or Tamiflu, has been used for years to treat influenza. It is approved for those two weeks of age and older and can be taken twice a day for five days, or if used prophylactically, once a day for 10 days. Both courses of therapy are best to begin within 48 hours of the onset of symptoms or the known exposure."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There is another medication approved to treat or as prophylaxis against the flu called baloxavir, or Xofluza, which is given as a one-time dose for those over five years of age, Dr. Tierney notes. "It is more expensive and usually well tolerated, but there are fewer years of experience with its use."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://parade.com/health/what-doctors-buy-ahead-of-cold-and-flu-season" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:4 Doctors Share the #1 Thing They Always Buy at CVS at the Start of Cold, Flu and COVID Season;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;4 Doctors Share the #1 Thing They Always Buy at CVS at the Start of Cold, Flu and COVID Season&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr. Evans agrees that the H3N2 super flu is responsive to antiviral treatments, so if you think you're infected, talk to your doctor right away to make sure you can access treatments that can get you feeling better fast.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Also, an important but often overlooked note: "Pregnant women are prone to more severe influenza," Dr. Tierney warns. "Therefore, they should consult their obstetrician if ill or exposed to the flu."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In terms of treating your aches, pains and fever, Dr. Freer says, "Rest, fluids and fever-reducing medications like &lt;a href="https://parade.com/health/common-cold-remedy-that-sends-people-to-hospital-according-to-er-doctor" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:acetaminophen;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;acetaminophen&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href="https://parade.com/health/combining-this-medication-with-coffee-can-boost-its-effects" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:ibuprofen;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;ibuprofen&lt;/a&gt; are key to symptom relief."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr. Robinson also recommends saline rinses if you have nasal congestion, while Dr. Shah says, "Try to eat small, light meals throughout the day to keep up your strength."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://parade.com/701835/lisamulcahy/10-ways-to-prevent-the-flu/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Here Are the 10 Best Ways To Prevent the Flu;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Here Are the 10 Best Ways To Prevent the Flu&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;How Long Does the Super Flu Last?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The good news about super flu? For most otherwise healthy people, you may not feel &lt;em&gt;too&lt;/em&gt; crummy for terribly long. "Most otherwise healthy people recover within about a week, though fatigue and cough can last longer," Dr. Ungerleider says. "Recovery can take several weeks for older adults, people with chronic conditions, or anyone who develops complications or requires hospitalization."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, make sure to pay attention to long-lasting symptoms. "If symptoms last longer than seven to 10 days, symptoms worsen after about a week or if difficulty breathing occurs, consult your healthcare provider," Dr. Tierney notes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even if your lingering symptoms don't seem serious to you, you should still get checked out just in case.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Lingering fatigue and cough are common, especially in older adults. If you aren't getting better in a week, you should see your doctor," Dr. Freer says. "Sometimes you can have complications from the flu, so if you are still symptomatic after a week, I would recommend you get checked by a health professional."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Up Next: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://parade.com/1146372/marijkevroomendurning/flu-symptoms-treatment/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Related: Do You Have the Flu? Here's Everything You Need To Know About Navigating Symptoms and Treatment;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Related: Do You Have the Flu? Here's Everything You Need To Know About Navigating Symptoms and Treatment&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Sources&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul class="caas-list caas-list-bullet"&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://publications.aap.org/aapnews/news/34114/CDC-9-children-have-died-of-flu-this-season?searchresult=1?autologincheck=redirected" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:CDC: 9 children have died of flu this season; previous season sets record;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;CDC: 9 children have died of flu this season; previous season sets record&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;em&gt;American Academy of Pediatrics. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/flu/signs-symptoms/index.html" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Signs and Symptoms of Flu;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Signs and Symptoms of Flu&lt;/a&gt;. Centers for Disease Control and Prevention&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.tylerevansmd.com/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Dr. Tyler B. Evans, MD, MS, MPH, AAHIVS, DTM&amp;amp;H, FIDSA;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Dr. Tyler B. Evans, MD, MS, MPH, AAHIVS, DTM&amp;amp;H, FIDSA&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.rwjbh.org/doctors/christopher-f-freer-do-facep-facep/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Dr. Christopher Freer, DO, FACEP;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Dr. Christopher Freer, DO, FACEP&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.bluebirdkids.com/providers/michael-glazier-md" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Dr. Michael Glazier, MD;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Dr. Michael Glazier, MD&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.bryant.edu/academics/faculty/hokeness-kirsten" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Dr. Kirsten Hokeness, Ph.D.;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Dr. Kirsten Hokeness, Ph.D.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.nfid.org/person/robert-h-hopkins-jr-md/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Dr. Robert Hopkins, Jr., MD;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Dr. Robert Hopkins, Jr., MD&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.huttonhealthconsulting.com/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Dr. Brad Hutton, MPH;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Dr. Brad Hutton, MPH&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://publichealth.nmsu.edu/about-us/faculty-directory/faculty/jagdish-khubchandani.html" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Dr. Jagdish Khubchandani, Ph.D., MPH, MBBS;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Dr. Jagdish Khubchandani, Ph.D., MPH, MBBS&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.serefin.com/who-we-are/about-serefin" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Dr. Vera Kohut, MD, Hon BSc;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Dr. Vera Kohut, MD, Hon BSc&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.goodrx.com/about/bio/karla-robinson?srsltid=AfmBOoqpCBBkuoEw7_zEQrYBEqDcKE8CSMYx6dMjy6ecUvAAL1EuR2fe" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Dr. Karla Robinson, MD;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Dr. Karla Robinson, MD&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.nychealthandhospitals.org/doctors-day-2022/sanjiv-shah/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Dr. Sanjiv Shah, MD, MPH;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Dr. Sanjiv Shah, MD, MPH&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.creighton.edu/campus-directory/tierney-maureen" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Dr. Maureen Tierney, MD, MSc;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Dr. Maureen Tierney, MD, MSc&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.shoshanaungerleider.com/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Dr. Shoshana Ungerleider, MD;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Dr. Shoshana Ungerleider, MD&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/flu/signs-symptoms/index.html" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Centers for Disease Control and Prevention;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Centers for Disease Control and Prevention&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;This story was originally published by &lt;a href="https://parade.com/health/h3n2-super-flu-symptoms-january-2026" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Parade;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Parade&lt;/a&gt; on Jan 8, 2026, where it first appeared in the &lt;a href="https://parade.com/health" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Health &amp;amp; Wellness;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Health &amp;amp; Wellness&lt;/a&gt; section. Add Parade as a &lt;a href="https://google.com/preferences/source?q=parade.com" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Preferred Source by clicking here.;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Preferred Source by clicking here.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>AOL.com</author><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 00:35:41 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiekFVX3lxTE5VZVp4c0dpTmRGdWZ6alNJUExlNjRCczlHUHpMY1FYb1FwMFIxTl9PVDh4Tl9ibHZsS2tJWTRwcFV4RmxZeDAtVk0yUXRkZGtveUJ1RTNTaVUybUxZREpWanpQZ1N4MWJGUHpqLUZwMF90aFVFNElaQ3hB</guid></item><item><title>维生素A的阴暗面：常见营养素如何帮助肿瘤逃避免疫系统- SciTechDaily</title><link>https://scitechdaily.com/vitamin-as-dark-side-how-a-common-nutrient-can-help-tumors-evade-the-immune-system/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>SciTechDaily</author><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 23:49:50 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMirAFBVV95cUxQdE8yUjktbVBqRGo3UklzQUtrdldLbVh0SXZkckdhWGhTZ0JwaHUwYXFzYV9NLVpjX09ER1ljbEtXMWxRRVhGbFFYX3BnNWYyWnc2b00zXzdGMWEwZEN1Z3lNT2liRndZazNLMXROenY0Y21fMGFjZHRkRkxMQVVlaml1NmV1NmliT01ncWxTal81XzNjNnZKems0UEQzc0w5OE1jQUxoUG1CclQx</guid></item><item><title>纽约市流感病例在十年来达到最高水平后下降-《纽约时报》</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2026/01/08/nyregion/nyc-flu-cases-drop-january.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The New York Times</author><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 23:28:22 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigAFBVV95cUxPbWtYUDR6aG9UTDB2NF9hdXJOT2FUcktlLVhORTdaOVBQeWhyV0otUzg0NWxIYmRIUkhwbkhmaEl2MGtJS1I0LVE3N2JJLU9EaUlSaDZfa094Tm84Nm9pZUJBX2E3UVlfQWtRUEpwN2d1amdiS1hQUm5pX09HM25qVQ</guid></item><item><title>2026年俄亥俄州首次报告麻疹疫情- WHIO TV</title><link>https://www.whio.com/news/local/first-measles-outbreak-ohio-reported-2026/EUYC54NN7VCPBNTGE6VOWOJSZQ/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article class="default__ArticleBody-sc-tl066j-1 jPcFTl article-body-wrapper"&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 lofITx body-paragraph"&gt;CUYAHOGA COUNTY, Ohio — The first measles outbreak has been reported in Ohio in 2026. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 lofITx body-paragraph"&gt;&lt;b&gt;[DOWNLOAD: &lt;/b&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.whio.com/mobile-apps/" target="_self" rel="" title="https://www.whio.com/mobile-apps/"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Free WHIO-TV News app for alerts as news breaks&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;b&gt;]&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 lofITx body-paragraph"&gt;The outbreak involves three unvaccinated children from a single household in Cuyahoga County, according to the &lt;a href="https://odh.ohio.gov/media-center/odh-news-releases/measles-outbreak-010826#:~:text=There%20are%20three%20infected%20individuals,cases%20had%20onsets%20in%202026." target="_blank" rel="noreferrer" title="https://odh.ohio.gov/media-center/odh-news-releases/measles-outbreak-010826#:~:text=There%20are%20three%20infected%20individuals,cases%20had%20onsets%20in%202026."&gt;Ohio Department of Health&lt;/a&gt; (ODH). &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 lofITx body-paragraph"&gt;The children were exposed when they traveled to an area in the United States with an ongoing measles outbreak. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="taboola-read-more" class="taboola-read-more"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 lofITx body-paragraph"&gt;&lt;b&gt;TRENDING STORIES:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 lofITx body-paragraph"&gt;ODH said it’s working with the Cuyahoga County Board of Health to follow up on potential exposures and to promote opportunities for vaccination.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 lofITx body-paragraph"&gt;One child’s illness began at the end of 2025, while the other two illnesses began in 2026. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 lofITx body-paragraph"&gt;“The fact that we again have measles cases in Ohio underlines the importance of being fully vaccinated,” Director Bruce Vanderhoff said. “This disease can be very serious, but it is also preventable. I strongly encourage you to protect yourselves and your children by getting vaccinated.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="taboola-read-more-8" class="taboola-read-more-8"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 lofITx body-paragraph"&gt;Measles is known for its extreme contagiousness and spreads primarily through coughing and sneezing, according to ODH.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 lofITx body-paragraph"&gt;Health experts said the measles vaccine, known as MMR, is highly effective, with two doses providing 97% immunity against the virus. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 lofITx body-paragraph"&gt;Those who are current on their vaccination have a significantly reduced risk of infection, the ODH said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 lofITx body-paragraph"&gt;Symptoms of measles typically include a rash, high fever, runny nose, cough and red watery eyes. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 lofITx body-paragraph"&gt;ODH said the rash lasts five to six days, starting at the hairline and reaching down the body. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 lofITx body-paragraph"&gt;Potential complications of measles include diarrhea and ear infections, with more severe outcomes for young children and those with weakened immune systems.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 lofITx body-paragraph"&gt;Last year, Ohio saw 45 measles cases and seven in 2024, the ODH said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 lofITx body-paragraph"&gt;Measles can be brought back to Ohio by people who travel to places with ongoing outbreaks. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 lofITx body-paragraph"&gt;Those who aren’t protected against the disease and are exposed have a 90% chance of becoming ill, according to the ODH. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 lofITx body-paragraph"&gt;Additional information about measles is available on the &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/measles/index.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer" title="https://www.cdc.gov/measles/index.html"&gt;CDC website&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 lofITx body-paragraph"&gt;&lt;b&gt;[SIGN UP: &lt;/b&gt;&lt;a href="https://membercenter.whio.com/newsletters" target="_self" rel="" title="https://membercenter.whio.com/newsletters"&gt;&lt;b&gt;WHIO-TV Daily Headlines Newsletter&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;b&gt;]&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 lofITx body-paragraph"&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 lofITx body-paragraph body-copyright"&gt;©2026 Cox Media Group&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>WHIO TV</author><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 21:44:38 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiowFBVV95cUxPOXpFOU9sR0RhQjhuSDR0VzN3UEl2Z2FSUVhpaUx3dWgxT1FIaTdYTmw0X2V5MlFXX1MxMVBEc3lGeWxUSUY4STZFaTVtYXlreExtZ2FEXzZ5dDRxWXpiLV83QzlyeURvMjdEa1l2cW85UXBIaWNhTmJlME1rcUZXWlFUc0ZtaVpBcE11a0xWV0Nmbk5Da2xrendTV0R0WHEzc0kw0gG3AUFVX3lxTE5fYzlBZUk1RjVaYjhGR3lJX1VXeTdDVnJVeHdXWE1qa2lhR2ZHMk9pdmVGcWFWNUVwVHhWaHFfSnFPaEM1ZGxja2t1MnpQM2NJTlY3a0lkNzBSdFNwWGdYZ2ZhTFNMaFBRdmhhT2JWdDZ3bjZUa0hZMzVUSndhY0xoUUdPUU1JVVdnMG0zOVlkQWh3eENGdDE4REdlOVlCcXFQNHpmNVJWc2FSTW1fQTBzRjlvck45MA</guid></item><item><title>新一组副作用较少的潜在糖尿病药物可以重新编程胰岛素抵抗细胞，使其更健康- Phys.org</title><link>https://phys.org/news/2026-01-group-potential-diabetes-drugs-side.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="success-screen" id="successScreen"&gt;
            &lt;p class="success-icon"&gt;✓&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;h2 class="success-title"&gt;Verification Complete&lt;/h2&gt;
            &lt;p class="success-subtext"&gt;This page will redirect in a moment...&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Phys.org</author><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 21:30:18 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiekFVX3lxTFBiSmgzSE1Ncm9yd1IxeWpDZll3ZW9TcHNpd01ua1RJbFUwUW5Ga2E5UTNnOXhXWFFwM0lxbTB6ZFRRZkZpZzVDQi1OdVpYNjdlYW1IU3Q1bHdZUTRfVTA1WmVsUUhkOEUtNGFWTEZWRUxqN1Z5MWRVZ1FB</guid></item><item><title>57迷人和令人不安的医学照片，不是每个人都能处理的（新图片） -无聊的熊猫</title><link>https://www.boredpanda.com/creepy-medical-cases-pics/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="body-content modal-body"&gt; &lt;label class="category-option"&gt; &lt;input type="checkbox" name="category[]" data-type="weekly" value="119509170107975610"&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;span class="title"&gt;Weekly&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="info"&gt; The week’s finest content carefully selected to bring you the best articles directly [once per week] &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/label&gt; &lt;label class="category-option"&gt; &lt;input type="checkbox" name="category[]" data-type="daily" value="119509170234852486"&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;span class="title"&gt;Daily&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="info"&gt; Our top news, meme articles, and a dose of the best content delivered straight to your inbox. [every day] &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/label&gt; &lt;label class="category-option"&gt; &lt;input type="checkbox" name="category[]" data-type="category" value="119509170245338276"&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;span class="title"&gt;Funny&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="info"&gt; The funniest articles of the week that had our audience in stitches [once per week] &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/label&gt; &lt;label class="category-option"&gt; &lt;input type="checkbox" name="category[]" data-type="category" value="119509170229609595"&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;span class="title"&gt;Animals&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="info"&gt; A delightful mix of top animal photos, memes, and a sprinkle of pet wellness articles [once per week] &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/label&gt; &lt;label class="category-option"&gt; &lt;input type="checkbox" name="category[]" data-type="category" value="119509170255824063"&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;span class="title"&gt;Good News&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="info"&gt; A dose of uplifting news delivered directly to your inbox. Pure positivity guaranteed [once per week] &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/label&gt; &lt;label class="category-option"&gt; &lt;input type="checkbox" name="category[]" data-type="category" value="154827377563666414"&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;span class="title"&gt;Best Deals&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="info"&gt; Exclusive discounts, our top shopping articles and ever more impressive deals directly to you [once per week] &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/label&gt; &lt;label class="category-option"&gt; &lt;input type="checkbox" name="category[]" data-type="category" value="119509170240095383"&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;span class="title"&gt;Art&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="info"&gt; The most captivating photographs, incredible art pieces, and amusing comics—all in one curated collection of the finest art articles [once per week] &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/label&gt; &lt;label class="category-option"&gt; &lt;input type="checkbox" name="category[]" data-type="category" value="119509170272601317"&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;span class="title"&gt;Parenting Stories&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="info"&gt; Discover relatable and unbelievable parenting anecdotes from the daily journey of raising a child [once per week] &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/label&gt; &lt;label class="category-option"&gt; &lt;input type="checkbox" name="category[]" data-type="category" value="119509170267358426"&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;span class="title"&gt;Brainy Panda&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="info"&gt; The most interesting trivia and quizzes in your inbox [once per week] &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/label&gt; &lt;label class="category-option"&gt; &lt;input type="checkbox" name="category[]" data-type="category" value="163332909941392922"&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;span class="title"&gt;BP Daily&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="info"&gt; BP Daily offers readers unbiased, nonpartisan reporting, analysis, and informed opinion in the areas of politics, policy, democracy, ethics, crime, and world news. [once per week] &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/label&gt; &lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Bored Panda</author><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 18:26:43 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiY0FVX3lxTE1wTE95TWY5UFM1R0s5S3g5bFJ3eExrTGloUjZ2UUpEYzZhQkZUYWNUYThsWHNDM0JqTzJLRVdFV1AyUDdMeFlHZEhtWVFjV3hQMF8tRG9FbzJyQjFwTXAxM2RMZw</guid></item><item><title>您是否正确服用补充剂？以下是他们的剂量限制指南-卫报</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/wellness/2026/jan/08/supplements-vitamins-safety-dosage-limit-guide</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body-commercial-selector article-body-viewer-selector dcr-hdpgoq"&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-15rw6c2"&gt;T&lt;/span&gt;here are more than &lt;a href="https://www.fda.gov/drugs/news-events-human-drugs/fdas-regulation-dietary-supplements-dr-cara-welch" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;100,000&lt;/a&gt; supplements on the US market – capsules, powders, tablets and gummies sold to improve or maintain health. Supplements can contain vitamins, minerals, botanicals and amino acids on their own or in various combinations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The consumption of these products is &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC10421343/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;surging&lt;/a&gt;. But it’s a common misunderstanding that these products are entirely safe, says Dr Pieter Cohen, an internist and associate professor at Harvard Medical School. Excessive amounts of nutrients can cause health problems, so it’s critical to know if you’re using the correct dosage of high-quality products.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="sign-in-gate"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Here’s what experts say about navigating the world of supplements, and what happens if you take too much of some common ones.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="choose-supplements-and-dosage-carefully" class="dcr-n4qeq9"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Choose supplements and dosage carefully&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Ideally, the nutrients we need come from the food we eat, says Dr Denise Millstine, director of integrative medicine at the Mayo Clinic Arizona. But that’s not always possible for various reasons, like a lack of access to nutritious foods or the effects of certain medications.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="de198331-d196-4414-a927-b0bac06b0c1d" data-spacefinder-role="richLink" data-spacefinder-type="model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.RichLinkBlockElement" class="dcr-47fhrn"&gt;&lt;gu-island name="RichLinkComponent" priority="feature" deferuntil="idle" props='{"richLinkIndex":5,"element":{"_type":"model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.RichLinkBlockElement","prefix":"Related: ","text":"Is it true that… you should take vitamin C when you’ve got a cold?","elementId":"de198331-d196-4414-a927-b0bac06b0c1d","role":"richLink","url":"https://www.theguardian.com/lifeandstyle/2025/dec/08/is-it-true-that-you-should-take-vitamin-c-when-youve-got-a-cold"},"ajaxUrl":"https://api.nextgen.guardianapps.co.uk","format":{"design":10,"display":2,"theme":4},"isInStarRatingVariant":false}'&gt;&lt;/gu-island&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“Some people may need a supplement; some people need to be careful that they’re not getting too much of a supplement,” says Joan Blake, a registered dietitian and clinical instructor at Boston University. “It’s all over the place.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;There are so many of these products for sale, and so many variants of what’s on a label, that shopping and selecting even a single supplement can be “dizzying” for consumers, says Millstine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;For some nutrients, there’s a &lt;a href="https://ods.od.nih.gov/HealthInformation/ODS_Frequently_Asked_Questions.aspx" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;recommended dietary allowance&lt;/a&gt; (RDA) – an amount to aim for daily, set in the US by the Food and Nutrition Board of the National Academies of Sciences, Engineering, and Medicine. The RDA can vary by sex, age and medical status. There’s also a tolerable upper intake level (UL), which is the maximum safe daily limit. Consuming more than the UL can cause health problems, depending on the nutrient.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Additionally, in the US, “there’s no vetting of products before they’re sold to ensure that the label is accurate,” says Cohen, whose&lt;a href="https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jama/fullarticle/2815523" data-link-name="in body link"&gt; research&lt;/a&gt; suggests contents and quantity labelling are often inaccurate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;There is limited government oversight over vitamins and supplements. The US Food and Drug Administration (FDA) &lt;a href="https://www.fda.gov/drugs/news-events-human-drugs/fdas-regulation-dietary-supplements-dr-cara-welch#:~:text" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;does not approve&lt;/a&gt; supplements or their labelling before they are sold. The only way to know if what’s listed on the label is accurate is if the product has been certified by the &lt;a href="https://www.nsf.org/consumer-resources/articles/supplement-vitamin-certification" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;National Sanitation Foundation&lt;/a&gt; (NSF) or &lt;a href="https://www.usp.org/verification-services/verified-mark" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;United States Pharmacopeia&lt;/a&gt; (USP), says Cohen. These are non-profits with “high-quality, third-party certification programs”, he explains. You can use &lt;a href="https://info.nsf.org/certified/dietary/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;their&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.quality-supplements.org/verified-products" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;websites&lt;/a&gt; to find verified products.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="check-with-your-doctor-before-taking-any-new-supplement" class="dcr-n4qeq9"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Check with your doctor before taking any new supplement&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Because the recommended amount differs from person to person, it’s critical to speak with a healthcare provider before starting something new. You need to know how the product might interact with anything else you’re consuming, like a medication or another supplement, explains Cohen. Adverse health effects could arise, or medications can become less effective.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Supplements can also affect blood tests, leading to inaccurate results, explains Dr Fernando Carnavali, an associate professor of internal medicine at the Icahn School of Medicine at Mount Sinai. He says it’s important to continue to discuss any vitamin or supplement use with your physician in case of evolving research about potential interactions, benefits or harms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;It’s best to use vitamins and supplements with caution, just as you would with over-the-counter medications like Tylenol, says Millstine. It’s also a good idea to stick to studied doses. She recommends using the National Center for Complementary and Integrative Health &lt;a href="https://www.nccih.nih.gov/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;website&lt;/a&gt; for information on dosing. The US Department of Agriculture also &lt;a href="https://www.nal.usda.gov/human-nutrition-and-food-safety/dri-calculator" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;has a tool&lt;/a&gt; for calculating the amount of vitamins and minerals you need.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Conversely, do not take dosing advice from the person selling the product, due to a risk of bias, says Millstine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Carnavali suspects that because vitamins and minerals are &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/wellness/2023/nov/13/natural-remedies-medication-true-self" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;perceived as natural&lt;/a&gt;, people are less likely to share what they are taking with their medical providers. It’s not uncommon for a patient to come in with questions about their health, only to learn that their vitamin and supplement habits were causing symptoms. “We’re not here to judge – we’re here to guide you,” says Carnavali.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="what-happens-if-you-take-too-much" class="dcr-n4qeq9"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What happens if you take too much?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Multivitamins: &lt;/strong&gt;Multivitamin supplements contain at least three vitamins and one mineral.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;There’s no regulation of what nutrients must be included or how much. &lt;a href="https://ods.od.nih.gov/factsheets/MVMS-HealthProfessional/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;According&lt;/a&gt; to the National Institutes of Health, some of these supplements contain vitamins and minerals in amounts higher than the established UL. Accordingly, there’s a risk of &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/17209210/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;excess nutrients&lt;/a&gt;, especially if you’re taking a multivitamin with other supplements.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;What &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/17209218/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;harm might occur&lt;/a&gt; depends on the excessive nutrient in question. “Multivitamins can be tricky because you need to look at each of the components, and there are just so many of them,” says Millstine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;There are risks associated with certain individuals. For example, the NIH &lt;a href="https://ods.od.nih.gov/factsheets/MVMS-HealthProfessional/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;states&lt;/a&gt; that smokers and former smokers might want to avoid multivitamins with large amounts of beta-carotene or vitamin A, which are linked to an increased risk of lung cancer in smokers. For people who are pregnant, more than &lt;a href="https://ods.od.nih.gov/pubs/Scoop%20Winter%202022.pdf" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;2,800micrograms (mcg)&lt;/a&gt; of vitamin A a day can increase the risk of birth defects.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;People who take blood thinners should speak with their doctor before using a multivitamin containing vitamin K, which can decrease the effectiveness of those drugs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Vitamin D: &lt;/strong&gt;“Vitamin D can become quite toxic when taken excessively,” says Millstine. High levels are associated with harms like nausea, vomiting and excessive urination. Extremely high levels are linked to kidney failure, irregular heartbeat and death. The NIH notes that high levels are &lt;a href="https://ods.od.nih.gov/factsheets/VitaminD-Consumer/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;“almost always&lt;/a&gt;” caused by excessive supplements.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Individual requirements can differ, Millstine says. According to the NIH, &lt;a href="https://ods.od.nih.gov/factsheets/VitaminD-Consumer/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;the RDA&lt;/a&gt; for adults between ages 19 and 70 is around 15mcg, or 600 International Units (IU). The upper limit for the same group is 100mcg, or 4,000 IU.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;If your healthcare provider recommends you take vitamin D, it’s advisable to start at the standard dose, then recheck your levels in three months, says Millstine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Omega-3 &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;fatty &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;acids: &lt;/strong&gt;Omega-3 fatty acids are found in certain foods, like fatty fish and chia seeds. Supplements &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/science/2025/feb/03/an-omega-3-dose-a-day-could-slow-ageing-process-healthspan-trial-finds" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;like fish oil&lt;/a&gt; or fish liver oil &lt;a href="https://www.nccih.nih.gov/health/omega3-supplements-what-you-need-to-know#:~:text" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;contain&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/wellness/2025/apr/07/do-fish-oil-supplements-work" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;two types&lt;/a&gt; of omega-3 fatty acids: docosahexaenoic acid, or DHA, and eicosapentaenoic acid, or EPA.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Experts &lt;a href="https://ods.od.nih.gov/factsheets/Omega3FattyAcids-Consumer/#:~:text" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;haven’t established&lt;/a&gt; recommended amounts for these two types, but the FDA recommends limiting the combined total to no more than 5 grams daily from dietary supplements. High doses can increase the risk of bleeding and stroke, &lt;a href="https://www.mayoclinic.org/drugs-supplements-fish-oil/art-20364810#:~:text=Taking%20high%20doses%20of%20fish,increase%20the%20risk%20of%20stroke." data-link-name="in body link"&gt;according&lt;/a&gt; to the Mayo Clinic.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;A low-quality omega-3 product comes with more risks of side effects, ranging from heartburn to nausea, explains Millstine. These supplements can contain other elements, like vitamins A and D, and &lt;a href="https://www.nccih.nih.gov/health/omega3-supplements-what-you-need-to-know" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;dosage can vary&lt;/a&gt; from product to product, so it’s important to check the label.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure data-spacefinder-role="inline" data-spacefinder-type="model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.NewsletterSignupBlockElement" class="dcr-173mewl"&gt;&lt;gu-island name="EmailSignUpWrapper" priority="feature" deferuntil="visible" props='{"index":29,"listId":6039,"identityName":"well-actually","description":"Practical advice, expert insights and answers to your questions about how to live a good life","name":"Well Actually","frequency":"Weekly","successDescription":"You are subscribed","theme":"lifestyle","idApiUrl":"https://idapi.theguardian.com","hideNewsletterSignupComponentForSubscribers":true}'&gt;&lt;/gu-island&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;For instance, if you’re taking a 1,000mg fish oil capsule with a 300mg omega-3 content, it’s worth checking what else is in the product, says Millstine. Non-EPA/DHA elements can cause issues like gastrointestinal symptoms and increased risk of bruising.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Another omega-3 fatty acid, alpha-linolenic acid (ALA), is found in plants. Apart from the food you eat, you can get ALA from flaxseed oil supplements. The recommended amount of ALA for adults is between 1.1 grams to 1.6 grams.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Calcium: &lt;/strong&gt;The typical recommendation for adults is 1,000mg to 1,200mg of calcium daily, divided into no more than around 500mg at a time, says Millstine. The &lt;a href="https://ods.od.nih.gov/factsheets/Calcium-Consumer/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;upper limit&lt;/a&gt; varies depending on your age and medical status. Calcium can negatively interact with other supplements and medications.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Too much supplemental calcium can &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC4708574/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;cause kidney stones&lt;/a&gt;. While research is &lt;a href="https://www.mayoclinic.org/diseases-conditions/heart-attack/expert-answers/calcium-supplements/faq-20058352" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;mixed&lt;/a&gt; and more is needed, some &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC7910980/#sec5-nutrients-13-00368" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;studies&lt;/a&gt; suggest calcium supplements can increase the risk of heart disease, specifically in postmenopausal women.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;According to the &lt;a href="https://www.nhs.uk/conditions/vitamins-and-minerals/calcium/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;National Health Service&lt;/a&gt;, more than 1,500mg of calcium a day can lead to stomach pain and diarrhea.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Vitamin C: &lt;/strong&gt;Vitamin C is one of the more overused supplements, because so many people use it to avoid sickness, Blake says. While it may slightly shorten the duration of a cold, &lt;a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/books/NBK279544/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;research&lt;/a&gt; suggests that it won’t prevent a cold.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Extra vitamin C simply exits the body during urination. But chronic excessive use can lead to gastrointestinal issues like nausea and diarrhea, explains Blake. Doses greater than &lt;a href="https://medlineplus.gov/ency/article/002404.htm" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;2,000mg&lt;/a&gt; a day can lead to stomach aches, diarrhea and kidney stones.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Millstine advises about 500mg to 1,000mg per day. “The problem with taking too much is it’s just not helping you, so why would you stress your kidneys in that way?” she asks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Vitamin B12: &lt;/strong&gt;The NIH recommends &lt;a href="https://ods.od.nih.gov/factsheets/VitaminB12-Consumer/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;2.4mcg&lt;/a&gt; of B12 daily for most adults, though personalized doses can vary. It’s available in different types of supplements, many of which have very high doses of B12.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;While rare, excessive B12 can be associated with symptoms like anxiety, agitation, flushing and headaches, says Millstine. It can interact with medications like gastric acid inhibitors and metformin. Other forms of vitamin B, &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/australia-news/2025/jul/27/what-is-vitamin-b6-toxicity-and-what-are-the-symptoms-of-taking-too-much" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;like vitamin B6&lt;/a&gt;, can be more toxic.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Magnesium: &lt;/strong&gt;Magnesium supplements come in various forms, including magnesium oxide, citrate and chloride. These have different effects: For example, magnesium citrate is used as a laxative, so those with more sensitive stomachs might want to avoid it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Generally, the RDA for adults is about 300mg to 400mg (depending on age and sex). The &lt;a href="https://ods.od.nih.gov/factsheets/Magnesium-HealthProfessional/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;UL for magnesium&lt;/a&gt; via supplements and medications specifically is 350mg.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;While there’s &lt;a href="https://ods.od.nih.gov/factsheets/Magnesium-HealthProfessional/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;no risk&lt;/a&gt; linked to too much magnesium in food, high doses of magnesium might cause nausea, abdominal cramping and &lt;a href="https://www.nejm.org/doi/full/10.1056/NEJM199104113241502" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;diarrhea&lt;/a&gt;. Very large doses can &lt;a href="https://medicine.tufts.edu/news-events/news/can-magnesium-supplements-improve-health" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;be fatal&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;People with kidney disease can’t excrete excess magnesium and should not take it unless it’s been discussed with their healthcare team, says Millstine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Probiotics: &lt;/strong&gt;There is &lt;a href="https://ods.od.nih.gov/factsheets/Probiotics-Consumer/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;no official&lt;/a&gt; recommendation for the use of probiotics by generally healthy individuals. Blake recommends speaking with a registered dietitian nutritionist to determine which strain and dosage is right for you. Possible negative side effects include eczema and inflammatory bowel disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;If you can tolerate probiotics, excessive use may not be toxic, but there could be other downstream effects.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“Probiotics can limit your ability to get to your natural, healthy microbiome,” says Millstine, because high-dose supplements can hinder the diversity of your gut bacteria. “I caution people to really consider if they need probiotics.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Creatine: &lt;/strong&gt;Creatine supplements can cause some bloating and GI symptoms, as well as nausea, says Millstine. She recommends sticking to 4 to 5 grams per day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Research suggests that higher doses of creatine &lt;a href="https://www.health.harvard.edu/exercise-and-fitness/what-is-creatine-potential-benefits-and-risks-of-this-popular-supplement" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;do not offer&lt;/a&gt; any advantages. Because there’s &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/10999421/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;mixed evidence&lt;/a&gt; of a negative effect on kidneys, people with &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/31859895/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;kidney disease&lt;/a&gt; are especially advised to speak with their healthcare provider before trying it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Collagen peptides: &lt;/strong&gt;Collagen peptides are smaller pieces of collagen and can come in powder and pill form. Collagen peptides can possibly help with &lt;a href="https://www.mdpi.com/2072-6643/15/6/1332" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;joint &lt;/a&gt;and &lt;a href="https://linkinghub.elsevier.com/retrieve/pii/S2405844023021680" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;skin health&lt;/a&gt;, though much more research is needed to support these claims, says Carnavali.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Though there’s no standardized dose, &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/31096622/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;some research&lt;/a&gt; shows between 2.5 grams to 15 grams daily is safe. However, research not sponsored by supplement manufacturers is scarce.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Millstine’s primary caution is not to use collagen peptides in place of a more complete protein powder, because they lack essential amino acids needed for overall health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Guardian</author><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 18:12:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimwFBVV95cUxNU2toeFNBZk1PN3NmSFU2OGtlSW9feGR2NXZmUUV3UGowY1IydE9jZjQ5QkJQRlJicmtkYjJhTWlieDg0VmdVUXljTlo5LXk5Uk1NaDhGd0tYZW9MbjlCaFg0RnFhck9zbGxFRmZRbGE2UnZZbU9Jd295VjQ4UUlaQzJrUWVLUlBXQTJNcUtESWpZU0hvMzQ2aUt0VQ</guid></item><item><title>州长韦斯·摩尔（ Wes Moore ）法案将允许马里兰州绕过联邦疫苗接种时间表-《华盛顿邮报》</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/dc-md-va/2026/01/08/maryland-vaccine-bill-wes-moore/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="UCBJFNNCTRFBLFMENM4UI2COEM" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;The administration of Maryland Gov. Wes Moore (D) on Thursday proposed legislation that would empower the state’s health secretary to issue vaccine recommendations and bypass federal guidance — making it the latest state to reject the Trump administration’s &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/health/2026/01/05/childhood-vaccine-immunization-schedule-overhaul/"&gt;overhaul of the childhood vaccine schedule&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiwFBVV95cUxOSlFwVE9wZDN1NmZmV2NLX3Z4WkE5ZmZRRDk3R0lzcWJzWkJUSVJXaHZRdHFDeEdHaDA4ZEVVVEtnWGZ5LUREWUNTTFRNVVN6RTV4WlpVTFdhckV4b29kQnk1cDlDWkN2azRHeG1yeDlnZEtPdWtoUW1ibHVMQ0psbFE4LVNUbk1Ebm1n</guid></item><item><title>随着疾病预防控制中心改变疫苗建议，西澳流感病例呈上升趋势，其中许多是儿童-西雅图时报</title><link>https://www.seattletimes.com/seattle-news/health/wa-flu-season-is-in-full-swing-especially-among-young-and-old/</link><description>&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMisAFBVV95cUxQanFGbVpEUTFmU3FDVUtFeHZqcmJmeUgxQUQ1UjJvMDdsekZHRWlreFpXYlNnN1p5OTRzbndWMkxlYTdqQXI3MXZDZXhpMTVqRDNwdTRHenF1YUFZdzVHVE9oRm1RM1F0czBuSlRTaHJ0YThDdUlRYWk2TFlDMEhYaEUxNXpfaE8yYm1CNFZvclJFc01PRFVYSnhRS0pWOWFyMzhoRVhJU0JoRWZLV2lPWg?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;WA flu cases are on the rise, many of them kids, as CDC changes vaccine recommendations&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Seattle Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMi-AFBVV95cUxNWTVWaXc2N1B1aUtJbUxCdm9XaG53OEtqbWo3ODR6VWlYLXFQYWhybHRYN3QxQXVHZFFudmtudnh1RXg2ajBtaE5xWHM4QUdHWHJ3eFVGSElIN3RZeHZ5UlN6SGhfSHl3OVg4UEd4T2x3aUt3bjRTd3JRMmRGLUJZdWFpR1VnRlpGTWRvSzNkQ2lhNGNNT2FVZ3lFVDRlWHQ4Ym8wVW92TDA2My1IY1diWjAyQTNfUTJGZms0OHNQc0xqR05FR1p4NVY4RU9rTmU3OGJXdW9wczBZZ3RibjVkX2pGbkwwZ2ZCYVducHZvdTNfVjBxd0pZZw?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;Respiratory illness positivity rates, including flu, spike across the Inland Northwest&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;KREM&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMixgFBVV95cUxNLURjRzNmUlF1cTg3ZFYxY3E4YWU3a2J0dVNldUhFR0ctbXFmbWwyTFltQ2R0WGpwMmhINF9Qdk9GNXducWNDU25oLXkzUEF6aURvcHEzLW5vTmlEVmstY2hqbDhMcFhzenFZVm1WVnpjLXlCODRPVG9MckRXQzJiNy10VUZDZC04MjFnYjBRZWI4aTBrRHh3dndsaW4xNVhnSFpPVW0zYWhIbDNDVjAzRkNTNVJseHBxdVdGbmhKSGZWWWpabVE?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;Rising cases in Kitsap signals potential for severe flu season ahead&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Kitsap Sun&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;</description><author>The Seattle Times</author><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMisAFBVV95cUxQanFGbVpEUTFmU3FDVUtFeHZqcmJmeUgxQUQ1UjJvMDdsekZHRWlreFpXYlNnN1p5OTRzbndWMkxlYTdqQXI3MXZDZXhpMTVqRDNwdTRHenF1YUFZdzVHVE9oRm1RM1F0czBuSlRTaHJ0YThDdUlRYWk2TFlDMEhYaEUxNXpfaE8yYm1CNFZvclJFc01PRFVYSnhRS0pWOWFyMzhoRVhJU0JoRWZLV2lPWg</guid></item><item><title>明尼苏达州支持全面的儿科疫苗接种计划，打破CDC - Star Tribune</title><link>https://www.startribune.com/minnesota-backs-full-pediatric-vaccine-schedule-breaking-with-cdc/601560183</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div data-astro-cid-nbv56vs3&gt; &lt;p data-astro-cid-nbv56vs3&gt;Vercel Security Checkpoint&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="hide-mobile" data-astro-cid-nbv56vs3&gt;|&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p data-astro-cid-nbv56vs3&gt;iad1::1767908057-IHUZ2SGwsshf8dQPLBYPeRZpT8YFEHbO&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Star Tribune</author><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 17:34:12 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipgFBVV95cUxPbUdZYjlQZjJfZVRxQmpOcTgwUUlJMUc2ZEVpYXNMdjhiRjZnN0Z5Q05JYzNiN0FEUUNQYkpQOXlVNEJvLXBpMmNZQTYyLTYxQmdFRjBLMWMwNWI2RmtoOWxaQ3NnVlBVSWxSeVYyOFZRTlF1dmdXR1FJVHpZbnFlWGVfSkVIR3FNdk10X2pZRkc2VzJMbHRVZ1VzcHh0a3hHR1BWRnpn</guid></item><item><title>许多脱离GLP-1药物的人在2年内体重恢复，评论建议- CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2026/01/08/health/weight-loss-drugs-regain-scli-intl-wellness</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article__content" data-editable="content" itemprop="articleBody" data-reorderable="content"&gt;
                
    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmk5f98wz001y26qmfecph2fk@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Many people who stop using &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2025/08/18/health/glp1-muscle-loss-strength-training-wellness"&gt;weight loss drugs&lt;/a&gt; will return to their previous weight within two years, a new review of existing research has found.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmk5f9faw0000356py33edjst@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            This rate of weight regain is significantly faster than that seen in those who have lost weight by changing other lifestyle factors, such as diet and exercise, rather than relying on GLP-1 medications, researchers from the University of Oxford report in a paper published Wednesday in &lt;a href="https://www.bmj.com/content/392/bmj-2025-085304" target="_blank"&gt;The BMJ journal&lt;/a&gt;.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmk5fkzou000c356pocpgenws@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            GLP-1, which stands for glucagon-like peptide-1, is a hormone naturally made by the body that helps signal to the brain and the gut that it’s full and doesn’t need to eat any more.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmk5fpgkz000i356pt8amw7e4@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Weight loss drugs mimic the action of this hormone by increasing the secretion of insulin to lower blood sugar.
    &lt;/p&gt;



    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmk5fpkxg000k356p69fnqkq1@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            They also slow the movement of food through the digestive tract, which helps people feel full more quickly and for longer, and they work in the brain to reduce appetite.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmk5fokxr000f356pgyrh4tl1@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            GLP-1 medications, which include Ozempic, Wegovy, Mounjaro and Zepbound, have proven to be highly effective for weight loss.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmk5fpmuj000n356pro7yu60n@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            However, University of Oxford researchers analyzed the results of 37 studies involving more than 9,300 adults.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmk5k1n7w0001356pcmpsngwq@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            They found that “weight regain after stopping drugs was faster than after ending behavioural weight loss programmes such as diet and exercise support by approximately 0.3 kg (0.7 pounds) per month,” they said in a statement.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmk5fyky00014356p0gm7dopb@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “This isn’t a failing of the medicines — it reflects the nature of obesity as a chronic, relapsing condition,” said study lead author Sam West, a postdoctoral researcher at the Nuffield Department of Primary Care Health Sciences, University of Oxford, in the statement.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmk5fz9vk0017356p45rpngmw@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “It sounds a cautionary note for short-term use without a more comprehensive approach to weight management.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

  

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmk5gc8ku001k356p3piyag86@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Adam Collins, associate professor of nutrition at the University of Surrey in England, who was not involved in the study, called the paper “timely and important.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmk5gea6m001q356pnn8cjwzx@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Collins underlined that weight regain is a common issue in all weight loss interventions, but the paper shows that this problem is amplified with GLP-1 medications.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmk5jadq8000a356phy0vv64b@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Collins also offered some possible explanations as to why this is the case.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmk5ge7ma001n356p9zuttxyr@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “Artificially providing GLP-1 levels several times higher than normal over a long period may cause you to produce less of your own natural GLP-1, and may also make you less sensitive to its effects,” he said in a statement shared with CNN by the Science Media Centre.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmk5ghh5e001v356pkhpefric@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Collins added that this isn’t a problem when taking these drugs, but taking away this source of GLP-1 then makes overeating “far more likely.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmk5ghhz5001x356pw8cc62ry@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “Like any addict, going cold turkey is a real challenge. This is further exacerbated if the individual in question has relied solely on GLP-1 to do the heavy lifting during weight loss,” he said, rather than making behavioral changes.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmk5fxsq20011356pq0qkx2xj@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Marie Spreckley, obesity researcher and public health nutritionist at the University of Cambridge in England, who was not involved in the study, cautioned that the paper’s long-term conclusions rely on modeled projections, rather than observed data, as the follow-up period for stopping treatment with newer medicines is limited to about 12 months.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmk5g8lgu001d356p6sx73bi1@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “As a result, longer-term statements, including full weight regain within two years, rely on extrapolation beyond the available data,” she said in a statement shared with CNN by the Science Media Centre, meaning that comparisons with behavioral changes should “be interpreted as suggestive rather than definitive.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmk5ldt43000h356pidoptxdt@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “In real-world terms, the findings reinforce that obesity management typically requires long-term planning. If people stop medication, many are likely to need ongoing nutritional and behavioural support, and health services should anticipate that cardiometabolic benefits may lessen as weight is regained,” Spreckley said, adding that this highlights “the need for further research into effective, scalable strategies for long-term weight maintenance alongside pharmacotherapy.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmk5gf8ep001t356p4pqp2x8f@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            GLP-1 medications have become widely used in recent years, and &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2025/08/18/health/glp1-muscle-loss-strength-training-wellness"&gt;more than 15 million Americans&lt;/a&gt; are now losing weight with the drugs.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmk5gkizp0023356pbk9lk4wu@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            And &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2025/01/20/health/glp-1-medications-benefits-risks-beyond-weight-loss-diabetes"&gt;a study&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;published in January 2025&lt;/a&gt; suggested that popular GLP-1 medications approved for weight loss, diabetes and heart disease may have untapped potential to reduce the risks of substance abuse disorders, psychosis, infections and some kinds of cancer and dementia.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmk5glten0026356pnsrwfkat@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            However, it is important to remember that using&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;the drugs to suppress appetite&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;doesn’t just contribute to&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;fat loss but also to reduced muscle mass.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmk5gpd4l002k356pzrhw1isl@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/38937282/" target="_blank"&gt;Studies have indicated&lt;/a&gt; that anywhere between 15% to 60% of the weight people lose is lean muscle mass, meaning that those who are using the drugs are advised to engage in a weekly exercise routine that includes strength training to stave off too much muscle loss.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmk5gr8ef002m356pvitgyoe9@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            It is particularly important for those 65 or older, who are already at risk of age-related loss of muscle mass, strength and function.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  

              &lt;/div&gt;
                  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>CNN</author><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 17:33:26 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiAFBVV95cUxNRnMtZ1VCWlpLOExIR0luRjZSNnplR0s1dkhWVVhMeGtna0ExTElLU25HSnNkZ0lEamlPNFlWc2dZNk9SeUhyTzcyaWR0ZEZWdzJQSVd5WVk5bmN5M09mQ1NaYTlhOF9FRnJJaTJoaTRFRTJUVHFFWVFVSTZrcmZ3dWY0a093bnE2</guid></item><item><title>排名第一的茶叶营养师推荐更好的大脑功能-真正简单</title><link>https://www.realsimple.com/number-1-tea-dietitians-suggest-for-better-brain-function-11877337</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="realsimple-sc-page_1-0" class="comp realsimple-sc-page mntl-sc-page mntl-block structured-content" data-sc-sticky-offset="90" data-sc-ad-label-height="24" data-sc-ad-track-spacing="100" data-sc-min-track-height="250" data-sc-max-track-height="600" data-sc-breakpoint="50em" data-sc-load-immediate="4" data-sc-content-positions="[1, 1250, 1550, 1950, 2350, 2750, 3150, 3550, 3950]" data-bind-scroll-on-start="true"&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-block_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block realsimple-sc-block-callout--summary realsimple-sc-block-callout mntl-sc-block-universal-callout theme-summary" data-tracking-id="mntl-sc-block-callout" data-tracking-container="true"&gt; &lt;h3 class="mntl-sc-block-universal-callout__heading"&gt;Key Takeaways&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;div class="mntl-sc-block-universal-callout__body"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Dietitians point to green tea’s unique combination of EGCG catechins, L-theanine, and low-dose caffeine as the reason it best supports brain health over time.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Compared to black tea or coffee, green tea delivers brain benefits with less caffeine, making it easier to drink throughout the day without jitters.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The biggest brain health perks come from consistency—aim for one to three cups of green tea a day, brewed gently and enjoyed regularly, rather than occasional drinking.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_2-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; When it comes to &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.realsimple.com/brain-boosting-habits-11762153" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;brain health&lt;/a&gt;, most people first consider their &lt;a href="https://www.realsimple.com/what-is-good-sleep-hygiene-8730838" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;sleep quality&lt;/a&gt;, meal choices, or lifestyle to keep them sharp. However, what you sip on throughout the day, whether it's &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.realsimple.com/health/how-much-water-to-drink-day" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="3" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;water&lt;/a&gt;, soda, or tea, can actually impact how well your brain functions, too. A few popular teas contain compounds that support your memory and attention, but there is one that consistently comes up in dietitian recommendations.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_3-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_4-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; We asked nutrition experts to identify the top tea for brain health, and explain in simple terms why it works so well. Their answer probably won’t surprise you: Green tea is widely available and backed by a significant amount of research. Here’s why they recommend drinking it regularly to keep your mind sharp, plus some clever ways to fit more green tea into your daily routine. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_5-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="mntl-sc-block_6-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block realsimple-sc-block-callout--meetourexpert mntl-sc-block-universal-callout--meetourexpert mntl-sc-block-universal-callout theme-meetourexpert callout--bordered" data-text="Meet the Expert" data-tracking-id="mntl-sc-block-callout" data-tracking-container="true"&gt;
&lt;div class="mntl-sc-block-universal-callout__body"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://totaste.com/about/lindsey-schoenfeld/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1" rel="nofollow"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;Lindsey Schoenfeld&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;, &lt;/strong&gt;RDN, a registered dietitian nutritionist, professional chef, and co-founder of To Taste&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.vandanasheth.com/about/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;Vandana Sheth&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;, &lt;/strong&gt;RDN, CDCES, FAND, a registered dietitian nutritionist with a focus on plant-based nutrition and diabetes care&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-the-best-tea-to-drink-for-brain-health"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_7-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block realsimple-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; The Best Tea to Drink for Brain Health &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_8-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; While &lt;a href="https://www.realsimple.com/teas-for-brain-health-11779146" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;several teas offer cognitive benefits&lt;/a&gt;, dietitians say one consistently shows up in research. “My top pick is green tea (including &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.realsimple.com/food-recipes/recipe-collections-favorites/popular-ingredients/what-is-matcha" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;matcha&lt;/a&gt;),” says Vandana Sheth, RDN, a registered dietitian nutritionist and former national media spokesperson at The Academy of Nutrition and Dietetics. “Although many teas are good for brain health, green tea stands out because of its unique combination of bioactive compounds.” 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_9-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_10-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Lindsey Schoenfeld, RDN, &lt;em&gt;a &lt;/em&gt;registered dietitian nutritionist, professional chef, and co-founder of To Taste, agrees. “Green tea takes the gold! When it comes to brain health, green tea tends to get the most attention,” she says. In fact, several long-term studies link regularly drinking green tea with a lower risk of &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.realsimple.com/age-brain-declines-study-11706222" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;cognitive decline&lt;/a&gt;, and “its natural compounds may help protect brain cells as we age,” Schoenfeld adds.&lt;span data-cite="1" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_11-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_12-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; So, what makes &lt;a href="https://www.realsimple.com/green-tea-vs-black-tea-11822262" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;green tea different from black tea&lt;/a&gt;? “Green tea provides catechins, especially EGCG, along with L-theanine and a small amount of &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.realsimple.com/food-recipes/shopping-storing/beverages/how-much-caffeine-per-day" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;caffeine&lt;/a&gt;,” Sheth explains. “This combination supports calm focus, mental clarity, and long-term brain health in a way most other teas do not.”
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_13-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_14-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; L-theanine specifically promotes a feeling of relaxation without drowsiness, and helps smooth caffeine's effects, Sheth points out.&lt;span data-cite="2" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Additionally, the green tea-specific catechins provide both &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.realsimple.com/fruits-with-more-antioxidants-than-green-tea-11739371" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;antioxidant&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.realsimple.com/anti-inflammatory-drinks-8707182" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;anti-inflammatory benefits&lt;/a&gt; that support brain cells. “This combination makes green tea especially good for sustained attention and cognitive health across the lifespan,” she says.&lt;span data-cite="3" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_15-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_16-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Drinking black tea can help your brain health, too. But unlike black tea, green tea leaves are minimally oxidized, which helps preserve higher levels of catechins like EGCG. That means you’re getting more of the compounds linked to long-term neuroprotection.&lt;span data-cite="4" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Green tea also has &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.realsimple.com/matcha-vs-coffee-8550568" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;less caffeine&lt;/a&gt; (about 25–40 milligrams per cup, compared to 40–70 milligrams), which means it’s easier to drink more of it midday than black tea or coffee. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_17-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_19-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_21-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-how-to-drink-more-green-tea"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_22-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block realsimple-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; How to Drink More Green Tea &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_23-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Green tea supports your brain health without overstimulation, but how much do you need to drink to reap the drink's benefits? Here’s what the experts say about fitting this brain-boosting tea into your daily life.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_24-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_25-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block realsimple-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Brew the Perfect Cup &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_26-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; First, you need to make sure you’re &lt;a href="https://www.realsimple.com/how-to-steep-tea-7153209" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;brewing your green tea correctly&lt;/a&gt; to maximize it's brain-boosting potential. “Sounds funny, but it's so important!”  Schoenfeld shares&lt;em&gt;. “&lt;/em&gt;Use hot, simmering water, not boiling water, and steep for 2–3 minutes max. This will keep it slightly sweet and not bitter.” (For reference, that means brewing your tea in water that’s around 160–180°F.)&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;Overheating or over-steeping green tea can degrade its most brain-supportive compounds. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_27-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_28-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block realsimple-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Focus on Consistency &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_29-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; But consistency matters more than chasing the perfect cup of tea, according to Schoenfeld. “Find a green tea you like, and it becomes much easier to turn tea into an &lt;a href="https://www.realsimple.com/daily-habits-that-will-make-you-happier-11862093" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;everyday habit&lt;/a&gt; rather than another wellness chore. The best tea for brain health is really the one you enjoy drinking.” Most research suggests aiming for one to three cups a day to deliver cognitive benefits over time. You’ll notice more impact when the tea is consumed regularly, rather than sporadically.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_30-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_31-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block realsimple-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Replace Other Drinks &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_32-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; There are so many opportunities to drink (or eat) green tea instead of something else. “Swap your second cup of coffee for brewed &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.realsimple.com/matcha-vs-green-tea-11687240" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;green tea or matcha&lt;/a&gt;; add matcha to &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.realsimple.com/food-recipes/recipe-collections-favorites/healthy-meals/heathy-breakfast-smoothies" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;smoothies&lt;/a&gt; or oatmeal for a gentle mental boost; sip green tea after meals as part of a calming routine; or keep tea bags or single-serve matcha at work for consistency,” says Sheth.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_33-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_34-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block realsimple-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Keep a Pitcher in the Fridge &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_35-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Make iced green tea to have on hand in a pinch—and mix it up with lemon, citrus peel, or fresh mint. “Keep it lightly sweetened, or free of artificial ingredients and added sugar,” says Schoenfeld, who suggests swapping one sweetened drink a day for green tea or a simple matcha latte. “Finally, find a friend who enjoys tea, as &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.realsimple.com/microhabits-for-better-health-11759744" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;wellness habits&lt;/a&gt; tend to be easier to establish when you are connected with friends,” she concludes.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Real Simple</author><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 17:23:17 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimAFBVV95cUxQam9fZ0ZzU2JBa0lpaW12X2xoOThJVmw0NnBWVHp2c1dDN1MyY0VGVGp4UGE0SFVhRktoQUIxYlBTT3RkcW5YMUxVSjk1MVpNQUJmLWNjLXlzeTRBUUJ4azI0NFpaX0llQzZfemV3U2psLWFlQkZXZXR5WVdNWVdYSkk5MlJrX1g3V0dSQWdIdTRXOTdXTHZQUA</guid></item><item><title>研究表明，前GLP-1使用者在约18个月后体重减轻-《华盛顿邮报》</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/wellness/2026/01/08/ozempic-wegovy-weight-regain-glp1/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="TALWJZN7MVCWVB42PAZTOJELIY" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;People who stop taking GLP-1 drugs such as Ozempic and Wegovy for weight loss are projected to regain their shed pounds within about 1½ years, a review of existing research has found.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="3C6KPGWDSZETLNXE7AKMF52ZZM" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;The paper also found that former users of a wider&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;list&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;of&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;weight-loss drugs regain weight four times more quickly than those who had used behavioral techniques like dieting or exercise. For sustained health benefits after coming off the drugs, scientists say, it is necessary to make lasting changes to your diet and exercise regime.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 16:33:44 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijgFBVV95cUxQVDBHS1ZSM004Qnpyc3ZGU3RVMHNjVnk2NUx6SEEwT1FuRkJpLVpLU2E1ZnR5azB1UlNyQ0VyRjlEVDJNTmlVY0NhYm8wX2xkQXhrb3hmR0Vqb0gzeWZBaEFPZ29la2JSbDRwdnlCaGxELTNxaDJMSEpvZGRZVHkxWV9BNTlTNkJOS2RHREJn</guid></item><item><title>科学评论显示， CBD在抗击癌症肿瘤方面具有“实质性承诺” -大麻时刻</title><link>https://www.marijuanamoment.net/cbd-has-substantial-promise-to-combat-tumors-from-cancer-scientific-review-shows/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="mvp-content-main" class="left relative"&gt;
														&lt;p&gt;Cannabidiol (CBD), a non-intoxicating compound in marijuana, “holds substantial promise as an anti-tumor agent” in addition to its other anti-inflammatory properties, a new scientific review&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Scientists explored CBD’s effect on many types of cancer—including some of the most aggressive ones, such as glioblastoma, which affects the brain. They also noted it can help suppressing the growth and metastasis of other cancers, including breast, lung, colorectal, ovarian and prostate, among others.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“CBD exhibits multi-targeted anti-tumor effects by disrupting key cancer hallmarks,” they found.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The paper, funded by National Natural Science Fund of China, was designed as a systematic review of previous studies evaluating the cancer fighting qualities of CBD.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The idea behind much of the research is to study how cancer cells survive by hijacking normal biological signals like growth cues, stress responses and immune pathways. The novelty scientists found was that CBD doesn’t seem to target just one of these systems and instead nudges several of them at once, pushing cancer cells toward collapse through overlapping and complementary effects.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In colon cancer models, for example, CBD interferes with a receptor called GPR55, which helps tumors grow and migrate. Blocking that receptor weakens a pathway cancer cells rely on to divide quickly, and in some cases makes tumors more responsive to chemotherapy. Other experiments show CBD dialing down genes linked to aggressive growth while switching on stress-related pathways that slow things down.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lung and breast cancers appear to respond in related but slightly different ways. In non-small cell lung cancer, combinations of CBD and THC reduce tumor growth by interfering with epithelial-mesenchymal transition, the process that allows cancer cells to spread. In breast cancer models, CBD has been shown to stop cells mid-cycle, trigger programmed cell death and activate autophagy, the cell’s internal recycling system turned destructive.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Cannabidiol (CBD), an FDA-approved and well-tolerated compound, demonstrates promising antitumor effects by inhibiting cancer growth, metastasis, and angiogenesis, while also alleviating cancer-related symptoms such as pain and nausea.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are also practical challenges, however. CBD is poorly absorbed when taken by mouth and is heavily metabolized, which means only a fraction may reach tumor tissue. To get around this, scientists are exploring nanoparticle-based delivery systems designed to improve absorption, target tumors more precisely and minimize side effects.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Looking ahead, researchers say progress will depend on careful, methodical work. Tools like single-cell sequencing could help clarify how different tumor populations respond to CBD. Well-designed clinical trials will be essential to determine whether the effects seen in the lab translate into benefits for patients, especially when CBD is used alongside standard treatments.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0944711325013716" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;study’s&lt;/a&gt; authors, who are affiliated with medical schools throughout China, noted the need to further explore the promise of CBD’s anti-tumor properties.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Future trials must stratify patients by tumor type and molecular markers to establish correlations between dosing, timing, and efficacy,” they wrote. The paper, which was not peer reviewed, was published in the December 2025 issue of the scientific journal Phytomedicine.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The new study follows a series of encouraging discoveries related to CBD’s properties.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In 2025, for example, a paper published in the journal Pharmacology &amp;amp; Therapeutics, assessed a range of clinical and preclinical findings that &lt;a href="https://www.marijuanamoment.net/medical-marijuana-could-increase-efficacy-of-chemotherapy-to-fight-cancer-while-reducing-side-effects-study-suggests/"&gt;the efficacy of chemotherapy drugs can be enhanced by medical marijuana&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In a sign of greater acceptance of medical applications of cannabis, President Donald Trump’s choice to serve as the next &lt;a href="https://www.marijuanamoment.net/senate-approves-trumps-white-house-drug-czar-pick-who-supports-medical-marijuana-as-rescheduling-looms/"&gt;White House drug czar has called medical marijuana a “fantastic” treatment option for seriously ill patients&lt;/a&gt; and said she doesn’t object to legalization, even if she might not personally agree with the policy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Also last year, a study found that “&lt;a href="https://www.marijuanamoment.net/medical-marijuana-provides-significant-improvements-in-cancer-symptoms-study-shows/"&gt;patients with cancer using cannabis&lt;/a&gt; report significant improvements in cancer-related symptoms.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="cb_p6_patreon_button"&gt;&lt;p class="cb_p6_message_over_post_button"&gt;Marijuana Moment is made possible with support from readers. If you rely on our cannabis advocacy journalism to stay informed, please consider a monthly Patreon pledge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a rel="nofollow" target="_blank" href="https://patreon.com/oauth2/become-patron?response_type=code&amp;amp;min_cents=100&amp;amp;client_id=zPbmyOq8oKTkWV14vdfNn0Jk468BpYoT2NT_tRx_w4Y8-M9OkllZFL8LohxJU1mm&amp;amp;scope=identity%20identity[email]&amp;amp;redirect_uri=https://www.marijuanamoment.net/patreon-authorization/&amp;amp;state=eyJmaW5hbF9yZWRpcmVjdF91cmkiOiJodHRwczpcL1wvd3d3Lm1hcmlqdWFuYW1vbWVudC5uZXRcL2NiZC1oYXMtc3Vic3RhbnRpYWwtcHJvbWlzZS10by1jb21iYXQtdHVtb3JzLWZyb20tY2FuY2VyLXNjaWVudGlmaWMtcmV2aWV3LXNob3dzXC8ifQ%3D%3D&amp;amp;utm_source=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.marijuanamoment.net%2Fcbd-has-substantial-promise-to-combat-tumors-from-cancer-scientific-review-shows%2F&amp;amp;utm_medium=patreon_wordpress_plugin&amp;amp;utm_campaign=749657&amp;amp;utm_term=&amp;amp;utm_content=post_unlock_button" aria-label="Click to become a patron at Patreon!"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.marijuanamoment.net/wp-content/plugins/patron-plugin-pro/plugin/lib/patron-button-and-widgets-by-codebard/images/become_a_patron_button.png" alt="Become a patron at Patreon!" loading="lazy" fetchpriority="low"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;																											&lt;/div&gt;
													&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Marijuana Moment</author><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 16:18:15 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiswFBVV95cUxONUtEZFp5T2FoWUlScGMxQUNhYkNrZWNNTERWVjU2N2w5UjVoR29vQmV4Nm1oTzNPOWpwLTFPLVpIblBBV0JYb2ZoWlZzM0FCdTlKNDFnNE93MnJnTGpTMkJvZ0t5SzJ6aVY3ZDFUTmNBVkRyOEN6Rk1vNHRoVFh5SGtsZEw5NlJwYmthQXZocjJlS1BaanI0SGFkZXdnS1NaVEpacXBkb0xYTmk5S25fTXFyUQ</guid></item><item><title>孟菲斯国际机场确诊麻疹病例，卫生部门表示- WREG.com</title><link>https://wreg.com/news/local/measles-case-confirmed-at-memphis-international-airport/</link><description>&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;
    
    
    &lt;noscript&gt;
      
    &lt;/noscript&gt;
  &lt;/body&gt;
</description><author>WREG.com</author><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 15:54:56 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijAFBVV95cUxQaFdOQU1teDlfWjRzZVFHdTJ3MjN6QktzbTZuVGFPeWpZNkItMDgwcHhTZHRHckFqX1doOHBrYjlLME5odXpkdEdFVlNEVHRrSTBBcUNLSFZPYTBzbjcwUTRxWE1JUHVDX3EyWmZiSHNId3RWT1JnU290TFkxMUpYMEdfZFYyNmVKcWNlWtIBkgFBVV95cUxPektmRDBubm83MElTWVl0cUpVT3RzRmFkS3lkS3N5VjhKSVY1Q0FZMF9jcmlpSjllLTRJWjU4LXVZdVltRjRRVVREb3lHWlg0akRmWmpXc2pldTVxSE1NTWtTZVNFT3VDTWVwVFBnbmdUZ3A3SHh1d0VwUHhVS1BmaGd1US1hNmppc0FaSUF3WDg2UQ</guid></item></channel></rss>