<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>GNews Health</title><link>https://news.google.com/</link><description></description><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>疫苗对老年人的帮助超过我们所知道的-《纽约时报》</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2026/01/03/health/vaccines-dementia-heart-elderly.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The New York Times</author><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 10:01:47 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihAFBVV95cUxNdHd0THJVQ0Y2Z1ZHUjZwbzlmT2VzbkZuWl95SkJaVU1WNVl4RWVtWDZFWWVOYjhnLVY1YVZYNUdDeU1fOGhIU2dkalNuZF9tMVpMM1BicE5GaDA4Q3NtMmI5Nk8wY21uQ3ZhY2RRQWRZX2FtRVRjTm9jVmNRV1lIY2txREo</guid></item><item><title>科学家测试了间歇性禁食而不减少进食，发现没有代谢益处- ScienceDaily</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/12/251228020018.htm</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p id="first" class="lead"&gt;A new study from the German Institute of Human Nutrition Potsdam-Rehbruecke (DIfE) and Charité -- Universitätsmedizin Berlin challenges a widely held belief about intermittent fasting. The research shows that time-restricted eating does not lead to measurable improvements in metabolic or cardiovascular health when calorie intake remains unchanged. However, the timing of meals did affect the body's internal clocks. These findings come from the ChronoFast study led by Prof. Olga Ramich and were published in &lt;em&gt;Science Translational Medicine&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

						&lt;div id="text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Time-restricted eating (TRE) is a form of intermittent fasting that limits daily food intake to a window of no more than ten hours, followed by a fasting period of at least 14 hours. The approach has become popular as a simple strategy to support weight management and metabolic health. Animal studies show that TRE can protect rodents from diet-related obesity and metabolic problems. In humans, earlier studies have reported benefits such as improved insulin sensitivity, healthier blood sugar and cholesterol levels, and modest reductions in body weight and body fat. As a result, TRE has been widely viewed as a promising tool for preventing insulin resistance and diabetes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Conflicting Evidence From Earlier Studies&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Despite its popularity, past research on TRE has produced mixed results. Many studies have not been able to determine whether observed health improvements came from shorter eating windows, unintentional calorie reduction, or a combination of both. In addition, most earlier trials did not carefully track calorie intake or control for other factors that could influence metabolic outcomes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To address these gaps, Prof. Olga Ramich, Head of the Department of Molecular Metabolism and Precision Nutrition at the DIfE and Professor at the Charité -- Universitätsmedizin Berlin, designed the ChronoFast trial. The goal was to test whether an eight-hour eating window could improve insulin sensitivity and other metabolic markers when calorie intake was kept constant.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How the ChronoFast Study Was Conducted&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The study used a randomized crossover design and included 31 women with overweight or obesity. Each participant followed two different eating schedules for two weeks at a time. One schedule involved early time-restricted eating between 8 a.m. and 4 p.m.(eTRE). The other followed a later schedule from 1 p.m. to 9 p.m. (lTRE). Throughout both phases, participants ate nearly identical meals with the same calorie and nutrient content (isocaloric).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="insertion_middle"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Researchers collected blood samples during four clinic visits and performed oral glucose tolerance tests to assess glucose and fat metabolism. Continuous glucose monitoring tracked blood sugar levels over 24 hours while food intake was recorded in detail. Physical activity was monitored using a motion sensor. In collaboration with Prof. Achim Kramer from the Charité -- Universitätsmedizin Berlin, the team also examined changes in the body's internal clock using isolated blood cells.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Measuring the Body's Internal Clock&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Human biology follows internally generated rhythms that roughly align with the length of a day, which is why they are known as circadian clocks (Latin: circa and dia). These rhythms help regulate nearly every physiological process, including sleep and metabolism. Almost all cells in the body contain their own internal clock, which can be influenced by light, physical activity, and food timing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To measure individual circadian phases, Prof. Dr. Achim Kramer developed the BodyTime assay. This test requires only a single blood sample and provides an objective snapshot of a person's internal timing. The ChronoFast study used this method and confirmed that eating schedules can shift internal clocks in humans.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;No Metabolic Improvements Found&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Despite expectations based on earlier research, the ChronoFast study found no clinically meaningful changes in insulin sensitivity, blood sugar, blood fats, or inflammatory markers after the two-week interventions. "Our results suggest that the health benefits observed in earlier studies were likely due to unintended calorie reduction, rather than the shortened eating period itself," explains Ramich.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="insertion_bottom"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While metabolic measures remained largely unchanged, the timing of meals did affect circadian rhythms. Analysis of blood cells showed that the internal clock shifted by an average of 40 minutes during the late eating schedule compared to the early schedule. Participants following the later eating window also went to bed and woke up later. "The timing of food intake acts as a cue for our biological rhythms -- similar to light," says first author Beeke Peters.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Calories and Individual Timing May Matter Most&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The findings highlight the importance of calorie balance in achieving health benefits from intermittent fasting. "Those who want to lose weight or improve their metabolism should pay attention not only to the clock, but also to their energy balance," Ramich concludes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Future research will need to explore whether combining time-restricted eating with reduced calorie intake produces stronger benefits. Scientists also aim to better understand how individual factors, including chronotype and genetics, may influence how people respond to different eating schedules.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

					&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceDaily</author><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 09:12:25 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMib0FVX3lxTE84YUsxR3ctbW1fSXJTTkxYQzdoc21KaUN0cmN5cnNwbGJPVW8xeWRwN3JaX3ZsYnp1eDM2NkU2WFRvWFRlOWRKSUJsclR0Q0pvbFNscEYxSlAweGw0NjY2QmdjdGtOUU9oUi15eklaNA</guid></item><item><title>在假期交通中，在美国两个主要机场检测到世界上传染性最强的病毒- AOL.com</title><link>https://www.aol.com/articles/worlds-most-contagious-virus-detected-193018261.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="caas-body"&gt;&lt;p&gt;During peak holiday travel, one of the most infectious diseases was detected at Newark Liberty International Airport in New Jersey.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/category/health/measles" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:A case of measles was identified;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;A case of measles was identified&lt;/a&gt; in a passenger at terminals B &amp;amp; C on Dec. 12, according to a New Jersey Department of Health (NJDOH) press release. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Measles symptoms include a high fever, cough, runny nose, watery red eyes, &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/category/health/beauty-and-skin" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:and a rash;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;and a rash&lt;/a&gt; that usually appears between three and five days after symptoms begin," the release says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/travel/holiday-travel-plans-could-ruined-you-wear-particular-item-airport" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Your Holiday Travel Plans Could Be Ruined If You Wear One Particular Item To The Airport;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Your Holiday Travel Plans Could Be Ruined If You Wear One Particular Item To The Airport&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The rash usually begins as flat red spots that appear on the face at the hairline and spread downward to the neck, torso, arms, legs and feet."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The airborne virus can spread when someone coughs or sneezes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://foxnews.onelink.me/xLDS/mvaj7wvj" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Read On The Fox News App;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;Read On The Fox News App&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure align-caption-with-image"&gt;&lt;div class="no-margin"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="caption-wrapper"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption-collapse"&gt;Measles was detected at Newark Liberty International Airport on Dec. 12.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Measles can stay in the air for up to two hours after an &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/category/health/infectious-disease" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:infected person;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;infected person&lt;/a&gt; leaves the area.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Officials are asking those who suspect exposure or illness to &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/category/health/health-care" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:call their health provider;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;call their health provider&lt;/a&gt; before visiting a medical care center or hospital.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/newsletters?cmpid=fnfirstnl" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Click Here To Sign Up For Our Lifestyle Newsletter;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Click Here To Sign Up For Our Lifestyle Newsletter&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"NJDOH is working in collaboration with local health officials on ongoing contact tracing and on efforts to notify people who might have been exposed and to identify additional exposures that may have occurred," says the release.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The New Jersey Department of Health says individuals at risk include those who have not been fully vaccinated or have not had measles in the past.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure align-caption-with-image"&gt;&lt;div class="no-margin"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="caption-wrapper"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption-collapse"&gt;Measles can stay in the air for up to two hours after an infected person leaves the area.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;This year, there have been &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/health/major-measles-outbreak-leads-hundreds-quarantined-us-county-officials-say" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:11 confirmed cases of measles;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;11 confirmed cases of measles&lt;/a&gt; in New Jersey, according to NJDOH.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A record 8.03 million travelers are expected to &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/category/travel/general/travel-safety" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:fly across America this holiday season;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;fly across America this holiday season&lt;/a&gt;, according to AAA.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/lifestyle" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Click Here For More Lifestyle Stories;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Click Here For More Lifestyle Stories&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Massachusetts Department of Public Health (DPH) also confirmed on Christmas Eve that a visitor from Texas was diagnosed with measles.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The traveler flew into &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/category/us/boston" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Boston Logan International Airport;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Boston Logan International Airport&lt;/a&gt; on American Airlines flight 2384 from Dallas-Fort Worth and was in terminal B, according to a DPH press release.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure align-caption-with-image"&gt;&lt;div class="no-margin"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="caption-wrapper"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption-collapse"&gt;As of Dec. 23, there have been 2,012 measles cases in the U.S., the CDC says.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;As of Dec. 23, there have been 2,012 measles cases in the U.S., according to the CDC.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/category/lifestyle/quizzes" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Test Yourself With Our Latest Lifestyle Quiz;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Test Yourself With Our Latest Lifestyle Quiz&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The single best way to protect your children and yourself from measles &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/health/major-measles-outbreak-leads-hundreds-quarantined-us-county-officials-say" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:is to be vaccinated;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;is to be vaccinated&lt;/a&gt;," Connecticut's DPH Commissioner Manisha Juthani, M.D., wrote in a statement, as Fox News Digital recently reported.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://foxnews.onelink.me/xLDS?pid=AppArticleLink&amp;amp;af_dp=foxnewsaf%3A%2F%2F&amp;amp;af_web_dp=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.foxnews.com%2Fapps-products" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Click Here To Download The Fox News App;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Click Here To Download The Fox News App&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"One dose of measles vaccine is about 93% effective, while two doses are about 97% effective."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Angelica Stabile of Fox News Digital contributed reporting.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Original article source:&lt;/em&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/travel/worlds-most-contagious-virus-detected-two-major-us-airports-amid-holiday-traffic" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:World's most contagious virus detected at two major US airports amid holiday traffic;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;World's most contagious virus detected at two major US airports amid holiday traffic&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>AOL.com</author><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 08:01:39 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiAFBVV95cUxPd2oyOXpmRUVsOTg2SXMtYm9mUU1sNWloWk85ZFpoRk1OZzJUWlM0dXRza05Cam93ZlN0ejRoUjk4M1o4bDN1ZF9iZzRmeWh0M29iNGExaGItU1dYYU1idnJKU0k4WXVhOF93c1AyVGFuOGdqSUhPcW5hdDd1R1V3ZEs4S21NNVNW</guid></item><item><title>一位通过饮食降低胆固醇的营养学家分享了4个简单的摄入更多纤维的建议- Business Insider</title><link>https://www.businessinsider.com/nutritionist-lowered-cholesterol-4-simple-ways-eat-more-fiber-2026-1</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;section class="post-body-content post-story-body-content" data-component-type="post-body-content" data-load-strategy="exclude" data-track-content="" data-post-type="story" data-track-marfeel="post-body-content"&gt;
            
                &lt;p&gt;When &lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.businessinsider.com/nutritionist-eats-high-protein-diet-without-ultra-processed-foods-2025-12" data-track-click='{"element_name":"body_link","event":"tout_click","index":"bi_value_unassigned","product_field":"bi_value_unassigned"}' rel=""&gt;Rob Hobson&lt;/a&gt;, a registered nutritionist based in the UK, found out his cholesterol levels were "really high" in June, he decided to manage them through diet, focusing particularly on increasing his fiber intake.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Six months later, when he tested again, his &lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.businessinsider.com/chickpea-recipes-to-lower-cholesterol-science-backed-advice-2025-7" data-track-click='{"element_name":"body_link","event":"tout_click","index":"bi_value_unassigned","product_field":"bi_value_unassigned"}' rel=""&gt;cholesterol levels&lt;/a&gt; had improved, and he'd discovered four tricks that make eating more fiber easy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cholesterol is a fatty substance the body needs for many bodily processes, but if a person has too much LDL or "bad" cholesterol, it can form sticky plaque in their arteries, putting them at greater risk of &lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.businessinsider.com/habits-that-look-healthy-heart-disease-failure-stroke-inflammation-2025-7" data-track-click='{"element_name":"body_link","event":"tout_click","index":"bi_value_unassigned","product_field":"bi_value_unassigned"}' rel=""&gt;cardiovascular disease&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To reduce cholesterol levels, the American Heart Association recommends exercising at least 150 minutes a week, quitting smoking and vaping, maintaining a healthy weight, and eating a heart-healthy diet that's low in saturated fats and high in fiber. If these measures don't help, then statins, a medication that lowers LDL cholesterol, will likely be prescribed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hobson, the author of "Unprocess Your Life" and "The Low Appetite Cookbook," already worked out for around an hour each morning, and ate &lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.businessinsider.com/habits-that-look-healthy-heart-disease-failure-stroke-inflammation-2025-7" data-track-click='{"element_name":"body_link","event":"tout_click","index":"bi_value_unassigned","product_field":"bi_value_unassigned"}' rel=""&gt;minimal ultra-processed foods&lt;/a&gt; and saturated fats. So he zeroed in on fiber.&lt;/p&gt;
              
            
              
            &lt;p&gt;Eating at least 5 to 10 grams of soluble fiber a day can help lower total cholesterol and LDL cholesterol, according to the National Lipid Association. Quinoa, oats, avocado, sweet potatoes, carrots, and chia or flax seeds are good examples.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Here are Hobson's tips for seamlessly adding more fiber to your diet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="1a4aa01f-6ea0-4848-8371-896ad3e1f530" data-toc-id="1a4aa01f-6ea0-4848-8371-896ad3e1f530"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Eat breakfast&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hobson is a big advocate of breakfast because it lends itself to high-fiber foods such as oats, nuts, and seeds. "It's really easy to get plenty of fiber in at that time of day," he told Business Insider.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He has two go-to breakfasts that he eats on repeat. The first is a &lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.businessinsider.com/quick-easy-high-protein-high-fiber-breakfast-every-morning-2025-11" data-track-click='{"element_name":"body_link","event":"tout_click","index":"bi_value_unassigned","product_field":"bi_value_unassigned"}' rel=""&gt;Greek yogurt bowl&lt;/a&gt; with berries, oats, and chia seeds. The second is overnight oats, which he makes with milk, protein powder, berries, honey, nuts, and seeds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="16694455-4bae-4acc-a454-c4db8f5516a8" data-toc-id="16694455-4bae-4acc-a454-c4db8f5516a8"&gt;Fiber cupboard&lt;/h2&gt;
              &lt;figure class="figure image-figure-image   " data-type="img" data-e2e-name="image-figure-image" data-media-container="image" itemscope="" itemtype="https://schema.org/ImageObject"&gt;
              
              
                
              
              &lt;span class="image-source-caption "&gt;
                    &lt;figcaption class="image-caption headline-semibold" data-e2e-name="image-caption"&gt;
                      Rob Hobson's fiber cupboard.
                      
              &lt;span class="image-source headline-regular" data-e2e-name="image-source" itemprop="creditText"&gt;
              
              Rob Hobson
              
              &lt;/span&gt;
                    &lt;/figcaption&gt;
                  &lt;/span&gt;
              &lt;/figure&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;Hobson created a "fiber cupboard" in his kitchen that's packed with fibrous foods. He challenges himself to include something from the cupboard in every meal. "Then at least you know that you are making the effort to do it," he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He stocks up on &lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.businessinsider.com/3-ways-add-beans-meals-protein-fiber-private-chef-2025-11" data-track-click='{"element_name":"body_link","event":"tout_click","index":"bi_value_unassigned","product_field":"bi_value_unassigned"}' rel=""&gt;lentils, beans, pulses&lt;/a&gt;, wholegrain pasta, brown rice, as well as snacks like fruit and nut bars, rye crackers that he likes to pair with some cottage cheese, and seaweed thins.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I'm always rooting around for stuff, and I just think having it all in one place is so much easier," he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="8e599fc6-b8d1-4acf-8b7c-eeb1438c25f3" data-toc-id="8e599fc6-b8d1-4acf-8b7c-eeb1438c25f3"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Add pulses and legumes to your meal and put the rest into a Tupperware in the fridge&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The easiest way to add fiber to a meal is to pour half a can of beans or pulses into it, Hobson said. Just one &lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.businessinsider.com/recipes-black-beans-to-reduce-inflammation-2025-7" data-track-click='{"element_name":"body_link","event":"tout_click","index":"bi_value_unassigned","product_field":"bi_value_unassigned"}' rel=""&gt;cup of black beans&lt;/a&gt;, for example, contains 15 grams of fiber. "You can add them to anything," he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mix some into a soup, sauce, or curry, or simply sprinkle a couple of tablespoons on top of a salad.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you're not using the whole can, decant the rest into a Tupperware and place it in the fridge, Hobson said. That way, they'll stay fresher for longer and be easily accessible. "Then you don't have to worry about, 'I'm going to waste the rest of the tin,'" he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="140201b5-2f70-454c-af06-f674067ade72" data-toc-id="140201b5-2f70-454c-af06-f674067ade72"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Keep the food you want to eat visible&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hobson recommends keeping the foods you want to eat in a visible spot. That way, you're more likely to reach for them. "Nuts and seeds, always keep them on the side so they're there," he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Research suggests that the foods you keep on your countertop could impact your body weight, a factor that can influence cholesterol levels. In a 2015 study published in &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://journals.sagepub.com/doi/10.1177/1090198115610571" data-track-click='{"click_type":"other","element_name":"body_link","event":"outbound_click"}' rel=" nofollow"&gt;Sage Journals&lt;/a&gt;, researchers at Cornell University analyzed the visible foods on 210 countertops in New York and measured their owners' BMIs. They found that those who had just fresh fruit visible weighed an average of 20 pounds less than those who had unhealthier snacks like candy, soda, and cereals on show.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It's your basic See-Food Diet — you eat what you see," Brian Wansink, the study's lead author, said of the findings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But if you're not ready to make changes to your kitchen layout, Hobson said to stick to one basic principle: "Make sure that you've got a bit of fiber on your plate every day with every meal," he said.&lt;/p&gt;
            
            
            &lt;/section&gt;
            
            
            
            
            
            
    
    
    
    
      &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Business Insider</author><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 07:07:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiogFBVV95cUxObFJERnZrbmgwUmg4aHZDUF85Y2pQSGR6cGVxaF9ZUmxLRUVaYnZtUTNCM19jbUphYkI4ejZIQTFvYV8wWng1X2RCcmRwZ3ZVVWZRMW9qX3pMamdMVFBZR2JvY0pQWFlsdzNKU2cwNEpsUzM4NmhOWDdISjZnalNFWXlxbDZsamhzQ0lIakVoVDRWV2JsZjNVOFFMc19PV0NjckE</guid></item><item><title>随着俄亥俄州青少年的死亡，流感病例在山谷中上升- WFMJ.com</title><link>https://www.wfmj.com/story/53350181/as-ohio-teen-dies-flu-cases-rise-in-the-valley</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="Article-paragraph" data-reactid="419"&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the Mahoning Valley, hospitalizations are rising as the winter season continues. During the week ending Dec. 27, 2025, Mahoning County reported 34 people hospitalized for the flu. Trumbull County had 17 hospitalizations, and Columbiana County had four. These figures represent an increase from the previous week in all three counties.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>WFMJ.com</author><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 02:37:30 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiigFBVV95cUxQN0J4WktfWnNPTzFJQ0tQYjEwcklWbk1jZ0FjUmx3QW44MUNhb25fejc3YmhPeml3REdnS05nTU9QWGxoUnlXdkFpdDRGMmdHcXF1UDBTbkM2dktYZGFqV3JMUDZCMUp1dlhEejBaMVdzbTZQSDdzX2NHZFNGSEZyeDJ4Y2NFbnVtVUE</guid></item><item><title>想要改善肠道-大脑连接吗？营养师分享发酵食品如何帮助|健康-印度斯坦时报</title><link>https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/want-to-improve-gut-brain-connection-dietician-shares-how-fermented-foods-help-101767362368582.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="detail " dataid="/lifestyle/health/want-to-improve-gut-brain-connection-dietician-shares-how-fermented-foods-help-101767362368582.html"&gt; &lt;div class="storyParagraphFigure"&gt; &lt;p&gt;The &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/aiims-trained-gastroenterologist-says-scrolling-before-bed-disrupts-gut-brain-axis-shares-6-sleep-mistakes-101761482862378.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="gut-brain"&gt;gut-brain&lt;/a&gt; link is a two-way connection in which the gut and the brain influence each other. It shows that the gut is responsible for much more than just digestion. &lt;span class="highlight"&gt;This highlights the need for a more well-rounded approach to nutrition, one that supports vital two-way connections such as the gut-brain, gut-skin and gut-immune axes.&lt;/span&gt; For now, let's focus on the gut-brain connection and explore which foods can help strengthen it and support overall health.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;figure class=""&gt; &lt;span class=""&gt; &lt;picture&gt; &lt;source media="(max-width:767px)" srcset="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2026/01/02/550x309/gut_health__1767363891014_1767363891161.jpg" alt="The gut is closely connected to the brain, so know which foods help to strengthen this connection. (Shutterstock)" title="The gut is closely connected to the brain, so know which foods help to strengthen this connection. (Shutterstock)"&gt;&lt;/source&gt; &lt;img src="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2026/01/02/550x309/gut_health__1767363891014_1767363891161.jpg" alt="The gut is closely connected to the brain, so know which foods help to strengthen this connection. (Shutterstock)" title="The gut is closely connected to the brain, so know which foods help to strengthen this connection. (Shutterstock)"&gt; &lt;/picture&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;figcaption&gt;The gut is closely connected to the brain, so know which foods help to strengthen this connection. (Shutterstock)&lt;/figcaption&gt; &lt;/figure&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;p id="readMoreFTUser"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;ALSO READ: &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/gastroenterologist-explains-disorder-of-gut-brain-interaction-shares-5-ways-stress-impacts-gut-health-101750736498153.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="Gastroenterologist explains disorder of gut-brain interaction; shares 5 ways stress impacts gut health"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Gastroenterologist explains disorder of gut-brain interaction; shares 5 ways stress impacts gut health&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="mt-10 mb-10 htEchoRecirculationWidget"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="mt10 mb10 htEchoArticlePromo"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="predictorShow mb20" data-vars-predictor="true" data-vars-quiz="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="quizShow mb20" data-vars-minimized="false" data-vars-predictor="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Tehseen Siddiqui, Chief Dietitian, Saifee Hospital, Mumbai, shared with HT Lifestyle that fermented foods help to support gut health. She explained their benefits and listed the key sources.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;Why should you eat fermented foods?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to the dietician, fermented foods are packed with probiotics. &lt;span class="highlight"&gt;They support beneficial gut bacteria and help maintain a healthy balance in the digestive system, while also facilitating key gut functions such as digestion and nutrient absorption.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="highlight"&gt;She also reminded that nearly 70 per cent of the immune system is linked to the gut, making it a critical line of defence against infections and inflammation.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;But beyond digestive and immune health, gut microbes also influence brain activity, mood and emotional regulation through the gut-brain axis. Tehseen shared that when gut health is well-balanced, which fermented foods help achieve, brain functions such as mood, stress regulation, and sleep also improve.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;Fermented food sources&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;h2&gt; &lt;/h2&gt; &lt;figure class="inlineIMG"&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;img data-src="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/05/02/original/bowl-with-yogurt-berries-high-angle_1746163634504.jpg" class="lazy" src="https://images.hindustantimes.com/default/550x309.jpg" alt="Add fermented foods like unsweetened yoghurt to diet. (Freepik)" title="Add fermented foods like unsweetened yoghurt to diet. (Freepik)"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;figcaption&gt;Add fermented foods like unsweetened yoghurt to diet. (Freepik)&lt;/figcaption&gt; &lt;/figure&gt; &lt;p&gt;Adding fermented food to your diet is actually easy. The dietician disclosed that it does not have to be complicated. She shared, “Starting with small portions of unsweetened yoghurt, kefir, sauerkraut, fermented vegetables, or traditional foods like curd and buttermilk can be effective.”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Moreover, she revealed that fermented foods can be consumed by adding them to meals and smoothies. When consumed regularly, they help maintain a healthy balance of gut bacteria, while also supporting digestion and immunity.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Note to readers: This article is for informational purposes only and not a substitute for professional medical advice. Always seek the advice of your doctor with any questions about a medical condition.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Hindustan Times</author><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 01:56:30 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi4AFBVV95cUxPc2JfOUo5d3hXSmw0TkpDZDExREl5dkNYODZNZnVvZmZCSkpiWlhZV1oxYnBVVV82YzYzRFo1WU9PQ01tc19UYWJ4aW9uN1llOWNMbXlKT1QxVXBFM3g1c3BhWjVEX25oSXdzTVZmSnVPZG96SFE2TVlGeGJ0dlJocktfRkNyZmNuekxJWWtqcF8xWHUxZWtuT2JKOWI1S0RvRjgtcGJkVzNLZktYY01NS01GX3Vaa1haWEJjSzNmM0FfeTFmYWZxczFEbUdfSWFUR2ZxTTM0Q1g5N3hXUk1mTtIB5gFBVV95cUxPOFlvQTNJbUljblRKN3BHS2RaenhjZkNZZGdWMlMxWGJrVVYtR3NNSFVzQk1xd3piU2p5UF9ickZvWFl2YVQtdWZWd08tTnpLZWkzSUEzYXJxQko4Umx4LVdrSFRpbTc4eGpNSlN6NTJpZTIzUTNjbXNuaW1hRE1ObS13T1hldWdfeE1sOTBEa2l2UVlIZnJqVVdORXZ3dGw3Q1F0eWlxZDVDZGpKenVMYzFsX1hVcmM1WlB1eFlhbTFKTHB1VVdONFpkbFFzZ2xQUWpXSlJOc1pCWnI0OGZ3VUVNSnR1UQ</guid></item><item><title>2026年的幸福感：康复、JOMO和大脑助推器- BBC</title><link>https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/c7v06q91v31o</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article&gt;&lt;p data-component="headline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 hNbOGD"&gt;&lt;h1 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 idLnWK"&gt;Wellbeing 2026: Recovery, JOMO and brain boosting supplements&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="byline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="byline" class="sc-573fa0e8-0 bWRWzH"&gt;&lt;span data-testid="byline-contributors" class="sc-573fa0e8-11 cOQNNv"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="byline-contributors-contributor-0" class="sc-573fa0e8-5 gXJgDY"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="sc-573fa0e8-7 gqeTMs"&gt;Ruth Clegg&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-testid="byline-contributors-contributor-0-role-location" class="sc-573fa0e8-8 bIfajQ"&gt; Health and wellbeing reporter &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 eRlINq"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="hero-image" class="sc-5340b511-1 cMIbKV"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20251210-151139-37baf2dfdd-web-2.36.1-1/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 gUePlo hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/3a5c/live/b4b5cfb0-e7e0-11f0-b67b-690eb873de1b.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/3a5c/live/b4b5cfb0-e7e0-11f0-b67b-690eb873de1b.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/3a5c/live/b4b5cfb0-e7e0-11f0-b67b-690eb873de1b.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/3a5c/live/b4b5cfb0-e7e0-11f0-b67b-690eb873de1b.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/3a5c/live/b4b5cfb0-e7e0-11f0-b67b-690eb873de1b.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/3a5c/live/b4b5cfb0-e7e0-11f0-b67b-690eb873de1b.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/3a5c/live/b4b5cfb0-e7e0-11f0-b67b-690eb873de1b.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/3a5c/live/b4b5cfb0-e7e0-11f0-b67b-690eb873de1b.jpg.webp" loading="eager" alt="Getty Images Young woman looking energetic and vibrant. She has blue tracksuit bottoms and orange crop top and orange hair. She is striding energetically in front of a blue sky" class="sc-5340b511-0 hLdNfA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 jVqbAn"&gt;Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Wellbeing has become such a priceless (or in many cases pricey) endeavour that we can't seem to get enough of it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Last year, we were mainlining magnesium, consuming creatine - a muscle boosting supplement that became mainstream, and we turned to AI chatbots for help with anything from a personalised training regime to a daily meal plan.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;And, that's against a backdrop of more than a million people paying privately for weight loss drugs, in some cases completely transforming their relationship with food and exercise.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;What is the multi-trillion pound industry focussing on in 2026? Several experts give us their thoughts on what's on the wellbeing agenda.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 hNbOGD"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 gXmhTb"&gt;Recovery&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;If 2025 was about smashing targets at the gym, tracking runs to the second and lifting heavier and heavier weights, then this year is all about recovery.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Jak Phillips, a growth director from global fitness brand Les Mills, says it's no longer about no pain no gain, something that "fitness has built on for years".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"Technology has made us so much smarter now," he says. "It's no longer about training ourselves into the ground."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;He says smartwatches have revolutionised our understanding of what it means to be fit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;By tracking our movement and our heart rate they tell us when to have rest days, warn us if we have trained too hard and highlight days when our fitness levels are "peaking".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"Now we have more data and understanding of our wellbeing - we can give ourselves a break."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Factor in rest days, reframe them as a way of staying fit, rather than "taking time off", he says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 gXrNRM"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 cMIbKV"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20251210-151139-37baf2dfdd-web-2.36.1-1/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 gUePlo hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/5a95/live/efdaba80-e7ed-11f0-aae2-2191c0e48a3b.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/5a95/live/efdaba80-e7ed-11f0-aae2-2191c0e48a3b.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/5a95/live/efdaba80-e7ed-11f0-aae2-2191c0e48a3b.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/5a95/live/efdaba80-e7ed-11f0-aae2-2191c0e48a3b.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/5a95/live/efdaba80-e7ed-11f0-aae2-2191c0e48a3b.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/5a95/live/efdaba80-e7ed-11f0-aae2-2191c0e48a3b.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/5a95/live/efdaba80-e7ed-11f0-aae2-2191c0e48a3b.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/5a95/live/efdaba80-e7ed-11f0-aae2-2191c0e48a3b.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Getty Images Young women chatting and getting ready" class="sc-5340b511-0 hLdNfA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 jVqbAn"&gt;Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;Recovery is just as important as scheduling training sessions in the week&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;And with that, a relatively new acronym will begin to seep into our consciousness, Mr Phillips predicts. This year will be about JOMO instead of FOMO.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"So many of us can relate to FOMO - the Fear Of Missing Out - but what if we stop trying to keep across everything?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"Why don't we experience JOMO - the Joy Of Missing Out?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;FOMO was first recognised by the Oxford Dictionary back in 2004, where we compare our lives to others, and put pressure on ourselves to keep up in a world that's often been created by our sparkling, shiny socials.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Now, more than 20 years later, a counter movement is growing to reduce the anxiety that often comes with worrying about what others are doing and trying not to spread ourselves too thinly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;It's not just as simple as saying no to things, Mr Phillips says, it's about learning to be more comfortable in ourselves and not needing external validation for how we choose to live our lives - whether that's the frequency of our workouts or how often we socialise.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"It's about understanding what's right for you, and not feeling guilt or shame for prioritising yourself," he says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 hNbOGD"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 gXmhTb"&gt;Brain boosting&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"Boosting, that's the key word here," Rachel Chatterton, a product director at Holland Barrett explains.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"Our customers are super interested in anything that gives them a boost - and this year will be about boosting their brain power."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Nootropics, supplements which purportedly enhance cognition which are sometimes referred to as "smart drugs", have been around for decades, but it's only in the past few years that their appeal has really taken off.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;These should not be confused with regulated pharmaceutical drugs which can help with conditions like ADHD, narcolepsy and Alzheimer's disease and should only be taken with a diagnosed medical condition.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;By 2030, the likes of &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC10675414/" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;lion's mane&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://ods.od.nih.gov/factsheets/Ashwagandha-HealthProfessional/" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;ashwagandha&lt;/a&gt; and&lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0271531724001684" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt; L-theanine&lt;/a&gt; could be &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.pharmiweb.com/press-release/2024-03-25/nootropics-market-poised-for-remarkable-growth-to-surpass-usd-137-billion-by-2032-enabling-112#:~:text=Nootropics%20Market%20Poised%20For%20Remarkable%2Cmemory%2C%20creativity%2C%20and%20motivation." class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;commanding an $11bn (£8bn) size slice&lt;/a&gt; of the wellbeing market.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;There may only be a number of small studies that suggest these supplements can improve cognition, enhance memory and reduce stress but Ms Chatterton says the market, especially among Gen Z, is booming.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 gXrNRM"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 cMIbKV"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20251210-151139-37baf2dfdd-web-2.36.1-1/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 gUePlo hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/a71e/live/60faab50-e800-11f0-b67b-690eb873de1b.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/a71e/live/60faab50-e800-11f0-b67b-690eb873de1b.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/a71e/live/60faab50-e800-11f0-b67b-690eb873de1b.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/a71e/live/60faab50-e800-11f0-b67b-690eb873de1b.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/a71e/live/60faab50-e800-11f0-b67b-690eb873de1b.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/a71e/live/60faab50-e800-11f0-b67b-690eb873de1b.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/a71e/live/60faab50-e800-11f0-b67b-690eb873de1b.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/a71e/live/60faab50-e800-11f0-b67b-690eb873de1b.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Getty Images Medicinal mushroom powders. Four different types of mushroom powders on spoons with the various mushroom types around them on a black slate" class="sc-5340b511-0 hLdNfA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 jVqbAn"&gt;Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;Nootropics have been around for years but it's only recently that they've really taken off&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"They are so much more interested in health than any other generation and I think that's driving a quite significant movement in terms of preventative health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"They are really thinking about how they can look after their brain at every life stage."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;And many of us might start "supplement stacking through the day," she suggests. "Not necessarily swapping any in or out, but mixing magnesium with lion's mane, for example."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;But boosting our brains does not end there, millions of us are downloading brain training apps to improve our processing speed, memory and to try to protect the 86 billion neurons we have stored in our heads - and as a way, we are told, of staying mentally resilient in the age of artificial intelligence.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Lifestyle GP, Dr Alex Maxwell, is not convinced by the purported power of nootropics and brain training.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"You're going to get much more bang for your buck by increasing the amount you sleep, that's a great brain protector, managing your cardiovascular and metabolic health through exercise - they are the kind of things that will help and are proven to help."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Nootropics have limited evidence they work on the general healthy population, he says, and taking a bit of a lion's mane, for example, is not going to get to the root cause of why someone is not getting enough sleep or help them feel less stressed in the long term.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 gXrNRM"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 cMIbKV"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20251210-151139-37baf2dfdd-web-2.36.1-1/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 gUePlo hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/bca6/live/e4764bc0-e7ff-11f0-b67b-690eb873de1b.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/bca6/live/e4764bc0-e7ff-11f0-b67b-690eb873de1b.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/bca6/live/e4764bc0-e7ff-11f0-b67b-690eb873de1b.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/bca6/live/e4764bc0-e7ff-11f0-b67b-690eb873de1b.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/bca6/live/e4764bc0-e7ff-11f0-b67b-690eb873de1b.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/bca6/live/e4764bc0-e7ff-11f0-b67b-690eb873de1b.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/bca6/live/e4764bc0-e7ff-11f0-b67b-690eb873de1b.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/bca6/live/e4764bc0-e7ff-11f0-b67b-690eb873de1b.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Getty Images A young man eating a healthy salad" class="sc-5340b511-0 hLdNfA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 jVqbAn"&gt;Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;Lifestyle GPs recommend going "back to basics" eating fresh food, sleeping and regular exercise&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 hNbOGD"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 gXmhTb"&gt;Nervous systems&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;So how can we cope with the stresses that this year will inevitably throw at us? If there's one nerve you want to touch in 2026 - it's the vagus nerve.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;As we begin to understand the vital role our nervous system plays in our ability to manage to stress, there is a growing body of evidence that the &lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/articles/cy0k9yz5wexo" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;vagus nerve might hold the key.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;TV doctor, GP Zoe Williams believes that by hacking into the nerve - known as the body's super highway - we can calm down more quickly in stressful situations and build up a level of stress resilience.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"Whether it's a work deadline or comparing yourself to somebody on social media or having an argument with your partner or missing the bus, they're all little doses of stress our body wasn't designed for," she explains.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 gXrNRM"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 cMIbKV"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20251210-151139-37baf2dfdd-web-2.36.1-1/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 gUePlo hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/60e0/live/dcdf73b0-e7f9-11f0-aae2-2191c0e48a3b.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/60e0/live/dcdf73b0-e7f9-11f0-aae2-2191c0e48a3b.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/60e0/live/dcdf73b0-e7f9-11f0-aae2-2191c0e48a3b.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/60e0/live/dcdf73b0-e7f9-11f0-aae2-2191c0e48a3b.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/60e0/live/dcdf73b0-e7f9-11f0-aae2-2191c0e48a3b.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/60e0/live/dcdf73b0-e7f9-11f0-aae2-2191c0e48a3b.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/60e0/live/dcdf73b0-e7f9-11f0-aae2-2191c0e48a3b.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/60e0/live/dcdf73b0-e7f9-11f0-aae2-2191c0e48a3b.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Getty Images Young female splashing face with water " class="sc-5340b511-0 hLdNfA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 jVqbAn"&gt;Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;Cold water therapy may stimulate the vagus nerve and lower your heart rate&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;She recommends several simple techniques which can help us activate it, to kick start our parasympathetic nervous system and put the brakes on the "fight or flight" situation many of us might find ourselves in on a daily basis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Techniques which can help activate the vagus nerve:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class="sc-6f869981-0 diUlgm"&gt;&lt;li class="sc-734a601e-0 cRgahm"&gt;Being aware of our breathing, Dr Williams recommends the "physiological sigh" which consists of two sharp intakes of breath followed by one long exhale&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="sc-734a601e-0 cRgahm"&gt;Cold water therapy - splashing cold water on your face can help lower your heart rate, and stimulate the vagus nerve&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="sc-734a601e-0 cRgahm"&gt;If you want to spend a few hundred pounds you could invest in a vagus nerve stimulator, small devices which are worn round the neck or clipped on the ear which gently vibrate&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 hNbOGD"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 gXmhTb"&gt;Back to basics?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Dr Maxwell says "back to basics" is his key wellness theme - eat well, sleep and move - those three things are key to being healthy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;He warns simplicity can sometimes be best, as some people are taking monitoring their daily lives to the extreme with life logging. You can now log your entire day using a new wearable AI device that constantly records audio. It lets you know who you have met, what you chatted about, summarises the exchange and basically gives you a rundown of the rich tapestry of your day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;What's not to love?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Dr Maxwell shakes his head as I give him this example.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"Sounds positively petrifying," he says. "Tech should be your servant, not your master.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"Do the research and check what evidence is behind these new trends," he recommends. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"Wellbeing should be a personal choice, and what works for one person might not necessarily work for you."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BBC</author><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 01:19:15 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiWkFVX3lxTE9kejJ1cElZYjVHanF4NHFXdjZWT25jZUtpQjhVVzVXUnU1c0JqLVpDa2hkaHhDT0ZLb2huOHpDckVqSnZWRi05MV9EejVsaE1sOGxOV2lRNC03UdIBX0FVX3lxTE5zczJEWTk0Vng0Q1hIeFo4QURXWExBU1EzbGtlMzlnalA1RUUwbjlBZVhnUlhDNmh1NzViS3pqcjVVWWdfby01WGxhbWs1V1p1a011eHdZUnZPdVdZVnJB</guid></item><item><title>把错误的东西倒进水槽会破坏城市。方法如下。- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/pouring-the-wrong-things-down-your-sink-can-damage-cities-heres-how</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Ever been about to pour rancid milk down the sink and thought…"Hmm, maybe I shouldn't…"? What about the tomato passata that's gone off? Or the water you washed the paint in? Or that pungent oil from a tuna can?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Let's consider the wisdom – or not – of putting everyday items down the plughole.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Unfortunately, they can cause problems by clogging or damaging pipes, creating health hazards and polluting the environment. And they add to the load on wastewater treatment plants.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Where it goes&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;All indoor wastewater is carried through the sewer system. Everything flushed down the toilet or drained from the kitchen sink, bathtub, or shower connects to the same pipes within our home.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/the-hidden-things-lurking-in-sink-drains-can-be-dangerous-even-deadly"&gt;The Hidden Things Lurking in Sink Drains Can Be Dangerous, Even Deadly&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;From there, the water flows into the municipal sewer — the large pipes running beneath backyards or streets — and eventually flows to a wastewater treatment plant. Wastewater treatment plants have large aerated tanks full of bacteria that decompose the organic matter in wastewater.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Chemical oxygen demand" measures how much oxygen is needed to break down organic matter. Every bit of additional matter – from passata to tuna oil – adds to the load. And a higher organic load requires greater aeration and larger tanks, thereby increasing the cost and complexity of operating a wastewater treatment plant.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://images.theconversation.com/files/709827/original/file-20251219-56-e3dt6e.jpg?ixlib=rb-4.1.0&amp;amp;rect=0%2C281%2C6240%2C3510&amp;amp;q=45&amp;amp;auto=format&amp;amp;w=754&amp;amp;fit=clip" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;(&lt;a class="source" href="https://unsplash.com/photos/a-group-of-metal-objects-7tZ006hSgKE"&gt;Mathias Reding/Unsplash&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a class="license" href="http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by/4.0/"&gt;CC BY&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Spilt milk&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Should you pour milk down the sink? Liquid dairy products, or any food item containing fat, oil and grease, including cooking oil, can &lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/listen/programs/melbourne-afternoons/fatberg/105534992"&gt;block sewer pipes&lt;/a&gt;. When oil and grease mix with cool water in wastewater pipes, they harden. Then, they can combine with other waste, such as wet wipes, to form a rock-hard blockage known as a "&lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Fatberg"&gt;fatberg&lt;/a&gt;".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cleaning such blockages is very expensive. For example, in the nine months up to July 2025, Sydney Water spent &lt;a href="https://www.sbs.com.au/news/article/this-is-why-water-utilities-want-you-to-water-your-plants-with-milk/4t2usuonc"&gt;A$12 million&lt;/a&gt; dealing with 11,805 "chokes" in the wastewater system.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Clogged sewers are not just a foul nuisance for the water industry — they are a problem that affects us all. They can trigger the release of raw and &lt;a href="https://www.sydneywater.com.au/water-the-environment/what-you-can-do/avoid-wastewater-overflows.html#:%7E:text=Something%20in%20the%20pipe%20is,contain%20a%20combination%20of%20these."&gt;untreated sewage&lt;/a&gt; into the environment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sbs.com.au/news/article/this-is-why-water-utilities-want-you-to-water-your-plants-with-milk/4t2usuonc"&gt;Sydney Water&lt;/a&gt; suggests people add water to old milk and pour it in moderation on plants, rather than into the sink. Alternatively, milk can be left in its container and put in your rubbish bin.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What about the old and expired sauces, dips and gravy, which often lurk in the fridge at this time of year? These can be &lt;a href="https://www.calgary.ca/waste/what-goes-where/default.html"&gt;composted&lt;/a&gt; or runny sauces can be soaked up with newspaper or paper towels and put in the rubbish bin.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Chemicals like bleach or paint&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;If a cleaning liquid such as bleach is approved to be sold in Australia, use it at the concentration specified on the container. But do not tip concentrated cleaning liquids &lt;a href="https://www.epa.nsw.gov.au/Your-environment/Waste/industrial-waste/hazardous-and-liquid-wastes"&gt;into the sink&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pouring your remaining paint or paint-brush cleaning water into the sink is not a good idea. You risk potentially clogging the plumbing system – exposing yourselves to heavy fumes – and pouring flammable liquids down the drain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We need an alternative. You could use a disposable brush, or – if the paint job lasts multiple days – wrap the brush in plastic and only clean when done with painting. You can soak the small amount of brush water into an old towel and &lt;a href="https://www.bunnings.com.au/diy-advice/diy-skills/painting/how-to-safely-dispose-of-paint-products?srsltid=AfmBOoo-tpr0bLrU_4uK9MXixQeJaR-f7cciLNhP1VQvZ7JoyoSE8HUv"&gt;dispose&lt;/a&gt; of that in the rubbish bin once the paint has dried.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/newsletter?utm_source=promo_generic_health"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-642x273.jpg" alt="Subscribe to ScienceAlert's free fact-checked newsletter" class="alignnone wp-image-182810 size-medium" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-642x273.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-768x326.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-600x255.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final.jpg 850w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, the best way to get rid of potentially hazardous household chemicals such as paint, cleaners, pesticides, motor oil, or cooking oil, is to take them to a &lt;a href="https://www.epa.nsw.gov.au/Your-environment/Recycling-and-reuse/household-recycling-overview/household-chemical-cleanout"&gt;Household Chemical Cleanout&lt;/a&gt; event. These events are free services held in some &lt;a href="https://www.sustainability.vic.gov.au/recycling-and-reducing-waste-at-home/hazardous-household-chemicals/dispose-of-household-chemicals-detox-your-home"&gt;states and territories&lt;/a&gt; specified dates.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And there are industries that have funded their own collection schemes, for example, "&lt;a href="https://www.paintback.com.au/find-location"&gt;paintback&lt;/a&gt;" drop off centres. Commercial and industrial entities will need proper &lt;a href="https://recyclingnearyou.com.au/"&gt;recycling&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.health.nsw.gov.au/environment/water/Pages/wastewater.aspx"&gt;treatment processes&lt;/a&gt; in place.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Collective problem&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;We should not put anything down the sink that we would not want in our waterways. Instead of using sinks as disposal points, households should adopt safer alternatives such as composting food waste and taking hazardous substances to approved chemical cleanout events.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The problem is not what one individual does, but what everyone in a city contributes together. Small individual actions, when combined across a city, make a significant difference in protecting plumbing infrastructure, public health, and our creeks and oceans.&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://counter.theconversation.com/content/269701/count.gif?distributor=republish-lightbox-basic" alt="The Conversation" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" loading="lazy"&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/profiles/faisal-hai-938602"&gt;Faisal Hai&lt;/a&gt;, Professor and Head of School of Civil, Mining, Environmental and Architectural Engineering, &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/institutions/university-of-wollongong-711"&gt;University of Wollongong&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This article is republished from &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com"&gt;The Conversation&lt;/a&gt; under a Creative Commons license. Read the &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/should-i-pour-this-down-the-sink-probably-not-and-heres-why-269701"&gt;original article&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 01:02:39 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMinAFBVV95cUxQdXZ6N19KcFBQdnEwRDRuVDFxM0phZnhXbEtzNWdmNXRTcnhlMDJIcG5SNVFjR2RJWUpjNm9PYklFa2pQTjNlTkdMQkZJUmhuSndFNWJXRDlGQ0tla0FfcUVzbU9NSnVyRHh3VEh2dzBhX19SZldybzJGamt6aVdjcjExMDBxd1RQRm1GM1oxa2l1bEJvc3E3djkzcE4</guid></item><item><title>16种过夜燕麦减肥食谱- EatingWell</title><link>https://www.eatingwell.com/overnight-oat-recipes-for-weight-loss-11871578</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-article-intro_1-0" class="comp mntl-article-intro mntl-block article-content__description"&gt;&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Wake up to a delicious meal by trying out these healthy overnight oats recipes. Each of these creamy breakfast dishes is &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/our-food-and-nutrition-philosophy-6746110" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;&lt;u&gt;lower in calories&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; to help support healthy weight loss. They’re also high in &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/7913446/what-is-protein-why-do-you-need-it/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;&lt;u&gt;protein&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; and/or &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/287742/10-amazing-health-benefits-of-eating-more-fiber/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="3"&gt;&lt;u&gt;fiber&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, which will help support lasting energy and keep you feeling fuller longer. Whether you’re dreaming of a dessert-inspired dish like our Blueberry Pie–Inspired Overnight Oats or a fruit-packed version like our High-Fiber Cranberry-Orange Overnight Oats, there’s a tasty option for everyone.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id="list-sc__content_1-0" class="comp list-sc__content mntl-sc-page mntl-block" data-sc-sticky-offset="90" data-sc-ad-label-height="24" data-sc-ad-track-spacing="100" data-sc-min-track-height="250" data-sc-max-track-height="600" data-sc-breakpoint="50em" data-sc-load-immediate="4" data-sc-content-positions="[1, 3, 6, 9, 12, 15, 18]" data-bind-scroll-on-start="true"&gt;&lt;div id="list-sc-item_1-0" class="comp list-sc-item mntl-block mntl-sc-list-item"&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-high-fiber-cranberry-orange-overnight-oats"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_3-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-list-item-title"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; High-Fiber Cranberry-Orange Overnight Oats &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure id="mntl-sc-block_4-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image--no-theme no-theme figure-square figure-high-res"&gt; 
&lt;figcaption id="mntl-figure-caption_1-0" class="comp mntl-figure-caption text-utility-100 figure-article-caption"&gt; &lt;span class="figure-article-caption-owner"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Photographer: Robby Lozano, Food Stylist: Isabelle Easter, Prop Stylist: Keoshia McGhee&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_5-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; These cranberry-orange overnight oats are pure fall sunshine in a jar. Each spoonful balances citrusy brightness, cranberry zing and cozy cinnamon spice between layers of creamy oats and chia seeds. These oats are perfect for meal prep or anytime you need a cheerful start to your day.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block-adslot_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block" data-item-index="1"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="list-sc-item_2-0" class="comp list-sc-item mntl-block mntl-sc-list-item"&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-cinnamon-pear-overnight-oats"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_7-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-list-item-title"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Cinnamon-Pear Overnight Oats &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure id="mntl-sc-block_8-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image--no-theme no-theme figure-square figure-high-res"&gt; 
&lt;figcaption id="mntl-figure-caption_2-0" class="comp mntl-figure-caption text-utility-100 figure-article-caption"&gt; &lt;span class="figure-article-caption-owner"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Photographer: Morgan Hunt Ward, Prop Stylist: Phoebe Hauser, Food Stylist: Emily Nabors Hall.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_9-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; These cozy spiced-pear overnight oats feature tender cinnamon-maple sautéed pears folded into creamy oats with crunchy pecans and chia seeds. A touch of Greek-style yogurt adds tang, while vanilla and cinnamon bring warmth. They’re perfect for make-ahead breakfasts throughout the week, and make a refreshing alternative to cooked oatmeal.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block-adslot_2-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block" data-item-index="2"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="list-sc-item_3-0" class="comp list-sc-item mntl-block mntl-sc-list-item"&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-lemon-poppyseed-overnight-oats"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_11-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-list-item-title"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Lemon-Poppyseed Overnight Oats &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure id="mntl-sc-block_12-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image--no-theme no-theme figure-square figure-high-res"&gt; 
&lt;figcaption id="mntl-figure-caption_3-0" class="comp mntl-figure-caption text-utility-100 figure-article-caption"&gt; &lt;span class="figure-article-caption-owner"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Photographer: Robby Lozano, Food Stylist: Emily Nabors Hall, Prop Stylist: Phoebe Hausser&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_13-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; These Lemon-Poppyseed Overnight Oats are a bright and refreshing twist on a breakfast classic. Creamy oats are infused with fresh lemon zest and juice, then stirred together with poppy seeds for a make-ahead breakfast that tastes like a lemon-poppyseed muffin in a jar. A touch of maple syrup adds sweetness to balance the tart lemon.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block-adslot_3-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block" data-item-index="3"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="list-sc-item_4-0" class="comp list-sc-item mntl-block mntl-sc-list-item"&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-blueberry-pieinspired-overnight-oats"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_16-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-list-item-title"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Blueberry Pie–Inspired Overnight Oats &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure id="mntl-sc-block_17-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image--no-theme no-theme figure-square figure-high-res"&gt; 
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_18-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; With a jammy blueberry filling and a crumble topping, these overnight oats taste like a slice of blueberry pie. Oat milk reinforces the flavor, while lemon zest and juice provide nice brightness. Fresh and frozen blueberries both work well here—let frozen blueberries thaw first before using.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block-adslot_4-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block" data-item-index="4"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="list-sc-item_5-0" class="comp list-sc-item mntl-block mntl-sc-list-item"&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-cosmic-brownieinspired-overnight-oats"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_20-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-list-item-title"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Cosmic Brownie–Inspired Overnight Oats &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure id="mntl-sc-block_21-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image--no-theme no-theme figure-square figure-high-res"&gt; 
&lt;figcaption id="mntl-figure-caption_4-0" class="comp mntl-figure-caption text-utility-100 figure-article-caption"&gt; &lt;span class="figure-article-caption-owner"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Photographer: Stacy K. Allen, Food Stylist: Marianne Williams, Prop Stylist: Abby Armstrong&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_22-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; These cosmic brownie–inspired overnight oats turn a childhood favorite into a nutritious breakfast with serious dessert vibes. These creamy oats are made with cocoa powder and a touch of maple syrup, with a chocolate topping that mimics the classic brownie ganache. For a fun and nostalgic touch, a scattering of rainbow sprinkles gives them their signature look.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block-adslot_5-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block" data-item-index="5"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="list-sc-item_6-0" class="comp list-sc-item mntl-block mntl-sc-list-item"&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-berry-crumble-overnight-oats"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_24-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-list-item-title"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Berry Crumble Overnight Oats &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure id="mntl-sc-block_25-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image--no-theme no-theme figure-square figure-high-res"&gt; 
&lt;figcaption id="mntl-figure-caption_5-0" class="comp mntl-figure-caption text-utility-100 figure-article-caption"&gt; &lt;span class="figure-article-caption-owner"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Photographer: Jen Causey, Food Stylist: Julian Hensarling, Prop Stylist: Clarie Spollen&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_26-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; With the perfect balance of creamy and crunchy textures, these berry crumble overnight oats will keep you satisfied all morning. The natural sweetness of the berries pairs beautifully with the cinnamon-spiced oat base, while the crumble topping adds a crunchy layer to each bite. The best part? You can use any mixture of berries or stick to your favorite—whether it’s juicy blueberries, tart raspberries, sweet strawberries or a blend of all three.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block-adslot_6-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block" data-item-index="6"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="list-sc-item_7-0" class="comp list-sc-item mntl-block mntl-sc-list-item"&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-york-peppermint-pattieinspired-overnight-oats"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_28-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-list-item-title"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; York Peppermint Pattie–Inspired Overnight Oats &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure id="mntl-sc-block_29-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image--no-theme no-theme figure-square figure-high-res"&gt; 
&lt;figcaption id="mntl-figure-caption_6-0" class="comp mntl-figure-caption text-utility-100 figure-article-caption"&gt; &lt;span class="figure-article-caption-owner"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Photographer: Hannah Hufham, Food Stylist: Nicole Hopper, Prop Stylist: Abby Armstrong&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_30-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; These minty York Peppermint Pattie–inspired overnight oats come together in just minutes. It’s the perfect recipe for meal prep because you can store it in jars, giving you a grab-and-go breakfast that’s worth waking up for.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block-adslot_7-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block" data-item-index="7"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="list-sc-item_8-0" class="comp list-sc-item mntl-block mntl-sc-list-item"&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-cranberry-cheesecake-overnight-oats"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_32-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-list-item-title"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Cranberry Cheesecake Overnight Oats &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure id="mntl-sc-block_33-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image--no-theme no-theme figure-square figure-high-res"&gt; 
&lt;figcaption id="mntl-figure-caption_7-0" class="comp mntl-figure-caption text-utility-100 figure-article-caption"&gt; &lt;span class="figure-article-caption-owner"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Photographer: Greg DuPree, Food Stylist: Chelsea Zimmer, Prop Stylist: Abby Armstrong&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_34-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; These fiber-rich cranberry cheesecake overnight oats will transform your breakfast into something special. Combining the tangy sweetness of cranberries with the rich, creamy flavors of cheesecake, these oats offer a delicious start to your day.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block-adslot_8-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block" data-item-index="8"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="list-sc-item_9-0" class="comp list-sc-item mntl-block mntl-sc-list-item"&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-high-protein-peanut-butter-banana--blueberry-overnight-oats"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_36-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-list-item-title"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; High-Protein Peanut Butter, Banana &amp;amp; Blueberry Overnight Oats &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure id="mntl-sc-block_37-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image--no-theme no-theme figure-square figure-high-res"&gt; 
&lt;figcaption id="mntl-figure-caption_8-0" class="comp mntl-figure-caption text-utility-100 figure-article-caption"&gt; &lt;span class="figure-article-caption-owner"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Photographer: Jake Sternquist, Food Stylist: Annie Probst, Prop Stylist: Joseph Wanek&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_38-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; These overnight oats pack 17 grams of protein per serving, thanks to Greek-style yogurt, peanut butter and soymilk. We sweeten these oats naturally with banana, and add blueberries for more fruity flavor. Divide the mixture into Mason jars for an easy grab-and-go breakfast.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block-adslot_9-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block" data-item-index="9"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="list-sc-item_10-0" class="comp list-sc-item mntl-block mntl-sc-list-item"&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-apple-pomegranate-overnight-oats"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_40-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-list-item-title"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Apple-Pomegranate Overnight Oats &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure id="mntl-sc-block_41-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image--no-theme no-theme figure-square figure-high-res"&gt; 
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_42-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Apple-pomegranate overnight oats are a delicious and nutritious breakfast option that combines the natural sweetness of apples and pomegranates with fiber-rich oats. The tartness of pomegranates complements the sweet, crisp flavor of apples. For the best flavor and sweetness, consider using sweet apple varieties such as Honeycrisp, Fuji or Gala.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block-adslot_10-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block" data-item-index="10"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="list-sc-item_11-0" class="comp list-sc-item mntl-block mntl-sc-list-item"&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-pumpkin-date-overnight-oats"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_44-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-list-item-title"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Pumpkin-Date Overnight Oats &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure id="mntl-sc-block_45-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image--no-theme no-theme figure-square figure-high-res"&gt; 
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_46-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; The combination of prebiotic ingredients like oats, flaxmeal and dates makes these pumpkin overnight oats a delicious and nutritious option for supporting gut health. Dates add natural sweetness, while yogurt adds tang as well as a healthy dose of probiotics to start your day off right.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block-adslot_11-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block" data-item-index="11"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="list-sc-item_12-0" class="comp list-sc-item mntl-block mntl-sc-list-item"&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-banana-cream-pieinspired-overnight-oats"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_48-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-list-item-title"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Banana Cream Pie–Inspired Overnight Oats &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure id="mntl-sc-block_49-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image--no-theme no-theme figure-landscape figure-high-res"&gt; 
&lt;figcaption id="mntl-figure-caption_9-0" class="comp mntl-figure-caption text-utility-100 figure-article-caption"&gt; &lt;span class="figure-article-caption-owner"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Photographer: Jennifer Causey, Food Stylist: Julian Hensarling, Prop Stylist: Christina Daley&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_50-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Start your day with a breakfast that feels like a treat—these layered overnight oats offer a delightful blend of banana, cinnamon and a touch of vanilla to elevate the taste. Right before enjoying, a finishing touch of crumbled graham crackers adds a pie-like charm to this easy breakfast. For the best results, use ripe bananas—their skin should be brown in spots and they should feel a little soft when you squeeze them.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block-adslot_12-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block" data-item-index="12"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="list-sc-item_13-0" class="comp list-sc-item mntl-block mntl-sc-list-item"&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-caramel-appleinspired-overnight-oats"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_52-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-list-item-title"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Caramel Apple–Inspired Overnight Oats &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure id="mntl-sc-block_53-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image--no-theme no-theme figure-landscape figure-high-res"&gt; 
&lt;figcaption id="mntl-figure-caption_10-0" class="comp mntl-figure-caption text-utility-100 figure-article-caption"&gt; &lt;span class="figure-article-caption-owner"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Photographer: Morgan Hunt Glaze, Prop Stylist: Josh Hoggle, Food Stylist: Amanda Stanfield&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_54-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; This easy, meal-prep-friendly recipe takes all the flavors of a caramel apple and imparts them into breakfast. Applesauce ensures the texture is creamy yet light while also providing balance to the sweet-tart flavor of the oats. If you don’t have Granny Smith apples on hand, Fuji, Gala or Honeycrisp apples work as well. Crushed honey-roasted peanuts mimic the coating of a caramel apple, but any salty-sweet nut would be delicious.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block-adslot_13-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block" data-item-index="13"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="list-sc-item_14-0" class="comp list-sc-item mntl-block mntl-sc-list-item"&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-overnight-steel-cut-oats"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_56-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-list-item-title"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Overnight Steel-Cut Oats &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure id="mntl-sc-block_57-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image--no-theme no-theme figure-square figure-high-res"&gt; 
&lt;figcaption id="mntl-figure-caption_11-0" class="comp mntl-figure-caption text-utility-100 figure-article-caption"&gt; &lt;span class="figure-article-caption-owner"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Photographer: Jen Causey, Food Stylist: Ruth Blackburn&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_58-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; These overnight steel-cut oats are the ultimate make-ahead breakfast. Make a batch for the whole family, or store the extra servings in the fridge to eat throughout the week. We love these creamy steel-cut oats topped with honey, bananas and raspberries, but any sweetener, chopped fruit or nut topping will work well.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block-adslot_14-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block" data-item-index="14"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="list-sc-item_15-0" class="comp list-sc-item mntl-block mntl-sc-list-item"&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-apple-pieinspired-overnight-oats"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_60-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-list-item-title"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Apple Pie–Inspired Overnight Oats &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure id="mntl-sc-block_61-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image--no-theme no-theme figure-landscape figure-high-res"&gt; 
&lt;figcaption id="mntl-figure-caption_12-0" class="comp mntl-figure-caption text-utility-100 figure-article-caption"&gt; &lt;span class="figure-article-caption-owner"&gt;Photographer: Brie Goldman, Food Stylist: Skyler Myers, Prop Stylist: Gabriel Greco&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_62-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; There's no better way to usher in fall than apple pie-inspired overnight oats in the morning. Prep and store this easy breakfast ahead of time to have on hand for busy work and school mornings. You can substitute any nondairy milk for the reduced-fat milk, or try kefir if you want your oats extra tangy.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block-adslot_15-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block" data-item-index="15"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="list-sc-item_16-0" class="comp list-sc-item mntl-block mntl-sc-list-item"&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-high-fiber-raspberry-vanilla-overnight-oats"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_64-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-list-item-title"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; High-Fiber Raspberry-Vanilla Overnight Oats &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure id="mntl-sc-block_65-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image--no-theme no-theme figure-square figure-high-res"&gt; 
&lt;figcaption id="mntl-figure-caption_13-0" class="comp mntl-figure-caption text-utility-100 figure-article-caption"&gt; &lt;span class="figure-article-caption-owner"&gt;Photographer: Rachel Marek, Food stylist: Holly Dreesman&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_66-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Get your day off to a healthy start with these raspberry-vanilla overnight oats. This grab-and-go breakfast delivers 8 grams of fiber, plus probiotics from kefir that may help support a healthy digestive system. We love sweet fresh raspberries to top off this easy breakfast, but any of your favorite berries or chopped fresh fruit will work well.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block-adslot_16-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block" data-item-index="16"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>EatingWell</author><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 01:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMifkFVX3lxTFByMFptaXlMQjNNel9uS0VVY3VnMEpzWjRpRU81Z0NKQTZ4R0JuMURkMlNJZUdpZ1FUR0pwV1FwZkNsYWtZbFEteFdXcWFGWTZYSUV5Rk9DbXdTYmtfX1dJQzNwOC1TeEpPclotZnMzcUVXdVdOc1dSN3I2T3J2UQ</guid></item><item><title>卫生部门最新数据显示呼吸道病毒活动激增- WJAR</title><link>https://turnto10.com/news/local/latest-health-department-data-shows-spike-in-respiratory-virus-activity-jan-2-2026</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="StoryText_storyText__C3hWI StoryText_storyText__C3hWI"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="dateline"&gt;(WJAR)  — &lt;/span&gt;The latest data posted by the Rhode Island Department of Health shows a spike in respiratory virus activity in the Ocean State.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In its dashboard summary, the total respiratory virus activity has risen across the board.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For the last three weeks, there have been increases in COVID-19 cases, flu cases, and RSV cases.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Emergency Department visits also saw a spike for flu cases, according to data from the RIDOH.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As of Dec. 27, 2025, there were 44 hospital  admissions for COVID-19 and 147 for the flu.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The health department says 12 people have died because of COVID-19 and 5 deaths over the Flue.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This story will be updated with more information.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>WJAR</author><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 23:26:15 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMitAFBVV95cUxNZWhXZS1ja1RjZHFyRUpOcGVwTjc2TUdvLVBtV3pFdzU4S1JxSkE0TzREai1CWTRtTjhtajZJM3F1b2NZXzJJZENYc0d2Q1NTd0syZkpmMzJkODR1VHRZLXpnQTJOLVpiMlVBY1Y4RmtMTnlQSi0zNlp1T3lwYzZtNzlvZmNOekpWYThkTkh2VDI0NEhmN1c1ZDlJaVp1VGJvY1c4MzlsQkdGVW5VczIzbWlHMVU</guid></item><item><title>车辆最终落在东格林威治（ WJAR ） 4号公路旁的树林里</title><link>https://turnto10.com/news/local/vehicle-ends-up-in-wooded-area-on-route-4-in-east-greenwich-jan-2-2026</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;h2 class="StoryPage_headline__AP3j8"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Vehicle ends up in woods off Route 4 in East Greenwich &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;div class="ByLineContainer_storyBylineContainer__0JNT7" id="js-Story-Byline-0"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="ByLine_storyByLineText__cze7l"&gt;by NBC 10 NEWS&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="ByLineContainer_storyDatelineText__yS9e8"&gt;Fri, January 2, 2026 at 8:52 AM&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="ByLineContainer_storyDatelineText__yS9e8"&gt;&lt;span class="ByLineContainer_updatedText__0D6FY"&gt;Updated &lt;/span&gt;Fri, January 2, 2026 at 5:37 PM&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;button class="UserWayButton_userWayButton__h8S9a ByLineContainer_userWayButton___vCFL"&gt;&lt;img alt="UserWay icon for accessibility widget" src="/resources/defaults/news_3.0/icons/accessibility/userway-transparent.svg"&gt;&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>WJAR</author><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 23:21:49 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipAFBVV95cUxPaWJwVHljcjhXSEVHWEZoQWl1OWl1M2NzcWhQY1JERFJvTVlJNUlKOU10aDZfZmdBeGZqak1PT0ZFNXNlMW5qd3RGVVc1aDI4MElVMTJCME1sTzVEZmM3azgxbkJfbVAwUVdRRUNZb1lzdFY2OVR5eVk3MVhGWE95Y3pwWHdYSnpoVGZWci1ZVTR5ZEszcmtmQzg4S25QLW1lUDdWbw</guid></item><item><title>德克萨斯州流感病例继续攀升的最新数字- ABC13休斯顿</title><link>https://abc13.com/post/latest-numbers-flu-cases-continue-climb-texas/18343679/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="xvlfx ZRifP TKoO eaKKC EcdEg bOdfO qXhdi NFNeu UyHES " data-testid="prism-article-body"&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao MvWXB TjIXL aGjvy ebVHC "&gt;&lt;span class="oyrPY qlwaB AGxeB  "&gt;HOUSTON, Texas (KTRK) -- &lt;/span&gt;ABC13 is continuing to monitor flu cases as they climb nationwide and here in Houston. The latest report from the CDC shows Texas is one of nine states recording a high number of flu cases.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;When our team spoke to the Houston Health Department this week, the director noted a continued growth in flu cases.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;"We have seen increases in influenza A in our wastewater monitoring, and we have also seen increases in our health care-related visits, almost double from a month ago," director Dr. Theresa Tran said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;The latest figures from the state health and human services department show that across age groups, more people are going to the ER for respiratory illnesses.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;The largest age group visiting the ER for respiratory illness is five to 11-year-olds, making up more than a quarter of visits for that age group. This time last year, that number was closer to 15%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;The numbers really began to build around Thanksgiving and have evolved from there. Health experts say that's a trend they expect on some level most years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;"This year, the trend is slightly higher than last year, so I anticipate the trend is going to continue to rise," Dr. Tran said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;According to the Houston Methodists' respiratory snapshot, there was a slight decrease in reported flu cases across the health system. The week of Dec.19, Methodist reported 1,051 positive flu A tests, but that number fell to 756 for Christmas week. That number is still higher than this time a month ago.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Experts say that symptoms after exposure can pop up in one to four days, and those first days of illness are crucial.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;&lt;strong class="vtkaO "&gt;The health department shared the following advice for those battling the flu:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;&lt;em class=" "&gt;1. Stay hydrated and fed.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;&lt;em class=" "&gt;2. An at-home flu test will confirm your suspicions, and drug store medications can help some of those harder symptoms, but won't cure the flu. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;&lt;em class=" "&gt;3. Unfortunately, the flu has to run its course.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;As kids head back to school, the health department warns we aren't out of the woods yet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;"It tends to get higher around January and February, but we have seen spikes in May and in April. It's just really hard to tell." Dr. Tran said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC eTIW sUzSN "&gt;&lt;em class=" "&gt;For more news updates, follow Lileana Pearson on &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://www.facebook.com/ABC13LileanaPearson" target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://twitter.com/abc13lileana" target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;X&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://www.instagram.com/lileanaabc13/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;Instagram&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="uvrxY zOGtW "&gt;Copyright © 2026 KTRK-TV. All Rights Reserved.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ABC13 Houston</author><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 23:06:18 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihAFBVV95cUxObU9iRC1SZkc0eTJFYVlfektlbk1lZThxNXY4dEVYRjBhTmM2X1MwQ0VlRWw0WnRNTjNtcDRtTTFsemxqSVhPLWdTNDBPZlpTaHAtRVBMTzV0alVPQVRfcExQZjNQd1NqMlNWdUY5bldJTkRTV3pVZmptZElWQ2RnVGZZQW_SAYoBQVVfeXFMTlFTbmxySDNJbGFqdDMyS3A1MU5hdnZVUzNFN3BMVjNEOFJjcUFVTThDZGZLYlZlV2ZFbEo1eUNRZVhVbUI3bHliNFd2Z0NqbHBuTmNrQ2JuVF9vaEUxZTVaWEFScUxZbDBERks5TnBOTGRPcWotXzV2S2tmRkdKZGgyVTJVdXhHUmdn</guid></item><item><title>利哈伊谷报告800例流感病例，北安普敦县约700例- WFMZ.com</title><link>https://www.wfmz.com/news/area/lehighvalley/lehigh-county/allentown-area/lehigh-valley-reports-800-flu-cases-northampton-county-with-about-700-cases/article_67033bf2-817e-43e5-b861-642b6864d5c2.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="article-body" itemprop="articleBody" class="asset-content  subscriber-premium" false&gt;
                                &lt;meta itemprop="isAccessibleForFree" content="true"&gt;
                                
                                
                                &lt;p&gt;ALLENTOWN, Pa. (WFMZ) -- Flu cases are on the rise across the country. This week, the CDC issued an alert that the number of those getting sick is the highest it has seen all season.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A local pediatrician tells us Lehigh County has had 800 flu cases so far and Northampton County, about 700.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many of those patients were diagnosed over the last couple of weeks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lehigh Valley Health Network pediatrician Dr. George Nassar has been busy treating sick patients in the ER the last couple of weeks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We've been getting slammed with a lot of flu and RSV. Everyone's getting together with their families over the holidays so there's an increased transmissibility there and then we're also seeing a very strong decline in flu vaccination which I'm sure is playing a role in the number of cases that we're seeing," Nassar explained.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nassar encourages families to isolate if someone is sick and stay home.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"If your child has any signs of trouble breathing, if you see their ribs when they're breathing, they're breathing really fast, if their face, lips or skin turns blue or if they have signs of dehydration and they're not drinking or they are persistently vomiting, can't keep anything down. If you have a baby and the baby is not making wet diapers, they should be making at least two wet diapers in twelve hours, those are signs of dehydration that people should look out for," Nassar stated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr. Heather Osher, a Medical Director at Patient First, tells us a lot more than just the flu has been going around.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="tncms-region-article_instory_middle" class="tncms-region hidden-print"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We've been seeing a whole lot of different illnesses. Lots of flu, flu is probably the biggest one that we've been seeing. After that some strep and a lot of GI bugs. The norovirus is a big one that's been going around and then COVID is going around as well," Osher said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She's also seen cases of people getting a viral infection like the flu or covid and then coming down with a bacterial infection one to two weeks later. She encourages people to get their flu shot as the first line of defense.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The biggest thing is going to be to get a flu vaccine just because the flu vaccine prevents significant disease, hospitalizations, things like that," Osher explained.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you start to feel sick, you can take an over-the-counter flu or covid test and the sooner you can get treated, the sooner you'll feel better. As for staying healthy, practice good habits.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Eat a good balanced meal, exercise, get a lot of sleep and just the normal thing is to prevent actually getting it, wash your hands as much as you can, wear a mask, don't touch your face. If you're sick, obviously don't go out, stay home, mask up, that kind of thing," Osher concluded.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The CDC says more than 19,000 people nationwide were admitted to the hospital with the flu last week.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The surge is being driven by a new strain of the virus.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="tncms-region-article_instory_bottom" class="tncms-region hidden-print"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
                                
                                
                            &lt;/div&gt;

                            

                            
    


                            
    


                            
                                &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>WFMZ.com</author><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipAJBVV95cUxNRVRseXplTWNkajN3QWRscU9JN1paOXY3NzRGT3JicnUyNXJPemdUbkVXUkt3Z3FMbHJZTy1FUVVGZDBpcWh5ZDdxOEkyTUtmalg5YWlRa29zZmFRRUFYOUdBcnRoWS0wd2FGeHk3bTlQbHM1b3BsR0Y1RnRzWG9TLVZmaW90Nm81WVV3TlBxTnQwTUlDLVpQaUZPMnpIN1JTVjRQazJ1Yy0zZVAwZ21Bd3NIQzFhUUdkWE5hcXZ6OG5jUGhUbmZLQ0t5N2hqaWhjbEJETUZCd1BRdzViR2hCRE5tSGF0Vmlrclh2bDNfNHNXRUxXc2FQS3RGWDV4TXZDNkZWOE44NUpoOUowWjhjc2MtUENGbWRNbG1ZLXJKQWZmX2VU</guid></item><item><title>威斯康星州的流感活动在假期激增，跟随全国趋势-密尔沃基哨兵杂志</title><link>https://www.jsonline.com/story/news/local/2026/01/02/wisconsin-flu-activity-surges-over-holidays-following-national-trend/87997906007/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_dt"&gt;Jan. 2, 2026, 4:56 p.m. CT&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="gnt_ar_b"&gt;&lt;ul class="gnt_sh"&gt;&lt;li class="gnt_sh_li"&gt;Flu activity surged in Wisconsin over the holidays, a trend also unfolding across the nation.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="gnt_sh_li"&gt;State health officials classified flu activity as "very high" the week ending Dec. 27, up from "moderate" the week before.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="gnt_sh_li"&gt;An explosion of cases countrywide is largely driven by a new variant of the influenza A virus.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="gnt_sh_li"&gt;Experts say it's too early to tell what overall impact the variant will have on the U.S. flu season.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;Flu activity spiked across Wisconsin over the holidays, with &lt;a href="https://www.dhs.wisconsin.gov/disease/respiratory-emergency-department.htm" data-t-l=":b|z|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;nearly 1 in 10 people&lt;/a&gt; visiting an emergency room the week of Dec. 21-27 having an influenza diagnosis, almost double the week prior.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;New respiratory illness data from the Wisconsin Department of Health Services show flu activity in the state was classified as "very high" that week, up from "moderate" the week before.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;Such an increase is typical as people travel and gather together for the holidays. But it's a warning sign of what could be a tough flu season ahead, driven largely by a new variant of the influenza A virus known as H3N2 subclade K.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;Over 620 people were hospitalized across Wisconsin with the flu the week ending Dec. 27, &lt;a href="https://www.dhs.wisconsin.gov/disease/respiratory-hospitalizations.htm" data-t-l=":b|z|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;data show&lt;/a&gt;, more than a two-fold increase from the week prior. The majority were residents ages 65 and older.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;Wisconsin is not alone. Flu cases are surging around the U.S., with the U.S. Centers for Disease Control and Prevention &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/fluview/surveillance/2025-week-51.html" data-t-l=":b|z|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;estimating&lt;/a&gt; at least 7.5 million illnesses, 81,000 hospitalizations and 3,100 deaths from the flu so far this season as of Dec. 20. The number of illnesses recorded grew 63% from the week prior.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;The 2025-2026 U.S. flu season's severity level is still classified as low, &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/flu/php/surveillance/in-season-severity.html" data-t-l=":b|z|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;according to the CDC&lt;/a&gt;, and health experts caution that it's too early to tell the impact of the new variant. The CDC &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/fluview/surveillance/2025-week-51.html" data-t-l=":b|z|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;does predict&lt;/a&gt; that influenza activity will continue for several weeks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;In the Milwaukee area, &lt;a href="https://www.dhs.wisconsin.gov/wastewater/influenza-rsv-surveillance.htm" data-t-l=":b|z|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;sharply rising levels of influenza A in wastewater&lt;/a&gt; – one way health officials measure the spread of respiratory disease – indicate sustained activity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;Last year's flu season was particularly intense in Wisconsin, peaking later in the season with more than 860 people hospitalized with the flu the &lt;a href="https://www.dhs.wisconsin.gov/disease/respiratory-hospitalizations.htm" data-t-l=":b|z|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;week of Feb. 8, 2025.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;State health officials say the best way to avoid the flu is to wash your hands, stay home if you are sick and get the flu vaccine, available to anyone 6 months and older.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;To get vaccinated, residents can check with their doctor, health department, pharmacy or other community clinic. People who do not have health insurance can use programs such as the &lt;a href="https://www.dhs.wisconsin.gov/immunization/vfc-parent.htm" data-t-l=":b|z|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;Vaccines for Children program&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.dhs.wisconsin.gov/immunization/vfa.htm" data-t-l=":b|z|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;Vaccines for Adults program&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_s gnt_ar_s0"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_s gnt_ar_s25"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_s gnt_ar_s50"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_s gnt_ar_s75"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_s gnt_ar_s100"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Milwaukee Journal Sentinel</author><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 22:56:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMizwFBVV95cUxNY3BQVXR3ME5MdkV4WWIzeElXeXRZUWVfWUN3Y0lVamhZMHM5TDR6dVdWNTc2TlIxX091R3dsT2QtaTVRdV9jS2dQMzRYc3kxOHpEUGNTNHNsa3I2aUl1QnVqWFM4d293RHkyaVZ3cmQ1RmxyUTc4Ql9iQ2swdFRpOVJfLUNacVJvbGs0Q3ZqUWZUVmtuVUN2cmFlQWNySGprNWJRUHFTT3dLcG1adE52TUE2WUhERVREQkdsRnh4RmJ4LWlqa00tc2dPR1ctU1k</guid></item><item><title>健康的18岁焊工差点死于炭疽--这是第九个这样令人费解的案例--Ars Technica</title><link>https://arstechnica.com/health/2026/01/anthrax-nearly-kills-healthy-18-year-old-welder-amid-puzzling-pattern/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content post-content-double"&gt;
          
          
&lt;p&gt;In 2022, &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC9029013/"&gt;CDC researchers found an unexpected pattern&lt;/a&gt;. Since 1997, there had been seven cases of infections from &lt;em&gt;Bacillus&lt;/em&gt; group bacteria producing the anthrax toxin—all in metalworkers. Six of the seven were welders, hence the term “welder’s anthrax,” with the remaining case in a person working in a foundry grinding metal. Of the six cases where a specific &lt;em&gt;Bacillus &lt;/em&gt;species was identified, &lt;em&gt;B. tropicus &lt;/em&gt;was the culprit, including in the newly reported case.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Speculating risks&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It’s unclear why metalworkers, and welders specifically, are uniquely vulnerable to this infection. In their 2022 report making the connection, CDC experts speculated that it may be a combination of having weakened immune responses in the lungs after inhaling toxic metal fumes and gases created during metalwork, and having increased exposure to the deadly germs in their workplaces.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the latest case, the teen did welding work four hours a day, four days a week, with limited ventilation, sometimes in confined spaces, and often didn’t use personal protective equipment, like a respirator. Environmental sampling of his workplace found anthrax-toxin-producing &lt;em&gt;Bacillus &lt;/em&gt;in 28 of 254 spot samples. Other investigations of welder’s anthrax cases have found similar results.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So far, all nine cases have been detected in either Louisiana or Texas. But the experts note that cases are likely underreported, and modeling suggests these dangerous germs could be thriving in many Southern US states.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The experts also speculated that iron exposure could play a role. &lt;em&gt;Bacillus&lt;/em&gt; bacteria need iron to live and thrive, and metalworkers can build up excess iron levels in their respiratory system during their work. Iron overload could create the perfect environment for bacterial infection. In the teen’s case, he was working with carbon steel and low-hydrogen carbon steel electrodes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For now, the precise risk factors and why the healthy teen—and not anyone else in his workplace—fell ill remain unknown. CDC and state officials recommended changes to the workplace to protect metalworkers’ health, including better use of respirators, ventilation, and dust control.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is also a vaccine for anthrax that’s recommended for those considered at high risk, such as certain military members, lab workers, and livestock handlers. It’s unclear if, in the future, metalworkers might also be considered in this high-risk category.&lt;/p&gt;


          
                  &lt;/div&gt;

                  
          &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Ars Technica</author><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 22:36:26 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMirgFBVV95cUxQSHVPbFhocGdfMWFpN012bnhNTHpCOG9mM05FWXBuZVJDYW1ZVnlJSzBBdmNlWG56ZkEwaTNKQzIybWdhcy13ZThMQUQwS1ExZFl1elktako3M1ZQa0kwRWxWX1d0N2NNUHI1dDdpdmpLOWlremI0Q2lXQVJPT216STYwY0QzQ3hEVi0wZk1Wb2M3WW5hZFBzTnhwZWJKT2dic3JSUTJpSllEdXI1T3c</guid></item><item><title>影响者保罗·金（ Paul Kim ）的妻子在他们5岁的儿子死于严重的流感病例后打破了沉默-雅虎新闻加拿大</title><link>https://ca.news.yahoo.com/influencer-paul-kims-wife-breaks-220512844.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="" data-article-body="true"&gt;&lt;h3 class="mb-4 text-lg font-bold"&gt;NEED TO KNOW&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul class="mb-4"&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Maggie Kim, the wife of influencer Paul Kim, broke her silence on Instagram after the death of their 5-year-old son on Dec. 31&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Paul previously told his Instagram followers on Dec. 21 that his son had been hospitalized following a “medical emergency”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;He later revealed that his son had caught a severe case of the flu, which had prompted sepsis and seizures and required Micah to be placed on life support&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Maggie Kim, the wife of influencer Paul Kim, has broken her silence on Instagram after the &lt;a href="https://people.com/influencer-paul-j-kim-son-micah-dies-after-severe-case-of-flu-11877386" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:death of their 5-year-old son;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;death of their 5-year-old son&lt;/a&gt;, Micah, on Dec. 31.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;On New Year’s Eve, Paul — a Catholic content creator — shared the devastating news of his son’s death in an emotional video posted to Instagram, &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/reels/DS-hIiekZBe/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:saying;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;saying&lt;/a&gt; that "after fighting 11 long hard days, [Micah] went home to the house of our father."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;"We are so proud of him,” said Paul. “I want to thank you from the bottom of my heart as his dad, on behalf of my family, for all the ways you guys prayed and lifted us up during this time.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;"Micah, I miss you. There is a deep, aching hole in my heart. Even though our home is filled with people, it’s too quiet without you," began the grieving mother in a new post shared to Instagram on Jan. 2. "I keep thinking I’ll look outside and see you laughing on the swings. Or you’ll slowly open my door and walk up to my bed and that I’ll hear your sweet voice saying, 'Mama?' "&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Continued Maggie: "Oh, the pain is indescribable. And yet, you have shown us in multiple ways that you are with us. It’s not the same joy as holding your hand or hearing your voice, but there is an unexplainable joy that only comes with knowing you are with Jesus. That you are in our true home. And that you are very, very happy."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;"Please continue to visit me and help mama keep going. You were always such a good helper and eager to make me smile. And I will keep asking for your help. My boy. I am so proud of you," she added in his post.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Paul, who has over 300,000 followers on Instagram where he shares videos about his Catholic faith, &lt;a href="https://people.com/influencer-paul-kim-health-update-for-5-year-old-son-on-life-support-11876879" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:first revealed;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;first revealed&lt;/a&gt; on Dec. 21 that his son had been rushed to the hospital in an ambulance following a “medical emergency.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="relative mb-4"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="relative text-sm mt-1 pr-2.5"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Paul Kim/Instagram&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; Paul Kim and Family&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;He gave his followers subsequent updates over the next two weeks, sharing that Micah had a &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/p/DS3vY0XjRe-/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:very severe case of the flu;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;very severe case of the flu&lt;/a&gt; that prompted sepsis and seizures and required that he be &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/p/DSkGib6jhYZ/?img_index=1" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:placed on life support;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;placed on life support&lt;/a&gt;. Paul also shared that brain scans &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/p/DSlEUNhEiak/?img_index=1" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:found;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;found&lt;/a&gt; that activity was “not present.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Micah’s health journey captured the attention of the globe — Paul revealed that his posts had reached all seven continents — including singer-songwriter Gwen Stefani, who commented on one of Kim’s posts, “🙏 praying for u.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Never miss a story — sign up for &lt;a href="https://people.com/people-news-daily-newsletter-sign-up-8692701" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:PEOPLE's free daily newsletter;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;PEOPLE's free daily newsletter&lt;/a&gt; to stay up-to-date on the best of what PEOPLE has to offer​​, from celebrity news to compelling human interest stories.  &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“This incredibly difficult, impossible time for our family — it's been the hardest thing I've ever been through in my life and it continues to be,” Paul said in the video sharing that his son had died. "For those two weeks we were fighting long and hard, we were consulting legal, health, ethical teams even outside the hospital. Just to make sure we weren't leaving any stone unturned. In many ways we were fighting for Micah to buy him as much time as possible, until he passed. As a father, that is my duty I was called to do that. Even if in God's ultimate will it wasn't meant for him to recover."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="relative mb-4"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="relative text-sm mt-1 pr-2.5"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Paul Kim/Instagram&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; Paul Kim's son Micah&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;He continued that coming home without his son was one of the most "heart-wrenching, awkward experiences."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Read the original article on &lt;a href="https://people.com/influencer-paul-kim-wife-breaks-silence-after-their-5-year-old-son-dies-11878601" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:People;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;People&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Yahoo News Canada</author><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 22:05:12 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMifkFVX3lxTE9iRFRUUkFUYXBpSWhjR1FTVkZvSVNSdS1qbHZUc3VQb2hTRXlST1RsSHFnbXVyMFlUWl9WaWtWc1RhZFlhQjdRcnJPUEEwOFNJM1R5MnNqMWJBLTAwTzh3cjRkUGM0TzdvVnRKNWNUZ1BHbEVXNGtFamJybFg3QQ</guid></item><item><title>处理疱疹爆发的地区-桑达斯基登记处</title><link>https://sanduskyregister.com/news/697295/district-dealing-with-herpes-outbreak/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="tText n"&gt;&lt;p&gt;
            Your session was unable to be renewed and will be expiring in &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span id="tTimer"&gt;0&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; seconds. 
            Click &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span id="tRenew"&gt;here&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; to attempt to renew your session.

            &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="tStatus"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
         &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Sandusky Register</author><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 22:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihgFBVV95cUxNNVp2SDJJX3VEWExXdExocWNlMVltS05Wb0lhUExNUDlKd0k2amFNbzZ0MDZjTnBZbWxYc1RvWHNYOHpzS1Z2bXpKTDRtSmVnSTBPMWRYb1dkUUdIeTdoUThjZGxxWDd3dEdhczdOcHZFYUNhYWdTWXVrMk12TTg1am1GVC02dw</guid></item><item><title>科学家追踪人类健康近50年，发现身体衰老真正开始的时间- SciTechDaily</title><link>https://scitechdaily.com/scientists-track-human-fitness-for-nearly-50-years-and-discover-when-physical-aging-really-starts/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>SciTechDaily</author><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 21:14:38 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiwAFBVV95cUxQVU50dTg3dnZYSVhVa3dfRlhNajBGM2RJTHF2cVc5UkpldVdBcG4xSDVQMEJnZEs0bXZnLUxXb3B1RmtWVEVlVVlySjRUTXM5QlZKUk1tYTJTX1NKbl9UNk9xbHZZaS1hV1M0RXJFUDdocnRtMXRWaVhVaWRKbnJZYVhIWW0zZmtDU1NicGRXMHN6dms1WDZkWGVubFhvMWNaQVp3ZU0zMTBhb1huQzM0OHQ0NHBhM3RKb21yYTB4bjA</guid></item><item><title>长寿研究人员不服用任何补充剂。以下是他的3个抗衰老习惯。- Business Insider</title><link>https://www.businessinsider.com/anti-aging-tips-longevity-researcher-running-intermittent-fasting-2025-10</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;section class="post-body-content post-story-body-content" data-component-type="post-body-content" data-load-strategy="exclude" data-track-content="" data-post-type="story" data-track-marfeel="post-body-content"&gt;
            
                &lt;p&gt;After studying stem cell aging for decades, Dr. Thomas Rando learned that some of the best &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="https://www.businessinsider.com/arnold-schwarzenegger-longevity-exercise-diet-aging-2025-10" data-track-click='{"element_name":"body_link","event":"tout_click","index":"bi_value_unassigned","product_field":"bi_value_unassigned"}' rel=""&gt;longevity advice&lt;/a&gt; is timeless.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I often make the joke that the billions of dollars that have been spent on studying healthy aging could come down to the two things your mother told you," Rando, the president of the American Federation for Aging Research and director of the Broad Stem Cell Research Center at UCLA, told Business Insider. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Eat a good diet and get plenty of exercise."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rando dedicated his career to studying how tissues repair themselves — and why they eventually lose the ability to do it well. What he learned is that many of the drugs tested in animals that are meant to extend lifespan work as effectively as a balanced &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="https://www.businessinsider.com/habits-longevity-researcher-follows-for-healthy-aging-2025-9" data-track-click='{"element_name":"body_link","event":"tout_click","index":"bi_value_unassigned","product_field":"bi_value_unassigned"}' rel=""&gt;diet and exercise do&lt;/a&gt;. One example was a 2022 study that found mice that were put on fasting diets were as resilient to stress as those injected with ketone bodies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He said that many drugs and interventions are "just in a way supplementing the challenges that humans face in dieting and exercising."&lt;/p&gt;
              
            
              &lt;div class="dynamic-module" data-component-type="dynamic-module" data-load-strategy="disable-lazy"&gt;
            
                  &lt;div class="dynamic-module-components" data-component-name="follow-author-inline-signup" data-component-segment="anonymous-fly-by"&gt;
                    
                    
                    
                    
                    &lt;div data-component-type="follow-author-inline-signup" data-author="{&amp;quot;name&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;Julia Pugachevsky&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;id&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;julia-pugachevsky&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;shortenedName&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;Julia&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;image&amp;quot;:{&amp;quot;type&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;image&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;id&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;6554f5d822cf74a57397cd84&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;attributes&amp;quot;:{&amp;quot;contentType&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;image/jpeg&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;description&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;Julia Pugachevsky's face on a gray background.&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;height&amp;quot;:3748,&amp;quot;source&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;Maya Baran for Business Insider&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;width&amp;quot;:2499},&amp;quot;links&amp;quot;:{&amp;quot;self&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;https://i.insider.com/6554f5d822cf74a57397cd84&amp;quot;}},&amp;quot;links&amp;quot;:{&amp;quot;self&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;https://cda.businessinsider.com/author/julia-pugachevsky&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;site&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;https://www.businessinsider.com/author/julia-pugachevsky&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;twitter&amp;quot;:{&amp;quot;href&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;https://x.com/jaypugz&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;meta&amp;quot;:{}}}}" data-load-strategy="exclude" class="follow-author-inline-signup" data-track-view='{"subscription_experience":"bi_value_unassigned","product_field":"inline","element_name":"follow_author","event":"module_in_view"}'&gt;
                        
                      &lt;div class="content-wrapper"&gt;
                        
                        &lt;p class="body-sm-subtle body"&gt;
                          Every time Julia publishes a story, you’ll get an alert straight to your inbox!
                        &lt;/p&gt;
                        &lt;p class="body-sm-subtle body-sm"&gt;
                          Stay connected to Julia and get more of their work as it publishes.
                        &lt;/p&gt;
                        
                      &lt;/div&gt;
                    &lt;/div&gt;
                  &lt;/div&gt;
                  
            
            
              &lt;/div&gt;
            
              &lt;figure class="figure image-figure-image   " data-type="img" data-e2e-name="image-figure-image" data-media-container="image" itemscope="" itemtype="https://schema.org/ImageObject"&gt;
              
              
                
              
              &lt;span class="image-source-caption "&gt;
                    &lt;figcaption class="image-caption headline-semibold" data-e2e-name="image-caption"&gt;
                      Rando said many medications compensate for sedentary lifestyles and eating ultra-processed foods.
                      
              &lt;span class="image-source headline-regular" data-e2e-name="image-source" itemprop="creditText"&gt;
              
              Nathalie Pellenkoft/Getty Images
              
              &lt;/span&gt;
                    &lt;/figcaption&gt;
                  &lt;/span&gt;
              &lt;/figure&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;In his own life, he said his research hasn't inspired too many drastic lifestyle changes as much as reinforcing healthy habits, like cutting ultra-processed foods after college or continuing to &lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.businessinsider.com/alcohol-year-unhealthy-moderate-drinking-2025-1" data-track-click='{"element_name":"body_link","event":"tout_click","index":"bi_value_unassigned","product_field":"bi_value_unassigned"}' rel=""&gt;drink in moderation&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Unlike some of his peers in the field, he &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="https://www.businessinsider.com/category/supplements" data-track-click='{"element_name":"body_link","event":"tout_click","index":"bi_value_unassigned","product_field":"bi_value_unassigned"}' rel=""&gt;doesn't take any supplements&lt;/a&gt;; he's more persuaded that lifestyle habits such as eating whole foods and taking care of his body are the keys to longevity. "From my own studies, if you are eating well, sleeping well, and exercising, it's unlikely that supplements are going to make a difference," he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rando shared the three longevity habits he's stuck to for years, from avid running to lots of socializing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="5d6796db-c8f1-4002-9325-7acd345896b9" data-toc-id="5d6796db-c8f1-4002-9325-7acd345896b9"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;He started running in his 30s&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
              &lt;figure class="figure image-figure-image   " data-type="img" data-e2e-name="image-figure-image" data-media-container="image" itemscope="" itemtype="https://schema.org/ImageObject"&gt;
              
              
                
              
              &lt;span class="image-source-caption "&gt;
                    &lt;figcaption class="image-caption headline-semibold" data-e2e-name="image-caption"&gt;
                      Rando slowly got into marathon running over the years.
                      
              &lt;span class="image-source headline-regular" data-e2e-name="image-source" itemprop="creditText"&gt;
              
              Elena Popova/Getty Images
              
              &lt;/span&gt;
                    &lt;/figcaption&gt;
                  &lt;/span&gt;
              &lt;/figure&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;By his 30s, Rando realized his work schedule made it hard to exercise: organizing basketball or squash games just took too much time. So, he started running solo a few miles a day, a few times a week.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;After a colleague convinced him to run a 5K, he fell in love with racing. He worked his way up to a 10K, half-marathon, and eventually, a marathon. He's been a &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="https://www.businessinsider.com/i-ran-my-first-marathon-advice-mistakes-2024-11" data-track-click='{"element_name":"body_link","event":"tout_click","index":"bi_value_unassigned","product_field":"bi_value_unassigned"}' rel=""&gt;marathon runner&lt;/a&gt; for the last few decades.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Not that people should do marathons, but I really believe in the rejuvenating powers of exercise," Rando said. While he's still researching all the ways that &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="https://www.businessinsider.com/a-longevity-scientist-shared-his-weekly-workout-routine-2025-4" data-track-click='{"element_name":"body_link","event":"tout_click","index":"bi_value_unassigned","product_field":"bi_value_unassigned"}' rel=""&gt;working out benefits longevity&lt;/a&gt;, he said there's lots of evidence to support that regular exercise lowers the risk of cardiovascular disease and Alzheimer's.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rando, who's currently dealing with an Achilles tendon injury, said he's running a little less often and focusing a little more on &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="https://www.businessinsider.com/exercise-for-healthy-aging-longevity-strength-training-personal-trainer-2024-8" data-track-click='{"element_name":"body_link","event":"tout_click","index":"bi_value_unassigned","product_field":"bi_value_unassigned"}' rel=""&gt;strength training&lt;/a&gt;, which is also important for healthy aging as muscle mass declines over time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Beyond the anti-aging benefits, he said he loves how running makes him feel. "I think clearly, I think I solve problems when I run," he said. "So that was an added icing on the cake."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="7d009965-fefe-45cd-98cb-fe50527e38cf" data-toc-id="7d009965-fefe-45cd-98cb-fe50527e38cf"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;He fasts one day a week&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
              &lt;figure class="figure image-figure-image   " data-type="img" data-e2e-name="image-figure-image" data-media-container="image" itemscope="" itemtype="https://schema.org/ImageObject"&gt;
              
              
                
              
              &lt;span class="image-source-caption "&gt;
                    &lt;figcaption class="image-caption headline-semibold" data-e2e-name="image-caption"&gt;
                      Rando often snacks on edamame.
                      
              &lt;span class="image-source headline-regular" data-e2e-name="image-source" itemprop="creditText"&gt;
              
              pada smith/Getty Images
              
              &lt;/span&gt;
                    &lt;/figcaption&gt;
                  &lt;/span&gt;
              &lt;/figure&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;Rando generally follows the &lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.businessinsider.com/mediterranean-diet-best-healthy-eating-longevity-rankings-2025-1" data-track-click='{"element_name":"body_link","event":"tout_click","index":"bi_value_unassigned","product_field":"bi_value_unassigned"}' rel=""&gt;Mediterranean diet&lt;/a&gt;, considered the healthiest diet in the world. He eats lean protein, fruits, and vegetables while cutting back on red meat, carbohydrates, and processed foods.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I love a steak dinner, and I'll splurge on that," Rando said. "But my typical dinners are either purely vegetarian or with some light meat or some fish."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For decades, he's practiced a form of &lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.businessinsider.com/intermittent-fasting-benefits-and-risks-for-longevity-weight-loss-cancer-2024-4" data-track-click='{"element_name":"body_link","event":"tout_click","index":"bi_value_unassigned","product_field":"bi_value_unassigned"}' rel=""&gt;intermittent fasting&lt;/a&gt; where he doesn't eat breakfast. He usually has a light lunch of edamame and hard-boiled eggs, and eats his biggest meal at dinner. Some studies find that intermittent fasting can help &lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.businessinsider.com/intermittent-fasting-burn-fat-control-blood-sugar-study-2024-9" data-track-click='{"element_name":"body_link","event":"tout_click","index":"bi_value_unassigned","product_field":"bi_value_unassigned"}' rel=""&gt;control blood sugar levels&lt;/a&gt; and burn fat, while others show &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="https://www.businessinsider.com/intermittent-fasting-linked-higher-risk-of-early-death-controversial-study-2024-3" data-track-click='{"element_name":"body_link","event":"tout_click","index":"bi_value_unassigned","product_field":"bi_value_unassigned"}' rel=""&gt;mixed evidence&lt;/a&gt; that intermittent fasting has sustained benefits.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Over the past few years, Rando also &lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.businessinsider.com/i-tried-intermittent-fasting-like-elon-musk-for-a-month-2023-3" data-track-click='{"element_name":"body_link","event":"tout_click","index":"bi_value_unassigned","product_field":"bi_value_unassigned"}' rel=""&gt;fasts for 24 hours&lt;/a&gt; once a week, another form of time-restricted eating. Because dinner is his biggest meal, he usually starts fasting until dinner the next day, rather than starting the fast in the morning.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Still, he isn't super strict about fasting. "My lifestyle is just not conducive to fasting multiple days in a row, partly because of the exercise, partly because I'm going to dinners and lunches with people," he said. "But I do believe in fasting as a means toward healthy aging."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Because intermittent fasting is still being studied, including any potential &lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.businessinsider.com/intermittent-fasting-linked-higher-risk-of-early-death-controversial-study-2024-3" data-track-click='{"element_name":"body_link","event":"tout_click","index":"bi_value_unassigned","product_field":"bi_value_unassigned"}' rel=""&gt;long-term risks&lt;/a&gt;, Rando considers it "a leap of faith."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I believe from the science that this will have a long-term benefit," he said. But it's not because he feels the same immediate effects as he does from exercising. "I just feel hungry."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="79f543fd-3c7e-4043-b25b-91b16aa4e42c" data-toc-id="79f543fd-3c7e-4043-b25b-91b16aa4e42c"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Socializing at work&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
              &lt;figure class="figure image-figure-image   " data-type="img" data-e2e-name="image-figure-image" data-media-container="image" itemscope="" itemtype="https://schema.org/ImageObject"&gt;
              
              
                
              
              &lt;span class="image-source-caption "&gt;
                    &lt;figcaption class="image-caption headline-semibold" data-e2e-name="image-caption"&gt;
                      Rando said he has a "very social" job.
                      
              &lt;span class="image-source headline-regular" data-e2e-name="image-source" itemprop="creditText"&gt;
              
              VioletaStoimenova/Getty Images
              
              &lt;/span&gt;
                    &lt;/figcaption&gt;
                  &lt;/span&gt;
              &lt;/figure&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;As president of AFAR, Rando naturally interacts with a lot of people. "Through my work, I lead a very social life," he said, including collaborating with other researchers, sitting on various committees, and attending events. He said he also makes it a point to &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="https://www.businessinsider.com/retirement-isolation-friends-rejection-2025-3" data-track-click='{"element_name":"body_link","event":"tout_click","index":"bi_value_unassigned","product_field":"bi_value_unassigned"}' rel=""&gt;socialize outside work&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While he said it's harder to quantify the impact of social ties on longevity, there's a lot of compelling anecdotal evidence in favor of it. Some of it comes from Rando's own research: &lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.businessinsider.com/longevity-habits-from-96-year-old-doctor-2025-9" data-track-click='{"element_name":"body_link","event":"tout_click","index":"bi_value_unassigned","product_field":"bi_value_unassigned"}' rel=""&gt;Dr. Ira Eliasoph&lt;/a&gt;, a 96-year-old AFAR study participant, said strong relationships helped him live a long life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I believe in the evidence that social interactions are really important as people get older," Rando said.&lt;/p&gt;
            
            
            &lt;/section&gt;
            
            
            
            
            
            
    
    
    
    
      &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Business Insider</author><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 21:03:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiqAFBVV95cUxPdGtjVGw1UXE3cUpJcEFUYzN4VHpMU1FDeUMzd1N4bUpCcWZYQW5rTDU1dDN3eldSUkFPOGx6TWFOOUpGRDlnNDV2WnBsZWc3Qk93S2RBWXJYOXl0Rzl1LW9EQ0doUGYxenhQelNGdElmbGh3NmJiRHZmeGVrT2Frc20tZi1WN0I1WDVxTlJHT0d0bHE5YjBaZGwtM096WXBhVTB5WkViS1I</guid></item><item><title>由于疫苗接种的担忧，南卡罗来纳州麻疹疫情增加到185例-半岛电视台</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2026/1/2/south-carolina-measles-outbreak-grows-to-185-cases-amid-vaccination-worries</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="wysiwyg wysiwyg--all-content" aria-live="polite" aria-atomic="true"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Officials in the United States have announced that the measles outbreak in the southern state of South Carolina has grown to 185 cases, up nine from earlier this week.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In Friday’s update, state officials specified that 172 of the cases involved patients who had not received the measles, mumps and rubella (MMR) vaccine, designed to protect against infection.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;section class="more-on"&gt;&lt;h2 class="more-on__heading"&gt;Recommended Stories &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;span class="screen-reader-text"&gt;list of 3 items&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="screen-reader-text"&gt;end of list&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;p&gt;Four others involved patients who were partially vaccinated, four had an unknown vaccination status, and another four cases are still under investigation. Only one of the infections involved a fully vaccinated person.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Measles, a highly infectious and sometimes deadly virus, was declared eliminated in the US more than 25 years ago. But the past year has presented increasing challenges to maintaining that status.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Diseases are generally declared eliminated when there is no local transmission in a given region, although cases can still be “imported” from abroad.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The US’s elimination status is largely credited to the success of the MMR vaccine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In 1963, the first measles vaccine was licensed in the US, and by 1971, the combination MMR vaccine was unveiled to protect against the three illnesses at once. Two shots are typically recommended to achieve full vaccination status.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Initially, in 1978, the US Centers for Disease Control and Prevention (CDC) set 1982 as a deadline to achieve the elimination of measles in the country. It missed that target by nearly 18 years, reaching elimination status in 2000.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But vaccine hesitancy has been blamed for allowing the virus to spread in the US, both then and now.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While the death rate for measles is relatively low, its infection rate is high. The CDC estimates that, if one person has the virus, they could infect nine out of every 10 people around them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The World Health Organization says that, for every 1,000 reported cases, there are about two to three deaths.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Children are especially vulnerable. Complications can include high fever, hearing or vision loss and encephalitis, an inflammation of the brain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Typically, medical professionals recommend children be vaccinated early in their lives, receiving their first dose before 15 months of age and their second by age six. The vaccine is widely accepted as safe.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But vaccine scepticism has been on the rise in the US, with critics blaming, in part, policies implemented under the administration of President Donald Trump.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to CDC data, the MMR vaccination rate in the US was 95.2 percent among kindergarteners during the 2019-2020 school year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That number, however, tumbled to 92.7 percent by the 2023-2024 school year, representing a difference of 280,000 kindergarteners.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;2025 represented a high-water mark in the resurgence of the measles virus. The CDC reported 2,065 cases of measles last year, the most since 1991 — and more than seven times the rate of 2024, when only 285 cases were reported.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One of the biggest outbreaks took place in Texas, where three people died from the virus, with the first reported last February. Prior to that incident, no death had been reported from measles in the US &lt;a href="/news/2025/2/27/us-reports-first-measles-death-since-2015"&gt;since 2015&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the wake of that death, Trump’s Health and Human Services Secretary Robert F Kennedy Jr &lt;a href="/news/2025/3/3/rfk-jr-noted-vaccine-sceptic-backs-measles-jab-amid-deadly-us-outbreak"&gt;encouraged&lt;/a&gt; vaccination, &lt;a href="https://x.com/SecKennedy/status/1908967854394982414" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;writing&lt;/a&gt; on social media, “The most effective way to prevent the spread of measles is the MMR vaccine.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But Kennedy, who is not a medical professional, has since expressed views that appeared to discourage the vaccine’s use.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In late April, for instance, he told NewsNation, “The MMR vaccine contains a lot of aborted fetus debris and DNA particles.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Experts, however, have denounced that claim as false. While the rubella part of the vaccine was developed using a cell culture that came from an elective abortion in the 1960s, no fetal tissue has been used since, nor is there any fetal issue in the vaccine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kennedy has also spread unfounded claims that purport to link vaccination to autism, despite widespread outcry from the medical community.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In South Carolina, the current measles outbreak is concentrated in the northwest. The South Carolina Department of Public Health says that the reported infections are largely in children under the age of 17.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One Democratic candidate running in the state’s 2026 midterm elections, paediatrician Annie Andrews, has made combating the outbreak a central part of her campaign. She hopes to unseat incumbent Senator Lindsey Graham, a Republican, in November’s vote.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“If you told me back in medical school that someday I would be running for the Senate and my campaign slogan would be ‘It’s me or the measles’ I WOULD DEFINITELY NOT HAVE BELIEVED YOU,” she wrote on social media on Friday.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Al Jazeera</author><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 21:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMitgFBVV95cUxQNV81dDR2M294OVc5eC1hNmZ1dGlQWnNwVllLbGJmaWtMSzBZQ1U2R1F6NWU0dUkzQ3FKODFEb1ZwT2hmN2RsTTRVMHRlSVdoX2hGYngwOWpJVTRUMm0zcmFjR25GV25GUzBRTlZ6SmNHZXR1LWZqR3FNb3FBNTEzXzFTTk1wQUIxVHU1NVJXdVZwTHItUVd3Ync3NVc0bkhjTUFHdV9nb3AxSEZFeGtyS0w2R2g3d9IBuwFBVV95cUxQa25QeGhGZl96LU45NlhpRTNXYXZNN2pRMUpqeUhZckNtNW1HVEFieVppckNWYktMZ2hrLVRKOWJPZEtLV1kyYkRLd3I1QklLUHRXa1VqdWJjMGd2RDBHTHFvOU4yUXplcHFjS09COEpkYmZIamQtZ2JkVU4tSk9DTEhwRFdzdFg3d1JScXhjcVI3c1g2Y3pTVkgwZFdyQV94OGF6SGpuQ21FbWo2aHNydzlYa1A4NkVnV0dJ</guid></item><item><title>纽约流感住院治疗人数创历史新高--哥谭氏症患者</title><link>https://gothamist.com/news/flu-hospitalizations-in-new-york-hit-record-high</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="streamfield-paragraph rte-text"&gt;&lt;p data-block-key="2ijth"&gt;More than 4,500 New York residents were hospitalized with the flu last week — marking the highest number ever recorded in a single week, health officials said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-block-key="1d72n"&gt;The state Department of Health said there were 4,546 flu hospitalizations last week, a 24% increase from the week before.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-block-key="2isf3"&gt;Health officials are warning of severe influenza cases and spread season and are urging people to get vaccinated if they haven’t.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-block-key="cm3lt"&gt;“We are having a more severe flu season than prior years, almost 1,000 more people were admitted to a hospital during this most recent seven-day period compared to the prior week,” state Health Commissioner Dr. James McDonald said in a statement on Friday.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-block-key="dit5g"&gt;“There is still time to get a flu shot and remember, flu can be treated with antiviral medication if started within 48 hours of symptom onset and your doctor deems appropriate.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-block-key="4atju"&gt;The number of people diagnosed with the flu overall — not just those who were hospitalized — also reached a record &lt;a href="https://gothamist.com/news/new-york-state-has-set-a-record-for-flu-cases-ahead-of-peak-season" rel="noopener" target="_blank"&gt;high last month&lt;/a&gt; of more than 72,000. Cases dropped last week by about a third to 49,000, state data show.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-block-key="drmio"&gt;Children, pregnant women, those with chronic medical conditions or those 65 years or older are at the highest risk for developing complications from the flu.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-block-key="969gg"&gt;Health officials say the best protection against the flu remains getting vaccinated. Vaccines are available at pharmacies, health care clinics or doctor’s offices and can be administered to children six months or older.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-block-key="6nqls"&gt;Other ways to prevent the spread of influenza includes: washing your hands often with soap and water for at least 20 seconds, cleaning and disinfecting frequently touched areas, staying home when sick, avoid touching your eyes, nose and mouth with unwashed hands and coughing or sneezing into a tissue and then discarding it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Gothamist</author><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 19:48:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigAFBVV95cUxPZ0ZYd2djb1o3VTBsRWdkaGRrYlFmZlZYUDVIMXNkZDZhaUk1MXBVdnVfVWlNSURBUGZwZUYtVF9RY2dON2pZUzJBZVNQdGVaMnpRVW9tOUNTVl9jZVQ1UmdJOUxpTEIzX1ZsZmJPX1F2SzlQRFNlcF9QbVNlQlN6ag</guid></item><item><title>自制啤酒疫苗的科学家： “它让我对病毒免疫” -泰晤士报</title><link>https://www.thetimes.com/us/news-today/article/beer-vaccine-homebrew-science-66bljr2jl</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;The makers of Guinness long ago claimed that it was good for you and anyone with a television set has been aware, since at least the 1970s, that Heineken supposedly refreshes the parts that other beers cannot reach. But no one until now has claimed that a pint could save your life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;Then came Chris Buck, a virologist at the National Cancer Institute, who is also an enthusiastic home brewer. Dr Buck believes he has created the world’s first beer vaccine. He brewed the first batch last summer using a yeast modified to contain a vaccine protein. It was a Lithuanian-style farmhouse ale that was awfully drinkable, and also appeared to immunise him against a virus linked to certain cancers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="paywall-EAB47CFD"&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;• &lt;a href="https://link.thetimes.co.uk/join/74t/signup-us?source=WebsiteArticle" class="link__RespLink-sc-1ocvixa-0 csWvlP"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Sign up for The Times’s weekly US newsletter&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;These tests suggested he had developed antibodies against two types of BK polyomavirus thought to cause certain types of bladder cancer, he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;In Buck’s view, this only the start of what a beer could do. “This one vaccine is just proving the principle,” he said. “Next on the agenda is Covid and flu and probably herpes viruses and adenovirus [associated with mild colds and flu] … Anything that is a common-cold virus is in our crosshairs now.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div id="3.4"&gt;&lt;div id="4b8161cc-ef17-499e-a054-980d0b7b55d2"&gt;&lt;div class="tc-view__TcView-nuazoi-0 responsive__PrimaryImg-sc-4v1r4q-3 hpWIYt"&gt;&lt;div class="tc-view__TcView-nuazoi-0 fPjBcr"&gt;&lt;div class="tc-view__TcView-nuazoi-0 responsive__InsetCaptionStyle-sc-1io40fc-2 fkMBIX"&gt;&lt;div class="tc-view__TcView-nuazoi-0 fPjBcr"&gt;&lt;div class="tc-view__TcView-nuazoi-0 fPjBcr"&gt;&lt;p class="tc-text__TcText-sc-15igzev-0 kwFxdN"&gt;The beer is a Lithuanian-style farmhouse ale&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;Nor does a vaccine have to be delivered in a beer. Buck, 55, thinks the modified yeast could be used to make yoghurt, or crisps, that could confer a similar immunity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;The scientist does not usually whip up experiments in his kitchen, and some of his peers are now alarmed that his homebrew adventures could damage public trust in vaccines. They also warn that one beer drinker conducting tests on himself does not establish the efficacy of a supposed treatment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;“I disagree,” said Buck, who has been a scientist at the National Institutes of Health since 2001. “I think if a food vaccine works in one person that tells you something very important, which is that it can work in &lt;i&gt;at least&lt;/i&gt; one person.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;Vaccines are often made inside insect cells, but they can also be created in yeast cells: there is then a tricky “purification” process, stripping everything else away to leave a protein particle for injection. “It eventually just occurred to me, like maybe we don’t have to purify,” he said. Perhaps the yeast could simply be eaten, or drunk in a foaming pint.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;The conventional wisdom is that this does not work because vaccine proteins are broken down by stomach acid, he said. This proved true when Buck and his colleagues fed mice with ground-up yeast containing vaccine proteins, supplied by a Lithuanian scientist named Alma Gedvilaite. But when they tried whole, live yeast containing the virus particles, the mice developed “robust antibody responses”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;“I literally felt weak at the knees,” Buck said. “I could see that this meant that the vaccine could be a food. And if it can be a food, it means you can regulate it like a food and it’s easy to distribute and many people will be happier about it than a shot. All of these implications were there at that first experiment a year and a half ago.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;Buck initially started working on potential vaccines for HIV, HPV and polyomaviruses. “Their name is ancient Greek for ‘many tumours’,” he said of the latter. “It causes cancer in mice for sure.” They can also cause serious problems for transplant patients taking immunosuppresant drugs. Buck’s laboratory at the National Cancer Institute is working with the biotech company Biological E on a vaccine for polyomaviruses that would be administered by injection, but they are still some distance from clinical trials. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;• &lt;a href="https://www.thetimes.com/us/news-today/article/measles-30-year-high-rfkj-cdc-9mqtjjxw0" class="link__RespLink-sc-1ocvixa-0 csWvlP"&gt;&lt;b&gt;US measles cases surpass 2,000 for first time in 30 years&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;A food-based, or beer-based vaccine, available at once, could potentially save lives, he said. “Anyone who is waiting for a transplant would like this vaccine,” he said. “If I were waiting for a transplant I would get it immediately.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;Besides being suspected of causing cancer, the polyomavirus can cause a painful bladder condition in patients who receive bone-marrow transplants. Buck recalls visiting a paediatric hospital that had installed sound-proofing in its lavatories to dampen the sounds of children with the condition screaming in the middle of the night. It may also cause a painful bladder condition in older women, he said. Patients with it “shed a lot of polyomavirus in their urine”, he said. “That’s not causality … but [if] you have painful bladder syndrome, you brew beer, you drink beer, and if the pain goes away, then you say ‘Yahtzee’.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;He said he tried to put the beer idea before an institutional review board at the National Institutes of Health. “A senior official in the chain bounced away the application before it could be considered,” he said. “The friction was that the institution is not accustomed to thinking about food.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;He thinks they were trying to assess it the way they would a drug.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;Buck didn’t have much patience for that red tape. “Instead of trying to convince them what the law was, I basically demonstrated what the law was by doing it in my kitchen,” he said. He got his younger brother Andrew to form a company, and sell batches of the beer to two close friends. “We just need a company with a record of sales,” said Buck, who lives in Bethesda, Maryland. “If something is already in the food supply and doesn’t appear to be causing problems, then the manufacturer can just say, look, it’s generally recognised as safe because it’s already there and we don’t know of any problems.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;Over the summer, after drinking his own beer but before tests showed he had developed antibodies, Buck spoke at a virology conference in southern Italy. Michael Imperiale, a virologist and emeritus professor at the University of Michigan Medical School, watched his presentation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;“I said: ‘What are you going to do if someone has a bad reaction to this?’” Imperiale said. He felt that one man and his brother drinking a beer vaccine was not enough to show that something was safe. He said that trials on, say, a thousand people with diverse genetics would be required. But his main concern was that with Robert F Kennedy Jr, a famous vaccine sceptic who as US health secretary has diminished trust in vaccines, it could make matters worse to have a government scientist brewing them in his kitchen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;“The US government itself is trying to actively get people to be against vaccines, right?” Imperiale said. “We, the scientific community, really have to keep that in mind … Is what we’re doing going to enhance the public trust or is it going to make it worse?”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div id="3.24"&gt;&lt;div id="a6cd19d8-50d5-4944-beca-8f518387f398"&gt;&lt;div class="tc-view__TcView-nuazoi-0 responsive__PrimaryImg-sc-4v1r4q-3 hpWIYt"&gt;&lt;div class="tc-view__TcView-nuazoi-0 fPjBcr"&gt;&lt;div class="tc-view__TcView-nuazoi-0 responsive__InsetCaptionStyle-sc-1io40fc-2 fkMBIX"&gt;&lt;div class="tc-view__TcView-nuazoi-0 fPjBcr"&gt;&lt;div class="tc-view__TcView-nuazoi-0 fPjBcr"&gt;&lt;p class="tc-text__TcText-sc-15igzev-0 kwFxdN"&gt;The beer becomes fluorescent under blue light&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;Several other scientists have told Science News, which first reported on Buck’s vaccine beer, that they have similar concerns.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;But Buck says his own mother is an antivaxer. “She lives in eastern Washington state, which is a very rural environment. All of her church friends are antivaxers,” he said. “I used to agree with the view that the solution to distrust of vaccines was to raise our safety standards and have more and more stringent qualifications for vaccines that hit the market. And with hindsight, I think it backfired.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;He thinks scientists’ efforts to show that they take elaborate care with a vaccine — Buck refers to it as “security theatre” — only made people think: “Wow, that thing must be really dangerous.” But producing a vaccine that people can make in their own kitchen proves a vaccine “is just some ordinary thing that is not that dangerous”, he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;On December 17, Buck and his brother published a non-peer-reviewed paper, &lt;i&gt;Vaccine Beer: A Personal Healthcare Report&lt;/i&gt;, which contained recipes for vaccine beer. In the coming months, he hopes to persuade a company to manufacture the modified yeast and to find a brewer willing to make a line of what he calls VAC-beer (Vaccine Antigen Containing) for sale in North America. (He doubts it could be sold in Britain or Europe, given the regulations on genetically modified foodstuffs.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;“I don’t know what Robert Kennedy is going to make of this,” he said. “This is my boss’s boss’s boss and I do not know whether he will think: ‘Oh, it looks like health food, I love it!’ Or: ‘Oh, it looks like a vaccine, I hate it.’ I have no idea how that’s going to come out.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;• &lt;a href="https://www.thetimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/article/vaccine-sceptic-conspiracist-liar-its-rfk-jr-ts9pkvpv7" class="link__RespLink-sc-1ocvixa-0 csWvlP"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Vaccine sceptic, conspiracist, ‘liar’: it’s Robert F Kennedy Jr&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;What about his mother?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;“Mom seems entirely amenable to beer vaccine,” he said. “But I wouldn’t call it an informative datapoint because my love for food and home fermentation projects was inherited directly from her. The more interesting datapoints are Mom’s church friends.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="last-paragraph" class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;He added: “In a couple cases, I intuited some level of quiet glee about the idea of having an excuse to drink beer.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Times</author><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 19:20:28 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijwFBVV95cUxQWlU3TzJELXhZUU1WR0ZWU3d6aDRISTZUcEYtMmlydDdDQlVsWWladjlFSlJwMVpyX0lqbVpoVlBPYmt5ZTJ2WFFQbklXaDdwRWV6TUdGaDhnQTNmbThjczJwY3cwaVdDTWxKQ3FjM3l3MFhhUU9uWi1FMS0waWx2bWlxWVlxaVljWXdYeVVQOA</guid></item><item><title>纽约报告一周内流感住院人数破纪录- ABC新闻</title><link>https://abcnews.go.com/Health/new-york-reports-record-breaking-number-flu-hospitalizations/story?id=128849108</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="xvlfx ZRifP TKoO eaKKC EcdEg bOdfO qXhdi NFNeu UyHES " data-testid="prism-article-body"&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao MvWXB TjIXL aGjvy ebVHC "&gt;New York is reporting the highest number of flu hospitalizations recorded in a single week, the state's health department said on Friday.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;During the week ending Dec. 27, 4,546 people were hospitalized with flu, a 24% increase from the 3,666 who were hospitalized the previous week, according to data from the New York State Department of Health (NYSOH)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;It comes after the state reported a record-breaking number of flu cases in a single week with 72,133 infections during the week ending Dec. 20.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;NYSDOH &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://health.ny.gov/diseases/communicable/influenza/seasonal/providers/prevention_of_influenza_transmission/docs/2025-12-02_flu_prevalent.pdf" target="_blank" dir="ltr"&gt;issued a declaration&lt;/a&gt; last month stating influenza is prevalent in New York, which requires health care facilities and agencies to ensure any staff who have not received this year's flu vaccine wear masks in any areas where patients and residents may be present.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;"We are having a more severe flu season than prior years, almost 1,000 more people were admitted to a hospital during this most recent seven-day period compared to the prior week," Dr. James McDonald, the state's health commissioner, said in a statement on Friday.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="oLzSq QrHMO fnRUo pvsTF EhJPu vPlOC zNYgW OsTsW RMeqy daRVX ISNQ sKyCY eRftA acPPc MENS nFwaT MCnQE mEeeY SmBjI xegrY rPLsU iulOd NIuqO zzscu lzDCc aHUBM IEgzD OjMNy eQqcx SVqKB GQmdz jaoD VWDdR ONJdw vrZxD OnRTz gbbfF roDbV GPGwb oMlSS gfNzt oJhud eXZcf zhVlX "&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="InlineImage GpQCA lZur asrEW " data-testid="prism-inline-image"&gt;&lt;figure class="kzIjN GNmeK pYrtp dSqFO " data-testid="prism-figure"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;div class="nMMea bNYiy Mjgpa dGwha DDmxa jgKNG RGHCC aBIU PriDW lZur " data-testid="prism-caption"&gt;&lt;p class="HXPPJ barbu yKsXL IzgMt VcHIt uhSzI YGNMU cRAsZ xqMcl QtRul "&gt;&lt;span class="hsDdd OOSI GpQCA lZur VlFaz " data-testid="prism-truncate"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="gtOSm FbbUW tUtYa vOCwz EQwFq yCufu eEak Qmvg nyTIa SRXVc vzLa jgBfc WXDas CiUCW kqbG zrdEG txGfn ygKVe BbezD UOtxr CVfpq xijV soGRS XgdC sEIlf daWqJ "&gt;Weekly flu hospitalizations in New York State, week ending Oct. 4, 2025 - week ending Dec. 27, 2025&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="qinlA IpWvx oqZz tylGM lyWxS nWcVF UhTug PPcLh YxlyB "&gt;&lt;span class="gtOSm FbbUW tUtYa vOCwz EQwFq yCufu eEak Qmvg nyTIa SRXVc vzLa jgBfc WXDas CiUCW kqbG zrdEG txGfn ygKVe BbezD UOtxr CVfpq xijV soGRS XgdC sEIlf daWqJ YNujN JGtjI aZFDu rkKLh "&gt;New York State Department of Health&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Meanwhile, flu activity is also spiking nationwide. The Centers for Disease Control and Prevention estimates there have been at least ​7.5 million illnesses, ​81,000 hospitalizations and ​3,100 deaths from flu so far this season.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;New York is one of 20 states recording "very high" levels of respiratory illness activity, according to the latest &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://www.cdc.gov/fluview/surveillance/usmap.html" target="_blank" dir="ltr"&gt;CDC data&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Public health experts previously told ABC News that many of this season's cases are linked to a new flu strain called subclade K -- a variant of the H3N2 virus, which is itself a subtype of influenza A.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Subclade K has been circulating since the summer in other countries and was a main driver of a spike in flu cases in Canada, Japan and the U.K.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Of the 1,600 flu samples &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://www.cdc.gov/fluview/surveillance/2025-week-51.html" target="_blank" dir="ltr"&gt;tested by the CDC&lt;/a&gt;, roughly ​92% were H3N2. Of those samples, nearly ​90% belonged to subclade K.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Experts expect flu-like illnesses to continue to climb in the coming weeks after holiday gatherings and colder weather. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Currently, the &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://www.cdc.gov/flu/vaccines/index.html" target="_blank" dir="ltr"&gt;CDC recommends&lt;/a&gt; that everyone aged 6 months and older, with rare exceptions, get a flu vaccine.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;The federal health agency states on its website that getting an annual flu shot prevents millions of illnesses and flu-related doctors' visits every year and is especially important for those at higher risk of serious complications.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;The flu vaccine is currently available to New Yorkers aged 2 years and older at a health care provider's office or at participating pharmacies while children aged 6 months and older can receive the flu vaccine at a health care provider's office, according to the state health department.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;"There is still time to get a flu shot and remember, flu can be treated with antiviral medication if started within 48 hours of symptom onset and your doctor deems appropriate," McDonald said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC eTIW sUzSN "&gt;&lt;em class=" "&gt;ABC News' Youri Benadjaoud contributed to this report.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ABC News</author><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 19:11:38 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMirgFBVV95cUxNY2h6bEd0OTltZ0t5c2ZDbnBONmN0WVZZck1NOGlaT3NubUpmTEFtMnlOUGlKZHNxMEtwRG9rQ1BwQU5ULW5TSVlGS041Wl9PbHN4YU15cExlT1Z4anE5ci1JeVZsaGpKX1lWV1JFSC1sLWtkaDBLVk12aW1RZXpyX1BRYk9uT3hnNC1SbGlRRFpZME1abnd4cm5DQl9obWFyeXJVTlpvUlZLMGV0S2fSAbMBQVVfeXFMT0d5djBIYWlOQk1iVFQtS2tVYjIzSWpBbXpVRklaWWd0QWs2SDllSC1CeTZtejJvcG4zZ2JwbGhabTEwU0xJR1RkWlA2N1F1Zm00a2VZcmdKYXJYYTdXMzJfZ3dRMnhLUU0zNlRVclV6SnUxa3NyV1R4TFU5Qmx6YWMweGRuMTdIeGR4enRKQ3N3TEVadC1JS2NjY0hsdDJpNGxGYUM2c3huNnl2WlQxYktPNEU</guid></item><item><title>Google AI Overviews通过误导性的健康建议使人们面临伤害风险-《卫报》</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2026/jan/02/google-ai-overviews-risk-harm-misleading-health-information</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body-commercial-selector article-body-viewer-selector dcr-hdpgoq"&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;People are being put at risk of harm by false and misleading health information in Google’s artificial intelligence summaries, a Guardian investigation has found.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The company has said its AI Overviews, which use generative AI to provide snapshots of essential information about a topic or question, are “&lt;a href="https://blog.google/products/search/generative-ai-google-search-may-2024/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;helpful&lt;/a&gt;” and “&lt;a href="https://search.google/intl/en-GB/ways-to-search/ai-overviews/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;reliable&lt;/a&gt;”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="sign-in-gate"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;But some of the summaries, which appear at the top of search results, served up inaccurate health information and put people at risk of harm.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;In one case that experts described as “really dangerous”, Google wrongly advised people with pancreatic cancer to avoid high-fat foods. Experts said this was the exact opposite of what should be recommended, and may increase the risk of patients dying from the disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;In another “alarming” example, the company provided bogus information about crucial liver function tests, which could leave people with serious liver disease wrongly thinking they are healthy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="180f50ba-2a37-479b-b92f-cc3092c578b2" data-spacefinder-role="richLink" data-spacefinder-type="model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.RichLinkBlockElement" class="dcr-47fhrn"&gt;&lt;gu-island name="RichLinkComponent" priority="feature" deferuntil="idle" props='{"richLinkIndex":5,"element":{"_type":"model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.RichLinkBlockElement","prefix":"Related: ","text":"Third of UK citizens have used AI for emotional support, research reveals","elementId":"180f50ba-2a37-479b-b92f-cc3092c578b2","role":"richLink","url":"https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2025/dec/18/artificial-intelligence-uk-emotional-support-research"},"ajaxUrl":"https://api.nextgen.guardianapps.co.uk","format":{"design":0,"display":0,"theme":0}}'&gt;&lt;/gu-island&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Google searches for answers about women’s cancer tests also provided “completely wrong” information, which experts said could result in people dismissing genuine symptoms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;A Google spokesperson said that many of the health examples shared with them were “incomplete screenshots”, but from what they could assess they linked “to well-known, reputable sources and recommend seeking out expert advice”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The Guardian investigation comes amid growing concern that AI data can confuse consumers who may assume that it is reliable. In November last year, a study found AI chatbots across a range of platforms &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2025/nov/18/warning-ai-chatbots-inaccurate-financial-advice-tips-chatgpt-copilot-uk" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;gave inaccurate financial advice&lt;/a&gt;, while similar concerns have been raised about &lt;a href="https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/articles/cq5ggew08eyo" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;summaries of news stories&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Sophie Randall, director of the Patient Information Forum, which promotes evidence-based health information to patients, the public and healthcare professionals, said the examples showed “Google’s AI Overviews can put inaccurate health information at the top of online searches, presenting a risk to people’s health”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Stephanie Parker, the director of digital at Marie Curie, an end-of-life charity, said: “People turn to the internet in moments of worry and crisis. If the information they receive is inaccurate or out of context, it can seriously harm their health.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The Guardian uncovered several cases of inaccurate health information in Google’s AI Overviews after a number of health groups, charities and professionals raised concerns.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Anna Jewell, the director of support, research and influencing at Pancreatic Cancer UK, said advising patients to avoid high-fat foods was “completely incorrect”. Doing so “could be really dangerous and jeopardise a person’s chances of being well enough to have treatment”, she added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Jewell said: “The Google AI response suggests that people with pancreatic cancer avoid high-fat foods and provides a list of examples. However, if someone followed what the search result told them then they might not take in enough calories, struggle to put on weight, and be unable to tolerate either chemotherapy or potentially life-saving surgery.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Typing “what is the normal range for liver blood tests” also served up misleading information, with masses of numbers, little context and no accounting for nationality, sex, ethnicity or age of patients.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Pamela Healy, the chief executive of the British Liver Trust, said the AI summaries were alarming. “Many people with liver disease show no symptoms until the late stages, which is why it’s so important that they get tested. But what the Google AI Overviews say is ‘normal’ can vary drastically from what is actually considered normal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“It’s dangerous because it means some people with serious liver disease may think they have a normal result then not bother to attend a follow-up healthcare meeting.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure data-spacefinder-role="inline" data-spacefinder-type="model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.NewsletterSignupBlockElement" class="dcr-173mewl"&gt;&lt;gu-island name="EmailSignUpWrapper" priority="feature" deferuntil="visible" props="{&amp;quot;index&amp;quot;:17,&amp;quot;listId&amp;quot;:4156,&amp;quot;identityName&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;morning-briefing&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;description&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;Our morning email breaks down the key stories of the day, telling you what’s happening and why it matters&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;name&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;First Edition&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;frequency&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;Every weekday&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;successDescription&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;We'll send you First Edition every weekday&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;theme&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;news&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;idApiUrl&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;https://idapi.theguardian.com&amp;quot;}"&gt;&lt;/gu-island&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;A search for “vaginal cancer symptoms and tests” listed a pap test as a test for vaginal cancer, which is incorrect.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Athena Lamnisos, the chief executive of the Eve Appeal cancer charity, said: “It isn’t a test to detect cancer, and certainly isn’t a test to detect vaginal cancer – this is completely wrong information. Getting wrong information like this could potentially lead to someone not getting vaginal cancer symptoms checked because they had a clear result at a recent cervical screening.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“We were also worried by the fact that the AI summary changed when we did the exact same search, coming up with a different response each time that pulled from different sources. That means that people are getting a different answer depending on when they search, and that’s not good enough.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Lamnisos said she was extremely concerned. “Some of the results we’ve seen are really worrying and can potentially put women in danger,” she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The Guardian also found Google AI Overviews delivered misleading results for searches about mental health conditions. “This is a huge concern for us as a charity,” said Stephen Buckley, the head of information at Mind.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Some of the AI summaries for conditions such as psychosis and eating disorders offered “very dangerous advice” and were “incorrect, harmful or could lead people to avoid seeking help”, Buckley said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Some also missed out important context or nuance, he added. “They may suggest accessing information from sites that are inappropriate … and we know that when AI summarises information, it can often reflect existing biases, stereotypes or stigmatising narratives.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Google said the vast majority of its AI Overviews were factual and helpful, and it continuously made quality improvements. The accuracy rate of AI Overviews was on a par with its other search features like featured snippets, which had existed for more than a decade, it added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The company also said that when AI Overviews misinterpreted web content or missed context, it would take action as appropriate under its policies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;A Google spokesperson said: “We invest significantly in the quality of AI Overviews, particularly for topics like health, and the vast majority provide accurate information.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Guardian</author><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 18:19:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMirwFBVV95cUxNQXBwR0FUdTRWaVBla050WU9xQW9YMDlERXdOc2hnZ0pLS2FBbjhmMmZaZ1ZKSTZNTUdMekc1ZmZWcExJaGRTVFctYm94dHlJZVNOOWJhOVdFcVdrVWx0RjZuSzhmeEdxbVRsRElfNDdMUERxVHNic293NVMyT1N2aDlRT09KMnY0NHkwODZlUzYwNjVtVDFtdlkyZ2JxWS1KMWwwRU1nTXRTNGk4a3dv</guid></item><item><title>专家遵循6条长寿规则，在2026年实现更健康的衰老-福克斯新闻</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/health/6-longevity-rules-experts-follow-healthier-aging-2026</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body"&gt; &lt;div id="beyondwords-wrapper" class="beyondwords-wrapper"&gt;&lt;p class="info"&gt;&lt;span class="label-bg"&gt;NEW&lt;/span&gt;You can now listen to Fox News articles!
  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="speakable"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PILLARS OF HEALTH — &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/health/6-pillars-healthier-lifestyle-2026-from-experts-staying-young" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;6 tips&lt;/a&gt; to extend longevity in the new year, according to experts&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="speakable"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WEIGHT-LOSS WAVE —&lt;/strong&gt; Oprah and other high-profile celebrities revealed &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/health/oprah-joins-wave-celebrities-who-revealed-dramatic-weight-loss-2025" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;dramatic transformations&lt;/a&gt; in 2025&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="image-ct inline"&gt; &lt;div class="info"&gt;&lt;div class="caption"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;To boost the success rate of resolutions, two doctors recommend pivoting from "quick fixes" and focusing more on science-based ways to achieve long-term wellness.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;(iStock)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DOSING DOUBTS —&lt;/strong&gt; Older Americans are quitting &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/health/older-americans-quitting-glp-1-weight-loss-drugs-4-key-reasons" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;GLP-1 weight-loss drugs&lt;/a&gt; for 4 key reasons&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/newsletters?cmpid=fnfirstnl"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;SIGN UP FOR OUR HEALTH NEWSLETTER&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;BRAIN BALANCE — &lt;/strong&gt;Alzheimer’s disease could be reversed by boosting &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/health/alzheimers-disease-could-reversed-restoring-brain-balance-study-suggests" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;critical chemical&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;HEALTH SPOTLIGHT&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;—&lt;/strong&gt; 5 celebrities who went public with alarming &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/health/celebrities-who-went-public-alarming-health-diagnoses-2025" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;medical diagnoses&lt;/a&gt; in 2025&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="image-ct inline"&gt; &lt;div class="info"&gt;&lt;div class="caption"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Billy Joel, Kim Kardashian and Eric Dane are among the handful of celebrities who have reported health complications in 2025.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;(Myrna M. Suarez/Getty Images; Aeon/GC Images; Marvin Joseph/The Washington Post via Getty Images)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;NATURAL REMEDY — &lt;/strong&gt;Traditional Brazilian plant shows &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/health/brazilian-coastal-plant-shows-early-promise-easing-arthritis-inflammation" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;unexpected strength&lt;/a&gt; against arthritis&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/health"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;LIKE WHAT YOU'RE READING? CLICK HERE FOR MORE HEALTH NEWS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;div class="article-meta"&gt;&lt;div class="author-bio"&gt;&lt;p&gt;This article was written by Fox News staff.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Fox News</author><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 18:17:42 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijAFBVV95cUxONVNYdW1keVBMakozY2NQZXVHTE5mWkRpV045VWhVSHE5dHFqSmZwS01sSU94RmdJaU5rbDdscFhqMlB2Nm1nM1VpUGE1ZFhlaTg3MUlTQmxiak9GcWZaM0gxOEtXVU5RajBERDNtalVfaTFjc0cybnVYWDE4bDZsY19DRnllazVKOFlNQQ</guid></item><item><title>“超级流感”正在严重打击儿童-有些人无法生存- Gizmodo</title><link>https://gizmodo.com/the-super-flu-is-hitting-kids-hard-and-some-arent-surviving-2000704822</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content prose dark:prose-invert lg:prose-xl prose-science dark:prose-science"&gt;
                &lt;p&gt;The influenza season is in full swing, and it’s already proving to be deadly for some of the most vulnerable Americans around: children.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Several states have reported their first pediatric flu deaths this week. Cases and hospitalizations are rising across the country as well, while some areas are experiencing record-level surges of illness. The season is being driven by the emergence of an unexpected strain of the H3N2 flu, named subclade K.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="not-prose my-8 -mx-5 xs:max-w-xs xs:mx-auto"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;Tragic deaths&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;Due to the holidays, the &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/fluview/surveillance/2025-week-51.html"&gt;most current flu data&lt;/a&gt; from the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention (CDC) is nearly two weeks old. Yet it’s still evident that this season is gearing up to be a nasty one.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;As of December 20, flu activity was high or very high in 32 regions of the U.S. and moderate in eight other jurisdictions. The cumulative flu hospitalization rate in week 51 was also the third highest it’s been at this point in the past 15 years (the 2022-23 and 2023-24 seasons were the other two).&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="not-prose"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Things have been even worse for some states. Last week, for example, New York health officials &lt;a href="https://www.health.ny.gov/press/releases/2025/2025-12-26_flu_cases.htm"&gt;reported&lt;/a&gt; experiencing the largest weekly surge in flu cases ever recorded in modern history—71,123 positive flu cases during the week of December 20.&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;p&gt;At least eight pediatric flu deaths this winter have also been recorded by the CDC so far, though local health officials and members of the public have documented more since.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;On December 30, for instance, the Kentucky Department for Public Health &lt;a href="https://www.chfs.ky.gov/News/Documents/Kentucky%20Reports%201st%20Pediatric%20Influenza%20Death%20This%20Respiratory%20Virus%20Season.pdf"&gt;reported&lt;/a&gt; its first pediatric flu death of the 2025-26 season: a child from Kenton County who did not receive a flu vaccination. The next day, the Ohio Department of Health (ODH) &lt;a href="https://odh.ohio.gov/media-center/odh-news-releases/first-pediatric-flu-death-123125"&gt;reported&lt;/a&gt; its first pediatric flu death, which involved a teenager from Greene County. And on Thursday, Paul Kim, a popular social media influencer and Minnesota resident, &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/catholic-influencers-5-year-old-son-dies-contracting-flu-rcna251834"&gt;announced&lt;/a&gt; that his five-year-old son died after contracting a severe bout of flu.&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;p&gt;“This death is tragic and our hearts go out to the family,” said Bruce Vanderhoff, director of the Ohio Department of Health, in a &lt;a href="https://odh.ohio.gov/media-center/odh-news-releases/first-pediatric-flu-death-123125"&gt;statement&lt;/a&gt;. “It also reminds us that influenza, though common, is a serious health threat, and we urge parents to protect their kids.”&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;h2&gt;A record bad winter?&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;Even during a typical winter, the seasonal flu will sicken millions of Americans, hospitalize hundreds of thousands, and kill tens of thousands. But it’s certainly possible that we could be in for two straight bad seasons in a row. Last winter, at least 280 children in the U.S. died of the flu, the &lt;a href="https://gizmodo.com/more-kids-are-dying-from-seasonal-flu-than-ever-2000668078"&gt;highest death toll&lt;/a&gt; in children for a non-pandemic flu seen in modern history.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p class="not-prose"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;This season is being fueled by the emergence of subclade K, an H3N2 variant noticeably different on a genetic level from the flu strains scientists predicted would be circulating this season. Since its arrival toward the end of the winter in the Southern Hemisphere, K has quickly taken over as the leading cause of flu cases worldwide, including in the U.S. Though the variant doesn’t appear to cause &lt;a href="https://www.who.int/emergencies/disease-outbreak-news/item/2025-DON586"&gt;more severe infections&lt;/a&gt; on average than other H3N2 strains, it has caused strong, early, or prolonged waves of illness in various parts of the world, including the &lt;a href="https://www.england.nhs.uk/2025/12/nhs-facing-worst-case-scenario-december-amid-super-flu-surge/"&gt;UK&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.japantimes.co.jp/news/2025/12/02/japan/science-health/flu-season/"&gt;Japan&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC12701333/"&gt;Australia&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;p&gt;Though the seasonal flu vaccine is mismatched to subclade K, it’s still worth getting your shot if you haven’t already. Data from the UK has &lt;a href="https://www.eurosurveillance.org/content/10.2807/1560-7917.ES.2025.30.46.2500854#html_fulltext:~:text=Despite%20the%20emergence,cohorts%20%5B26%5D." target="_blank" rel="false noopener"&gt;found&lt;/a&gt; that vaccination this season is still effective at preventing serious flu complications, especially in children.&lt;/p&gt;      &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Gizmodo</author><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 18:05:28 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilAFBVV95cUxQTzlYMGVxTVIxRWUtZUYwYjNudkNSOHU1MldwS1ZsalROTmNrWkhmNEdRSUx2bU1pT0JKeHkyZENCMTlHaVdoYWRkODFZc0NRR0JVeXZ5VW1Fb3RJVzlZeFJ1OWV0Wks0WGVoZU5UdDZ4ODJ5b1JVNmtoc3BQcEo0RXZualF5bzdBZHp1MlRDRzYzaTRU</guid></item><item><title>错过早期疫苗接种的儿童更有可能在2岁前没有接种MMR疫苗：研究- ABC新闻</title><link>https://abcnews.go.com/Health/children-miss-early-vaccines-mmr-shot-age-2/story?id=128843493</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="xvlfx ZRifP TKoO eaKKC EcdEg bOdfO qXhdi NFNeu UyHES " data-testid="prism-article-body"&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao MvWXB TjIXL aGjvy ebVHC "&gt;Children who miss early vaccinations are far more likely to miss the measles, mumps, rubella (MMR) vaccine by age 2, a new study found.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;The findings come as the U.S. recently surpassed 2,000 measles cases for the first time in more than 30 years, according to &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://www.cdc.gov/measles/data-research/index.html" target="_blank" dir="ltr"&gt;data&lt;/a&gt; from the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention (CDC).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;CDC data shows that MMR vaccination declined over the last several years, but the authors say that factors linked to delayed or missed vaccination since the COVID-19 pandemic have not been well studied.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;For &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jamanetworkopen/fullarticle/2843286" target="_blank" dir="ltr"&gt;the new study&lt;/a&gt;, published Friday in the journal JAMA Network Open, the team looked data from Truevata, an electronic health records database that includes several U.S. health care systems.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Participants included more than 321,000 children who received routine care within the first two months, first year and second year of life between Jan. 1, 2018 and April 30, 2025.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="oLzSq QrHMO fnRUo pvsTF EhJPu vPlOC zNYgW OsTsW RMeqy daRVX ISNQ sKyCY eRftA acPPc MENS nFwaT MCnQE mEeeY SmBjI xegrY rPLsU iulOd NIuqO zzscu lzDCc aHUBM IEgzD OjMNy eQqcx SVqKB GQmdz jaoD VWDdR ONJdw vrZxD OnRTz gbbfF roDbV GPGwb oMlSS gfNzt oJhud eXZcf zhVlX "&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="InlineImage GpQCA lZur asrEW " data-testid="prism-inline-image"&gt;&lt;figure class="kzIjN GNmeK pYrtp dSqFO " data-testid="prism-figure"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;div class="nMMea bNYiy Mjgpa dGwha DDmxa jgKNG RGHCC aBIU PriDW lZur " data-testid="prism-caption"&gt;&lt;p class="HXPPJ barbu yKsXL IzgMt VcHIt uhSzI YGNMU cRAsZ xqMcl QtRul "&gt;&lt;span class="hsDdd OOSI GpQCA lZur VlFaz " data-testid="prism-truncate"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="gtOSm FbbUW tUtYa vOCwz EQwFq yCufu eEak Qmvg nyTIa SRXVc vzLa jgBfc WXDas CiUCW kqbG zrdEG txGfn ygKVe BbezD UOtxr CVfpq xijV soGRS XgdC sEIlf daWqJ "&gt;In this March 1, 2025, file photo, a family supports a young child as he receives the MMR vaccine at a vaccine clinic put on by Lubbock Public Health Department in Lubbock, Texas.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="qinlA IpWvx oqZz tylGM lyWxS nWcVF UhTug PPcLh YxlyB "&gt;&lt;span class="gtOSm FbbUW tUtYa vOCwz EQwFq yCufu eEak Qmvg nyTIa SRXVc vzLa jgBfc WXDas CiUCW kqbG zrdEG txGfn ygKVe BbezD UOtxr CVfpq xijV soGRS XgdC sEIlf daWqJ YNujN JGtjI aZFDu rkKLh "&gt;Jan Sonnenmair/Getty Images, FILE&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;The CDC currently &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://www.cdc.gov/measles/vaccines/index.html" target="_blank" dir="ltr"&gt;recommends&lt;/a&gt; that people receive two doses of the MMR vaccine, the first at ages 12 to 15 months and the second between 4 and 6 years old. One dose is 93% effective, and two doses are 97% effective against measles, the CDC says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Most children during the study period received the MMR vaccine on time, with 78.4% doing so.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;About 13.9% of children had delayed vaccination, 1% received the MMR vaccine early and 6.7% did not receive the MMR vaccine by age 2, according to the study.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;The strongest predictors for no MMR vaccination was delay in receiving the recommended 2-month and 4-month vaccines, the study noted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;These early vaccines included diphtheria, tetanus, and acellular pertussis (DTaP); Haemophilus influenzae type b (Hib); pneumococcal conjugate vaccine (PCV); and the inactivated poliovirus vaccines (IPV).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Nina Masters, lead author of the study and senior applied research scientist at Truveta, told ABC News that it's not surprising children who miss early vaccines also miss later vaccines, but it highlights that some parents become vaccine hesitant when their children are young.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;"This also means the opportunity for intervention to engage parents and provide more education about the safety and effectiveness of vaccines has to happen very early," she said. "This may be challenging as parents may have yet had the time to forge a strong bond with their child's pediatrician, but the study highlights the importance of pediatric providers having vaccination discussions and building trust as early as possible with parents."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Results from the study showed that those who received their 2-month vaccines on time were seven times more likely to get the MMR vaccine.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;The team found that the percentage of children who received the MMR vaccine on time changed over the study period, increasing from 75.6% in 2018 to 79.9% in 2021, and then falling to 76.9% in 2024.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;This decrease between 2021 and 2024 was associated with an increase in the percentage of children who did not receive the MMR vaccine by age 2, increasing from 5.3% in 2020 to 7.7% in 2024, according to the study.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Children who were more likely to be unvaccinated for the MMR shot by age 2 were boys, and white and non-Hispanic or Latino, the study found.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Rural residence slightly increased the risk of no MMR vaccination, even among children receiving routine care, according to the study.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;The study only included children with regular access to care, so real-world vaccination delays may be worse in the broader U.S. population, the team noted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;The authors added that these results point to increased vaccine hesitancy or unmeasured access challenges, highlighting the importance of timely intervention so children are less likely to delay or miss vaccination.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="oLzSq QrHMO fnRUo pvsTF EhJPu vPlOC zNYgW OsTsW RMeqy daRVX ISNQ sKyCY eRftA acPPc MENS nFwaT MCnQE mEeeY SmBjI xegrY rPLsU iulOd NIuqO zzscu lzDCc aHUBM IEgzD OjMNy eQqcx SVqKB GQmdz jaoD VWDdR ONJdw vrZxD OnRTz gbbfF roDbV GPGwb oMlSS gfNzt oJhud eXZcf zhVlX "&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="InlineImage GpQCA lZur asrEW " data-testid="prism-inline-image"&gt;&lt;figure class="kzIjN GNmeK pYrtp dSqFO " data-testid="prism-figure"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;div class="nMMea bNYiy Mjgpa dGwha DDmxa jgKNG RGHCC aBIU PriDW lZur " data-testid="prism-caption"&gt;&lt;p class="HXPPJ barbu yKsXL IzgMt VcHIt uhSzI YGNMU cRAsZ xqMcl QtRul "&gt;&lt;span class="hsDdd OOSI GpQCA lZur VlFaz " data-testid="prism-truncate"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="gtOSm FbbUW tUtYa vOCwz EQwFq yCufu eEak Qmvg nyTIa SRXVc vzLa jgBfc WXDas CiUCW kqbG zrdEG txGfn ygKVe BbezD UOtxr CVfpq xijV soGRS XgdC sEIlf daWqJ "&gt;In this March 1, 2025, file photo, a child is held by his mother while he receives an MMR vaccine at a vaccine clinic put on by the Lubbock Public Health Department in Lubbock, Texas.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="qinlA IpWvx oqZz tylGM lyWxS nWcVF UhTug PPcLh YxlyB "&gt;&lt;span class="gtOSm FbbUW tUtYa vOCwz EQwFq yCufu eEak Qmvg nyTIa SRXVc vzLa jgBfc WXDas CiUCW kqbG zrdEG txGfn ygKVe BbezD UOtxr CVfpq xijV soGRS XgdC sEIlf daWqJ YNujN JGtjI aZFDu rkKLh "&gt;Jan Sonnenmair/Getty Images, FILE&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Dr. Amesh Adalja, a senior scholar at Johns Hopkins Center for Health Security, who was not involved in the study, said the findings have major public health implications because there are questions about whether the U.S. will retain its measles elimination status and increasing vaccination is "the way out of this problem."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;"If you want to live in a society where measles is a problem of the past, where we don't have to think about it, where schools don't have to come up with contingency plans, where we don't have children unnecessarily dying from measles, then that's a reason to get the vaccine," he told ABC News.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Adalja added that vaccination doesn't just protect the individual against infection, but it also has a community benefit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;"The higher the vaccination level is in a given community, the more resilient that community will be to those infectious diseases," he said. "And if you're someone that's immunocompromised, you may want to live in to live in an area that has high vaccination rates because you are at higher risk, and if you're in a high vaccination area, there's going to be a lowering of that risk because of the community level immunity that exists in that area. "&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC eTIW sUzSN "&gt;&lt;em class=" "&gt;Crystal Richards, MD, MS is a p&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em class=" "&gt;ediatric resident doctor at New-York Presbyterian Hospital Columbia University Medical Center&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em class=" "&gt; &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em class=" "&gt;and a member of the ABC News Medical Unit.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ABC News</author><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 17:16:14 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilwFBVV95cUxQbnZSYU1TSFR6ZUN2a3lVdUZMX0ZZdFpJY3hBSTRGTERGUmdiWFJOb0RudUQ5RlIzTjlYVFQ2NDVYd1RPTzhGMmlfR2tyWXctNWx0TWYtMU95S1MwdlVrajZ6dXNlVlZvejRDZVNFUUxUWG85d0phdWZQdWwxT2pSaThTT3JuSnYyZ0NOeXRZRFRhN1N2R2NJ0gGcAUFVX3lxTE5Za2RwYmpwb1FWakF4RzNMWUVWemswcmNIRDhNdl9TYUlCYTJFSjlYSl81TVRsdU1xaFJnSjFEbVhld0Y1Q3VvWGJQdnRhQm4tVWNLZXpNdlY0cUtMY2MzMTlqdjVja29qUDJPOU1uZ0t1RVdRVXp1NlJxVTFUdzlEUEZUcno5VlpzN3ZxM2c2ZXh1T2tnVFdsN0NsNQ</guid></item><item><title>根据专家的说法，为什么“少吃，多动”对减肥不起作用-独立报</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/health-and-fitness/weight-loss-science-belly-fat-diet-b2880856.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="sc-jbiisr-0 gIQPHK sc-jbiisr-1 sc-1wfc891-0 fooWDH" id="main"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="big-letter"&gt;I&lt;/span&gt;t will be no surprise that &lt;a href="/topic/weight-loss"&gt;weight loss&lt;/a&gt; is one of the most common &lt;a href="/topic/exercise"&gt;exercise&lt;/a&gt; goals on the planet, especially at this time of year. But if losing belly fat is one of your resolutions and you think that &lt;a href="/topic/exercise"&gt;exercise&lt;/a&gt; is the key, then it’s time to think again. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The single best thing we can do for ourselves is exercising. It works on almost all diseases we can measure – but not for weight loss,” says &lt;a rel="nofollow" target="_blank" href="https://cbmr.ku.dk/research/research-groups/clemmensen-group/?pure=en/persons/293530"&gt;Professor Christoffer Clemmensen&lt;/a&gt; of the University of Copenhagen’s Novo Nordisk Foundation Centre for Basic Metabolic Research. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In fact, studies have repeatedly shown the “eat less; move more” mantra parroted to those looking to lose &lt;a href="/topic/body-fat"&gt;body fat&lt;/a&gt; is ineffective. And nor is willpower the vital key that many people believe it to be. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Weight loss is not a matter of willpower,” adds his colleague, PhD fellow Valdemar Brimnes Ingemann Johansen. “It’s critical to acknowledge the powerful biological mechanisms that interact with your environment. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Genetic predisposition is a big determinant of our body size and how we look – and this powerful biology that underlies our body size is often beyond an individual’s control.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The pair are responsible for a recent literature review, published in the &lt;a rel="nofollow" target="_blank" href="https://www.cell.com/cell/fulltext/s0092-8674(25)00677-4"&gt;Cell&lt;/a&gt; journal, which dives deep into this topic. Here, they reveal more about the lesser-known mechanisms behind weight loss that might just help you achieve your goals this year. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-kk992l-0 dDVXDN"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;The problem with a calorie deficit &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A calorie is a unit of energy – more specifically, one kilocalorie is the estimated amount of energy needed to heat 1kg of water by 1C. Since the 19th century, this has been the most common unit of measurement used for listing energy in food and drink. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A calorie deficit is the common denominator behind weight loss, and so it is widely prescribed to people looking to lose body fat, presenting the idea that if you expend more calories than you consume, you will create a negative energy balance and lose weight. This fact is not disputed by our experts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Anyone can lose weight if you put them in a restrictive environment,” says Professor Clemmensen. “It’s the laws of thermodynamics and it will work on everyone; if you have a negative energy balance, you will lose weight. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“But you can’t tell people to stay in a negative energy balance in the free world, because you have these strong biological forces that are telling people to eat. Unless you can restrict your meal size, or you have someone to put a lock on your cabinets, it’s just impossible.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Calorie deficit comments disregard the power of biology underlying weight control. It’s like telling people who are stressed to relax, or telling people who have psychological illnesses to just get their act together.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Read more: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="/health-and-fitness/nutrionist-healthy-longevity-diet-b2862364.html"&gt;What foods nutrition experts really eat to stop chronic illness in old age (and always avoid)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="sc-awdjp1-2 cbpRGD sc-awdjp1-3 image align-center"&gt;&lt;figure class="sc-1cbdeug-0 cXcwgU"&gt;&lt;div data-gallery-length="4" class="sc-awdjp1-0 hjimhY"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.independent.co.uk/2025/09/09/22/46/iStock-2196789730.jpeg" srcset="https://static.independent.co.uk/2025/09/09/22/46/iStock-2196789730.jpeg?quality=75&amp;amp;width=320&amp;amp;auto=webp 320w, https://static.independent.co.uk/2025/09/09/22/46/iStock-2196789730.jpeg?quality=75&amp;amp;width=640&amp;amp;auto=webp 640w" loading="lazy" alt="A calorie deficit will cause you to lose weight, but studies suggest the results do not last long-term" class="sc-1mc30lb-0 ggpMaE inline-gallery-btn"&gt;&lt;p class="hydrate-root sc-10wlkbs-0 sc-awdjp1-1 bMDiiD" data-component="AutoGalleryButton" data-theme-name="base"&gt;&lt;button class="sc-1uf4o3q-0 dkRtZs inline-gallery-btn" id="trigger-autogallery-317570"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-1uf4o3q-1 hwVecx"&gt;open image in gallery&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-1cbdeug-1 sc-1cbdeug-3 gtVitN hgzWpY"&gt;A calorie deficit will cause you to lose weight, but studies suggest the results do not last long-term&lt;span class="sc-1cbdeug-7 exGSyR"&gt; (Getty/iStock)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="sc-kk992l-0 dDVXDN"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;The new science behind weight loss &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Obesity is classified as a chronic, relapsing disease by the &lt;a rel="nofollow" target="_blank" href="https://www.who.int/news-room/fact-sheets/detail/obesity-and-overweight"&gt;World Health Organisation&lt;/a&gt;, with the institution reporting: “In 2021, higher-than-optimal BMI caused an estimated 3.7 million deaths from noncommunicable diseases such as cardiovascular diseases, diabetes, cancers, neurological disorders, chronic respiratory diseases and digestive disorders.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So why would our bodies contain “strong biological forces” to promote or protect a condition linked to ill &lt;a href="/topic/health"&gt;health&lt;/a&gt;? The answer, according to Johansen, lies with our predecessors. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stored fat would have helped our human ancestors stave off starvation when food was scarce, so the body “remembers” it and tries to replenish these stores when food becomes available, he says. As part of this, the body treats weight loss like a threat, fighting it by releasing a flood of hunger hormones and heightening food cravings while reducing our energy expenditure. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Historically, this might have been helpful; in the 21st century, where energy-dense foods are more accessible than ever and movement is optional, these impulses can be harmful.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Professor Clemmensen led a 2025 literature review on this topic, which found evidence to support the presence of what he describes as an “obesity memory”. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“This idea about memory of obesity is a little bit elusive," he says. “We don’t know where that memory is stored, but you can see it’s there. If you look at studies where people have undergone extreme weight loss, most of them will find their way back quite accurately to their original weight. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“There seems to be a very specific memory, for want of a better term, of what your weight was. That’s what we’re working on in our lab to try to understand.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The role of this memory will, as with most things in the human body, vary from person to person depending on factors such as genetics.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“How much people are able to sustain lost body fat and how they will respond to different types of interventions – both behavioural and pharmacological, like weight loss drugs – will depend on the person,” Johansen explains. “We see quite some variability among people when we look at big clinical trials.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“It would be interesting, and very valuable, if we could understand more about what makes one person regain all their lost bodyweight in just a couple of months, while another person is able to sustain their weight loss for years. This is probably, if I am allowed to speculate, down to the interaction between the environment that person is living in and their genetic make-up.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Read more: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="/health-and-fitness/running-marathon-hyrox-endurance-sport-b2847344.html"&gt;Is the rise of endurance sports a harmless health kick – or dangerous addiction to adventure?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="sc-awdjp1-2 cbpRGD sc-awdjp1-3 image align-center"&gt;&lt;figure class="sc-1cbdeug-0 cXcwgU"&gt;&lt;div data-gallery-length="4" class="sc-awdjp1-0 YIVyy"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.independent.co.uk/2022/07/19/10/newFile-4.jpg" srcset="https://static.independent.co.uk/2022/07/19/10/newFile-4.jpg?quality=75&amp;amp;width=320&amp;amp;auto=webp 320w, https://static.independent.co.uk/2022/07/19/10/newFile-4.jpg?quality=75&amp;amp;width=640&amp;amp;auto=webp 640w" loading="lazy" alt="Someone’s ability to achieve and sustain weight loss, as well as their response to various interventions such as weight loss drugs and diets, will depend on individual factors such as genetics" class="sc-1mc30lb-0 ggpMaE inline-gallery-btn"&gt;&lt;p class="hydrate-root sc-10wlkbs-0 sc-awdjp1-1 bMDiiD" data-component="AutoGalleryButton" data-theme-name="base"&gt;&lt;button class="sc-1uf4o3q-0 dkRtZs inline-gallery-btn" id="trigger-autogallery-317571"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-1uf4o3q-1 hwVecx"&gt;open image in gallery&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-1cbdeug-1 sc-1cbdeug-3 gtVitN hgzWpY"&gt;Someone’s ability to achieve and sustain weight loss, as well as their response to various interventions such as weight loss drugs and diets, will depend on individual factors such as genetics&lt;span class="sc-1cbdeug-7 exGSyR"&gt; (Getty/iStock)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="sc-kk992l-0 dDVXDN"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What actually works for weight loss? &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Anyone who has tried to lose weight will be aware of a disconnect between &lt;em&gt;wanting&lt;/em&gt; to reduce body fat and &lt;em&gt;succeeding &lt;/em&gt;in doing so. Professor Clemmensen’s idea of “obesity memory” provides a possible explanation for this. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, if “eat less; move more” does not work as an approach, what does? This is a tricky question to answer, Professor Clemmensen says, as research into the topic is ongoing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Do we actually have enough knowledge to guide people on how to live, in terms of losing weight? I don’t think so. I think that’s part of the hard truth we, as researchers, sometimes have to deliver,” he says. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This does not mean &lt;a href="/topic/diet"&gt;diet&lt;/a&gt; and exercise are unimportant – wider health-promoting behaviours, regardless of their impact on body weight, should always be encouraged. Eating a nourishing diet rich in a large variety of vegetables combined with protein and some kind of fish is more likely to have a favourable impact on the body – compositionally and hormonally – than less nutrient-dense alternatives like junk food, helping you feel and function better. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Macronutrient composition will have different effects on the various hormonal systems in the body,” Professor Clemmensen explains. “If you get all your calories from liquid sugar versus from chicken breast, it will have very different impacts on the hormonal environment in the body, and subsequent feelings of hunger.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The same applies for exercise. Moving more will have a transformative effect on health markers such as blood pressure and your risk of chronic diseases, but Professor Clemmensen says, “There is very little evidence to suggest it can override that memory of prior bodyweight.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There is no single intervention that provides an all-encompassing solution, and people’s varied genetic make-ups render blanket prescriptions impossible. But a combination of manageable interventions appears to be the most productive course of action. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Developing sustainable habits such as sufficient sleep, a nutritious diet and regular exercise will form part of the puzzle. These are things you can implement to improve overall health – and possibly assist in appetite regulation, energy balance and weight management too. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But Professor Clemmensen and Johansen suggest that environmental and societal changes, long-term planning and pharmacological interventions are also necessary in reversing wider obesity rates in the long run. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Read more: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="/health-and-fitness/negative-health-effects-of-sitting-down-b2842653.html"&gt;From back pain to heart health – Experts reveal how to counter the negative effects of too much sitting down&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="sc-awdjp1-2 cbpRGD sc-awdjp1-3 image align-center"&gt;&lt;figure class="sc-1cbdeug-0 cXcwgU"&gt;&lt;div data-gallery-length="4" class="sc-awdjp1-0 cDKnxE"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.independent.co.uk/2025/10/21/15/23/iStock-2223395151.jpg" srcset="https://static.independent.co.uk/2025/10/21/15/23/iStock-2223395151.jpg?quality=75&amp;amp;width=320&amp;amp;auto=webp 320w, https://static.independent.co.uk/2025/10/21/15/23/iStock-2223395151.jpg?quality=75&amp;amp;width=640&amp;amp;auto=webp 640w" loading="lazy" alt="Sufficient sleep quantity and quality can help with appetite regulation" class="sc-1mc30lb-0 ggpMaE inline-gallery-btn"&gt;&lt;p class="hydrate-root sc-10wlkbs-0 sc-awdjp1-1 bMDiiD" data-component="AutoGalleryButton" data-theme-name="base"&gt;&lt;button class="sc-1uf4o3q-0 dkRtZs inline-gallery-btn" id="trigger-autogallery-317572"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-1uf4o3q-1 hwVecx"&gt;open image in gallery&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-1cbdeug-1 sc-1cbdeug-3 gtVitN hgzWpY"&gt;Sufficient sleep quantity and quality can help with appetite regulation&lt;span class="sc-1cbdeug-7 exGSyR"&gt; (Getty/iStock)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="sc-kk992l-0 dDVXDN"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;The obesity solution&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“To reduce obesity rates, we have to look at a more long-term perspective, thinking about generations beyond our little existence,” says Professor Clemmensen. “I think we need to funnel a lot of research into preventative strategies and learning how to create societies where we will have fewer gene-environment interactions that lead to obesity in the first place.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In other words, the world needs to change to encourage healthier behaviours – for example, greater prominence and availability of nourishing foods over ultra-processed energy-dense alternatives, and neighbourhoods that prioritise walking and cycling over travelling by car. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What about weight loss drugs like Ozempic, Wegovy and Mounjaro, which fall under the banner of “pharmacological interventions”?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I think weight loss drugs have actually helped people acknowledge how difficult it is to sustain weight loss through willpower,” Professor Clemmensen continues. “Now we have pharmacological tools that we know work, and they will be relevant for people who are made sick by their excess body fat.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yet, as Johansen points out, many of these weight loss drugs “don’t seem to be good at maintaining weight loss when people stop the treatment”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“People also experience comorbidities like diabetes, high blood pressure and systemic inflammation when they stop the treatment,” he adds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Some evidence suggests that a combination of exercise and pharmacological weight loss can be very beneficial for supporting weight loss maintenance.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Professor Clemmensen also emphasises the importance of promoting healthy behaviours in children – particularly those aged seven and below, due to their more “malleable weight regulation system”. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“There are different critical periods of your life,” Professor Clemmensen says. “There’s your time in the womb, then post-birth, then there’s this growth spurt between four and seven – then again, as a teenager.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“There is some genetic predisposition [to changes in weight], but if you put that person or those genes in an environment that is really unsuitable, you risk developing excess fat mass in those critical periods. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“It’s not about restricting these children or individuals, but creating an environment in which they don’t have free access to a ton of calories 24/7, or exposure to a lot of screens, poor sleep and poor psychological health.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This could mean reducing the marketing of junk food to children, investing in healthier school meals, standardising restaurant portion sizes and encouraging regular exercise. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Developing favourable traits in childhood to suit the genetic hand someone has been dealt could then set them on a trajectory to having less body fat as an adult, Professor Clemmensen ventures. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But his ultimate goal, and the intervention he believes has the greatest scope for success, is researching, identifying and altering an individual’s “obesity memory”. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="taboola-mid-article-thumbnails-us-premium-ii" class="sc-looa6c-0 cPCVUJ"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“We still think if we can understand where and how this memory resides, maybe we can erase it and help people reset their body weight,” he says. “If we can learn to understand the physiology, we can learn how to intervene.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Read more: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="/health-and-fitness/diet-fasting-longevity-expert-ozempic-b2859119.html"&gt;Longevity expert says this diet is more effective than Ozempic at changing the human body&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Independent</author><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 17:09:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMingFBVV95cUxQb1lGQ21OSzZQTndTZktxVEd2cGxUcXhnWGE4RjBGZXR4dDJkdXNLX0lLM2RKXzZwbE1WSi0zSGx5QXVMVmRXcUE1azZsbGVqWlhzSDUzMWVERXJ3UnFIVlJIeWVFR2FFc3d4UFdnYmEtUkVEUmUxNEpUV2lTUzBBVWw4ZnJTSWVYalNLT2ZoTnNfOUtIVFlpekhNU3MxZw</guid></item><item><title>如何成为“超级老人” --《华盛顿邮报》</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/podcasts/post-reports/how-to-be-a-super-ager-1/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="Episode_episode-description__mlBrI Episode_episode-content-wrapper__8Q2oZ"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Today, we revisit one of our favorite episodes from this past year, about super agers: people who continue to thrive into their 80s and 90s. One of them lives just down my block.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Ednajane Truax, who is known to friends and neighbors as “E.J.,” can often be found on her hands and knees in the dirt, working in the garden at the Sherwood Recreation Center in Northeast Washington. She also has an impressive garden of her own and helps out with other neighbors’ gardens. She works out several times a week, sometimes while wearing a shirt that says, “You don’t stop lifting when you get old — you get old when you stop lifting.” She can bench press 55 pounds and leg press 250.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Truax has never married — “just lucky, I guess,” she jokes when I ask her about that — but she has remained social her entire life. She volunteers, goes to the gym, throws parties, knows her neighbors and their children by name. Truax says her secret to thriving as she ages is simple: Be active.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;It turns out that &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/lifestyle/2025/08/28/thriving-at-90-super-ager-truax/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;research backs her up&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;If you’re looking for more surprising, delightful stories about the best of humanity, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/optimist/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;check out The Optimist&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; from The Washington Post. We also have a newsletter: Subscribe to get &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/newsletters/the-optimist/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;stories from The Optimist in your inbox&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; every Sunday morning.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Today’s show was produced by Maggie Penman with help from Ted Muldoon, who also mixed the show. The Optimist’s editor is Allison Klein. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;If you liked hearing this story on “Post Reports,” send us an email at &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="mailto:podcasts@washpost.com" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;em&gt;podcasts@washpost.com&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;. You can email Maggie directly at &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="mailto:maggie.penman@washpost.com" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;em&gt;maggie.penman@washpost.com&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Subscribe to The Washington Post &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://subscribe.washingtonpost.com/acquisition/?s_l=OFFSITE_PODCAST&amp;amp;p=s_v&amp;amp;s_dt=yearly&amp;amp;utm%5B%E2%80%A6%5De-podcast&amp;amp;utm_medium=acq-nat&amp;amp;utm_campaign=podcast-subs" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 17:01:24 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihAFBVV95cUxNOFZubVpUcUFXVXRLYUc4eGNNMl9OZkpGMHBmYUxZOFI5MUhaZ25MSzdCZVdrUU15MzNKd010TmREYkNfcDFoY1plZ2owaDB3UUlpWXFZcEQtZWhnQmpGUVF1R0o3NDdtVWJTSjUwTFJpMy00MEFhZnV5dXlYbzNyekRNUzk</guid></item><item><title>幼龙虾如何在佛罗里达群岛落入致命的自然陷阱- Phys.org</title><link>https://phys.org/news/2026-01-juvenile-lobsters-fall-deadly-natural.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="success-screen" id="successScreen"&gt;
            &lt;p class="success-icon"&gt;✓&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;h2 class="success-title"&gt;Verification Complete&lt;/h2&gt;
            &lt;p class="success-subtext"&gt;This page will redirect in a moment...&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Phys.org</author><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 16:10:01 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMifEFVX3lxTE5hUTk0dWljSHpaRGp1TWtPYmc2N09HcjJTUlVYZlJlVVZjaEg3QWwzV3EzLUJfVFJaQ3ZvdEMyTzV2T29UX3BxMFpXLVVVZEVwX3V6akhOenh3VHZhRVVMYVl6SUY5SWpkQzY0UE93czVDb3cyRFdQWlctU1o</guid></item><item><title>天主教影响者保罗·金（ Paul Kim ）的儿子在严重流感病例后去世，享年五岁-《独立报》</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/paul-kim-son-dead-flu-b2893561.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="sc-jbiisr-0 gIQPHK sc-jbiisr-1" id="main"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="hydrate-root sc-10wlkbs-0" data-component="SupportNSCNative" data-loading="lazy" data-theme-name="base"&gt;&lt;aside class="sc-hez36s-0 dFpFuY"&gt;&lt;div class="sc-hez36s-1 iBibVd"&gt;&lt;h3 data-testid="support-nsc-title" class="sc-hez36s-2 jVZWGn"&gt;Your support helps us to tell the story&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;div class="sc-hez36s-8 juUDRT"&gt;&lt;div class="sc-hez36s-13 cqPbFA"&gt;&lt;div class="sc-aja53j-0 rAFIl sc-hez36s-16 jZSKtc"&gt;&lt;div class="sc-aja53j-6 PdmgT"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="dropdown-with-gradient-collapsed-content-container" class="sc-aja53j-5 eZqxmv"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div data-testid="dropdown-with-gradient-collapsed-content" class="sc-aja53j-4 tawua"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div data-testid="support-nsc-collapsed-content-tablet" class="sc-hez36s-7 gZmYS"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-1uza6dc-0 iCTyfe"&gt;From reproductive rights to climate change to Big Tech, The Independent is on the ground when the story is developing. Whether it's investigating the financials of Elon Musk's pro-Trump PAC or producing our latest documentary, 'The A Word', which shines a light on the American women fighting for reproductive rights, we know how important it is to parse out the facts from the messaging.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-1uza6dc-0 iCTyfe"&gt;At such a critical moment in US history, we need reporters on the ground. Your donation allows us to keep sending journalists to speak to both sides of the story.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-1uza6dc-0 iCTyfe"&gt;The Independent is trusted by Americans across the entire political spectrum. And unlike many other quality news outlets, we choose not to lock Americans out of our reporting and analysis with paywalls. We believe quality journalism should be available to everyone, paid for by those who can afford it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;strong class="sc-1uza6dc-1 cglitp"&gt;Your support makes all the difference.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;button class="sc-aja53j-1 keLMOw sc-aja53j-7 eMEmGu"&gt;&lt;span data-testid="dropdown-with-gradient-dropdown-tablet" class="sc-aja53j-3 dHXFkr"&gt;&lt;span data-action-type="Read more" class="sc-aja53j-2 dcYUYI"&gt;Read more&lt;/span&gt;&lt;svg class="sc-eaj12q-0 hUgQwJ sc-culv3z-0 eifaJK sc-a5wy94-0 hyKPon"&gt;&lt;use href="#ee6613da15642019"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a rel="nofollow" target="_blank" href="/life-style/influencer-vlogger-brand-marketing-trust-b2867570.html"&gt;Influencer&lt;/a&gt; Paul Kim, who speaks about his &lt;a rel="nofollow" target="_blank" href="/news/world/americas/us-politics/catholic-bishops-immigration-trump-b2864598.html"&gt;Catholic&lt;/a&gt; faith in social media videos, said that his five-year-old son, Micah, has died.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Father-of-six Kim initially shared on December 21 that Micah had been hospitalized with a &lt;a rel="nofollow" target="_blank" href="/news/health/flu-death-ohio-kentucky-cases-b2893153.html"&gt;severe case of the flu&lt;/a&gt; and continued to post frequent updates for his 372,000 Instagram followers. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The flu was so severe, Kim said, that it caused seizures and sepsis in the young boy, leading to him being placed on life support. Kim also said that a scan revealed that activity in Micah’s brain was “not present.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="article-im-prompt"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a January 1 video, Kim said that “after fighting 11 long hard days, [Micah] went home to the house of our father.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“We are so proud of him. I want to thank you from the bottom of my heart as his dad, on behalf of my family, for all the ways you guys prayed and lifted us up during this time,” Kim continued. “This incredibly difficult, impossible time for our family. It's been the hardest thing I've ever been through in my life and it continues to be.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="taboola-mid-article-thumbnails-ii" class="sc-looa6c-0 cPCVUJ"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="sc-awdjp1-2 cbpRGD sc-awdjp1-3 image align-center"&gt;&lt;figure class="sc-1cbdeug-0 cXcwgU"&gt;&lt;div data-gallery-length="2" class="sc-awdjp1-0 cYKtne"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.the-independent.com/2026/01/02/14/03/vlcsnap-2026-01-02-14h48m14s041.png" srcset="https://static.the-independent.com/2026/01/02/14/03/vlcsnap-2026-01-02-14h48m14s041.png?quality=75&amp;amp;width=320&amp;amp;auto=webp 320w, https://static.the-independent.com/2026/01/02/14/03/vlcsnap-2026-01-02-14h48m14s041.png?quality=75&amp;amp;width=640&amp;amp;auto=webp 640w" loading="lazy" alt="Influencer Paul Kim’s five-year-old son has died after a severe case of the flu" class="sc-1mc30lb-0 ggpMaE inline-gallery-btn"&gt;&lt;p class="hydrate-root sc-10wlkbs-0 sc-awdjp1-1 bMDiiD" data-component="AutoGalleryButton" data-theme-name="base"&gt;&lt;button class="sc-1uf4o3q-0 dkRtZs inline-gallery-btn" id="trigger-autogallery-310835"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-1uf4o3q-1 hwVecx"&gt;open image in gallery&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-1cbdeug-1 sc-1cbdeug-3 gtVitN hgzWpY"&gt;Influencer Paul Kim’s five-year-old son has died after a severe case of the flu&lt;span class="sc-1cbdeug-7 exGSyR"&gt; (Instagram/@heypjk)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;“As much as this time I just want to have privacy and have time to mourn with my family I felt like I owed all of you an update, just out of gratitude. Micah is already in Heaven at work, seriously, so many testimonies, so many ways in which God is using the light in my five-year-old to truly save souls and change the world.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The influencer acknowledged that deacons, priests, and even cardinals reached out to offer prayers for Micah during his hospitalization. “I’m thankful. I love you in Christ,” Kim said in the video.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“For those two weeks we were fighting long and hard, we were consulting legal, health, ethical teams even outside the hospital. Just to make sure we weren't leaving any stone unturned. In many ways we were fighting for Micah to buy him as much time as possible, until he passed. As a father, that is my duty I was called to do that. Even if in God's ultimate will it wasn't meant for him to recover.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kim has shared media coverage of his son’s death on Instagram, saying: “God is using Micah to evangelize the world. He’s taken over daddy’s ministry. Go son, go! My heart is broken but so proud of you. Ask God to allow you to be canonized so I can finally take mommy on that trip to Italy.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Micah’s death comes amid a surge of severe flu cases impacting people of all ages, including children.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The child death toll from flu rose again this week as &lt;a rel="nofollow" target="_blank" href="/news/flu-washington-japan-canada-united-kingdom-b2892431.html"&gt;cases of super flu continued to surge&lt;/a&gt; across more than a dozen states in the U.S. The nationwide tally ticked up to &lt;a rel="nofollow" target="_blank" href="https://www.cdc.gov/fluview/surveillance/2025-week-51.html"&gt;nine children&lt;/a&gt;, with health officials in Ohio and Kentucky reporting their &lt;a rel="nofollow" target="_blank" href="/news/health/children-flu-hospital-rates-care-doctors-b2707352.html"&gt;first pediatric flu deaths&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The announcements come on the heels of the &lt;a rel="nofollow" target="_blank" href="/news/health/flu-symptoms-cases-spike-b2694411.html"&gt;worst flu season in nearly 15 years in 2024.&lt;/a&gt; This year, the agency &lt;a rel="nofollow" target="_blank" href="https://www.cdc.gov/fluview/surveillance/2025-week-51.html"&gt;estimates&lt;/a&gt; that there have been 7.5 million infections, more than 81,000 hospitalizations and 3,100 flu deaths across the country.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Independent</author><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 15:35:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiggFBVV95cUxOeC1pVUJaYzJaT1dwbFM4dVE0Ulh5d3RrZVo4WjVFbGNNckFxYnAwakJBV0tMVmpGWktqQ2FlYjJhQzh4ckdFQkh1LTlWZ0ZCMzh1bnM5XzRwd2NHNjd3OWpNa184ZHRmRWNQcnpqR2g4VV9WVlJwN3RZWXZTaW51Rnln</guid></item><item><title>我最喜欢的高蛋白食谱帮助我减掉了25磅- EatingWell</title><link>https://www.eatingwell.com/this-high-protein-recipe-helped-me-lose-25-pounds-11874286</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-page_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-page mntl-block structured-content" data-sc-sticky-offset="90" data-sc-ad-label-height="24" data-sc-ad-track-spacing="100" data-sc-min-track-height="250" data-sc-max-track-height="600" data-sc-breakpoint="50em" data-sc-load-immediate="4" data-sc-content-positions="[1, 1250, 1550, 1950, 2350, 2750, 3150, 3550, 3950]" data-bind-scroll-on-start="true"&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-block_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-callout--summary mntl-sc-block-universal-callout--tips mntl-sc-block-universal-callout theme-summary callout--bordered" data-text="Key Points" data-tracking-id="mntl-sc-block-callout" data-tracking-container="true"&gt;
&lt;div class="mntl-sc-block-universal-callout__body"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;When a writer learned she had high blood sugar, she began searching for high-protein recipes.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;This simple, flavorful za’atar roasted chicken and chickpea recipe became one of her go-tos.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Eating more protein and fewer highly processed carbs helped her lose 25 pounds.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_2-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Whenever your doctor says, “We need to talk about your blood work,” you know you’re in for a tough call.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_3-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_4-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;br&gt;I was in my mid-40s and feeling pretty good about myself. Was I a health fanatic? No. But I went to the pool several times a week. I happily cooked most of my meals from scratch. I genuinely liked all fruits and vegetables, and I certainly didn’t need to be lectured on the evils of ultraprocessed foods. What could possibly be wrong with my bloodwork? Was there a problem?
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_5-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_6-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;br&gt;Turns out, there wasn’t &lt;em&gt;a&lt;/em&gt; problem. There were several. Among them were low iron and high blood sugar. It seems that a combination of perimenopause and a growing habit of eating toast for dinner when I was on deadline wasn’t exactly working in my favor. My doctor’s recommendations included meals that met three requirements: high fiber, low sugar and high protein. I knew what that meant. Legumes, and lots of them. I can’t say I was all that enthusiastic.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_7-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_9-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_10-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; I wasn’t against &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/8061834/healthiest-beans-to-eat/" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;lentils, beans and chickpeas&lt;/a&gt;, per se. They’re easy. They’re budget-friendly. They’re &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/290550/10-everyday-superfoods/" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;nutritional superstars&lt;/a&gt;. They’re just so … sensible. Horribly sensible and terribly dull. I found myself recalling a lentil-and-sesame-seed cooking experiment that turned out to have the texture of sand, and I shuddered. My memories of a 12-bean potluck salad with zero seasoning were equally gloomy. As such, I set about my research with grim determination. Perhaps it’s no surprise that when I stumbled upon this &lt;em&gt;EatingWell &lt;/em&gt;recipe for&lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/zaatar-roasted-chicken-with-chickpeas-8786583" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="3"&gt; Za’atar-Roasted Chicken with Chickpeas&lt;/a&gt;, I felt a glimmer of optimism. It looked like a recipe with potential. It looked like a recipe with &lt;em&gt;flavor.&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_11-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_12-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;br&gt;And it was. I’m not exaggerating when I say that this recipe changed my life.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_13-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_14-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;br&gt;
It’s a chickpea-forward recipe with so much going on that it made me forget about my legume ambivalence. It doesn’t taste like the kind of recipe you eat after your doctor calls to lecture you about your blood work. But it absolutely should be. A generous amount of &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/7908775/what-is-zaatar-everything-to-know-about-this-middle-eastern-spice-blend/" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;lemon juice and za’atar spice blend&lt;/a&gt; makes things sing. Throw in some onions, garlic and fresh herbs, and you have an absolute powerhouse of flavors. The chicken ups the protein factor, providing an impressive 29 grams per serving. And everything comes together in minutes with no fuss. It’s so good that I habitually swipe my fingers across the empty pan afterward, scooping up the last little bits of the earthy, punchy, tangy sauce. And, best of all, it has me eating my chickpeas without complaint.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_15-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_17-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_18-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; While I’d happily eat this meal prepared exactly the way the recipe says, it didn’t take long before I started putting my own spin on things. It’s endlessly flexible and such a great way to use up leftover veggies. In summer, I was loading my tray with tiny cherry tomatoes from my garden. In the fall, Brussels sprouts were added to the mix. With winter rolling in, the sweet, peppery flavor of parsnips became a welcome addition. No matter what I did, everything came together in less than 15 minutes of hands-on time. Then I didn't have to do a thing until my timer dinged—perfect for when I’m so busy that I can barely look up from my work. And, for the first time ever, I actually started saving leftover chickpeas to eat the next day, usually for breakfast, in a quick hash and with a fried egg on top.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_19-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_20-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;br&gt;
As much as I’d like to joke around and dismiss them, there is no denying that chickpeas and other legumes are precisely what I need right now. &lt;a href="https://cathyrichardsrd.com/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1" rel="nofollow"&gt;Cathy Richards, RD&lt;/a&gt;, wholeheartedly agrees. “As a registered dietitian, I often recommend chickpeas because they add &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai pseudoStyle" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/proteins-to-eat-every-week-11684415" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;satisfying protein&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/best-high-fiber-carbs-to-eat-11835357" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="3"&gt;gut-loving fiber&lt;/a&gt; and a subtly nutty flavor to meals. They’re a simple, delicious way to boost both health and taste,” she says.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_21-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_22-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Legumes, like chickpeas, are also a food choice heartily endorsed by a myriad of health care organizations. That includes Diabetes Canada (in Canada, where I live) and the American Diabetes Association and the American Heart Association in the U.S.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="2"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="1"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="3"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; After all, chickpeas are rich in fiber (1 cup of canned chickpeas gives you nearly 10 grams). They’re also a &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/low-glycemic-diet-vs-low-carb-diet-which-is-healthier-8559250" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;low-glycemic-index choice&lt;/a&gt;, which is key for anyone grappling with &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/lifestyle-tweaks-healthy-blood-sugar-levels-11792895" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;blood sugar regulation&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="5"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="4"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; It doesn’t hurt that they also give you a little bit of iron, providing 8% of the Daily Value per cup. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_23-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_24-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;br&gt;OK, legumes. I’m starting to get the hype. Is there anything you can’t do?&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_25-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_27-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_28-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; I didn’t set out to lose weight. I’m lucky to have a doctor who cares about more numbers than just the ones on the scale. I was focused on making changes that would improve both my blood sugar and my iron levels. But those changes, including increasing my intake of fiber and lean proteins while cutting back on high-glycemic index foods, like white carbohydrates, align closely with tried-and-true weight-loss advice. As such, working this &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/gallery/8017960/cozy-sheet-pan-dinners-with-three-steps-or-less/" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;super-easy sheet-pan meal&lt;/a&gt; into my weekly meal rotation for the past year has helped me lose 25 pounds and counting. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_29-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_30-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;br&gt;However, I’m even more thrilled that my blood work has significantly improved. Best of all, these changes feel sustainable. This recipe feels like I’m nourishing myself, taking care of myself and finding what works for me, my health and my cooking style. Who would have thought that prosaic ol’ chickpeas would be at the forefront of that?
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_31-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-the-bottom-line"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_32-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; The Bottom Line &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_33-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Finding out your blood sugar is high can come as a surprise. But small changes, like having a go-to &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/gallery/7948927/best-15-minute-dinner-recipes/" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;quick, healthy recipe&lt;/a&gt; you love—like this easy roasted chicken and chickpea dish—can help you get things back on track. Combined with eating more lean protein and fewer highly processed carbs, it may even help you lose some weight.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_34-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>EatingWell</author><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 15:29:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijgFBVV95cUxOZFlnNlFhdEdfandheXVRU2NuRGh4ZWFMSUxEM1RUTHc0d1g2NWw3bDlJMUMyQzRjcnNTS25iT3B4UUVXOVlfYXZnZzI0b3NTVWhWdmJWLTktRW85WVlqNUN4OFBuRzVVOTRHR1RGV0g3aDd5RDBuYzY5c2N2Qmo3d2FrTDR1TXJLN1EycmVB</guid></item><item><title>一项“艰巨”的基因研究刚刚发现了一种治疗多动症的新方法- ScienceDaily</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/12/251225035342.htm</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p id="first" class="lead"&gt;Attention disorders such as ADHD occur when the brain has trouble separating meaningful signals from constant background input. The brain continuously processes sights, sounds, and internal thoughts, and focus depends on its ability to ignore distractions while responding to what matters. Most current treatments improve attention by increasing activity in brain circuits that control focus, especially in the prefrontal cortex.&lt;/p&gt;

						&lt;div id="text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A new study suggests a different solution. Instead of increasing brain activity, the research points to reducing baseline activity as a way to lower mental noise and improve attention.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A Gene Linked to Calmer Focus&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In research published in &lt;em&gt;Nature Neuroscience&lt;/em&gt;, scientists report that a gene called &lt;em&gt;Homer1&lt;/em&gt; plays an important role in attention by shaping how quiet or noisy the brain is at rest. Mice with reduced levels of two specific forms of this gene showed calmer brain activity and performed better on tasks requiring focus.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These findings may represent an early step toward new treatments aimed at calming the mind rather than stimulating it. The implications extend beyond ADHD, since &lt;em&gt;Homer1&lt;/em&gt; has also been linked to disorders involving early sensory processing differences, including autism and schizophrenia.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"The gene we found has a striking effect on attention and is relevant to humans," says Priya Rajasethupathy, head of the Skoler Horbach Family Laboratory of Neural Dynamics and Cognition at Rockefeller.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;An Unexpected Genetic Target&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When the research team began exploring the genetics of attention, &lt;em&gt;Homer1&lt;/em&gt; was not an obvious candidate. Scientists have long known the gene for its role in neurotransmission, and many interacting proteins of &lt;em&gt;Homer1&lt;/em&gt; have appeared in genetic studies of attention disorders, but &lt;em&gt;Homer1&lt;/em&gt; itself had not previously stood out as a key driver.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="insertion_middle"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To investigate more broadly, the researchers analyzed the genomes of nearly 200 mice bred from eight different parental strains, including some with wild ancestry. This approach was designed to reflect the genetic diversity seen in human populations and allowed subtle genetic influences to emerge.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"It was a Herculean effort, and really novel for the field," says Rajasethupathy, who credits PhD student Zachary Gershon for leading the work.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A Large Genetic Effect on Attention&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This large-scale genetic analysis revealed a clear pattern. Mice that performed best on attention tasks had much lower levels of &lt;em&gt;Homer1&lt;/em&gt; in the prefrontal cortex, a brain region essential for focus. The gene was located within a stretch of DNA that explained nearly 20 percent of the variation in attention among the mice.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"[That's] a huge effect," Rajasethupathy says. "Even accounting for any overestimation here of the size of this effect, which can happy for many reasons, that's a remarkable number. Most of the time, you're lucky if you find a gene that affects even 1 percent of a trait."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Timing Is Critical During Brain Development&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Further analysis showed that not all forms of &lt;em&gt;Homer1&lt;/em&gt; contributed equally. Two specific versions, known as &lt;em&gt;Homer1a&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;Ania3&lt;/em&gt;, were responsible for the attention differences. Mice that excelled at attention tasks naturally had lower levels of these versions in their prefrontal cortex, while other forms of the gene were unchanged.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="insertion_bottom"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When researchers experimentally reduced &lt;em&gt;Homer1a&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;Ania3&lt;/em&gt; during a brief developmental period in adolescent mice, the effects were striking. The animals became faster, more accurate, and less distractible across several behavioral tests. Making the same changes in adult mice produced no benefit, showing that &lt;em&gt;Homer1&lt;/em&gt; influences attention during a limited early-life window.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How Quieting the Brain Improves Focus&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The most unexpected insight came from examining how &lt;em&gt;Homer1&lt;/em&gt; affects brain cells. Lowering &lt;em&gt;Homer1&lt;/em&gt; levels in prefrontal cortex neurons caused those cells to increase GABA receptors -- the molecular brakes of the nervous system.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This change reduced unnecessary background firing while preserving strong, focused bursts of activity when important cues appeared. Instead of responding constantly, neurons conserved their activity for moments that required attention, leading to more accurate responses.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"We were sure that the more attentive mice would have more activity in the prefrontal cortex, not less," Rajasethupathy says. "But it made some sense. Attention is, in part, about blocking everything else out."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A Calmer Way to Think About Attention&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For Gershon, who lives with ADHD, the findings felt intuitive. "It's part of my story," he says, "and one of the inspirations for me wanting to apply genetic mapping to attention."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He was also the first in the lab to notice that lowering &lt;em&gt;Homer1&lt;/em&gt; improved focus by reducing distractions. In his view, the results align with common experiences. "Deep breathing, mindfulness, meditation, calming the nervous system -- people consistently report better focus following these activities," he says.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Rethinking Future Treatments&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Current treatments for attention disorders typically increase excitatory signaling in prefrontal brain circuits using stimulant medications. The new findings point toward a different possibility: therapies that improve attention by calming neural activity instead of amplifying it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Because &lt;em&gt;Homer1&lt;/em&gt; and its interacting proteins have been linked to ADHD, schizophrenia, and autism, further research may reshape how scientists understand multiple neurodevelopmental conditions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Future studies from the Rajasethupathy lab will focus on refining the genetic understanding of attention, with the goal of developing therapies that precisely adjust &lt;em&gt;Homer1&lt;/em&gt; levels.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"There is a splice site in &lt;em&gt;Homer1&lt;/em&gt; that can be pharmacologically targeted, which may be an ideal way to help dial the knob on brain signal-to-noise levels," Rajasethupathy says. "This offers a tangible path toward creating a medication that has a similar quieting effect as meditation."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

					&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceDaily</author><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 15:22:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMib0FVX3lxTFBPUFQyVlhMRkc1dktyUFRkLVhjOE1abzZ5SzdYem12Wm1Oc2N6Y3RJR3ZPWm1yWWkwcmxZWDUwZ2s1c1BWZDlGSHMwRDZnM0pkQ0NxYlJsNVhwRXVrRnVzRDRPSUd1WVU5V2xBaFEtbw</guid></item><item><title>纳米颗粒疗法重新编程肿瘤免疫细胞，从内部攻击癌症- Phys.org</title><link>https://phys.org/news/2026-01-nanoparticle-therapy-reprograms-tumor-immune.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="success-screen" id="successScreen"&gt;
            &lt;p class="success-icon"&gt;✓&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;h2 class="success-title"&gt;Verification Complete&lt;/h2&gt;
            &lt;p class="success-subtext"&gt;This page will redirect in a moment...&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Phys.org</author><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 14:49:42 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihgFBVV95cUxPbGl6dkJxOVc1RVJzSF8tZDFfZnJZMHNfTjFNd2lPMkpvT1ZRTFoybkgzY25yUmdFc2IwMkU4eHctME1MUDBXRWlTQ3YwdjdDOHlmMjNkWU52dURmYjVEYVJHLUFMWEZiVnlOaXktUG9nQ1U1eUR5b05CZk9iYXFKb2pVaFBkQQ</guid></item><item><title>视频： Golden Retriever Puppy在未能转身后反击- DogTime</title><link>https://dogtime.com/news/201001-golden-retriever-puppy-reverse-walk-video-funny</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content wp-block-post-content is-layout-flow wp-block-post-content-is-layout-flow"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Early puppyhood is often filled with clumsy movements, curious discoveries, and moments that are unintentionally hilarious. For many pet parents, these fleeting stages pass quickly, making them worth capturing on camera whenever possible. One such moment recently caught the internet’s attention, thanks to a short but charming video of a Golden Retriever puppy figuring out how his body works.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-video-shows-golden-retriever-puppy-walk-in-reverse-because-he-can-t-turn-around"&gt;Video shows Golden Retriever puppy walk in reverse because he can’t turn around&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-instagram wp-block-embed-instagram"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;p&gt;In a recent video shared by @adventures.of.pilot, a &lt;a href="https://dogtime.com/dog-breeds/golden-retriever"&gt;Golden Retriever&lt;/a&gt; puppy called Pilot is attempting to navigate his surroundings but ends up walking backward instead.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Onscreen text explains the situation: “Enjoy this video of my puppy walking in reverse because he didn’t know how to turn around.” The puppy takes hesitant, wobbly steps as he slowly backs up, appearing genuinely unsure of what to do next.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Pilot is also wearing a small harness, which some viewers speculated may have added to his confusion. Whether it was the harness or simply a case of puppy brain, the result was a hilarious and wholesome scene. As he carefully reverses, his movements are cautious but determined, as if he believes backing up is the only logical solution.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="pb-in-article-content test-1"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;It didn’t take long for the clip to gain traction. The video quickly racked up more than 310K likes and drew over a hundred comments from viewers who related to Pilot’s behavior or simply found it hilarious.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Many shared stories of their own dogs going through similar phases, noting how common it is for puppies to struggle with basic movements as they learn coordination and spatial awareness.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;One viewer jokingly wrote “beep beep beep,” comparing Pilot’s backward steps to a vehicle reversing. Another called him “a little goofball,” while someone else said their own puppy looked like he was “processing how to walk” during his early days.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;One popular comment summed up the playful tone by saying Golden Retrievers are “just orange cats in disguise,” joking that they all seem to share “one single brain cell.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;



&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>DogTime</author><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 14:48:47 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihgFBVV95cUxOekVac0tJMWdpZERGMGE1LU92WkRBM3UtOUNBX3d4bHFrRldMWXN3UjhSd1ZING5SNG4wbEJOOFY5QW1jb3pNNVJaekRvRVNJX083alRKNlhCZDladmRsN0U0RC10aU9maDBIVUo5dU1DTng4Sms3NHptVERBNnFpRUdKSUhqd9IBiwFBVV95cUxNN1g2WU9ETXFRTEl1MV95a2Myamk0M1M5LWZKcG41Sk9WUTFWNEJSV3hkblBqRGR4VE1qNDAzd2xmbDhEc01pTVY4NTU2bU5FVUVIME5pSW93UWRrMUZWd1NudW83UnN4NzZCSlZwNjN5amhlX1RJNmt5cWk0c0U1eDdaWDZIeVpwd1lv</guid></item><item><title>视频： Golden Retriever Puppy在未能转身后反击-雅虎</title><link>https://www.yahoo.com/lifestyle/articles/video-golden-retriever-puppy-hits-144847871.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="" data-article-body="true"&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Early puppyhood is often filled with clumsy movements, curious discoveries, and moments that are unintentionally hilarious. For many pet parents, these fleeting stages pass quickly, making them worth capturing on camera whenever possible. One such moment recently caught the internet’s attention, thanks to a short but charming video of a Golden Retriever puppy figuring out how his body works.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mb-4 text-xl font-bold md:text-2xl"&gt;Video shows Golden Retriever puppy walk in reverse because he can’t turn around&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;In a recent video shared by @adventures.of.pilot, a &lt;a href="https://dogtime.com/dog-breeds/golden-retriever" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Golden Retriever;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Golden Retriever&lt;/a&gt; puppy called Pilot is attempting to navigate his surroundings but ends up walking backward instead.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Onscreen text explains the situation: “Enjoy this video of my puppy walking in reverse because he didn’t know how to turn around.” The puppy takes hesitant, wobbly steps as he slowly backs up, appearing genuinely unsure of what to do next.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Pilot is also wearing a small harness, which some viewers speculated may have added to his confusion. Whether it was the harness or simply a case of puppy brain, the result was a hilarious and wholesome scene. As he carefully reverses, his movements are cautious but determined, as if he believes backing up is the only logical solution.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;It didn’t take long for the clip to gain traction. The video quickly racked up more than 310K likes and drew over a hundred comments from viewers who related to Pilot’s behavior or simply found it hilarious.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Many shared stories of their own dogs going through similar phases, noting how common it is for puppies to struggle with basic movements as they learn coordination and spatial awareness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;One viewer jokingly wrote “beep beep beep,” comparing Pilot’s backward steps to a vehicle reversing. Another called him “a little goofball,” while someone else said their own puppy looked like he was “processing how to walk” during his early days.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;One popular comment summed up the playful tone by saying Golden Retrievers are “just orange cats in disguise,” joking that they all seem to share “one single brain cell.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://dogtime.com/news/201001-golden-retriever-puppy-reverse-walk-video-funny" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Video: Golden Retriever Puppy Hits Reverse After Failing To Turn Around;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Video: Golden Retriever Puppy Hits Reverse After Failing To Turn Around&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a href="https://dogtime.com" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:DogTime;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;DogTime&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Yahoo</author><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 14:48:47 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikwFBVV95cUxQNG9adThuVEt2ZG13TUJBcFIxWUlLU2FJdURFZWpmYUd2dFZ5ZE4zdV95ZzRtRVh6ckFYMkVzdTZ2clREU21PcE1SUXVQOUpPRWpIaG4td2lUM3d4eDBEWDNySmNEbHVfRzFPcDRibXp6bS04dlk0eXRzUEJvVnRGMUwzTVZlUUhJbGxid1ZtU1VVOW8</guid></item><item><title>在中国， A.I.发现医生可能会错过的胰腺癌--《纽约时报》</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2026/01/02/world/asia/china-ai-cancer-pancreatic.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The New York Times</author><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 14:34:13 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigwFBVV95cUxNQkhJMktSeGRHTGlCS2pCM3pmaERKMVE5T1laSE95MEN6T1pVd2F1YVlDUjljZlFqYW5wRmVzX2FhQ045ZWhmVFVxaGFmeDI1ZWY5ZFN4cU1XQXpaT0VkSFNwRl9pdTZGTndFVDlsbzhBZTVPa2hHYWh1Q3pxZ3VIVWdQWQ</guid></item></channel></rss>