<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>GNews Health</title><link>https://news.google.com/</link><description></description><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>是时候停止食用塑料了。首先，清理这7件充满微塑料的物品- CNET</title><link>https://www.cnet.com/health/its-time-to-stop-eating-plastic-start-by-trashing-these-7-items-full-of-microplastics/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article class="c-ShortcodeContent c-ShortcodeContent-theme:default sm:u-col-2 md:u-col-6 lg:u-col-12"&gt;&lt;p class="u-speakableText-p1"&gt;It's a strange thought, but you're probably consuming tiny bits of plastic with your meals every day. They're called &lt;span section="shortcodeLink"&gt;&lt;a href="/health/nutrition/microplastics-are-everywhere-heres-how-to-avoid-them-in-8-common-foods/" rel class="c-shortcodeLink c-shortcodeLink-active"&gt;&lt;span&gt;microplastics&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;, and these invisible particles are practically everywhere-in our food, our water, and even the air. For a long time, no one was sure what that meant, but we're now learning this constant exposure might be a real problem for our health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="u-speakableText-p2"&gt;For example, a &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41591-024-03453-1" target="_self"&gt;February 2025 study&lt;/a&gt; found that these plastic bits aren't just passing through our systems. They can actually build up inside our bodies. That discovery has obviously raised serious questions about what this could mean long-term, especially as scientists look into potential links to major health issues.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So where is all this plastic coming from? A huge source is a place you'd least expect: your own kitchen. Between food wrap, containers, and even some cookware, the plastics add up. The good news is, you can lower your exposure with a few easy changes. Let's start by looking at where they're most likely hiding.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.google.com/preferences/source?q=cnet.com" target="_self"&gt;Don't miss any of CNET's unbiased tech content and lab-based reviews. Add us as a preferred Google source on Chrome.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Are microplastics harmful?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Microplastics have become a serious problem for pollution, and now scientists worry about their potential health effects. An estimated &lt;a href="https://www.ciel.org/breathing-plastic-the-health-impacts-of-invisible-plastics-in-the-air/" target="_self"&gt;22 million micro and nanoplastics&lt;/a&gt; are inhaled by humans each year, and that is largely because they are so hard to avoid. You're exposed to microplastics in &lt;a href="https://hsc.unm.edu/news/2024/08/hsc-newsroom-post-minimizing-microplastics.html" target="_self"&gt;three ways&lt;/a&gt;: inhalation, ingestion or touch.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement" class="c-adDisplay_container c-pageArticle_ad c-pageArticle_ad-90 g-outer-spacing-bottom-medium c-adDisplay_container_incontent-all-top spaced blank"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Microplastics &lt;a href="https://www.nejm.org/doi/full/10.1056/NEJMoa2309822?query=featured_home" target="_self"&gt;have been shown&lt;/a&gt; to cause a number of issues in the human body. Microplastics and nanoplastics found in blood vessels &lt;a href="https://newsnetwork.mayoclinic.org/discussion/whats-lurking-in-your-body-mayo-researchers-probing-health-risks-of-tiny-plastic-particles/" target="_self"&gt;have been linked&lt;/a&gt; to an increased risk of heart attack, stroke and, in severe cases, even death. Tissue inflammation, cell death and lung and liver impacts &lt;a href="https://magazine.hms.harvard.edu/articles/microplastics-everywhere" target="_self"&gt;have all been noted&lt;/a&gt;. In animals and marine life, they can also cause oxidative and DNA damage, as well as cancer. Mice were shown to have reduced sperm count, ovarian scarring and hereditary metabolic disorders.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Much is still unknown about the exact effects of microplastics, but studies so far have been sobering. They've inspired many home chefs to reconsider what they use in the kitchen and put in their bodies. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="c-shortcodeImage u-clearfix c-shortcodeImage-large c-shortcodeImage-hasCaption"&gt; &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;span class="c-shortcodeImage_caption g-inner-spacing-right-small g-text-xxsmall"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Microplastics are plastic particles smaller than 5 millimeters. Nanoplastics are much smaller and invisible to the naked eye, ranging from 1 to 1,000 nanometers -- a fraction of the width of a human hair. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="c-shortcodeImage_credit g-inner-spacing-right-small g-outer-spacing-top-xsmall g-color-text-meta g-text-xxxsmall"&gt;Svetlozar Hristov/Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement" class="c-adDisplay_container c-pageArticle_ad c-pageArticle_ad-90 g-outer-spacing-bottom-medium c-adDisplay_container_incontent-ad-plus-billboard-middle spaced blank"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Where microplastics hide in your kitchen&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;figure class="c-shortcodeImage u-clearfix c-shortcodeImage-small c-shortcodeImage-pullRight"&gt;&lt;a rel href="https://www.cnet.com/health-tips/" target="_blank" class="c-shortcodeImage_imageContainer"&gt;   &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Microplastics are more common than you think. These are some places they may be hiding in your kitchen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;1. Nonstick cookware&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;A new study found that plastic and nonstick cookware &lt;a href="https://pml.ac.uk/news/new-study-shows-plastic-and-non-stick-cookware-is/" target="_self"&gt;released microplastics&lt;/a&gt; into food during cooking, heightening one's exposure to these potentially harmful pollutants. Australian researchers &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S004896972205392X" target="_self"&gt;estimate&lt;/a&gt; that Teflon-coated cookware contains thousands, maybe millions, of microplastic particles, while a simple crack or fracture in your pan &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S004896972205392X" target="_self"&gt;could mean&lt;/a&gt; exposure to over two million microplastic particles.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;2. Plastic food containers&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Your Uber delivery could inadvertently be damaging your health, and it has nothing to do with what you order. With the rise of home delivery services, plastic containers are more common than ever, but these containers &lt;a href="https://www.ewg.org/news-insights/news/2023/11/safer-storage-avoiding-microplastic-concerns-while-managing-holiday" target="_self"&gt;can easily add&lt;/a&gt; microplastics to your food when heated or washed. One study found that all reusable plastic takeout containers typically used by restaurants contain microplastics.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;3. Plastic utensils&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;figure class="c-shortcodeImage u-clearfix c-shortcodeImage-large c-shortcodeImage-hasCaption"&gt; &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;span class="c-shortcodeImage_caption g-inner-spacing-right-small g-text-xxsmall"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Plastic utensils can leach microplastics into your food when exposed to high heat levels.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="c-shortcodeImage_credit g-inner-spacing-right-small g-outer-spacing-top-xsmall g-color-text-meta g-text-xxxsmall"&gt;Kinga Krzeminska/Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement" class="c-adDisplay_container c-pageArticle_ad c-pageArticle_ad-90 g-outer-spacing-bottom-medium c-adDisplay_container_incontent-ad-plus-billboard-middle spaced blank"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Studies also show that plastic utensils &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S016041202400326X" target="_self"&gt;release microplastics&lt;/a&gt; into your food, especially when used with hotter foods. When you ingest the food, you also ingest microplastics that settle into your body and bloodstream.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;4. Tea bags&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;It may come as a surprise, but microplastics could be hiding in your tea bags. When you brew tea, the bag is exposed to extremely high temperatures that &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC10389239/" target="_self"&gt;can release&lt;/a&gt; its microplastics. This comes from polypropylene, a key component in the manufacturing of tea bags. Researchers at Spain's Autonomous University of Barcelona found that billions of microplastic and nanoplastic particles &lt;a href="https://www.uab.cat/web/newsroom/news-detail/-1345830290613.html?detid=1345940427095" target="_self"&gt;are released&lt;/a&gt; from a single tea bag for every millimeter of water it is submerged in.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="c-shortcodeImage u-clearfix c-shortcodeImage-large c-shortcodeImage-hasCaption"&gt; &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;span class="c-shortcodeImage_caption g-inner-spacing-right-small g-text-xxsmall"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Research has shown that a single plastic tea bag can release billions of microplastic fragments.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="c-shortcodeImage_credit g-inner-spacing-right-small g-outer-spacing-top-xsmall g-color-text-meta g-text-xxxsmall"&gt;Zarina Lukash/Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement" class="c-adDisplay_container c-pageArticle_ad c-pageArticle_ad-90 g-outer-spacing-bottom-medium c-adDisplay_container_incontent-ad-plus-billboard-middle spaced blank"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;5. Certain spices&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Depending on how it is packaged, that bottle of paprika could be full of microplastics. Many spices today use plastic packaging, which is concerning because one recent study found microplastics in all plastic containers tested. This can result in food contamination, which &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S0269749122019613" target="_self"&gt;has increased&lt;/a&gt; in recent decades.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;6. Plastic straws&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Plastic straws are especially concerning because &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S2772416623000992" target="_self"&gt;studies show&lt;/a&gt; that they release microplastics and nanoplastics, which can then be directly inhaled. Unfortunately, plastic straws are extremely prevalent, with about eight million metric tons of plastic &lt;a href="https://www.nrdc.org/stories/single-use-plastics-101" target="_self"&gt;found in waterways&lt;/a&gt; each year. Once these straws and other plastics are in the water, they can affect not just the water but also the soil and animals found in it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;7. Canned food linings&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;BPA was a controversial &lt;a href="https://www.ewg.org/news-insights/news/bpa-update-tracking-canned-food-phaseout" target="_self"&gt;material used&lt;/a&gt; in the manufacturing of canned food linings that could cause serious health effects. Today, non-BPA acrylic or polyester epoxies are more commonly used, but these are not proven safe either, as they too contain microplastics.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Kitchen material swaps to reduce microplastics&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Luckily, you have alternatives. Before putting on your apron, consider adding these items to your kitchen to lower your risk of exposure to microplastics.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Wooden or stainless spatulas&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;There are alternatives to plastic spatulas. Consider trying out a &lt;a href="https://www.earlywooddesigns.com/products/wooden-kitchen-utensil-set" target="_self"&gt;wooden utensil set&lt;/a&gt; or one made from stainless steel. This can significantly reduce your exposure to microplastics while upgrading your used utensils.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Wooden or stainless steel utensils&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Instead of plastic utensils, try to use stainless steel utensils that can be better for the body and also the environment. Wooden utensils can also be a great substitute, working as a more eco-friendly option for your kitchen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Glass or stainless steel food containers&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;You can't do much about how restaurants choose to package their food, but you can avoid using them in the future. At home, try to stick to glass, ceramic and stainless steel containers to skip the microplastics.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement" class="c-adDisplay_container c-pageArticle_ad c-pageArticle_ad-90 g-outer-spacing-bottom-medium c-adDisplay_container_incontent-ad-plus-billboard-middle spaced blank"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Loose tea leaves and strainers or infusers&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tea bags can be filled with plastic, but a safer alternative could be loose tea leaves. Many companies nowadays offer loose tea leaves that can be used with a stainless steel strainer or infuser, which works the same as a tea bag but can be much healthier.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Spices in bulk or glass containers&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;To avoid potential contamination from your spices, switch to glass or ceramic packaging instead. This allows your spices to remain on your shelf without being infused with potentially harmful microplastics that can seep into your food.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Reusable metal or bamboo straws&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Plastic straws take a toll on both the environment and your body, causing serious issues for both. A better alternative would be metal or bamboo straws that can be washed and reused. Even paper straws are a better alternative than plastic ones.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="c-shortcodeImage u-clearfix c-shortcodeImage-original c-shortcodeImage-hasCaption"&gt; &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;span class="c-shortcodeImage_caption g-inner-spacing-right-small g-text-xxsmall"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Reusable metal or bamboo straws are great alternatives to plastic ones. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="c-shortcodeImage_credit g-inner-spacing-right-small g-outer-spacing-top-xsmall g-color-text-meta g-text-xxxsmall"&gt;Luliia Bondar/Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Fresh produce or frozen produce&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Plastic linings in canned food can hold microplastics, so to eliminate your exposure, look for foods that are packaged in glass instead. You can also opt to use fresh and frozen foods and produce that skips the packaging altogether.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement" class="c-adDisplay_container c-pageArticle_ad c-pageArticle_ad-90 g-outer-spacing-bottom-medium c-adDisplay_container_incontent-ad-plus-billboard-middle spaced blank"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Cast iron, carbon steel or stainless steel cookware&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Plastic cookware is common in many kitchens, but there are alternatives. Products like &lt;a href="https://www.cnet.com/home/kitchen-and-household/best-stainless-steel-skillet/" target="_self"&gt;stainless steel skillets&lt;/a&gt;,&lt;a href="https://www.cnet.com/home/kitchen-and-household/best-frying-pan/" target="_self"&gt; frying pans&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.cnet.com/home/kitchen-and-household/lighter-cast-iron-frying-pan-options/" target="_self"&gt;cast iron pans&lt;/a&gt; can all be great ways to upgrade your cookware without risking further exposure to microplastics.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;The bottom line&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Microplastics can lurk in our kitchens, hiding in our cookware and utensils and making their way into our food. Though research continues, microplastics have been shown to cause damage to the human body, causing huge concerns over the products we use and the materials used to make them. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, hope is not lost. With a few simple changes, you can lessen your exposure to microplastics, thus better protecting your health. To learn more, &lt;a href="https://www.cnet.com/health/nutrition/eating-these-9-foods-you-might-be-swallowing-microplastics/" target="_self"&gt;here are the most common foods with microplastics&lt;/a&gt; and tips for reducing your intake. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>CNET</author><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMitAFBVV95cUxQVFBUYjNyWEZSMXhVRXdmUFpFbUhZU3BiREFNcVdZRFVGS0gtSGFWUk1LOGczVzdKUWduelJTTWVDTFUwNjFyVllsTERYU21jOW9ieklYVFlxallTakFGZk9tTHhZdjQ2U1U4aXk0WWpBSXExM250QVJWNlpyYTRYSmI4dHdCUGFSM1BmN2dnUThvMmstc0tCdXZEY1lqVlVVNWlfSW1ETWlwdW03TGYyZG5ac2M</guid></item><item><title>当简单的游泳会带来危险疾病的风险时--《纽约时报》</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/09/15/health/schistosomiasis-children.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The New York Times</author><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 09:00:13 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMie0FVX3lxTE1KbWFBQTNLX1pldGx2Q3dWa3ZtODhKZTNmQXdZVHUwV1pJcTRlaUM2a05rRkJaZlp3WU1ldXRuYjZTZHJpbkljVExHSHFkNzFkSUZqd1h0RmNFaW5hYXNvSDUtQjhVX0lha3I2SERRMS1uU2RScTdlczJYaw</guid></item><item><title>是镁还是按摩？关于睡眠用镁乳的事实- NPR</title><link>https://www.npr.org/2025/09/15/nx-s1-5529375/magnesium-lotion-massage-sleep</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="storytext" class="storytext storylocation linkLocation"&gt;
      &lt;div id="resg-s1-88349" class="bucketwrap image large"&gt;
            
&lt;div class="credit-caption"&gt;
    

    &lt;span class="credit" aria-label="Image credit"&gt;
        
        Microgen Images/Getty Images/Science Photo Library RF
        
    &lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;The latest health craze to hit social media: magnesium lotion.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Magnesium is an essential mineral that the body uses for a number of functions. It has long been thought to help with sleep when taken as an oral supplement, though there is &lt;a href="https://www.npr.org/sections/shots-health-news/2024/08/05/nx-s1-5060416/sleep-magnesium-supplements" target="_blank"&gt;little scientific evidence&lt;/a&gt; to back up that claim. &lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Influencers now promote magnesium in lotion form as an elixir for improving sleep as well as for addressing a wide range of problems, including cortisol and insulin imbalance, muscle soreness, fibromyalgia and arthritis.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"Did you know rubbing magnesium cream on your child's feet can help with sleep?" asks one woman on TikTok who goes by cottagecalderon and who promises that it can help with growing pains and improving mood.&lt;/p&gt;   
   &lt;p&gt;"No midnight leg cramps," says a man on the account tap.the.orange.cart. "It works for me and my wife."&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"Y'all," says another TikTokker, well over 40ish, "this magnesium lotion and spray is magic in the bottle."&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;h3 class="edTag"&gt;The claim &lt;/h3&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Enthusiasts claim that magnesium lotion — specifically applied to feet — can improve sleep. Many also argue it can be applied all over the body to remedy a variety of other health ailments.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;People are buying the idea, literally. &lt;a href="https://growthmarketreports.com/report/topical-magnesium-creams-market" target="_blank"&gt;One market research group&lt;/a&gt; estimated the market in 2024 for topical magnesium was more than $400 million.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;h3 class="edTag"&gt;The evidence &lt;/h3&gt;   &lt;p&gt;There is little proof that magnesium can be absorbed through the skin.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"The problem with this is that the skin is a barrier, not a sponge," says &lt;a href="https://connects.catalyst.harvard.edu/Profiles/display/Person/162855" target="_blank"&gt;Nicholas Theodosakis&lt;/a&gt;, a dermatologist and researcher at Harvard University.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Most medications are best delivered orally, which allows for quick absorption into the bloodstream. A few kinds of substances are well suited to absorption through the skin, he says. Often, transdermal patches are used for medications that need to be slowly absorbed over time.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;There's no evidence that magnesium is in this category.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Theodosakis theorizes that any benefits realized from magnesium lotion are likely from the massage used to apply it or the lotion's moisturizing ingredients. &lt;/p&gt;   
   &lt;p&gt;" You apply a cream or a lotion or an ointment that contains some active ingredient and, yeah, your skin looks better than maybe some place you didn't apply it," says Theodosakis. "But that's because the cream itself promotes skin health. Anything that comes in like a cream base or an ointment base is just automatically gonna be good for the skin."&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;h3 class="edTag"&gt;The nuance&lt;/h3&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Despite the lack of evidence, at least one doctor says if magnesium lotion is working for you — go for it. "I think the risks of applying magnesium to your skin are probably extremely small," says Dr. &lt;a href="https://sleep.hms.harvard.edu/faculty-staff/john-winkelman" target="_blank"&gt;John Winkelman&lt;/a&gt;, a sleep expert at Harvard.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;He says he had at least one patient report using "magnesium butter," for sleep. (" I thought you put that on toast, but no, in fact, you rub it on your legs," says Winkelman.) "She did say magnesium butter was helping."&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Winkelman says in matters of sleep especially, placebo can be powerful — and he's not one to discourage whatever safe remedies work for his patients.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;That said, Winkelman is not planning to recommend it anytime soon. Supplements and related products are not regulated by the Food and Drug Administration, which leaves consumers vulnerable to buying the lotion without knowing exactly what's in it.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;For some of the sleep conditions that magnesium lotion supposedly treats, says Winkelman, there are medically proven treatments. Restless legs syndrome, for example — something some influencers say is eased with an application of magnesium lotion — has actual tested medical therapies. &lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"I really don't feel that it's fair to recommend things that I really don't think have been substantiated as effective," says Winkelman. "I'm a big believer in scientific evidence."&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;h3 class="edTag"&gt;The bottom line&lt;/h3&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Though there is no proof that magnesium lotion promotes sleep or addresses medical problems, experts, including dermatologist Nicholas Theodosakis, agree that magnesium lotion likely won't hurt, except, he says, "in the pocketbook."&lt;/p&gt;   
   &lt;p&gt;He notes that as a dermatologist, he sees many health fads. "I think it's just the nature of skin," he notes. "It's highly linked to emotional well-being and psychology and culture. Also, you just have quite a lot of it."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>NPR</author><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 09:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigAFBVV95cUxNaUMycDFmR2NUSXNFNjJjRUxjVUcwNFQtcWhWQ3JJQjZJOUdDRVlPaTRDeHl0UnR6Qm9yQjhWRXdnRkVkNXpYX2VZX2QxODlseGpSTDZteFgwaWl6NUFDMHBxMmRPSzNGYmdhOHdmdXlKbjVOcmxzOW9YVkIwZ3ViNg</guid></item><item><title>每日滴眼液可能会使老花镜过时- ScienceDaily</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/09/250914205832.htm</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p id="first" class="lead"&gt;Everybody develops presbyopia as they age - a difficulty in focusing on near objects and text - and often have to resort to reading glasses. However, the solution might be as simple as using special eye drops two or three times a day.&lt;/p&gt;

						&lt;div id="text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A retrospective study of 766 patients presented on September 14 at the 43&lt;sup&gt;rd&lt;/sup&gt; Congress of the European Society of Cataract and Refractive Surgeons (ESCRS) [1], found that the majority could read an extra two, three or more lines on the eye chart used for testing near visual acuity (the Jaeger chart) after using specially formulated eye drops. This improvement was sustained for up to two years.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dr Giovanna Benozzi, director of the Center for Advanced Research for Presbyopia, in Buenos Aires, Argentina, said: "We conducted this research due to the significant unmet medical need in presbyopia management. Current solutions such as reading glasses or surgical interventions have limitations, including inconvenience, social discomfort, and potential risks or complications. There is a group of presbyopia patients who have limited options besides spectacles, and who are not candidates for surgery; these are our primary focus of interest. We sought to provide robust clinical evidence supporting an innovative pharmacological solution to offer patients a non-invasive, convenient and effective alternative."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The eye drops, developed by Dr Benozzi's father, the late Dr Jorge Benozzi of the same centre, contain a combination of two active agents: pilocarpine, a drug that constricts the pupils and contracts the ciliary muscle, which is a muscle controlling the eye's accommodation for seeing objects at varying distances, and diclofenac, a non-steroidal anti-inflammatory drug (NSAID) that reduces inflammation and the discomfort that pilocarpine often causes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Patients administered the eye drops twice a day, usually on waking and again approximately six hours later, with an optional third dose if symptoms recurred or additional visual comfort was needed. The group of patients (373 women and 393 men, with an average age of 55) were divided into three groups to receive one of three eye drop formulations. Each formulation had a fixed dose of diclofenac but concentrations of pilocarpine were 1%, 2% and 3%.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The researchers assessed the improvement in how well patients could read the Jaeger chart without reading glasses (uncorrected near visual acuity) one hour after the first administration of the drops, and they followed up the patients for two years.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dr Benozzi told the Congress: "Our most significant result showed rapid and sustained improvements in near vision for all three concentrations. One hour after having the first drops, patients had an average improvement of 3.45 Jaeger lines. The treatment also improved focus at all distances.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="insertion_middle"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Impressively, 99% of 148 patients in the 1% pilocarpine group reached optimal near vision and were able to read two or more extra lines. Approximately 83% of all patients maintained good functional near vision at 12 months. Importantly, no significant adverse events like increased intraocular pressure or retinal detachment were observed."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the 2% group, 69% of 248 patients were able to read three or more extra lines on the Jaeger chart, and in the 3% group, 84% of 370 patients could read three or more extra lines.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The improvement in the patients' vision was sustained for up to two years, with a median duration of 434 days. Adverse side effects were mild, with the most common being temporary dim vision, which occurred in 32% of cases, irritation when the drops were instilled (3.7%) and headache (3.8%). No patients discontinued the treatment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Common adverse side effects of pilocarpine can also include eye redness, watery eyes, blurred vision, dim or dark vision, sensitivity to light or problems changing focus between objects, seeing flashes of light or "floaters" in vision, and, in rare cases, detached retinas.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dr Benozzi continued: "Nearly all patients experienced positive improvements in near visual acuity, although the magnitude of the improvement depended on the status of their vision before treatment at baseline. Our study revealed that optimal pilocarpine concentrations could be individualized depending on the baseline severity of presbyopia as assessed by the initial Jaeger scores. Patients with less severe presbyopia responded best to 1% concentrations, while those with more advanced presbyopia required higher 2% or 3% concentrations to achieve significant visual improvement."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She concluded: "These results suggest this combination therapy offers a safe, effective, and well-tolerated alternative to traditional presbyopia management. It significantly reduces dependence on reading glasses, providing a convenient, non-invasive option for patients, although these eye drops may not eliminate the need for glasses in all individuals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="insertion_bottom"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Importantly, this treatment is not intended to replace surgical interventions, but rather to serve as a valuable solution for patients who need safe, effective, and personalised alternatives and seek freedom from the inconvenience of eyewear. Eye care professionals now have an evidence-based pharmacological option that expands the spectrum of presbyopia care beyond glasses and surgery."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Besides the group of patients in this study, Dr Benozzi has other patients who have received the treatment for more than ten years. Dr Benozzi plans further research to measure improvements in patients' quality of life, and to explore the underlying physiological mechanisms of the eye drops.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Strengths of the study include the large number of patients included and the long follow-up time. It is the first systematic evaluation comparing three different pilocarpine concentrations in combination with diclofenac. A limitation is that it is a retrospective, single-centre study, which could limit the generalizability of the findings and introduce selection bias.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ESCRS President-Elect, Professor Burkhard Dick, chair of the ophthalmology department at the University Eye Hospital Bochum, Germany, was not involved in the research. He commented: "While surgery for age-related near vision loss has advanced, some patients are not candidates. The single-centre retrospective study by Dr Benozzi suggests that eye drops containing pilocarpine and diclofenac may improve near vision for up to two years, but the limited design means the results may not apply to everyone. Long-term pilocarpine use can sometimes cause side effects such as reduced night vision, dimmer vision in low light, eye strain, irritation and, in rare cases, retinal detachment, while prolonged topical NSAID use may pose corneal risks. Broader, long-term, multi-centre studies are needed to confirm safety and effectiveness before this treatment can be widely recommended."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Notes&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ol&gt;    &lt;li&gt;Abstract number: ESCRS25-FP-3944, 'Dose-dependent efficacy and safety of pilocarpine-diclofenac eye drops for presbyopia: a real-world single-center study," by Giovanna Benozzi &lt;em&gt;et al&lt;/em&gt;. Free paper session on 'Miscellaneous topics in cataract and refractive surgery', 16:30-18:00 hrs CEST, Sunday, September 14, &lt;a href="https://pag.virtual-meeting.org/escrs/escrs2025/en-GB/pag/presentation/570375"&gt;https://pag.virtual-meeting.org/escrs/escrs2025/en-GB/pag/presentation/570375&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

					&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceDaily</author><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 05:31:57 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMib0FVX3lxTFA5WXgtdDJTQVJDQVJaLXUzWWwzZHp1dWVfMWlkWVlNMXFuS3JEYU9hREV0b2FKbldRWGcwLW94Zk1yTV8xWmtZNFlnMEhIczhJbkU5UFFzT0JGNFBYQ1VIMmpKOGFsbFJ2N3pTQS1fTQ</guid></item><item><title>世界需要更多的疫苗。美国的抗疫苗无济于事。-《纽约时报》</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/09/15/world/asia/anti-vaccine-america-world-covid.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The New York Times</author><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 04:01:12 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiwFBVV95cUxObnJQUlNTTW4tQ3FKRWVZQWU0bUdDQVo4S3ZiR1dzeExCTFNhNlN3aWtBRGEzZlRSNWZZQUEyV0ctb2tVWktKM2JjZkRZV05DSnlkazBzM0ZBSDBOYmFTVjhYZ2RuR2piM0tMd2JJX0tXQ0U1Zlo1VER4SHktZlE4Zm5pWDdNbFVkTUdn</guid></item><item><title>疼痛医学医生揭示了7种缓解慢性疼痛的自然疗法：姜黄、CBD、鱼油等|健康-印度斯坦时报</title><link>https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/pain-medicine-physician-reveals-7-natural-relief-options-to-manage-chronic-pain-turmeric-cbd-fish-oil-and-more-101757842398300.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="detail " dataid="/lifestyle/health/pain-medicine-physician-reveals-7-natural-relief-options-to-manage-chronic-pain-turmeric-cbd-fish-oil-and-more-101757842398300.html"&gt; &lt;div class="storyParagraphFigure"&gt; &lt;p&gt;Living with &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/science/the-discovery-of-a-gene-for-chronic-pain-could-herald-new-treatments-101755766622871.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="chronic pain"&gt;chronic pain&lt;/a&gt; can be exhausting, and while prescription medicines are often necessary, many people look to &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/gastroenterologist-says-chewing-sugar-free-gum-after-meals-sleeping-on-left-reduces-heartburn-7-natural-remedies-101754019871931.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="natural remedies"&gt;natural remedies&lt;/a&gt; for additional relief. From herbs and vitamins to essential nutrients, certain supplements may support the body’s ability to manage inflammation, ease discomfort, and improve overall quality of life.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;figure class=""&gt; &lt;span class=""&gt; &lt;picture&gt; &lt;source media="(max-width:767px)" srcset="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/09/14/550x309/pain_1757842629567_1757842629725.jpg" alt="Living with chronic pain is hard - here are seven natural pain relief options you can try out!(Unsplash)" title="Living with chronic pain is hard - here are seven natural pain relief options you can try out!(Unsplash)"&gt;&lt;/source&gt; &lt;img src="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/09/14/550x309/pain_1757842629567_1757842629725.jpg" alt="Living with chronic pain is hard - here are seven natural pain relief options you can try out!(Unsplash)" title="Living with chronic pain is hard - here are seven natural pain relief options you can try out!(Unsplash)"&gt; &lt;/picture&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;figcaption&gt;Living with chronic pain is hard - here are seven natural pain relief options you can try out!(Unsplash)&lt;/figcaption&gt; &lt;/figure&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;p id="readMoreFTUser"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Also Read | &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/heart-attack-or-heartburn-doctor-explains-how-to-know-when-chest-pain-is-serious-101757825185931.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="Heart attack or heartburn? Doctor explains how to know when chest pain is serious"&gt;Heart attack or heartburn? Doctor explains how to know when chest pain is serious&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="mt-10 mb-10 htEchoRecirculationWidget"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="mt10 mb10 htEchoArticlePromo"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="predictorShow mb20" data-vars-predictor="true" data-vars-quiz="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="quizShow mb20" data-vars-minimized="false" data-vars-predictor="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Dr Kunal Sood, an anesthesiology and interventional pain medicine physician, has shared seven natural relief options to manage chronic pain. In an Instagram video he posted on September 12, the doctor highlighted how certain &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/natural-supplements-v-s-allopathy-what-works-better-in-boosting-immune-system-101680090386542.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="natural supplements"&gt;natural supplements&lt;/a&gt; can aid in managing chronic pain. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;He cautioned viewers to seek medical advice before use, since dosing varies based on medical history, and suggested beginning with smaller amounts to watch for side effects. Still, he emphasized that for many people, the benefits are likely to outweigh the risks.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Turmeric&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Turmeric is rich in the active compound curcumin, which has anti-inflammatory and &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/cardiologist-calls-matcha-tea-science-in-a-cup-shares-top-5-benefits-fat-burn-antioxidant-weight-loss-caffeine-101752815578622.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="antioxidant"&gt;antioxidant &lt;/a&gt;properties, according to Dr Sood.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;Vitamin D&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr Sood states that the whole body has &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/vitamin-d3-supplements-vegan-options-for-stronger-immunity-and-active-lifestyle-101757418357652.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="vitamin D"&gt;vitamin D&lt;/a&gt; receptors, including the nervous system. He continues, “Some research suggests that vitamin D may play a role in regulating pain perception and nerve function, improving quality of life in chronic pain patients.” The doctor also mentions that vitamin D can be beneficial for bone health and reducing inflammation.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;Ashwagandha&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stress and anxiety is believed to aggravate chronic pain. Dr Sood suggests consuming &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/can-ashwagandha-boost-memory-and-thinking-study-unlocks-unknown-potential-of-this-herb-101751090770201.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="ashwagandha"&gt;ashwagandha &lt;/a&gt;to manage anxiety and improve sleep, which helps with recovery.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;Fish oil&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to Dr Sood, fish oil is loaded with &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/dermatologist-suggests-6-diet-tips-to-cure-psoriasis-consume-anti-inflammatory-foods-drink-water-101756891986133.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="anti-inflammatory"&gt;anti-inflammatory&lt;/a&gt; properties and research shows that it helps with pain related to arthritis.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Also Read | &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/aiims-gastroenterologist-dr-saurabh-sethi-explains-if-eating-undercooked-chicken-can-paralyse-your-body-warning-signs-101757816572456.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="AIIMS trained gastroenterologist explains eating undercooked chicken can paralyse your body: Here's why"&gt;AIIMS trained gastroenterologist explains eating undercooked chicken can paralyse your body: Here's why&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;Magnesium&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr Sood recommends taking magnesium to deal with muscle pain and cramping. Besides this, it also induces sleep, improving sleep quality, and relieves &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/topic/constipation" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="constipation"&gt;constipation&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;CBD&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cannabidiol or &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/pet/amazing-benefits-of-cbd-oil-for-your-pet-expert-says-it-can-ease-anxiety-joint-pain-101687766894119.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="CBD"&gt;CBD &lt;/a&gt;is the oil extracted from cannabis plants. According to Dr Sood, research shows that CBD has promising pain-relief and anti-inflammatory properties. He continues, “There is some research showing it can help with knee osteoarthritis and neuropathic pain,” but also adds that more studies are required in the area.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;Glucosamine/chondroitin&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Glucosamine and chondroitin are natural compounds found in cartilages, the tissues that cushion joints, according to the &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.nccih.nih.gov/health/glucosamine-and-chondroitin-for-osteoarthritis-what-you-need-to-know#:~:text=Glucosamine%20and%20chondroitin%20are%20constituents,in%20its%20resistance%20to%20compression." target="_blank" class="backlink" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="National Centre for Complementary and Integrative Health"&gt;National Centre for Complementary and Integrative Health&lt;/a&gt;. Dr Sood highlights that it is great for managing secondary pain caused due to &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/woman-59-who-struggled-to-walk-reveals-how-she-reversed-arthritis-diabetes-lost-7-kg-with-just-strength-training-101756280369734.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="arthritis"&gt;arthritis&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Note to readers: This article is for informational purposes only and not a substitute for professional medical advice. It is based on user-generated content from social media. HT.com has not independently verified the claims and does not endorse them.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Hindustan Times</author><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 01:59:26 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiwJBVV95cUxNdk1wZXpmX3pUSFdNRHc1SllLb1lGTklNOXk5cTdfbmNUS2d6aDR1b2N3Y00xckl2S3dnc3NsUDFLYlBJMTZmUXZWRVRmeDlRQVJXbzl1TkQyTndZTFBYVmtfYTI2SzgyMl9CVkdCenVkWjlody1nazFsblU3cWVnaVZldXVCOXJ6eWlsN045a3pscGh0UUZHMWJTaGI2bUJsWEpMUTFZV2VQTDQ5NWdoTlpzMUdKVlJiOG52S0ZCTlNyaXBUajNRZW5NRWFmSnZxb1dwXzZxUWx0NzVLWUI3Vk1MVUhvc2t4b3d6YlFOLTNhZDJfcU5fZUZEZGliSldYNU40WkxhajlWQVHSAZACQVVfeXFMTXEwNDB3b1czMGVIMGdESnZHamhWdmkyWGhsTzc2N3RpM0xyVFJZWkl3Nm9CSDlnMDRBVl9mS1oyeUVTRE4yVE9xaFktTEZHWDVjNVNUWEF0Unhwd051VzdzSlRoQ1E2MlYzYVNyOHJrdmFHazR3LURUSUl6OWJKZzFXUG56RzQzOVZlZklQN0VaYnBlNTRxTnB4dnlGckdkY3hfSWxmc0dHSklERXpST2NINDROTTV3UmxsdHZoeHctRnhvRTVBVTlmdW0xbjVCS2QtVWFZX0dXekpIMmtGRWE2aXBOekdEeDFLZUZ3NjUzVjlpNmltM2xDbUd3M0otcFQ5R3h3dkNSWWVYNEtmdnA</guid></item><item><title>痴呆症与糖尿病相关的10个关键原因- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/10-key-reasons-dementia-is-linked-with-diabetes</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;The link between  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/diabetes" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73018" data-postid="174214" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;diabetes&lt;/a&gt; and dementia is becoming increasingly clear. New research shows how blood sugar problems affect brain health and vice versa. Here are ten evidence-based insights into how the two conditions are related.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;1. Diabetes raises the risk of dementia&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;People with diabetes are about &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC4722942/"&gt;60% more likely&lt;/a&gt; to develop dementia than those without, and frequent episodes of low blood sugar are linked to a 50% higher chance of cognitive &lt;a href="https://dmsjournal.biomedcentral.com/articles/10.1186/s13098-024-01346-4"&gt;decline&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;2. Insulin resistance affects the brain too&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Insulin resistance – the major cause of type 2 diabetes – happens when cells stop responding properly to insulin. This means that too much sugar, in the form of glucose, is left in the blood, leading to complications.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/an-early-signal-of-dementia-could-be-hidden-in-how-we-read-faces"&gt;An Early Signal of Dementia Could Be Hidden in How We Read Faces&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It usually affects the liver and muscles, but it also affects the brain. In  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/go/IaO" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73015" data-postid="174214" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;Alzheimer's&lt;/a&gt;, this resistance may make it harder for brain cells to use glucose for energy, contributing to &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC4351418/"&gt;cognitive decline&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;3. A brain sugar shortage in dementia&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The brain is only 2% of our body weight, but uses about 20% of the body's energy. In dementia, brain cells appear to lose the ability to use glucose &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC7948516/"&gt;properly&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This mix of poor use of glucose and insulin resistance is sometimes unofficially called &lt;a href="https://www.alzheimersresearchuk.org/dementia-information/dementia-risk/diabetes-and-dementia-risk/"&gt;type 3 diabetes&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_174225" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-174225" class="wp-caption aligncenter"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/09/Woman-with-Diabetes-Wearing-a-CGM-Device-on-Her-Arm-Reading-a-Book.jpg" alt="Woman with Diabetes Wearing a CGM Device on Her Arm Reading a Book" class="size-full wp-image-174225" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/09/Woman-with-Diabetes-Wearing-a-CGM-Device-on-Her-Arm-Reading-a-Book.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/09/Woman-with-Diabetes-Wearing-a-CGM-Device-on-Her-Arm-Reading-a-Book-533x415.jpg 533w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/09/Woman-with-Diabetes-Wearing-a-CGM-Device-on-Her-Arm-Reading-a-Book-600x467.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-174225" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Frequent episodes of low blood sugar are linked to a 50% higher chance of cognitive decline. (&lt;a href="https://www.pexels.com/photo/woman-with-diabetes-wearing-a-cgm-device-on-her-arm-reading-a-book-17947755/"&gt;Nutrisense Inc/Pexels&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;h2&gt;4. Alzheimer's can raise diabetes risk&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;People with Alzheimer's often have &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC2993007/#abstract1"&gt;higher fasting blood glucose&lt;/a&gt;, even if they don't have diabetes. This is a form of pre-diabetes. Animal studies also show that Alzheimer's-like changes in the brain &lt;a href="https://link.springer.com/article/10.1007/s00125-016-3960-1"&gt;raise blood glucose levels&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Also, the highest genetic risk factor for Alzheimer's, the &lt;em&gt;APOE4&lt;/em&gt; genetic variant, reduces insulin sensitivity by &lt;a href="https://www.cell.com/neuron/references/S0896-6273(17)30791-2"&gt;trapping the insulin receptor inside the cell&lt;/a&gt;, where it cannot be switched on properly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;5. Blood vessel damage links both conditions&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Diabetes damages blood vessels, causing complications in the eyes, kidneys and heart. The brain is also at risk. High or varying blood glucose levels can injure vessels in the brain, reducing blood flow and oxygen delivery.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Diabetes can also weaken the brain's protective barrier, letting harmful substances in. This leads to inflammation. Reduced blood flow and brain inflammation are strongly &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC6571853/"&gt;linked to dementia&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;6. Memantine: a dementia drug born from diabetes research&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Memantine, used to treat moderate to severe Alzheimer's symptoms, was originally developed as a diabetes medication. It didn't succeed in controlling blood glucose, but researchers later discovered its benefits for &lt;a href="https://www.tandfonline.com/doi/full/10.1517/14656566.2011.558006"&gt;brain function&lt;/a&gt;. This story shows how diabetes research may hold clues for treating brain disorders.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;7. Metformin might protect the brain&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Metformin, the most widely used diabetes drug, does more than just lower blood glucose. It gets into the brain and may &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40710317/"&gt;lower brain inflammation&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some studies suggest that people with diabetes who take metformin are less likely to develop dementia, and those who stop taking it may see their &lt;a href="https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jamanetworkopen/fullarticle/2810994"&gt;risk increase again&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Trials are testing its effects in people &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40434891/"&gt;without diabetes&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;8. Weight-loss injections may reduce plaque buildup&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;GLP-1 receptor agonist drugs, such as semaglutide (Ozempic, Wegovy), lower blood glucose and support weight loss. Records show that people with diabetes on these drugs have a lower dementia risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Comparing GLP-1 drugs to metformin, studies have found that they were even &lt;a href="https://drc.bmj.com/content/13/4/e004902"&gt;more effective than metformin&lt;/a&gt; at reducing dementia risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Two major trials, &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/39780249/"&gt;Evoke and Evoke Plus&lt;/a&gt;, are testing oral semaglutide in people with mild cognitive impairment or early mild Alzheimer's.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_174227" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-174227" class="wp-caption aligncenter"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/09/Persons-Hands-Preparing-Semaglutide-Ozempic-Injection.jpg" alt="Person's Hands Preparing Semaglutide Injection" class="size-full wp-image-174227" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/09/Persons-Hands-Preparing-Semaglutide-Ozempic-Injection.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/09/Persons-Hands-Preparing-Semaglutide-Ozempic-Injection-533x415.jpg 533w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/09/Persons-Hands-Preparing-Semaglutide-Ozempic-Injection-600x467.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-174227" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;People with diabetes on GLP-1 receptor agonist drugs have a lower dementia risk. (imyskin/Canva)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;h2&gt;9. Insulin therapy might help the brain&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Since insulin resistance in the brain is a problem, researchers have tested insulin sprays given through the nose. This method delivers insulin straight to the brain while reducing effects on blood sugar.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Small studies suggest these sprays &lt;a href="https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jamaneurology/fullarticle/1107947"&gt;may help memory&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/34101779/"&gt;reduce brain shrinkage&lt;/a&gt;, but delivery methods remain a challenge. Sprays vary in how much insulin reaches the brain, and long-term safety has not yet been proven.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;10. SGLT2 inhibitors may lower dementia risk&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;New evidence suggests that compared to GLP-1 receptor agonists, SGLT2 inhibitors, (a type of diabetes drug) are superior at &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S1262363625000187"&gt;reducing dementia risk&lt;/a&gt;, including Alzheimer's and vascular dementia, in people with type 2 diabetes. These tablets lower blood sugar by increasing sugar removal in urine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This study builds on early evidence suggesting they lower dementia risk by &lt;a href="https://www.neurology.org/doi/10.1212/WNL.0000000000209805"&gt;reducing inflammation in the brain&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This growing body of evidence suggests that managing diabetes protects more than the heart and kidneys, it also helps preserve brain function.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Questions remain whether diabetes drugs only reduce the diabetes-associated dementia risk or whether these drugs could also reduce risk in people without diabetes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, diabetes research has been very successful in creating at least 13 different classes of drugs, multiple combination therapies, giving rise to at least 50 different medicines. These reduce blood sugar, improve insulin sensitivity and reduce inflammation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A 'side effect' may be better preservation of brain health during ageing.&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://counter.theconversation.com/content/264393/count.gif?distributor=republish-lightbox-basic" alt="The Conversation" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" loading="lazy"&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/profiles/craig-beall-200960"&gt;Craig Beall&lt;/a&gt;, Associate Professor in Experimental Diabetes, &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/institutions/university-of-exeter-1190"&gt;University of Exeter&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/profiles/natasha-macdonald-2471147"&gt;Natasha MacDonald&lt;/a&gt;, PhD Candidate, Biochemistry, &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/institutions/university-of-exeter-1190"&gt;University of Exeter&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This article is republished from &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com"&gt;The Conversation&lt;/a&gt; under a Creative Commons license. Read the &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/ten-ways-diabetes-and-dementia-are-linked-264393"&gt;original article&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 01:49:08 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiggFBVV95cUxPWU12b3Zjc3VEZ3V5UFVnLWdQZGFKMjBTUnhBRkhpOE9MUUVPLXRUcUljU2pKY2Z1TkVTLWJjTjN4bVhtMVpVeWJjN1BIUU9yeFlrbWhUeFkzeHRJYzlHbENEOVZWT3ZEZnpDZEVzUEJScW5lYXZuZV9Sd3ZVb1gtNEV3</guid></item><item><title>在马桶上使用手机？ 7种健康状况告诉你为什么这是个坏主意-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/using-your-phone-on-the-toilet-7-health-conditions-that-tell-you-why-its-a-bad-idea/photostory/123889757.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="COQxt" data-ua-type="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;These days, scrolling through your phone while sitting on the toilet has become a nearly universal habit. Whether you’re catching up on messages, watching videos, reading the news, or just passing the time, the bathroom ritual often doubles as a digital break, as the toilet becomes a mini escape from the world. On the surface, it feels harmless – a few extra minutes here and there. But emerging research suggests this convenience could carry hidden risks to health – especially in the digestive, anal, and pelvic areas.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A new study published in PLOS One by researchers at Beth Israel Deaconess Medical Center in Boston found that adults who use smartphones on the toilet have a 46% higher risk of hemorrhoids than those who don’t. Why? Because using a phone tends to prolong the time spent on the toilet, it increases pressure in the rectal veins. That alone may explain much of the risk. What drives this risk? Mainly, increased time sitting on the toilet (especially more than 5 minutes per visit), more pressure on anal and rectal veins, reduced physical activity, and distraction leading to poor habits. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But that’s just one of several problems being connected to this modern bathroom behaviour. From infections to pelvic damage, posture issues to digestive trouble, using your phone during bathroom visits might be doing more harm than you think.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In this article, we explore seven specific health conditions or risks linked with phone use on the toilet. We discuss what recent studies show, how each condition develops, and simple changes you can make to avoid becoming vulnerable. Even if you don’t bring your phone into the bathroom, some of these risks apply to prolonged sitting. Learning these can help you make smarter choices about when and how to use your phone — especially in your most private moments.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The following are several health conditions that are (or may be) linked to this particular bathroom habit, how the phone-on-toilet behavior contributes, and what you can do to reduce the risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 01:12:43 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijwJBVV95cUxQLUR0eTlKYWFXRjJDQ1F2aTQwNkNtMXdfUDFPVzA5Q1p5U2xCa0wwUThfX1NZYXNHWFd1VklOSnVPQWMyT3g3U0NXdkVCYjdxX1JuUHlZVjJITFVvbUc2SzlRMXBjdVdBMHNmblFBZGI2QUItMzJXbW9FelBndE01eFpGNk14RVV1czdpS3A5TC1yNUgwb2ZHMTV3c0NyeUtncXo4SVB2YmEzRlRwT1VVbWRLeFdDLUdYcGpwLWRnb1pUeHg0dm1FZ196RlNYTWFsdlFCMW9HWDZGRlV3dVFzY2lyeGliNkItYjZiaTg2dkNtQXdrRWxacFBJdWhmaGNIT0wzSTBwTFc0eWdiemVF0gGXAkFVX3lxTFBHYnE1NmxMc1BpdURlcVNJR0JlQk9pTlVLTzRmWEU5eXpCdXRaME81N3RuMnJKR0VhWkVmalJTaTRnUGlLTmFQNTRUSWY4WkRMcGpkcDZQaHd2cWpiNU1iT0lKQm9hNHpRZjJSSzRPVmZlelgzWG5ud25jdDJhaWJBdHpOSVhDMVduaFRMbzdzMFRGS2FPWm1KSF9ORFNqVGZBTVU0cUdyZ1Fza3hkM05ZNFAzQXBBeXFRX1MwZWgtX3Q0ZldXSTIxRllMY3lwaHRjX1U0b2VUMi1XRFBCbHY3Y0NZTm9JOWlJeEdJQVBHTEpYZk55d3F6ZEpYYmp2bzhfbk9mZ2FhM0k1YVVvQXFfOHNyVXYtVQ</guid></item><item><title>另有十几起案件报告，马歇尔县的退伍军人案件达到52起- WHO13.com</title><link>https://who13.com/news/iowa-news/another-dozen-cases-reported-legionnaires-cases-hit-52-in-marshall-county/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-content article-body rich-text "&gt;
		
		


&lt;p&gt;MARSHALL COUNTY, Iowa — A dozen more cases of Legionnaires’ disease have been reported in Marshall County over the past few days, putting the total number at 52. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href="https://who13.com/news/iowa-news/iowa-hhs-investigates-21-legionnaires-disease-cases-1-death-in-marshalltown/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Iowa Department of Health and Human Services announced an investigation into a group of 21 Legionnaires’ disease cases,&lt;/a&gt; and one resulting death, on September 4. Over the past &lt;a href="https://who13.com/news/iowa-news/marshall-county-residents-want-answers-after-34-cases-of-legionnaires-disease-confirmed/" data-type="link" data-id="https://who13.com/news/iowa-news/marshall-county-residents-want-answers-after-34-cases-of-legionnaires-disease-confirmed/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;few weeks, the number of cases has continued to grow. &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;On Friday the &lt;a href="https://who13.com/news/iowa-news/legionnaires-disease-cases-grow-to-40-in-marshall-county-iowa-hhs-says/" data-type="link" data-id="https://who13.com/news/iowa-news/legionnaires-disease-cases-grow-to-40-in-marshall-county-iowa-hhs-says/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Iowa HHS reported 40 cases of Legionaries’ disease&lt;/a&gt;, by Sunday morning they had raised that number to&lt;a href="https://hhs.iowa.gov/health-prevention/disease-information" data-type="link" data-id="https://hhs.iowa.gov/health-prevention/disease-information" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt; 52 cases.&lt;/a&gt; As of Sunday, there has still only been one reported death.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p hidden data-minutemedia-viewport="mobile" data-player-id="4m92we4y" data-stn-player="" data-s2n-api="minuteMediaS2NApi"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;p&gt;Legionnaires’ disease is caused by bacteria that spreads through the inhalation of aerosolized water droplets, such as cooling towers and fountains. Health officials say the disease is not contagious and most healthy people who become exposed do not become sick.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p hidden data-minutemedia-viewport="desktop" data-player-id="4m92we4y" data-stn-player="" data-s2n-api="minuteMediaS2NApi"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Health officials say individuals with weakened immune systems, chronic respiratory conditions, smokers and those 50 years and older are most likely to experiences severe illness from Legionnaires’ disease. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Common symptoms of Legionnaires’ disease include:&lt;/p&gt;





&lt;ul class="wp-block-list"&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fever&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;Cough&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;Muscle aches&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;Chest pain&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;Headaches&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;Shortness of breath&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;Gastrointestinal symptoms, like nausea or diarrhea&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The Iowa HHS, Marshall County Public Health Department, and CDC continue their investigation into the disease cluster. For more information on&lt;a href="https://hhs.iowa.gov/health-prevention/disease-information" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt; Legionnaires’ disease and the investigation visit the Iowa HHS website&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;



		&lt;div class="article-content-cta-group"&gt;
			&lt;div class="modal--suggest-correction article-content-cta-group__cta" data-component="modal"&gt;
				&lt;button data-modal-trigger class="suggest-correction-button"&gt;Suggest a Correction&lt;/button&gt;
				&lt;div class="modal__dialog"&gt;
					&lt;div class="modal__dialog-content"&gt;
						&lt;button class="modal__close-button" aria-label="Close Modal Content"&gt;
							&lt;span class="icon"&gt;
								&lt;svg aria-hidden="true" tabindex="-1" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 16.85 16.875"&gt;
									&lt;title&gt;Close Modal&lt;/title&gt;
									&lt;path fill="#fff" d="M9.65 8.454l6.88-7.063a.809.809 0 0 0 0-1.15.782.782 0 0 0-1.14 0L8.52 7.305 1.37.241a.782.782 0 0 0-1.14 0 .809.809 0 0 0 0 1.15l7.15 7.063-7.15 7.063a.809.809 0 0 0 0 1.15.824.824 0 0 0 .6.219.787.787 0 0 0 .59-.219l7.15-7.063 6.87 7.063a.824.824 0 0 0 .6.219.619.619 0 0 0 .54-.219.792.792 0 0 0 0-1.15z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;
								&lt;/svg&gt;
							&lt;/span&gt;
						&lt;/button&gt;
						&lt;h3 class="modal__dialog-title"&gt;Suggest a Correction&lt;/h3&gt;
						
					&lt;/div&gt;
				&lt;/div&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;

	
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>WHO13.com</author><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 00:59:38 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiqwFBVV95cUxOY1NDUEJ0b3Q1RF9EOU1pNHhPVlNBTGZkM3BJOVVfNVVNMDBxdW9KZUo4OHhDVFZXTG9oMEhJWDlVUEZrS2xERHhZN19pbDFzSVFxS29pSHpDdnVIYUVaZHZIY3E1WHpXYV9WQVF6cy13b1YyNTNNMWVsTUpBWklLYVpNUjYtcmJtTndHaWRqX0dhTFJTQTdhb3c1NVRJaTVRNWdMdjFJWUJOdGPSAbABQVVfeXFMTWNEV3BRT1dCRGFqeU1IbVFIUUZfWXgyYUg1Qll4aHY3M2hINHVzenROcFVTWndOUENEV0RyTVh0U01yT0V1N3NHVV9BRk1xZ21MbkhqdHQtM1JxWWFGSW5fVUc0S09BMXpxRlFxbzF1aEdmWmVjTEg5M0ROYkNlM1A5VTVHUnhoa21uTW1zUWZISVZMVW90NU5zSmRoMzNMWFVsa0lHR0N0RFljaFZLZ0k</guid></item><item><title>澳大利亚批准接种疫苗以保护考拉免受衣原体感染- NPR</title><link>https://www.npr.org/2025/09/14/nx-s1-5541358/australia-koala-chlamydia-vaccine</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="storytext" class="storytext storylocation linkLocation"&gt;
      &lt;div id="resg-s1-88699" class="bucketwrap image large"&gt;
            
&lt;div class="credit-caption"&gt;
    &lt;div class="caption-wrap"&gt;
        &lt;div class="caption" aria-label="Image caption"&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;
                A koala and joey climb a tree in bushland located near central Brisbane on Dec. 14, 2024.
                &lt;b class="credit" aria-label="Image credit"&gt;
                    
                    David Gray/AFP via Getty Images
                    
                &lt;/b&gt;
                &lt;b class="hide-caption"&gt;&lt;b&gt;hide caption&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;
            &lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;


            &lt;b class="toggle-caption"&gt;&lt;b&gt;toggle caption&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;

    &lt;span class="credit" aria-label="Image credit"&gt;
        
        David Gray/AFP via Getty Images
        
    &lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;A vaccine has been approved to help protect koalas against chlamydia, a measure researchers are hailing as a world-first in fighting the disease that is a leading cause of death for the beloved marsupials.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Researchers at the University of the Sunshine Coast (UniSC) in Australia said Wednesday it took more than 10 years to develop a single-dose vaccine that does not require a booster that it hopes will aid in "reducing the rapid, devastating spread of this disease."&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"Some individual colonies are edging closer to local extinction every day, particularly in South East Queensland and New South Wales, where infection rates within populations are often around 50 percent and in some cases can reach as high as 70 percent," Peter Timms, a microbiology professor at the university who led the research team, &lt;a href="https://www.usc.edu.au/about/unisc-news/news-archive/2025/september/world-first-unisc-s-koala-vaccine-approved-to-fight-deadly-disease" target="_blank"&gt;said in a statement&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;   
   
   

   &lt;p&gt;Chlamydia in koalas can cause blindness and lead them to starve to death because they cannot locate trees to climb for food, &lt;a href="https://koalaconservationaustralia.org.au/pages/disease" target="_blank"&gt;according to Koala Conservation Australia&lt;/a&gt;. It can also cause infertility and damage a koala's bladder to the point where the inner wall becomes inflamed and the marsupial passes blood, the organization said. &lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;The disease occurs in koalas multiple ways, including through mating, infected discharges and at birth. Baby koalas, known as joeys, can also catch chlamydia by eating pap, a substance produced by a mother that's similar to feces, if their mother is infected.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Antibiotics have been used to treat the disease but it is not always effective and does not prevent future infections, according to the university. Antibiotics can also lead to gastrointestinal side effects that could hinder koalas' ability to digest eucalyptus leaves, which are the animals' main food source. Depending on the severity of the chlamydia and if it has progressed too far, euthanasia may be an only option.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;That's why scientists are optimistic about the vaccine.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Sam Phillips, a senior researcher at the UniSC, said the vaccine has been tested on hundreds of wild koalas and koalas in captivity.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"It's based on Chlamydia pecorum's major outer membrane protein (MOMP), and offers three levels of protection – reducing infection, preventing progression to clinical disease and, in some cases, reversing existing symptoms," Phillips said in a statement.&lt;/p&gt;   
   &lt;p&gt;The study led by Phillips &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41541-024-00938-5" target="_blank"&gt;that published last year&lt;/a&gt; found that the vaccine reduced signs of chlamydia during a koala's breeding age and decreased death from the disease by 64%.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;The university said the vaccine has been approved for production and widespread use by the Australian Pesticides and Veterinary Medicines Authority (APVMA).&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;The agency told NPR it approved a permit authorizing use of the vaccine in koalas in June that runs through June 2027.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>NPR</author><pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 00:11:23 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihAFBVV95cUxQX3V6MWU5d0kyWEhZdFcyZmQ1eE9TSGh4MVNGYzdqYUN5Tm9EbG9HNS1yRFJVV3VCYV9KNm5SY1RtVnMtSFd2alJUck1pOVg3YkJHNGUwNDJ1NGhIME5Zc2U2aE5hdEhtQ2NRWkhkaDN6X2lURUZObldnUEY0eVVWaUUyTzg</guid></item><item><title>科学支持的5种可能秘密伤害记忆的日常习惯-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/5-everyday-habits-that-may-be-secretly-harming-memory-backed-by-science/photostory/123880467.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="COQxt" data-ua-type="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Memory is critical to everyday functioning and affects learning, decision-making, and problem-solving. While some of the most prevalent factors (daily activities) impact our memory and are easily recognizable, some less typical habits can also be responsible for diminished cognitive function. Scientific studies have identified a series of actions that can compromise the brain's ability to store information and recall.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Times of India</author><pubDate>Sun, 14 Sep 2025 23:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi7wFBVV95cUxON0VNRjNYLVJPQ09HM2FDV2pWTFpDMWlMcWdPTmNQWHlDdFJObHZjWW44cnBvcVByYXVzZEkyaXJUS1lFQ0VOcEo5QS03OHE0SDU2WlJ6NkdsUkRDa2JWdXZQZ2NrWmVCbmwtd1haQ21wRDVfR21WS05kaF92MnBpQVA4NXdLVVVtbHNHeEtIT2FHRjRPazA3NW52TnlJZ2o4ZmowbFIzR1JhMjJzRkRxLXhicEUtOWMtSUhraGFmVFlhMnQwdjZuT1BQaEw5MDY3UkMyeXNmZmN1QTZHLUNJS3RBNFczS3VCXzMwU3Zla9IB9wFBVV95cUxPSWs4dTYtUDNMV3VZZTFnOWdwMHVTT0cxUnVkZ0NPaXBXQUpmQno2NHAydWliX3F3TUF3TGh3cjVQRGNmbFVmbWxORzJpVU10OWM2eHExUmxHRnJjWmt3TU5zd3kyWlo0UUxDVDFHdHQtNjFlX2tiOEZIeGVUbE9XTVVOVFlsTGNTX1VRclkxbHp5RHdRNnd4Q2xKRV9NdEdNdXBEWDNtek14WjJJem9UUDk2RnJNUEpITndobDVlUUJtcHlrZVlNVGQ5TlRLeUJGWWE1MVRCZzUtWWp4REIyOFNNdS1pWmw5Nk9pYlNka0hxNUpLR0dJ</guid></item><item><title>4万年前，人类已经在深海捕捞金枪鱼和鲨鱼- Earth.com</title><link>https://www.earth.com/news/40000-years-ago-humans-were-already-fishing-for-tuna-and-sharks-in-deep-waters/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="page_content__AwOj6"&gt;&lt;p&gt;People living on islands in Southeast Asia were not just getting by 40,000 years ago. They were heading into deep water and coming back with big, fast fish.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Organic boats and ropes usually rot away, so direct proof is rare. What survives are tools, fish bones, and clues in microscopic wear on stone edges.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Riczar Fuentes of &lt;a href="https://www.ateneo.edu/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Ateneo de Manila University&lt;/a&gt; and his colleagues focus on what stone tools reveal about plant processing and boat work. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Their approach links tool wear and plant fibers to practical needs like rope, nets, and bindings for watercraft and in a recent publication, they argued that a web of indirect signs can confirm real maritime skill. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The identification of boat building materials through direct or indirect evidence is vital in understanding movements across and within island environments,” wrote Fuentes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The same stone tools carry tiny traces that point to fiber extraction. Those fibers become cordage, lines, and netting strong enough for boat seams and &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/one-third-of-shark-species-face-extinction-despite-fishing-bans/"&gt;fishing&lt;/a&gt; gear.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This kind of tracing work has a name. Researchers call it traceology, a method that reads microscopic wear to reconstruct how a tool was used.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-why-seafaring-this-early-matters"&gt;Why seafaring this early matters&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Crossing channels between islands takes planning, timing, and control. Drifting on rafts would not explain repeated arrivals in specific places over long spans of time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The region in question is Island Southeast Asia, a sprawl of land and sea that demanded reliable water travel. Within it sits Wallacea, the chain of islands between Asia and Australia that always required open-water crossings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Archaeologists now think people here were more than lucky passengers on currents. The tool evidence suggests deliberate building, organized labor, and coordination.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That kind of know-how changes how we picture daily life. It also explains how communities kept moving, trading, and adapting across thousands of years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-hooks-sharks-and-tuna-at-jerimalai"&gt;Hooks, sharks, and tuna at Jerimalai&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Here we report remains of a variety of pelagic and other fish species dating to 42,000 years before the present,” wrote Sue O’Connor from Australian National University, in a &lt;a href="https://openresearch-repository.anu.edu.au/bitstreams/395b3624-7aba-44e8-ae54-08a923e67615/download"&gt;report&lt;/a&gt; describing the fish record and early gear.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The same study documents the earliest known shell fishhooks at Jerimalai, a rock shelter on Timor-Leste’s coast dated between about 23,000 and 16,000 years ago. These are small, precise tools that speak to careful crafting and targeted fishing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The bone counts are not trivial. The team identified 38,687 fish bones from 2,843 individual fish. Crucially, the assemblage includes remains of pelagic species that live in deeper water beyond reefs. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-from-timor-to-the-philippines"&gt;From Timor to the Philippines&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Timor-Leste is only part of the picture. A broad record from the Philippines now shows long-term &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/ice-age-art-discovery-reveals-15800-year-old-fishing-secrets/"&gt;fishing&lt;/a&gt; that spans at least 30,000 years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S2352409X23003978"&gt;Work&lt;/a&gt; in Mindoro’s caves adds detail on how coastal people managed reefs and deeper zones. That study tracked which fish families show up, and when, across changing shorelines and habitats.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These finds tie into plant fibers and tool wear in the same region. The combined record points to people who planned, built, and fished with skill, not luck.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Patterns like these do not appear once and vanish. They persist, which suggests teaching, apprenticeship, and shared practice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-how-boats-came-together"&gt;How boats came together&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wood planks, sewn edges, and lashings would have relied on sturdy plant fibers. The tool traces match steps needed to strip, twist, and finish those fibers into ropes and lines.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Other &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41598-020-61839-w"&gt;research&lt;/a&gt; shows that making string is not a recent trick, citing evidence that short fibres fragment from Abri du Maras in France records twisted plant strands more than 40,000 years ago.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This does not mean people in Europe and Southeast Asia did the same thing in the same way. It shows that fiber technology was within the reach of human hands and minds wherever materials allowed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If people could twist string, they could weave nets, lash boat parts, and make lines. That opens the door to deep-water travel and targeted fishing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-rethinking-migration-across-islands"&gt;Rethinking migration across islands&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Obsidian moving between islands in southeastern Indonesia and Timor-Leste points to sustained contact. The &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S0305440316301613"&gt;pattern&lt;/a&gt; fits a late Pleistocene to early Holocene interaction zone rather than one-off drifts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stone does not sail itself, and it does not walk across channels. Its movement reflects planned trips, return journeys, and social ties.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Those ties likely included sharing routes and seasons. You do not reach a tuna run by guessing, you reach it by knowledge passed along.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As knowledge spreads, technology improves. Better ropes, better lines, and better boats raise the odds of a safe return.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-why-this-changes-the-story-we-tell"&gt;Why this changes the story we tell&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;For a long time, scholars looked for the earliest big changes in a few famous regions. These finds push us to broaden the map and timeline.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Here, technical skill is not just tool design, it is teamwork. People needed group effort to build, carry, launch, and maintain boats.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But not teamwork alone, it is also about logistics. Fibers must be harvested, processed, and stored, and repairs must be made fast when seawater and sun wear things down.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Taken together, the &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/ancient-fish-bones-reveal-clues-about-the-evolution-of-eating/"&gt;fish bones&lt;/a&gt;, the hooks, and the traces on stone tools point to a culture that understood the sea. The work looks careful, repeatable, and tied to seasons and migrations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-what-remains-to-figure-out"&gt;What remains to figure out&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Boats do not preserve well, so many details will stay hidden. Even so, the indirect signs add up and form a consistent picture.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Future experiments can test which plants, tools, and fiber twists hold up under load. Those trials can feed back into the archaeological read on use wear.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;More underwater and coastal work could reveal net weights, sinkers, or preserved cord in unusual conditions. Every new fragment can lock one more piece into place.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Across all of this, one message stands firm. People in Island Southeast Asia were organized and capable on the water far earlier than many assumed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study is published in &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S2352409X25000525?via%3Dihub" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Journal of Archaeological Science: Reports&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;—–&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Like what you read?&lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/subscribe/"&gt; Subscribe to our newsletter&lt;/a&gt; for engaging articles, exclusive content, and the latest updates. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Check us out on&lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/earthsnap/"&gt; EarthSnap&lt;/a&gt;, a free app brought to you by&lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/author/eralls/"&gt; Eric Ralls&lt;/a&gt; and Earth.com.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;—–&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Earth.com</author><pubDate>Sun, 14 Sep 2025 23:12:12 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiqgFBVV95cUxNQXc3YUU5VVpxSy1nck9id0ZMRmVNM1NoZzZQN0ppRkU5cDRjYlRLSDY1d1BXQ00tNExkU2lVVDlnSjFyYjZ0NDZzak9Ra3JyOFIxWFZEYzhXOWYxSHFYeTZZLVFJQ0FJSGt0SWN5NHZZVUZWdHdKSEJULXZXa0FCV3ZVVkhwbUV5dDN6Z1JTMk9LTDdmQzJmeDhMZkliVlNWd1ZmU2F3SUMtZw</guid></item><item><title>新的研究表明，癌症如何在激素的帮助下欺骗免疫系统- Earth.com</title><link>https://www.earth.com/news/cancer-tricks-the-immune-system-with-the-help-of-hormone-scg2/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="page_content__AwOj6"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cancer sometimes gets the &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/daylight-boosts-the-immune-systems-ability-to-fight-infections/"&gt;immune system&lt;/a&gt; to back off. A new study shows that a natural signal, a hormone, can tell certain white blood cells to slow down, which lets tumors grow.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This finding points to a fresh target for treatment. It also helps explain why powerful cancer drugs work well for some people but not for others.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-why-this-study-matters"&gt;Why this study matters&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The work was co-led by Cheng Cheng “Alec” Zhang, Ph.D., Professor of Physiology at &lt;a href="https://utswmed.org/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;UT Southwestern Medical Center&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Across common cancers like lung, kidney, and melanoma, only about 20 to 30 percent of patients benefit from these drugs called &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s12276-018-0130-1" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;immune checkpoint inhibitors&lt;/a&gt; – medicines that remove natural brakes on T-cells so those cells attack tumors more strongly. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They help many people but not all. That leaves a lot of patients needing new options. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many tumors build up cells from a group called &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41392-021-00670-9" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;myeloid cells&lt;/a&gt;, early responder white blood cells that usually help start immune defense. These cells can turn suppressive in cancer and hold back T-cells.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cancer also changes the immune system beyond the tumor site. That broader shift matters for whether treatments work, a 2021 review explains.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-study-focuses-on-scg2"&gt;Study focuses on SCG2&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The team focused on &lt;a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/gene/7857" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;secretogranin 2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;(SCG2) which acts like a hormone – a chemical messenger that cells release to send signals through the body. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They discovered that SCG2 latches onto &lt;a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/gene/11006" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;LILRB4&lt;/a&gt;, a receptor, which is a docking site on the surface of certain myeloid cells that catches a signal like a hormone.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When SCG2 binds LILRB4, it tells those cells to ease off their tumor fighting jobs. It also interferes with the call for backup from T-cells.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Inside these cells, the signal turns on &lt;a href="https://medlineplus.gov/genetics/gene/stat3/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;STAT3&lt;/a&gt;, a protein that switches many genes on or off. When STAT3 is active in myeloid cells, those cells tend to suppress other immune cells.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The result is a one two punch. The early responders stop helping, and the later responders do not get to the tumor in normal numbers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-how-the-tests-were-done"&gt;How the tests were done&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers first confirmed the SCG2 to LILRB4 match in dishes of cells. They showed that the binding turned down myeloid cell activity that would otherwise help fight tumors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They then used mice whose myeloid cells carried the human form of LILRB4. Tumors that produced SCG2 grew faster in those mice, while blocking LILRB4 slowed growth, and removing SCG2 also slowed growth.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The team also showed that the growth boost from SCG2 depended on T-cells. When T-cells were taken out of the picture, the advantage went away.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Myeloid cells are among the first group of immune cells recruited to tumors, but very quickly these tumor-fighting cells turn into tumor-supporting cells. Our study suggests that receptors on these myeloid cells get stimulated by this &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/oxytocin-cuddle-hormone-fosters-love-boosts-memory-and-may-cure-addiction/"&gt;hormone&lt;/a&gt; and end up suppressing the immune system,” said Zhang.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-what-it-could-mean-for-care"&gt;What it could mean for care&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Blocking LILRB4 could become a new way to help more patients respond to treatment. It makes sense to test LILRB4 blockers with existing checkpoint drugs in careful trials.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There is early support for targeting this receptor from other diseases. In multiple &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/walking-each-day-at-any-speed-lowers-the-risk-of-cancer/"&gt;myeloma&lt;/a&gt;, blocking LILRB4 slowed disease growth in lab and animal tests.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The pathway also leans on STAT3, which is a central control switch in these suppressive cells. A 2025 review notes that STAT3 helps these cells grow and shut down T-cells, so pairing a LILRB4 blocker with a STAT3 focused drug might be useful.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There is another angle too. Because SCG2 can quiet myeloid cells, carefully adding SCG2 might one day help calm certain inflammatory conditions that run too hot.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-questions-people-may-ask"&gt;Questions people may ask&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Can doctors measure SCG2 in blood or &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/computer-model-can-identify-tumor-fighting-immune-cells/"&gt;tumor&lt;/a&gt; tissue to guide care. That will require tests that are accurate and easy to run in clinics.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Will blocking LILRB4 cause infections or other issues since the receptor helps keep inflammation in check. Safety will need close monitoring in early trials.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Could tumors switch to a different signal if LILRB4 is blocked. Cancers often adapt, so combinations may be important.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;How would doctors choose who gets a LILRB4 blocker. Matching the drug to tumors that use the SCG2 to LILRB4 route will likely matter.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-where-research-goes-next"&gt;Where research goes next&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Build a reliable test for SCG2 levels and LILRB4 activity. Use it to pick patients who are most likely to benefit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Run trials that add LILRB4 blockers to checkpoint therapy. Track whether more patients respond and how long responses last.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Map this pathway in different &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/pfas-forever-chemicals-in-tap-water-linked-to-33-percent-increase-in-cancer-rates/"&gt;cancers&lt;/a&gt; and in human samples over time. Learn when the pathway turns on and how best to shut it off.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Study whether carefully giving SCG2 can help dial down harmful inflammation in certain diseases. Keep a close eye on side effects while doing so.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study is published in &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41590-025-02233-4" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Nature Immunology&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;—–&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Like what you read?&lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/subscribe/"&gt; Subscribe to our newsletter&lt;/a&gt; for engaging articles, exclusive content, and the latest updates. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Check us out on&lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/earthsnap/"&gt; EarthSnap&lt;/a&gt;, a free app brought to you by&lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/author/eralls/"&gt; Eric Ralls&lt;/a&gt; and Earth.com.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;—–&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Earth.com</author><pubDate>Sun, 14 Sep 2025 22:52:30 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikwFBVV95cUxPbTVhX3gxcEVVQ0ZSM3NpWGNjTzRLRDRXWERJM0NLTXdfMFZWam8zZVdKWG1uNTFHUnoxN1BITkJGWWQ0dnRzb3YzNFRPMTFjUFVmNzZLZGdSZllISnZScGZqeWJuMHptUmVpOHA3TjNqYVNtTVd0NG1sWTZnMThDTGw0elcyTms5Q2gwd1hsUDF4UlE</guid></item><item><title>三倍剂量的诺和诺德药物在试验中实现了19%的体重减轻-英国《金融时报》</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/581ef56d-8f25-4f04-8386-74d35de0d755</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="o-grid-row details-section o3-type-body-base css-pmzbjb"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;FT newspaper delivered Monday-Saturday, plus FT Digital Edition delivered to your device Monday-Saturday.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Financial Times</author><pubDate>Sun, 14 Sep 2025 22:30:09 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMicEFVX3lxTE05Q3BfeTR0MlRIclRta3pud3RFV29fSnhNQ3dlUEJ6X3lhU1ZrSUpPeXRLNzA1SXkyckxCTXNIUG12dzFtQl9JWEdiN1NSdWJ3Y0hleFAwdkRjc2t2eFpzaUhsWk1WN3pHWDJXNEhOaXo</guid></item><item><title>临床试验证实，较高剂量的semaglutide可以安全地增强肥胖成人的减肥效果- Medical Xpress</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-09-higher-doses-semaglutide-safely-weight.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="mt-4 article-main"&gt;
									    
&lt;div class="article-gallery lightGallery"&gt;
    &lt;div data-thumb="https://scx1.b-cdn.net/csz/news/tmb/2025/weight-loss.jpg" data-src="https://scx2.b-cdn.net/gfx/news/hires/2025/weight-loss.jpg" data-sub-html="Credit: Pixabay from Pexels"&gt;
        &lt;figure class="article-img"&gt;
            &lt;img src="https://scx1.b-cdn.net/csz/news/800a/2025/weight-loss.jpg" alt="weight loss" title="Credit: Pixabay from Pexels"&gt;
             &lt;figcaption class="text-darken text-low-up text-truncate-js text-truncate mt-3"&gt;
                Credit: Pixabay from Pexels
            &lt;/figcaption&gt;        &lt;/figure&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;A higher weekly dose of semaglutide (7.2 mg) can significantly improve weight loss and related health outcomes in adults living with obesity, including those with type 2 diabetes (T2D), according to the results of two large-scale, international phase 3 clinical trials.&lt;/p&gt;

                                        
                                                                                &lt;p class="w-100 my-4 d-print-none"&gt;
     
     
     &lt;ins class="adsbygoogle" data-ad-layout="in-article" data-ad-format="fluid" data-ad-client="ca-pub-0536483524803400" data-ad-slot="7587637799"&gt;&lt;/ins&gt;
     
&lt;/p&gt;  
                                         

                                                                                                                                    &lt;p&gt;The findings, published in &lt;i&gt;The Lancet Diabetes &amp;amp; Endocrinology&lt;/i&gt; journal, suggest that a higher dose of semaglutide offers a promising new option for people with obesity, including those with T2D, who have not achieved sufficient weight loss with existing treatments.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The STEP UP and STEP UP T2D &lt;a href="https://medicalxpress.com/tags/clinical+trials/" rel="tag" class="textTag"&gt;clinical trials&lt;/a&gt; are the first to investigate whether increasing the dose of semaglutide from the currently approved dose of 2.4 mg to 7.2 mg is safe and leads to additional weight reduction. Trial participants were randomized to receive either the higher 7.2 mg dose of semaglutide, the currently approved 2.4 mg dose, or placebo over 72 weeks. All participants—regardless of treatment group—received lifestyle interventions such as dietary counseling and increased physical activity recommendations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In adults without diabetes, a 7.2 mg dose of semaglutide led to an average weight loss of nearly 19%, surpassing the 16% loss seen with 2.4 mg and 4% with placebo. Nearly half of the participants on the higher dose lost 20% or more of their &lt;a href="https://medicalxpress.com/tags/body+weight/" rel="tag" class="textTag"&gt;body weight&lt;/a&gt;, with about one-third losing at least 25%. Participants also experienced improvements in &lt;a href="https://medicalxpress.com/tags/waist+circumference/" rel="tag" class="textTag"&gt;waist circumference&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://medicalxpress.com/tags/blood+pressure/" rel="tag" class="textTag"&gt;blood pressure&lt;/a&gt;, blood sugar, and &lt;a href="https://medicalxpress.com/tags/cholesterol+levels/" rel="tag" class="textTag"&gt;cholesterol levels&lt;/a&gt;, all key factors in reducing obesity-related health risks.&lt;/p&gt;

                                                                                                        
    &lt;p class="w-100 mb-4 ads"&gt;
          
        
        &lt;ins class="adsbygoogle" data-ad-layout="in-article" data-ad-format="fluid" data-ad-client="ca-pub-0536483524803400" data-ad-slot="7099578867"&gt;&lt;/ins&gt;
        
    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                                                                                                                                                                &lt;p&gt;Similarly, in adults with obesity and T2D, the 7.2 mg dose resulted in an average 13% weight loss compared to 10% with 2.4 mg and 3.9% with placebo, along with significant reductions in &lt;a href="https://medicalxpress.com/tags/blood+sugar/" rel="tag" class="textTag"&gt;blood sugar&lt;/a&gt; levels and waist size.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Both trials reported that the higher dose of semaglutide was safe and generally well tolerated. Gastrointestinal side effects like nausea and diarrhea, and some sensory symptoms like tingling, were the most common. However, most side effects were manageable, resolved over time, and did not lead to participants dropping out of the trial. No increase in serious adverse events or severe hypoglycemia was observed with the higher dose.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By delivering greater weight reduction and metabolic benefits while maintaining a favorable safety profile, the authors say this higher dose could help more people reach their health goals and reduce the burden of obesity-related complications worldwide. However, they highlight that further research is needed to fully understand the long-term benefits and risks.&lt;/p&gt;

                                                                                                                                    
                                                                                
                                        											&lt;div class="article-main__more p-4"&gt;
												                                                    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;More information:&lt;/strong&gt;
                                                    Daily steps and health outcomes in adults: a systematic review and dose-response meta-analysis, &lt;i&gt;The Lancet Diabetes &amp;amp; Endocrinology&lt;/i&gt; (2025). &lt;a data-doi="1" href="https://dx.doi.org/10.1016/S2213-8587(25)00226-8" target="_blank"&gt;DOI: 10.1016/S2213-8587(25)00226-8&lt;/a&gt;
																								
																								&lt;/p&gt;
																							&lt;/div&gt;
                                        											
																					
                                                                                                                        
                                        
                                        &lt;div class="d-none d-print-block"&gt;
                                            &lt;p class="mb-4"&gt;
                                                 &lt;strong&gt;Citation&lt;/strong&gt;:
                                                 Higher doses of semaglutide can safely enhance weight loss for adults living with obesity, clinical trials confirm (2025, September 14)
                                                 retrieved 15 September 2025
                                                 from https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-09-higher-doses-semaglutide-safely-weight.html
                                            &lt;/p&gt;
                                            &lt;p class="border text-muted p-3"&gt;
                                            This document is subject to copyright. Apart from any fair dealing for the purpose of private study or research, no
                                            part may be reproduced without the written permission. The content is provided for information purposes only.
                                            &lt;/p&gt;
                                        &lt;/div&gt;
                                        
									&lt;/div&gt;
								&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Medical Xpress</author><pubDate>Sun, 14 Sep 2025 22:30:01 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiigFBVV95cUxOdjlVbHZLVHlaLXZ6LUNnWU1oZFduZmdsLUJueURSenBtMzlYX2l4d09yOGlvVVpzYmlNLXQzcDJoeFlVVjRYdDQta212Nmw3eEEwS0FSN1BjdGZIMzVVQk5YVDBicGhvdV9PSkVQS2dHUjNfWlZtbEpyd2htQ1A2OWJyOFg4cDd4S1E</guid></item><item><title>大麻使用与患2型糖尿病的风险增加两倍，研究发现超过400万成年人- Medical Xpress</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-09-cannabis-quadrupled-diabetes-million-adults.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="mt-4 article-main"&gt;
									    
&lt;div class="article-gallery lightGallery"&gt;
    &lt;div data-thumb="https://scx1.b-cdn.net/csz/news/tmb/2025/cannabis-use.jpg" data-src="https://scx2.b-cdn.net/gfx/news/hires/2025/cannabis-use.jpg" data-sub-html="Credit: Kampus Production from Pexels"&gt;
        &lt;figure class="article-img"&gt;
            &lt;img src="https://scx1.b-cdn.net/csz/news/800a/2025/cannabis-use.jpg" alt="cannabis use" title="Credit: Kampus Production from Pexels"&gt;
             &lt;figcaption class="text-darken text-low-up text-truncate-js text-truncate mt-3"&gt;
                Credit: Kampus Production from Pexels
            &lt;/figcaption&gt;        &lt;/figure&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cannabis use is linked to an almost quadrupling in the risk of developing diabetes, according to an analysis of real-world data from over 4 million adults, being presented at the Annual Meeting of the European Association for the Study of Diabetes (&lt;a href="https://www.easd.org/annual-meeting/easd-2025/" target="_blank"&gt;EASD&lt;/a&gt;) held in Vienna, Austria (15–19 Sept).&lt;/p&gt;

                                        
                                                                                &lt;p class="w-100 my-4 d-print-none"&gt;
     
     
     &lt;ins class="adsbygoogle" data-ad-layout="in-article" data-ad-format="fluid" data-ad-client="ca-pub-0536483524803400" data-ad-slot="7587637799"&gt;&lt;/ins&gt;
     
&lt;/p&gt;  
                                         

                                                                                                                                    &lt;p&gt;Cannabis use is increasing globally with an estimated 219 million users (4.3% of the global adult population) in 2021, but its long-term metabolic effects remain unknown. While some studies have suggested potential anti-inflammatory or weight management properties, others have raised concerns regarding glucose metabolism and &lt;a href="https://medicalxpress.com/tags/insulin+resistance/" rel="tag" class="textTag"&gt;insulin resistance&lt;/a&gt;, and the magnitude of the risk of developing diabetes hasn't been clear.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To strengthen the evidence base, Dr. Ibrahim Kamel from the Boston Medical Center, Massachusetts, U.S. and colleagues analyzed &lt;a href="https://medicalxpress.com/tags/electronic+health+records/" rel="tag" class="textTag"&gt;electronic health records&lt;/a&gt; from 54 health care organizations (TriNetX Research Network, with centers from across U.S. and Europe) to identify 96,795 outpatients (aged between 18 and 50 years, 52.5% female) with cannabis-related diagnoses (ranging from occasional use to dependence, including cases of intoxication and withdrawal) between 2010 and 2018.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They were matched with 4,160,998 healthy individuals (with no record of substance use or major chronic conditions) based on age, sex, and underlying illnesses at the start of the study, and followed for five years.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After controlling HDL and LDL cholesterol, uncontrolled high blood pressure, atherosclerotic cardiovascular disease, cocaine use, alcohol use and several other lifestyle risk factors, the researchers found that new cases of diabetes were significantly higher in the cannabis group (1,937; 2.2%) compared to the healthy group (518; 0.6%), with statistical analysis showing cannabis users at nearly four times the risk of developing diabetes compared to non-users.&lt;/p&gt;

                                                                                                        
    &lt;p class="w-100 mb-4 ads"&gt;
          
        
        &lt;ins class="adsbygoogle" data-ad-layout="in-article" data-ad-format="fluid" data-ad-client="ca-pub-0536483524803400" data-ad-slot="7099578867"&gt;&lt;/ins&gt;
        
    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                                                                                                                                                                &lt;p&gt;While the authors note that more research is needed to fully explain the association between cannabis and diabetes, it may come down to insulin resistance and unhealthy dietary behaviors. Nevertheless, the study's results have immediate implications for metabolic monitoring practices and public health messaging.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"As cannabis becomes more widely available and socially accepted and legalized in various jurisdictions, it is essential to understand its potential health risks," said lead author Dr. Kamel.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"These new sights from reliable real-world evidence highlight the importance of integrating diabetes risk awareness into substance use disorder treatment and counseling, as well as the need for health care professionals to routinely talk to patients about &lt;a href="https://medicalxpress.com/tags/cannabis+use/" rel="tag" class="textTag"&gt;cannabis use&lt;/a&gt; so that they can understand their overall diabetes risk and potential need for metabolic monitoring."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The authors note that more research is needed on the long-term endocrine effects of cannabis use and whether diabetes risks are limited to inhaled products or other forms of cannabis such as edibles.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Despite the important findings, this is a retrospective study and cannot prove that cannabis use causes &lt;a href="https://medicalxpress.com/tags/diabetes/" rel="tag" class="textTag"&gt;diabetes&lt;/a&gt;, and the authors cannot rule out the possibility that other unmeasured factors may have influenced the results despite efforts to reduce confounding bias via propensity score matching. This study has limitations due to a lack of detailed cannabis consumption data and potential misclassification.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The authors acknowledge that the inherent limitations of real-world data often result from inconsistent patient reporting in electronic medical records.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They also note that there is a risk of bias because of imprecise measures of cannabis exposure and the reliance on participants to accurately report any cannabis use, even when they lived in places where the drug is illegal.&lt;/p&gt;

                                                                                                                                    
                                                                                
                                        											
																					&lt;p class="d-inline-block text-medium my-4"&gt;
												Provided by
																									European Association for the Study of Diabetes
												 
											&lt;/p&gt;
                                                                                                                        
                                        
                                        &lt;div class="d-none d-print-block"&gt;
                                            &lt;p class="mb-4"&gt;
                                                 &lt;strong&gt;Citation&lt;/strong&gt;:
                                                 Cannabis use associated with quadrupled risk of developing type 2 diabetes, finds study of over 4 million adults (2025, September 14)
                                                 retrieved 14 September 2025
                                                 from https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-09-cannabis-quadrupled-diabetes-million-adults.html
                                            &lt;/p&gt;
                                            &lt;p class="border text-muted p-3"&gt;
                                            This document is subject to copyright. Apart from any fair dealing for the purpose of private study or research, no
                                            part may be reproduced without the written permission. The content is provided for information purposes only.
                                            &lt;/p&gt;
                                        &lt;/div&gt;
                                        
									&lt;/div&gt;
								&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Medical Xpress</author><pubDate>Sun, 14 Sep 2025 22:10:04 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikAFBVV95cUxPdTlhdGhmRXptZWxXTEVvQzFFZzdlOW82bmg0TF92T0djQzg4eHA4VFo5akdsbVhEVk53WkR0c21QRE9kNkJLaWlURXhGU0l5Zkg5bDdWUHZ5cGVlWkV0MTZSdUthN2swWFM4NzRwVTMyR1FTZlNXOExZVEdUbTZGUThWdWJ3b2FzbUpZSDluRno</guid></item><item><title>是的，你可以太早接种流感疫苗-现在是接种的最佳时机-预防</title><link>https://www.prevention.com/health/a66013230/best-time-for-flu-shot/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div data-journey-body="standard-article" class="article-body-content article-body standard-body-content css-n3hm4j et2g3wt6"&gt;&lt;ul data-node-id="0" class="css-kw9lqy emevuu60"&gt;&lt;li data-node-id="0.0"&gt;&lt;em data-node-id="0.0.0"&gt;Many pharmacies are already encouraging people to get their annual flu shot.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-node-id="0.1"&gt;&lt;em data-node-id="0.1.0"&gt;Doctors say that timing is important with your flu shot. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-node-id="0.2"&gt;&lt;em data-node-id="0.2.0"&gt;It’s best to aim to get your shot in a specific window of time this fall.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;hr data-node-id="1" class="css-18pb4rg emevuu60"&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="2" class="css-i9p093 emevuu60"&gt;The summer season has wrapped up for the year, causing plenty of people to look ahead to fall. With that, it’s understandable to wonder about when to get your flu shot—especially since big-name pharmacy chains like CVS and Walgreens are already posting signs about getting the annual vaccine. But is it too early for a flu shot? &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="3" class="css-i9p093 emevuu60"&gt;Infectious disease doctors say it’s possible to get your flu shot &lt;em data-node-id="3.1"&gt;too early&lt;/em&gt;, and making this move could raise your risk of being vulnerable to the flu before influenza season is over. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="4" class="css-i9p093 emevuu60"&gt;During last year’s flu season, there were at least 35 million illnesses, 400,000 hospitalizations, and 25,000 deaths from the flu, according to estimates from the &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/flu/weekly/index.htm" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.cdc.gov/flu/weekly/index.htm" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="Centers for Disease Control and Prevention" data-node-id="4.1" class="body-link css-inlxvj emevuu60"&gt;Centers for Disease Control and Prevention&lt;/a&gt; (CDC). While the flu shot may not prevent you from getting sick, public health officials say that it can lower the odds you’ll get seriously ill with the virus.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="6" class="body-tip css-1707dxl emevuu60"&gt;&lt;strong data-node-id="6.0"&gt;Meet the experts&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;a href="https://www.vumc.org/health-policy/person/william-schaffner-md" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.vumc.org/health-policy/person/william-schaffner-md" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="William Schaffner, M.D.," data-node-id="6.2" class="body-link css-inlxvj emevuu60"&gt;William Schaffner, M.D.,&lt;/a&gt; an infectious disease specialist and professor at the Vanderbilt University School of Medicine; infectious disease expert &lt;a href="https://publichealth.jhu.edu/faculty/3528/amesh-adalja" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://publichealth.jhu.edu/faculty/3528/amesh-adalja" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="Amesh A. Adalja, M.D., " data-node-id="6.4" class="body-link css-inlxvj emevuu60"&gt;Amesh A. Adalja, M.D., &lt;/a&gt;senior scholar at the Johns Hopkins Center for Health Security; &lt;a href="https://nursing.buffalo.edu/additional-info/faculty-and-staff/faculty_directory.host.html/content/shared/nursing/faculty-and-staff-directory/faculty/full-time-faculty-profiles/haas-melinda.detail.html" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://nursing.buffalo.edu/additional-info/faculty-and-staff/faculty_directory.host.html/content/shared/nursing/faculty-and-staff-directory/faculty/full-time-faculty-profiles/haas-melinda.detail.html" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="Melinda Haas, D.N.P" data-node-id="6.6" class="body-link css-inlxvj emevuu60"&gt;Melinda Haas, D.N.P&lt;/a&gt;., clinical assistant professor at the University at Buffalo School of Nursing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="when-does-flu-season-start-and-end" data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="7" class="body-text css-i9p093 emevuu60"&gt;So, when it too early for the flu shot and what is the sweet spot to aim for? Here’s what medical providers recommend.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="when-does-flu-season-start-and-end" data-node-id="8" class="body-h2 css-14d214d emevuu60"&gt;&lt;strong data-node-id="8.0"&gt;When does flu season start and end?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="9" class="css-i9p093 emevuu60"&gt;There is no official start and end date for the flu, but it tends to follow a pattern in the U.S. Flu season usually starts to ramp up in October, per the &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/flu/about/season/index.html" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.cdc.gov/flu/about/season/index.html" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="CDC" data-node-id="9.1" class="body-link css-inlxvj emevuu60"&gt;CDC&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="10" class="css-i9p093 emevuu60"&gt;Flu season tends to peak in December and February, and fades by the spring, according to the CDC. However, some seasons are longer than others, and there can be higher levels of the flu circulating as late as May. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="is-it-too-early-for-a-flu-shot" data-node-id="11" class="body-h2 css-14d214d emevuu60"&gt;&lt;strong data-node-id="11.0"&gt;Is it too early for a flu shot?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="12" class="css-i9p093 emevuu60"&gt;Doctors generally agree that right now is too early for a flu shot. “The concern is that the protection will wane,” says &lt;a href="https://www.vumc.org/health-policy/person/william-schaffner-md" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.vumc.org/health-policy/person/william-schaffner-md" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="William Schaffner, M.D.," data-node-id="12.1" class="body-link css-inlxvj emevuu60"&gt;William Schaffner, M.D.,&lt;/a&gt; an infectious disease specialist and professor at the Vanderbilt University School of Medicine. “If you can wait a bit, that’s better.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="13" class="css-i9p093 emevuu60"&gt;Infectious disease expert &lt;a href="https://publichealth.jhu.edu/faculty/3528/amesh-adalja" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://publichealth.jhu.edu/faculty/3528/amesh-adalja" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="Amesh A. Adalja, M.D., " data-node-id="13.1" class="body-link css-inlxvj emevuu60"&gt;Amesh A. Adalja, M.D., &lt;/a&gt;senior scholar at the Johns Hopkins Center for Health Security, agrees. “The influenza season can last into mid-spring,” he points out. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="14" class="css-i9p093 emevuu60"&gt;The only people who may benefit from getting vaccinated now are children under the age of 8 who have never had a flu shot, Dr. Schaffner says. “They will need two doses, spaced apart, so you can get it now and then later,” he explains. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="what-are-my-flu-vaccine-options" data-node-id="15" class="body-h2 css-14d214d emevuu60"&gt;&lt;strong data-node-id="15.0"&gt;What are my flu vaccine options?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="16" class="css-i9p093 emevuu60"&gt;You have a few choices when it comes to getting vaccinated against the flu. Most Americans under the age of 65 who get the flu shot will get a trivalent vaccine, which targets three strains of the flu, per the &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/flu/prevent/keyfacts.htm" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.cdc.gov/flu/prevent/keyfacts.htm" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="CDC" data-node-id="16.1" class="body-link css-inlxvj emevuu60"&gt;CDC&lt;/a&gt;. However, it’s recommended that adults 65 and up get a quadrivalent flu vaccine, which targets four strains of the flu. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="17" class="css-i9p093 emevuu60"&gt;There are variations within those types of vaccines, including flu shots that are egg-free, if you prefer one of those. You also have the option of getting a nasal flu vaccine called FluMist, which is sprayed into your nose, bypassing the needle altogether. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="when-is-the-best-time-to-get-a-flu-shot" data-node-id="18" class="body-h2 css-14d214d emevuu60"&gt;&lt;strong data-node-id="18.0"&gt;When is the best time to get a flu shot?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="19" class="css-i9p093 emevuu60"&gt;It’s hard to figure out an exact time to get your shot. However, the CDC usually &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/flu/spotlights/2022-2023/flu-vaccination-recommendations-adopted.htm" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.cdc.gov/flu/spotlights/2022-2023/flu-vaccination-recommendations-adopted.htm" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="recommends" data-node-id="19.1" class="body-link css-inlxvj emevuu60"&gt;recommends&lt;/a&gt; getting your shot by Halloween, aka the end of October. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="20" class="css-i9p093 emevuu60"&gt;“October is when I recommend getting the vaccine as there is more actual influenza activity then—there is very little now,” Dr. Adalja says. “The vaccine will last further into the season if administered in October.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="21" class="css-i9p093 emevuu60"&gt;Also worth considering: It takes about two weeks after you’re vaccinated for your body to develop antibodies against the flu, per the &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/flu/prevent/keyfacts.htm" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.cdc.gov/flu/prevent/keyfacts.htm" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="CDC" data-node-id="21.1" class="body-link css-inlxvj emevuu60"&gt;CDC&lt;/a&gt;. So, if you have a big indoor event coming up sometime in late October or November, you may want to plan to get your flu vaccine a few weeks ahead of that, just to be safe. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="22" class="css-i9p093 emevuu60"&gt;But if now is the only time you can get vaccinated, Dr. Adalja says it’s better than nothing. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="how-long-does-flu-shot-protection-last" data-node-id="23" class="body-h2 css-14d214d emevuu60"&gt;&lt;strong data-node-id="23.0"&gt;How long does flu shot protection last?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="24" class="css-i9p093 emevuu60"&gt;It’s hard to put an exact number on how long protection from your flu shot will last. Everyone has different factors that influence this, including your own immune system, Dr. Schaffner says. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="25" class="css-i9p093 emevuu60"&gt;But there is a general range you can expect. “The flu vaccine typically provides protection for about six to eight months,” says &lt;a href="https://nursing.buffalo.edu/additional-info/faculty-and-staff/faculty_directory.host.html/content/shared/nursing/faculty-and-staff-directory/faculty/full-time-faculty-profiles/haas-melinda.detail.html" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://nursing.buffalo.edu/additional-info/faculty-and-staff/faculty_directory.host.html/content/shared/nursing/faculty-and-staff-directory/faculty/full-time-faculty-profiles/haas-melinda.detail.html" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="Melinda Haas, D.N.P" data-node-id="25.1" class="body-link css-inlxvj emevuu60"&gt;Melinda Haas, D.N.P&lt;/a&gt;., clinical assistant professor at the University at Buffalo School of Nursing. “However, it’s important to note that this can vary depending on individual factors and the specific strains of the flu virus in a given season.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="26" class="css-i9p093 emevuu60"&gt;Overall, doctors stress the importance of getting your flu vaccine. “Flu vaccination is best thought of as a way of increasing your resilience to respiratory virus season,” Dr. Adalja says. “It is an important tool to help you avoid the disruptive and serious consequences of influenza infection.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-ad-exclude="true" id="journey-inline" class="css-ciejky e1ye6jr30"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Prevention</author><pubDate>Sun, 14 Sep 2025 20:15:54 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMidkFVX3lxTE5qOGc2SmQ5YXE4WTZFT2h2ZFpqbFpSTGRRTnlkYnhXUVBiRy0yQ2RQTkowdmx3RDJlM0pocWhuZ2tyWjZpUHQxTEZmUmFRNkl0ZWhVbE15dG1EbURkUlVIbGo2bllsRm5LNDhIZkZZV1R2NTNOOFE</guid></item><item><title>埃博拉疫苗接种在刚果南部开始- NBC新闻</title><link>https://www.nbcnews.com/world/africa/ebola-vaccination-begins-southern-congo-rcna231173</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body__content"&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-43e172" class="body-graf"&gt;LAGOS, Nigeria — Vaccination for those exposed to the Ebola virus and front-line health workers has begun in southern Kasai province, the World Health Organization said Sunday.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-b4a394" class="body-graf"&gt;An outbreak of the highly contagious disease &lt;a href="https://apnews.com/article/congo-ebola-outbreak-a42c28f0c8c1a4d8cecca5072b392593"&gt;was announced&lt;/a&gt; earlier this month in the locality of Bulape, in Kasai, and has left at least 16 dead and 68 suspected cases, according to last week’s briefing by the Africa Centers for Disease Control and Prevention.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="taboolaReadMoreBelow"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-62294c" class="body-graf"&gt;Only an initial 400 doses of the Ervebo vaccine have been dispatched, with the rest to be delivered later, the WHO said. The operation has been hampered by &lt;a href="https://apnews.com/article/congo-ebola-vaccine-kasai-outbreak-who-0e0a872716a46bee185237478cb597ff"&gt;limited access and scarce funds.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="recommended-intersection-ref" data-activity-map="recommended-article-body-recommended" data-testid="recommended-wrapper"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="recommended-intersection-ref" data-activity-map="recommended-article-body-recommended" data-testid="recommended-wrapper"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-f8b2bc" class="body-graf"&gt;The vaccination is expected to pick up later as the International Coordinating Group on Vaccine Provision approved roughly 45,000 additional vaccines, the WHO said, adding to an initial stockpile of 2,000 doses was already in the country.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-83902f" class="endmark body-graf"&gt;The latest Ebola outbreak is Congo’s 16th since 1976, and it is caused by the Zaire species, named after the country’s former name. It adds another layer of worry for the central African country that is battling a multi-pronged conflict with rebel groups, especially in the eastern region of the country, where violence has decimated the health system.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>NBC News</author><pubDate>Sun, 14 Sep 2025 19:45:13 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikAFBVV95cUxPQmFkRm5nbFYtc3czRm9UVWd4TldHWXNsalkwMWpnMGlEOGYyNzVZOUxWdVQ3Nk82Q1NETlkwUktSNjZJSGVyVWVzVVlrR0loOXV6eTFoZUtTa1NWdnVUcFZWa0g0R2pUZFlnTTQ3NHh4MVRfSG9JbV9XTUx0ejlUelozaWJnTVBQUEZjQ3ZsWDDSAVZBVV95cUxPX3N5OWZ4eTUyTlJPakdueGZwWmxTX2dIeEVKU1lFNEZDQl9OVEtZMURHcmMtYVFSbGtLMVlqbUdLUURlRnp0YzAwejktQXJ2bVpXclg1UQ</guid></item><item><title>埃博拉疫苗接种在最近疫情爆发期间在刚果南部开始- PBS</title><link>https://www.pbs.org/newshour/world/ebola-vaccination-begins-in-southern-congo-amid-latest-outbreak</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="body-text"&gt;
                    &lt;p&gt;LAGOS, Nigeria (AP) — Vaccination for those exposed to the Ebola virus and front-line health workers has begun in southern Kasai province, the World Health Organization said Sunday.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;An outbreak of the highly contagious disease was announced earlier this month in the locality of Bulape, in Kasai, and has left at least 16 dead and 68 suspected cases, according to last week’s briefing by the Africa Centers for Disease Control and Prevention.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.pbs.org/newshour/world/congo-announces-new-ebola-outbreak-after-case-confirmed-in-southern-province"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;READ MORE:&lt;/strong&gt; Congo announces new Ebola outbreak after case confirmed in southern province&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Only an initial 400 doses of the Ervebo vaccine have been dispatched, with the rest to be delivered later, the WHO said. The operation has been hampered by limited access and scarce funds.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The vaccination is expected to pick up later as the International Coordinating Group on Vaccine Provision approved roughly 45,000 additional vaccines, the WHO said, adding to an initial stockpile of 2,000 doses was already in the country.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The latest Ebola outbreak is Congo’s 16th since 1976, and it is caused by the Zaire species, named after the country’s former name. It adds another layer of worry for the central African country that is battling a multi-pronged conflict with rebel groups, especially in the eastern region of the country, where violence has decimated the health system.&lt;/p&gt;

                                            &lt;div class="inline-invite inline-invite-type__funding inline-invite-style__default"&gt;
        
                    &lt;div class="inline-invite-funding__box"&gt;
                &lt;figure class="invite__logo"&gt;
                    &lt;svg class="svg"&gt;&lt;use xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xlink:href="#pbs-newshour-horiz-refresh"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;
                &lt;/figure&gt;
                &lt;p class="invite_heading"&gt;
                    We're not going anywhere.
                &lt;/p&gt;
                &lt;p class="invite_body"&gt;
                    Stand up for truly independent, trusted news that you can count on!
                &lt;/p&gt;
                &lt;a href="https://give.newshour.org/page/85597/donate/1?ea.tracking.id=nh_july_2025_rescission_article&amp;amp;supporter.appealCode=N2507QW07000AA" class="donation-link ga-click-funding ga-click-ender-funding"&gt;
                    &lt;button class="donate-button"&gt;Donate now&lt;/button&gt;
                    &lt;svg viewbox="0 0 16 16" fill="#000000" class="bi bi-arrow-right-short" version="1.1" id="svg1" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" xmlns:svg="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"&gt;
                    &lt;defs id="defs1"&gt;&lt;/defs&gt;
                    &lt;path fill-rule="evenodd" d="M4 8a.5.5 0 0 1 .5-.5h5.793L8.146 5.354a.5.5 0 1 1 .708-.708l3 3a.5.5 0 0 1 0 .708l-3 3a.5.5 0 0 1-.708-.708L10.293 8.5H4.5A.5.5 0 0 1 4 8z" id="path1"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;
                    &lt;/svg&gt;
                &lt;/a&gt;
            &lt;/div&gt;
            &lt;/div&gt;


                                    &lt;/div&gt;
            &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>PBS</author><pubDate>Sun, 14 Sep 2025 19:42:49 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMinwFBVV95cUxPNXJsM3Z2NVBRSk94eDd4R2Z5eW5UdExBTHlFb2Vnbi0tbVJFODdub3lHQlVtNkRaTHNXcmt4am9QSUlpUnVQOHBkb1M3MFJEZkRhbDRxYXl0MHgxVHBieHdrMjUzeTBTNER1NUxJbE9oNThpYmxGaFpqVnRpRkxtRzdEREVCSmJJYXpWZjhHTnppbTdwTmc5MUVsRVhFN2_SAaQBQVVfeXFMTWdBbEF0X1NzSzdFQ1ZzMDFPMm4xLXRpM0p6MG5DazF0S25CRGZoczZrdDZjZGdwNXgtNFVKR1pxdko2b0ZKd1pEaUFRajJ1UlVUN2ZNZmZPV2FEYUV2eWdjcElOR3FGNzg1dnhTaDNBLW5hTFJxNjROZjNMa2h3SENVQnF2QVVSM1lsYzY0aXY2RGdpaFFUTkJ5WkNyRnFwQ29lNGU</guid></item><item><title>您晚年吃饭的时间可能预示着过早死亡- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/the-time-of-day-you-eat-in-later-life-could-foreshadow-an-early-death</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;A new longitudinal study by an international team of researchers has found a link between eating breakfast later in the day and a greater chance of an early death among elderly people, raising questions about the relationship between mealtimes and illness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It's not just the food we eat that affects our body's health and well-being; the time we eat our meals is also known to &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1161/JAHA.124.039373"&gt;affect our body's functioning&lt;/a&gt;. Yet our body's condition can also determine when we may be craving a bite.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Data from 2,945 adults living in Newcastle and Manchester, UK, were collected between 1983 and 2017. The participants were aged between 42 and 94 when they signed up, and information was collected through optional questionnaires on their health, lifestyle, and &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/eating-eggs-can-actually-lower-bad-cholesterol-new-study-says"&gt;eating habits&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/switching-off-one-crucial-protein-appears-to-reverse-brain-aging-in-mice"&gt;Switching Off One Crucial Protein Appears to Reverse Brain Aging in Mice&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The statistics revealed the volunteers tended to eat breakfast and dinner later in the day as they aged, extending their daily eating over a smaller window of time, too. These later eating times were linked to poorer physical and &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/these-2-key-lifestyle-changes-can-treat-mild-depression-as-well-as-therapy"&gt;mental health&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When it came to all-cause mortality – the likelihood of dying for any reason – the researchers found a significant link between eating breakfast later and a higher mortality risk. For each hour later that &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/kids-who-eat-breakfast-every-day-share-something-in-common"&gt;breakfast was taken&lt;/a&gt;, the chance of dying during the study period went up 8-11 percent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Our research suggests that changes in when older adults eat, especially the timing of breakfast, could serve as an easy-to-monitor marker of their overall health status," &lt;a href="https://www.massgeneralbrigham.org/en/about/newsroom/press-releases/meal-timing-in-older-adults-health-and-longevity"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; nutrition scientist Hassan Dashti, from Harvard Medical School.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_173208" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-173208" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/09/EatingChart.jpg" alt="Eating chart" class="wp-image-173208 size-full" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/09/EatingChart.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/09/EatingChart-582x415.jpg 582w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/09/EatingChart-600x428.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-173208" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;The researchers tracked eating times as people got older. (Dashti et al., &lt;em&gt;Commun. Med.&lt;/em&gt;, 2025)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers aren't saying that eating breakfast later is going to cause you to die at an earlier age – or that shifting your breakfast time forward a few hours will guarantee you get &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/lifespan-is-shaped-more-by-your-choices-than-your-genes-study-finds"&gt;an extra few years&lt;/a&gt; added on at the end of your life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In fact, they suggest the relationship is likely to be driven in the other direction. &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/can-vitamin-d-slow-aging-a-new-study-says-yes-but-theres-a-catch"&gt;As we get older&lt;/a&gt; and a greater number of health problems mount up, and increase in severity, that means an earlier death is more likely, and also causes later breakfast times.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Poorer health leading to a &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/just-one-night-of-poor-sleep-can-change-how-your-brain-sees-food"&gt;lack of sleep&lt;/a&gt; is one way that might play out, with trouble sleeping leading to difficulty getting up. Deteriorating physical health also means most tasks – including making breakfast – take longer too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Up until now, we had a limited insight into how the timing of meals evolves later in life and how this shift relates to overall health and longevity," &lt;a href="https://www.massgeneralbrigham.org/en/about/newsroom/press-releases/meal-timing-in-older-adults-health-and-longevity"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; Dashti.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Our findings help fill that gap by showing that later meal timing, especially delayed breakfast, is tied to both health challenges and increased mortality risk in older adults."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One way the study findings might be useful is in identifying older people who are more at risk in terms of their health. It also gives us a greater understanding of how &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/study-reveals-intermittent-fasting-has-2-key-benefits-for-people-with-obesity"&gt;changes in eating habits&lt;/a&gt; might affect younger people and older people differently.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The world's population &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/heat-waves-can-accelerate-aging-as-much-as-smoking-or-drinking-study-shows"&gt;is aging overall&lt;/a&gt; – meaning a larger proportion of the total number of people on the planet are older – which makes it increasingly important to spot and interpret these kinds of patterns.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Patients and clinicians can possibly use shifts in mealtime routines as an early warning sign to look into underlying physical and mental health issues," &lt;a href="https://www.massgeneralbrigham.org/en/about/newsroom/press-releases/meal-timing-in-older-adults-health-and-longevity"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; Dashti.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Also, encouraging older adults in having consistent meal schedules could become part of broader strategies to promoting healthy aging and longevity."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The research has been published in &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1038/s43856-025-01035-x"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Communications Medicine&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Sun, 14 Sep 2025 18:55:27 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMinwFBVV95cUxQemlZSVR2QTEzY01MRUk1aGtFaktTOU5lZ3owaDhScVJSLVpWV0hrVFQ1SXZadkU3enBTOFhZazlSVnFOYnA1cDVHTXVENTNuNGxYeXp1WWlVOHI4RkVTSjRBcFhyclBpWHI0NWtjTjR1QnpNLUJ0dXdaUWdGOTM1NWxad3NkbnN3cXd5TVI3ZFFyRlI0dlcyMGc2WnJqTWc</guid></item><item><title>研究表明，滴眼液可以代替眼镜或远视手术-《卫报》</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/society/2025/sep/14/eye-drops-could-replace-glasses-surgery-longsighted-study</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body-commercial-selector article-body-viewer-selector dcr-11jq3zt"&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Doctors have developed special eye drops for people with longsightedness that could replace the need for reading glasses or surgery.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Hundreds of millions of people worldwide have presbyopia, which is when the eyes find it difficult to focus on objects and text up close. Glasses or surgery can usually resolve the problem but many find wearing spectacles inconvenient and having an operation is not an option for everyone.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="sign-in-gate"&gt;&lt;gu-island name="SignInGateSelector" priority="feature" deferuntil="visible" props='{"contentType":"Article","sectionId":"science","tags":[{"id":"science/medical-research","type":"Keyword","title":"Medical research"},{"id":"society/health","type":"Keyword","title":"Health"},{"id":"science/science","type":"Keyword","title":"Science"},{"id":"world/world","type":"Keyword","title":"World news"},{"id":"society/society","type":"Keyword","title":"Society"},{"id":"type/article","type":"Type","title":"Article"},{"id":"tone/news","type":"Tone","title":"News"},{"id":"profile/andrew-gregory","type":"Contributor","title":"Andrew Gregory"},{"id":"publication/theguardian","type":"Publication","title":"The Guardian"},{"id":"theguardian/mainsection","type":"NewspaperBook","title":"Main section"},{"id":"theguardian/mainsection/uknews","type":"NewspaperBookSection","title":"UK news"},{"id":"tracking/commissioningdesk/uk-home-news","type":"Tracking","title":"UK Home News"}],"isPaidContent":false,"isPreview":false,"host":"https://www.theguardian.com","pageId":"society/2025/sep/14/eye-drops-could-replace-glasses-surgery-longsighted-study","idUrl":"https://profile.theguardian.com","contributionsServiceUrl":"https://contributions.guardianapis.com","editionId":"US"}'&gt;&lt;/gu-island&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Now experts say the solution could be as simple as using eye drops twice a day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;A study presented on Sunday at the European Society of Cataract and Refractive Surgeons (ESCRS) in Copenhagen showed that most people could read extra lines on eye test charts after using the drops. The improvement was sustained for two years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The treatment could provide a safe and effective alternative for patients who “seek freedom from the inconvenience” of wearing glasses or who are unable or unwilling to access surgery, experts said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The drops contain pilocarpine, a drug that constricts the pupils and contracts the muscle that controls the shape of the eye’s lens to enable focus on objects at different distances, and diclofenac, a non-steroidal anti-inflammatory drug (NSAID) that reduces inflammation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The study involved 766 people in Argentina who used the drops twice a day, upon waking and about six hours later.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;They were divided into three groups, receiving different formulations. Each of the drops had a fixed dose of diclofenac, but the concentration of pilocarpine varied between 1%, 2% and 3%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;In the 148 given the 1% drops, almost all were able to read two or more extra lines on the chart. In the 2% group, 69% of the 248 patients were able to read three or more extra lines, and in the 3% group, 84% of the 370 patients could read three or more extra lines.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Dr Giovanna Benozzi, the director of the Centre for Advanced Research for Presbyopia in Buenos Aires, said: “Our most significant result showed rapid and sustained improvements in near vision for all three concentrations. One hour after having the first drops, patients had an average improvement of 3.45 Jaeger lines [the measurement used for testing near visual acuity]. The treatment also improved focus at all distances.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“Impressively, 99% of 148 patients in the 1% pilocarpine group reached optimal near vision and were able to read two or more extra lines.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The findings suggest the therapy “offers a safe, effective and well-tolerated alternative to traditional presbyopia management”, Benozzi said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Common side-effects were temporary dim vision, irritation when the drops were administered, and headaches.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Experts welcomed the findings and called for more research. Prof Burkhard Dick, the president-elect of ESCRS, said: “Broader, long-term, multi-centre studies are needed to confirm safety and effectiveness before this treatment can be widely recommended.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Guardian</author><pubDate>Sun, 14 Sep 2025 18:28:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiqAFBVV95cUxOTzg2amhVYjUycFlPOVpLWEk5NW1WZHpHMGp5cWlJWm55bXVUSXJwVW5lNnhhTkV0bFgxWW9xQm15Qk5EbFI4SW50N1FvUlJoRGNBTUxYbUQwdG9RQXkxbDhVUDh2eVdzZU12ZTIxTlZJSUViZEJfMTBYUHVtZFB5NENrdlZJNFZ6aUQzOE5nV25kTFFySGg3WjdrOUV0WklDcE1hZUppOTg</guid></item><item><title>对RFK Jr.疫苗小组迫在眉睫的儿童注射决定的担忧- Politico</title><link>https://www.politico.com/news/2025/09/14/rfk-jr-s-vaccine-panel-to-consider-major-changes-to-childhood-shots-00563165</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Politico</author><pubDate>Sun, 14 Sep 2025 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiuAFBVV95cUxQdlZXOXpSNktNcXU1cnhDNURmeFBHaElwRF8tWWhaS3ZXOXNIOC12LUJrRy0xazRaTTN4UDNZY2tueW5sd3BZMnluNW0wb1NiWjBkNk1Ybm5LNU5kbkl2b0wySUVIYkxHNS1IOHVMVTVldEh5Y3N2cENSRF9HcnJFUEpRMWNyTjFUb0k4dzI5M09BOHZRSGxKQXlKQnBoSDA5c3drMDdVYTZYOUs4NGRteGl6UjNBVHJH</guid></item><item><title>CDC授予RPI疫苗自闭症研究合同-时代联盟</title><link>https://www.timesunion.com/news/article/cdc-contract-vaccine-autism-research-rpi-21047511.php</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;TROY — The U.S. government may tap researchers at Rensselaer Polytechnic Institute to investigate if there are links between vaccines and the prevalence of autism — a relationship that vaccine skeptics have long championed without evidence.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Centers for Disease Control and Prevention, which operates within the U.S. Department of Health and Human Services, intends to award the Troy institution a bid-free contract to take on such research, &lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/us-cdc-award-research-contract-vaccines-autism-2025-09-12/" data-link="native" class=""&gt;Reuters&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.axios.com/2025/09/12/cdc-autism-research-contract-vaccines" data-link="native" class=""&gt;Axios&lt;/a&gt; first reported.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;RPI has a “unique ability to link children to maternal cohorts using proprietary databases and de-identified data sets, enabling advanced statistical analyses within the project’s timeframe,” read &lt;a href="https://sam.gov/workspace/contract/opp/280398e7b4b54c0fac7de5efcbb80a80/view" data-link="native" class=""&gt;a notice of intent on the System for Award Management’s website&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chris Ingraham, a spokesman for the college, said in a statement to the Times Union that RPI acknowledges and appreciates CDC’s intention to award the contract to the school. He noted that &lt;a href="https://faculty.rpi.edu/juergen-hahn" data-link="native" class=""&gt;biomedical engineer and autism researcher Juergen Hahn&lt;/a&gt; will spearhead the project if it is ultimately awarded.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Details on the contract’s funding and timeline remain unclear. The U.S. Department of Health &amp;amp; Human Services, which operates the CDC, didn’t immediately respond to a request for comment on Sunday.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;This contract comes under the leadership of Secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr., who was appointed by President Donald Trump and confirmed by Congress in February to lead the U.S. Department of Health and Human Services. Prior to becoming health secretary, Kennedy rejected scientific research that vaccines don’t cause autism.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;In April, Kennedy &lt;a href="https://www.science.org/content/article/claiming-autism-epidemic-rfk-jr-describes-nih-initiative-find-environmental-causes" data-link="native" class=""&gt;claimed autism was a burgeoning “epidemic”&lt;/a&gt; that could be caused by environmental factors and announced plans to find the root cause of the disorder by September. Around the same time of his announcement, &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/mmwr/volumes/74/ss/ss7402a1.htm" data-link="native" class=""&gt;the CDC released a report&lt;/a&gt; that suggested the rise of autism prevalence in children was due to increased awareness of the condition and improved methods of diagnosis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the final weeks of the Biden administration in 2024, &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/vaccine-safety/about/autism.html" data-link="native" class=""&gt;the CDC noted on its website&lt;/a&gt; that “no links have been found between any vaccine ingredients and (Autism Spectrum Disorder).” The page includes further information about CDC studies and work by other research institutions that have investigated vaccine safety.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This is a developing story.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times Union</author><pubDate>Sun, 14 Sep 2025 17:12:39 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimAFBVV95cUxQNi05NHVmQ0ZNOGNWcUp1ZlJzdlJSX09WdDRaT2pIbHVIWEhGN2pFMkhEc1g1YjQ0VllPbVlWTERMTXpkS0ttT0lXcm84Ny1zZXJkdDQ5MjhLZlptS0ZGcUF3S2hzR2k2VnJ1RTNQV29wSnJ2UFJDVjJMellFM3BwX3VKNzA1cUdpTFJUQlFwLWNSNFNDM3JmLQ</guid></item><item><title>传染病更新2025年9月14日-每日科斯</title><link>https://www.dailykos.com/stories/2025/9/14/2339914/-Infectious-Updates-9-14-2025</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="story__text"&gt;
          &lt;p&gt;DR Congo &lt;a href="https://www.cidrap.umn.edu/ebola/dr-congo-declares-ebola-outbreak-kasai-province" target="_blank"&gt;declares another Ebola outbreak.&lt;/a&gt;  More &lt;a href="https://www.cidrap.umn.edu/ebola/who-shares-more-dr-congo-ebola-outbreak-details-more-suspected-cases-reported" target="_blank"&gt;details emerge.&lt;/a&gt;  Suspected cases &lt;a href="https://www.cidrap.umn.edu/ebola/suspected-cases-dr-congo-ebola-outbreak-rise-68" target="_blank"&gt;have risen to 68,&lt;/a&gt;  and more regions are involved.  This is a new zoonotic spillover, not related to previous outbreaks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mpox &lt;a href="https://www.cidrap.umn.edu/mpox/hot-spots-shift-africa-s-mpox-battle-cholera-activity-spikes-chad-and-republic-congo" target="_blank"&gt;Continues to be a problem for Africa&lt;/a&gt;, as the rest of the world winds down its health emergency.  Also, cholera is a severe problem.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A previously stored sample from a CA dairy herd &lt;a href="https://www.cidrap.umn.edu/avian-influenza-bird-flu/earlier-h5n1-detection-adds-texas-dairy-herd-total-researchers-cant" target="_blank"&gt;tested positive for H5N1,&lt;/a&gt; but no new detections have occurred in cattle in the last 30 days.  A turkey farm has been hit, the second recent detection in South Dakota.  Avian flu &lt;a href="https://www.cidrap.umn.edu/avian-influenza-bird-flu/cdc-says-avian-flu-may-infect-gut-though-risk-low" target="_blank"&gt;may infect the gut, though the risk is considered low.&lt;/a&gt;  Seems clear to me that pets infected by raw foods got it that way, not by breathing it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In related developments, a multisector group made up of experts in poultry, public health, science, and policy is meeting for the first time this week in Brazil to address the escalating avian flu threat to animal health, human health, and livelihoods, the UN Food and Agriculture Organization&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.fao.org/newsroom/detail/avian-influenza--first-global-dialogue-targets-the-rising-pandemic-threat/en" target="_blank"&gt;said today&lt;/a&gt;. The group called the response unprecedented.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Avian flu is now a global challenge, not a sporadic threat, Beth Bechdol, MS, the FAO's deputy director-general, said in a statement, "No single country or sector can tackle this threat in isolation—and failure is not an option. Practical, science-based collaboration like this is essential to protect our agrifood systems, livelihoods, and public health."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of the OTHER bird flus is still causing human cases &lt;a href="https://www.cidrap.umn.edu/avian-influenza-bird-flu/four-more-h9n2-avian-flu-cases-confirmed-china" target="_blank"&gt;In China&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There was measles exposure &lt;a href="https://idahocapitalsun.com/2025/09/09/repub/utah-health-officials-warn-of-measles-exposure-at-large-cycling-event/?emci=19ddf5c1-ca8d-f011-b484-6045bdeb7413&amp;amp;emdi=86e572af-3d8e-f011-b484-6045bdeb7413&amp;amp;ceid=491687" target="_blank"&gt;At a large cycling event in Utah.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A sad reminder that measles can kill years later: an LA child &lt;a href="http://www.cidrap.umn.edu/measles/la-county-confirms-childs-death-late-measles-complication" target="_blank"&gt;Who caught measles as an infant&lt;/a&gt; has died of subacute sclerosing panencephalitis, a rare and fatal sequel of measles that occurs 10 or more years after the original infection.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;States are stepping up &lt;a href="https://www.cidrap.umn.edu/covid-19/minnesota-new-york-issue-executive-orders-promoting-access-covid-vaccines" target="_blank"&gt;To secure vaccine access for their citizens&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;New studies show &lt;a href="https://www.cidrap.umn.edu/covid-19/studies-show-how-common-long-covid-globally-and-teens" target="_blank"&gt;just how prevalent long Covid is.&lt;/a&gt;  To be avoided if at all possible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And you might give &lt;a href="https://www.cidrap.umn.edu/covid-19/dogs-exposed-covid-positive-people-show-increased-risk-infection" target="_blank"&gt;Covid to your dog&lt;/a&gt;, who really doesn't deserve it either.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Healthy full term infants are also &lt;a href="https://www.cidrap.umn.edu/respiratory-syncytial-virus-rsv/severe-rsv-doesnt-spare-healthy-full-term-infants-data-suggest" target="_blank"&gt;at risk of severe RSV illness&lt;/a&gt;, highlighting the need for maternal and infant vaccination.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Salmonella in delivered meals:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The Centers for Disease Control and Prevention (CDC) has posted a notice about a&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span&gt;Salmonella&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;Enteritidis outbreak linked to&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/salmonella/outbreaks/homedeliverymeals-09-25/investigation.html" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;meals from Metabolic Meals&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;, a home delivery company. So far, at least 16 people in 10 states have been sickened, with 7 people requiring hospitalization. No deaths have been reported.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the odd diseases corner we have N. meningitidis eye infections &lt;a href="https://www.cidrap.umn.edu/misc-emerging-topics/report-describes-n-meningitidis-conjunctivitis-outbreak-us-military-base" target="_blank"&gt;on a military base.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And &lt;a href="https://www.cidrap.umn.edu/borealpox/six-recent-sporadic-borealpox-cases-alaska-tied-rodents" target="_blank"&gt;Boreal pox in Alaska,&lt;/a&gt; which is spread from rodents.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Multidrug resistant &lt;a href="https://www.cidrap.umn.edu/candida-auris/multidrug-resistant-yeast-cases-rising-rapidly-europe-survey-shows" target="_blank"&gt;Candidiasis in European hospitals&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And Jamestown Canyon virus, first human case &lt;a href="https://www.cidrap.umn.edu/misc-emerging-topics/vermont-reports-its-first-human-jamestown-canyon-case" target="_blank"&gt;In Vermont.&lt;/a&gt;  No, I never heard of it before either.  It's spread by mosquitoes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The voluntary recall of some &lt;a href="https://www.fda.gov/safety/recalls-market-withdrawals-safety-alerts/dermarite-industries-issues-voluntary-nationwide-recall-dermakleen-dermasarra-kleenfoam-and" target="_blank"&gt;DermaRite products&lt;/a&gt; has expanded, due to Burkholderia contamination.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;..&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class="table-wrapper"&gt;
&lt;table align="center" class="basic-table"&gt;
	&lt;tbody&gt;
		&lt;tr&gt;
			&lt;td&gt;
			&lt;div&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.dailykos.com/groups/Infectious%20Information" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Infectious Information&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; is a DK group for collecting diaries on all things infectious, both basic educational material and breaking news updates.&lt;/p&gt;

			&lt;p&gt;Given the precarious state of public health agencies under the Orange Menace, it is my hope that the information &lt;em&gt;itself&lt;/em&gt; can be infectious, spread widely to all your contacts, in the hope of promoting self-defense from disease. Knowledge is the best inoculation against misinformation!&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;

			&lt;div&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.dailykos.com/users/strawbale" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Kosmail&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; for an invitation if you want to join and have info to contribute, or&lt;a href="https://www.dailykos.com/groups/Infectious%20Information" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;strong&gt; follow the group&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; to get these posts automatically in your activity stream.&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;
			&lt;/td&gt;
		&lt;/tr&gt;
	&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class="is-empty-p"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



        &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Daily Kos</author><pubDate>Sun, 14 Sep 2025 17:00:01 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihwFBVV95cUxNNlN0UUxLaU1sYVNqT1RwWEd1UXNuV0pYNmxhdExLSTBzMVdvM1diWU5Xb0lQZTEzUEF2QlJLTWJ0TDJheGtvNzN1Z0tfYVhNcnJVbkxocUlWNkNUQXowczcxZWgtLURoVTl0ZVhteGF6WUVvR1doQlN4ZUpuYWtseGs3eW1TV28</guid></item><item><title>“你的恐惧是有根据的” ：人类活动如何提高了莱姆病等蜱传疾病的风险- Live Science</title><link>https://www.livescience.com/health/viruses-infections-disease/your-fear-is-well-founded-how-human-activities-have-raised-the-risk-of-tick-borne-diseases-like-lyme</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="article-body" class="text-copy bodyCopy auto"&gt;
&lt;p id="d6ba3bd8-9871-45c2-a640-2743998b78fb"&gt;When you think about &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.livescience.com/health/tick-bites-symptoms-treatment-and-tick-borne-diseases" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.livescience.com/health/tick-bites-symptoms-treatment-and-tick-borne-diseases"&gt;&lt;u&gt;ticks&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, you might picture nightmarish little &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.livescience.com/animals/why-we-need-parasites-despite-them-leeching-life-from-others" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.livescience.com/animals/why-we-need-parasites-despite-them-leeching-life-from-others"&gt;&lt;u&gt;parasites&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, stalking you on weekend hikes or afternoons in the park.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="ad-unit-1" class="ad-unit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Your fear is well-founded. Tick-borne diseases are the &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://royalsocietypublishing.org/doi/full/10.1098/rsos.240837" target="_blank" data-url="https://royalsocietypublishing.org/doi/full/10.1098/rsos.240837" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;most prevalent vector-borne diseases&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; — those transmitted by living organisms — in the United States. Each tick feeds on multiple animals throughout its life, absorbing viruses and bacteria along the way and passing them on with its next bite. Some of those viruses and bacteria are harmful to humans, causing diseases that can be debilitating and sometimes lethal without treatment, such as &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.mayoclinic.org/diseases-conditions/lyme-disease/symptoms-causes/syc-20374651" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.mayoclinic.org/diseases-conditions/lyme-disease/symptoms-causes/syc-20374651" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Lyme&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://my.clevelandclinic.org/health/diseases/24809-babesiosis" target="_blank" data-url="https://my.clevelandclinic.org/health/diseases/24809-babesiosis" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;babesiosis&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.cdc.gov/rocky-mountain-spotted-fever/about/index.html" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.cdc.gov/rocky-mountain-spotted-fever/about/index.html" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Rocky Mountain spotted fever&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a id="elk-seasonal" data-url="" href="" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p id="d6ba3bd8-9871-45c2-a640-2743998b78fb-2"&gt;But contained in every bite of this infuriating, insatiable pest is also a &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://academic.oup.com/jme/article-abstract/47/5/707/881591" target="_blank" data-url="https://academic.oup.com/jme/article-abstract/47/5/707/881591" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;trove of social, environmental and epidemiological history&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="mid-article-leaderboard" class="ad-unit sm:hidden block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="b3025e63-be2a-4eb8-8ccc-3ae1984350d8"&gt;In many cases, human actions long ago are the reason ticks carry these diseases so widely today. And that’s what makes ticks fascinating for &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://history.wvu.edu/faculty-and-staff/faculty/sean-lawrence" target="_blank" data-url="https://history.wvu.edu/faculty-and-staff/faculty/sean-lawrence" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;environmental historians like me&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="ad-unit-2" class="ad-unit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a id="elk-90b0d7fa-4e6e-47b3-992e-d33210e1d15a" data-url="" href="" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;h2 id="changing-forests-fueled-tick-risks-3"&gt;Changing forests fueled tick risks&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="c6aa0b95-3042-42bf-b060-079276a06b05"&gt;During the 18th and 19th centuries, settlers &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://insider.si.edu/2013/09/400-year-study-finds-northeast-forests-resilient-changing-%EF%BB%BF/" target="_blank" data-url="https://insider.si.edu/2013/09/400-year-study-finds-northeast-forests-resilient-changing-%EF%BB%BF/" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;cleared more than half&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; the forested land across the northeastern U.S., cutting down forests for timber and to make way for farms, towns and mining operations. With large-scale land clearing came a sharp decline in wildlife of all kinds. Predators such as bears and wolves were driven out, as were deer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As farming moved westward, Northeasterners began to recognize the ecological and economic value of trees, and they &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://doi.org/10.2307/1942027" target="_blank" data-url="https://doi.org/10.2307/1942027" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;returned millions of acres to forest&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The woods regrew. Plant-eaters such as deer returned, but the apex predators that once kept their populations in check did not.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div id="slice-container-newsletterForm-articleInbodyContent-M69yF2N432PWmUrKsBbKUT" class="slice-container newsletter-inbodyContent-slice newsletterForm-articleInbodyContent-M69yF2N432PWmUrKsBbKUT slice-container-newsletterForm"&gt;&lt;div data-hydrate="true" class="newsletter-form__wrapper newsletter-form__wrapper--inbodyContent"&gt;&lt;div class="newsletter-form__container"&gt;&lt;section class="newsletter-form__main-section"&gt;&lt;p class="newsletter-form__strapline"&gt;Get the world’s most fascinating discoveries delivered straight to your inbox.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;As a result, &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.aphis.usda.gov/news/stories/cattle-fever-tick-program-highlights-story-map" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.aphis.usda.gov/news/stories/cattle-fever-tick-program-highlights-story-map" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;deer populations&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; grew rapidly. With the deer came &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S1877959X23001140" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S1877959X23001140" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;deer ticks&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; (&lt;em&gt;Ixodes scapularis&lt;/em&gt;) carrying &lt;em&gt;Borrelia burgdorferi&lt;/em&gt;, the bacterium that causes Lyme disease. When a tick feeds on an infected animal, it can take up the bacteria. The tick can pass the bacteria to its next victim. In humans, Lyme disease can cause fever and fatigue, and &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.cdc.gov/lyme/about/index.html" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.cdc.gov/lyme/about/index.html" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;if left untreated&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; it can affect the nervous system.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="van-image-figure inline-layout" data-bordeaux-image-check id="632c80fa-133f-4a75-b9bb-996d77267c71"&gt;&lt;figcaption itemprop="caption description" class=" inline-layout"&gt;&lt;span class="caption-text"&gt;The black-legged tick, &lt;em&gt;Ixodes scapularis&lt;/em&gt;, also known as the deer tick, ranges across the eastern half of the country. It’s one of many disease-carrying ticks in the U.S. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="credit" itemprop="copyrightHolder"&gt;(Image credit: &lt;a href="http://cdc.gov/ticks/about/where-ticks-live.html" data-url="http://cdc.gov/ticks/about/where-ticks-live.html" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;National Center for Emerging and Zoonotic Infectious Diseases&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p id="835e778c-f04d-40bb-ab1b-3e0c763441a0"&gt;The eastern U.S. became a global hot spot for tick-borne Lyme disease starting around the 1970s. Lyme disease &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.cdc.gov/ticks/data-research/facts-stats/tickborne-disease-surveillance-data-summary.html" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.cdc.gov/ticks/data-research/facts-stats/tickborne-disease-surveillance-data-summary.html" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;affected over 89,000 Americans in 2023, and possibly many more&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a id="elk-fe0ea7ae-9690-4f7a-aac1-ac3f50e52bf8" data-url="" href="" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;h2 id="californians-move-into-tick-territory-3"&gt;Californians move into tick territory&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="33d9e9af-db20-4697-9a20-3837ccde98f3"&gt;For centuries, changing patterns of human settlements and the politics of land use have shaped the role of ticks and tick-borne illnesses within their environments.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In short, humans have made it easier for ticks to thrive and spread disease in our midst.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In California, the Northern Inner Coast and Santa Cruz mountain ranges that converge on San Francisco from the north and south were never clear-cut, and predators such as mountain lions and coyotes still exist there. But competition for housing has &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://criticalurbanenvironments.ucsc.edu/projects/wildland-urban-interface-wui-research-for-resilience/" target="_blank" data-url="https://criticalurbanenvironments.ucsc.edu/projects/wildland-urban-interface-wui-research-for-resilience/" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;pushed human settlement&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; deeper into &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://data-usfs.hub.arcgis.com/documents/usfs::wildland-urban-interface-2020-map-service/explore?path=" target="_blank" data-url="https://data-usfs.hub.arcgis.com/documents/usfs::wildland-urban-interface-2020-map-service/explore?path=" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;wildland areas to the north, south and east of the city&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, reshaping tick ecology there.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="van-image-figure inline-layout" data-bordeaux-image-check id="cbb662cd-d806-4bde-8352-fee92099c59f"&gt;&lt;figcaption itemprop="caption description" class=" inline-layout"&gt;&lt;span class="caption-text"&gt;A range map for the western black-legged tick. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="credit" itemprop="copyrightHolder"&gt;(Image credit: &lt;a href="http://cdc.gov/ticks/about/where-ticks-live.html" data-url="http://cdc.gov/ticks/about/where-ticks-live.html" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;National Center for Emerging and Zoonotic Infectious Diseases&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p id="17bd505e-2ffe-400a-b1ef-89de2c2259ee"&gt;While western black-legged ticks (&lt;em&gt;Ixodes pacificus&lt;/em&gt;) tend to swarm in large forest preserves, the Lyme-causing bacterium is actually more prevalent &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://doi.org/10.1098/rsos.240837" target="_blank" data-url="https://doi.org/10.1098/rsos.240837" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;in small, isolated patches of greenery&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. In these isolated patches, rodents and other tick hosts can thrive, safe from large predators, which need more habitat to move freely. But isolation and lower diversity also means infections are spread more easily within the tick’s host populations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;People tend to build isolated houses in the hills, rather than large, connected developments. As the Silicon Valley area south of San Francisco sprawls outward, this checkerboard pattern of settlement has fragmented the natural landscape, &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://royalsocietypublishing.org/doi/full/10.1098/rsos.240837" target="_blank" data-url="https://royalsocietypublishing.org/doi/full/10.1098/rsos.240837" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;creating a hard-to-manage public health threat&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fewer hosts, more tightly packed, often means more infected hosts, proportionally, and thus more dangerous ticks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="van-image-figure inline-layout" data-bordeaux-image-check id="49627924-8ecc-4d22-965c-1ece7add9565"&gt;&lt;figcaption itemprop="caption description" class=" inline-layout"&gt;&lt;span class="caption-text"&gt;A tick’s mouth is barbed so it can hold on as it draws blood over hours. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="credit" itemprop="copyrightHolder"&gt;(Image credit: &lt;a href="https://www.flickr.com/photos/nihgov/48881159777" data-url="https://www.flickr.com/photos/nihgov/48881159777" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;National Institute of Allergy and Infectious Diseases&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p id="40a184fa-56db-4f9f-921a-d3afeefcce69"&gt;Six counties across these ranges, all surrounding and including San Francisco, account for &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.cdc.gov/ticks/data-research/facts-stats/geographic-distribution-of-tickborne-disease-cases.html" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.cdc.gov/ticks/data-research/facts-stats/geographic-distribution-of-tickborne-disease-cases.html" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;44% of recorded tick-borne illnesses in California&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a id="elk-8743daa3-30cf-4c03-bf59-9da2cb55aebe" data-url="" href="" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;h2 id="a-lesson-from-texas-cattle-ranches-3"&gt;A lesson from Texas cattle ranches&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="402b636c-0d78-4d54-adb8-760c7010652c"&gt;Domesticated livestock have also shaped the disease threat posed by ticks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In 1892, at a meeting of cattle ranchers at the Stock Raiser’s Convention in Austin, Texas, Dr. B.A. Rogers introduced a novel theory that ticks were behind recent devastating plagues of Texas cattle fever. The disease had arrived with cattle imported from the West Indies and Mexico in the 1600s, and it was taking &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.nal.usda.gov/exhibits/speccoll/exhibits/show/parasitic-diseases-with-econom/parasitic-diseases-with-econom/texas-cattle-fever" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.nal.usda.gov/exhibits/speccoll/exhibits/show/parasitic-diseases-with-econom/parasitic-diseases-with-econom/texas-cattle-fever" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;huge tolls on cattle herds&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. But how the disease spread to new victims had been a mystery.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Editors of Daniel’s Texas Medical Journal found the idea of ticks spreading disease &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC9173108/" target="_blank" data-url="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC9173108/" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;laughable and lampooned the hypothesis&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, publishing a satire of what they described as an “early copy” of a forthcoming report on the subject.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The tick’s “fluid secretion, it is believed, is the poison which causes the fever … [and the tick] having been known to chew tobacco, as all other Texans do, the secretion is most probably tobacco juice,” they wrote.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fortunately for the ranchers, not to mention the cows, the U.S. Department of Agriculture sided with Rogers. Its cattle fever tick program, started in 1906, curbed cattle fever outbreaks by &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.frontiersin.org/journals/physiology/articles/10.3389/fphys.2012.00195/pdf" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.frontiersin.org/journals/physiology/articles/10.3389/fphys.2012.00195/pdf" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;limiting where and when cattle should cross tick-dense areas&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="van-image-figure inline-layout" data-bordeaux-image-check id="5fb43c4f-ede3-421f-8488-bfcbf05aa637"&gt;&lt;figcaption itemprop="caption description" class=" inline-layout"&gt;&lt;span class="caption-text"&gt;Engorged ticks feed on a calf’s ear. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="credit" itemprop="copyrightHolder"&gt;(Image credit: &lt;a href="https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Rhipicephalus-appendiculatus-calf-ear.jpg" data-url="https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Rhipicephalus-appendiculatus-calf-ear.jpg" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;Alan R Walker&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc-sa/4.0/" data-url="http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc-sa/4.0/" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;CC BY-NC-SA&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p id="1f5332bd-4388-4828-b1bc-df746171d08a"&gt;By 1938, &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.aphis.usda.gov/news/stories/cattle-fever-tick-program-highlights-story-map" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.aphis.usda.gov/news/stories/cattle-fever-tick-program-highlights-story-map" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;the government had established a quarantine zone&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; that extended 580 miles by 10 miles along the U.S.-Mexico border in South Texas Brush Country, a region favored by the cattle tick.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This innovative use of natural space as a public health tool helped to &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.aphis.usda.gov/news/stories/cattle-fever-tick-program-highlights-story-map" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.aphis.usda.gov/news/stories/cattle-fever-tick-program-highlights-story-map" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;functionally eradicate&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; cattle fever from 14 Southern states by 1943.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a id="elk-a5bf147b-77d8-4cb5-9f93-c9abe904e7ab" data-url="" href="" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;h2 id="ticks-are-products-of-their-environment-3"&gt;Ticks are products of their environment&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="d9758ef1-ddb5-43c3-b1d9-105d5019c782"&gt;When it comes to tick-borne diseases the world over, location matters.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Take the hunter tick (&lt;em&gt;Hyalomma spp.&lt;/em&gt;) of the Mediterranean and Asia. As a juvenile, or nymph, these ticks feed on small forest animals such as mice, hares and voles, but as an adult they prefer domesticated livestock.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For centuries, this tick was an occasional nuisance to nomadic shepherds of the Middle East. But in the 1850s, the Ottoman Empire passed laws to &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.jstor.org/stable/40647178?seq=1" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.jstor.org/stable/40647178?seq=1" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;force nomadic tribes to become settled farmers instead&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. Unclaimed lands, &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.academia.edu/40661841/Its_a_bad_fate_to_be_born_near_a_forest_Forest_People_and_Buffaloes_in_mid_Nineteenth_Century_North_Western_Anatolia" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.academia.edu/40661841/Its_a_bad_fate_to_be_born_near_a_forest_Forest_People_and_Buffaloes_in_mid_Nineteenth_Century_North_Western_Anatolia" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;especially on the forested edges of the steppe&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, were offered to settlers, creating ideal conditions for hunter ticks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As a result, farmers in what today is &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://doi.org/10.1371/journal.pntd.0005021%22%22" target="_blank" data-url="https://doi.org/10.1371/journal.pntd.0005021%22%22" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Turkey saw spikes in tick-borne diseases&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, including a virus that causes Crimean-Congo hemorrhagic fever, &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.who.int/news-room/fact-sheets/detail/crimean-congo-haemorrhagic-fever" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.who.int/news-room/fact-sheets/detail/crimean-congo-haemorrhagic-fever" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;a potentially fatal condition&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="aef7a5a8-3458-4bbb-8c7d-4c68568a04db"&gt;It’s probably too much to ask for sympathy for any ticks you meet this summer. They are bloodsucking parasites, after all.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Still, it’s worth remembering that the tick’s malevolence isn’t its own fault. Ticks are products of their environment, and humans have played many roles in turning them into the harmful parasites that seek us out today.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This edited article is republished from &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="http://theconversation.com/" target="_blank" data-url="http://theconversation.com/" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Conversation&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt; under a Creative Commons license. Read the &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://theconversation.com/ticks-carry-decades-of-history-in-each-troublesome-bite-257110" target="_blank" data-url="https://theconversation.com/ticks-carry-decades-of-history-in-each-troublesome-bite-257110" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;em&gt;original article&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a id="elk-3b395a65-2e0f-4979-aed4-8f74e943314d" data-url="" href="" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Live Science</author><pubDate>Sun, 14 Sep 2025 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi9AFBVV95cUxPRWV6VDB1d0FwV1hVUk1wREtJeDBVZDdwTHdRM1J5dDZBeDlFV21aNUdNQ0ZCSi03UGQxODNQdU1xQVVaa3J3aUxXaGlmdktBRzlSYjBEbFNFdlZiQzBXVFV4bE9EWVRTRHdVYkFraFNWUUJYbFpObkJTNkZMQXNCd3pfVzRSTmZzRElyU2R3UEJiZTkweXdyeXk3eE14YXZpNV8wWHIyWkluekhUenJwd29KRVBsWWVMZWVFT1RLUFlIaFZEQjJoVms3RTJldkFaN05WUEJ3WWFlLXA4Qm1ZNTlLOUE2a2JwRmpVbFRIekhYQjdi</guid></item><item><title>不是红肉，不是黄油：这5种日常习惯可能导致心脏病发作-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/not-red-meat-not-butter-these-5-everyday-habits-may-be-causing-heart-attacks/articleshow/123880413.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;p&gt;For years, red meat and butter have sometimes been blamed as culprits that help bring on heart disease. But increasingly, evidence points to another culprit that can harm cardiovascular health. Most of us are not aware and never would have thought that this, could also be the reason of heart attacks that are increasing by the second. Modern foods and lifestyle patterns are quietly undermining the body's capacity for nitric oxide production, a molecule that is essential for keeping blood vessels functional and the heart healthy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="3"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr. Eric Berg, a trained wellness expert and best-selling author, warns about how a potential decrease in nitric oxide can significantly lead to heart attacks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="6"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="lOvcW vdo_embedd"&gt;&lt;div class="k7lcu"&gt;&lt;p class="efT4r"&gt;Beware! Processed Meat Might Lead to Cancer: Dr Zeeshan Ali Reveals Why Meat Is Called The New Tobacco&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="8"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nitric oxide is used to relax blood vessels, facilitate circulation, and guard against arterial plaque buildup. When the levels of this molecule severely decline, high blood pressure, stroke, and heart attack risk increase. Scroll down to see the list of few of the worst enemies of nitric oxide are amazingly prevalent in normal life:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="11"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="12"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Refined sugar&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-pos="0" class="id-r-component QbQNS undefined  
        "&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;img alt="1" msid="123880436" width="" title="Credit: canva" placeholdersrc="https://static.toiimg.com/photo/83033472.cms" imgsize="23456" resizemode="4" offsetvertical="0" placeholdermsid="" type="thumb" src="https://static.toiimg.com/photo/83033472.cms" class="" data-src="https://static.toiimg.com/photo/imgsize-23456,msid-123880436,resizemode-4/1.jpg" data-api-prerender="true"&gt;&lt;p class="q3gJl"&gt;Credit: canva&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="14"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Refined sugar occurs in soft drinks, desserts, sauces, cereals, and most packaged foods. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Its effect on nitric oxide production is considerable and detrimental.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="18"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="19"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;It rapidly elevates blood sugar levels, leading to inflammation in the lining of blood vessels.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;It boosts oxidative stress, which kills nitric oxide molecules.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;In the long run, it causes insulin resistance, further inhibiting nitric oxide production.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Regular use of refined sugar harms the endothelium, the inner lining of blood vessels, which is in charge of generating nitric oxide.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="20"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="21"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Refined starch&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="22"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Refined white flour foods, including white bread, crackers, and pastries, function similarly to sugar in the body.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="24"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="25"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;They quickly break down into glucose matter, thereby creating a surge in blood sugar levels&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;This leads to inflammation and metabolic stress.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;This causes damage to endothelial function and decreases nitric oxide production.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Refined starch contains none of the fiber and antioxidants present in whole grains, which serve to defend the vascular system.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="26"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="27"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;keyword id="28871355" type="General" weightage="20" keywordseo="industrial-seed-oils" source="keywords"&gt;Industrial seed oils&lt;/keyword&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="29"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Soybean oil, corn oil and sunflower oil, are all processed and commonly used in our daily life, consumed in the form of fast food or packaged items.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="31"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="32"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;These oils contain high levels of omega-6 fatty acids, which can contribute to chronic inflammation.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;They are very unstable when heated and readily oxidize, resulting in toxic compounds.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Oxidative stress and inflammation contribute to reduced production of nitric oxide.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Chronic use of seed oils has been associated with decreased arterial compliance and increased risk of cardiovascular disease.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="33"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="34"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Smoking&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="35"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="37"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Smoking is already classified as injurious for health and imagine the degree of damage it would do if Both smoking and vaping were to be combined. Together, they responsible for the degradation of nitric oxide within the body. Tobacco smoke consists of chemicals that destroy the endothelial lining of blood vessels.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="41"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="42"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;It decreases the functioning of the enzyme that is responsible for producing nitric oxide.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Free radicals in smoke destroy existing molecules of nitric oxide.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Smokers have far lower levels of nitric oxide and suffer more from vascular disease and compromised circulation.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="43"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="44"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Antibacterial mouthwash&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="45"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;While often used for the cleanliness of the mouth, numerous antiseptic mouthwashes contain chemicals that disrupt the creation of nitric oxide.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="47"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="48"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Some oral bacteria are responsible for breaking down dietary nitrates into nitric oxide.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Antibacterial mouthwash eliminates these helpful bacteria.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The outcome is a quantifiable decrease in nitric oxide levels and an increase in blood pressure.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Daily use of high-strength antiseptic mouthwash has the potential to escalate the risk of heart issues by interfering with the nitrate pathway.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="49"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="50"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Aiding Nitric Oxide Production&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="52"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Healthy nitric oxide levels can be maintained through certain dietary and lifestyle factors. Some food naturally encourages its production and maintains blood vessel health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="55"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Food that aids nitric oxide&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="57"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="58"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Leafy greens like spinach, arugula, and kale&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Beets and beet juice&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Garlic and onions&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Citrus fruits, particularly lemons and oranges&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Pomegranate&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Nuts and seeds, particularly those rich in arginine&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Dark chocolate (with high cocoa content)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="59"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="60"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Lifestyle habits that nourish nitric oxide:&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="61"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Consistent physical activity, particularly aerobic exercise&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Quality sleep every night&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Getting enough sunlight, which nourishes nitric oxide through chemistry of the skin&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Stress management through breathing, nature walks, or quiet rituals&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="62"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The worst enemies of heart health are not necessarily the most apparent ones. Sometimes, we need to look away from the obvious food items to know what is actually harming our heart and body. Refined sugar, processed starches, industrial seed oils, smoking, and even run-of-the-mill mouthwash can sneakily compromise the body's nitric oxide production capability. This degrades the blood vessels and enhances the risk of cardiovascular disease in the long term.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="64"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="65"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Times of India</author><pubDate>Sun, 14 Sep 2025 15:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi9wFBVV95cUxNa3BZVlFJZmZQd3h5dW9iM29UOUlUekNkcWhhR0F3eU1YVVdOZ19mVXlGZlBKVF9kOGtzdnp0bGJ3VS1CQ2RJSFZyWmluQjFHT1FZbVJtT242N2dJVXdsN016ZGlHNC1KTjN6VG9rTjU1ckV5U0xiWlN5ZG9JbEltUHdJalAyQnk0MlBydGF6bl96Wk1zVHV1cUdkM0RIWERMWi1leGxrNkJYT2NQbnQyLWNLbXRwYWJybjFjeXYwZ3VJVjBCWDlxcVZFbGg3TXlpU2xqNklQcHB5SWZaaWRzTS1KTjVYMjAwSHdLaGVfc19nSUptVFpr</guid></item><item><title>根据科学研究，这种看似无害的饮料以关键的方式加速衰老- valleyvanguardonline.com</title><link>https://www.valleyvanguardonline.com/this-seemingly-harmless-drink-speeds-up-aging-in-a-critical-way-according-to-science/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content" itemprop="text"&gt;
			&lt;p data-start="90" data-end="459"&gt;&lt;strong data-start="90" data-end="457"&gt;&lt;em data-start="92" data-end="455"&gt;For many of us, it’s the drink we reach for at lunch, during a movie, or when we need a quick burst of energy. It feels refreshing in the moment, but research shows this sweet habit may actually be shaving years off our lives. Scientists warn that one of the world’s most popular beverages doesn’t just damage our health—it accelerates the aging process itself.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="code-block code-block-3"&gt;

&lt;ins class="adsbygoogle" data-ad-client="ca-pub-5177416233695826" data-ad-slot="3757471395" data-ad-format="auto" data-full-width-responsive="true"&gt;&lt;/ins&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p data-start="90" data-end="459"&gt;&lt;span id="more-3607"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 data-start="460" data-end="515"&gt;Premature Aging: The Drink Behind Cellular Decline&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p data-start="516" data-end="1082"&gt;The culprit? &lt;strong&gt;Soda&lt;/strong&gt;. Beyond the sugar highs and inevitable crashes, sodas have been directly linked to premature cellular aging. A landmark 2014 study published in the &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em data-start="682" data-end="717"&gt;American Journal of Public Health&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; found that people who regularly drank soda had shorter telomeres—protective caps at the ends of our chromosomes. Think of telomeres like the plastic tips on shoelaces; when they wear down, the laces fray. In our bodies, shorter telomeres mean reduced longevity and a higher risk of chronic illnesses such as diabetes, cardiovascular disease, and certain cancers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 data-start="1083" data-end="1119"&gt;What Scientists Have Discovered&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p data-start="1120" data-end="1566"&gt;Elissa Epel, a professor of psychiatry at the &lt;strong&gt;University of &lt;a href="https://www.valleyvanguardonline.com/neon-blue-wild-pigs-in-california-the-surprising-reason-behind-their-color-change/"&gt;California&lt;/a&gt;, San Francisco&lt;/strong&gt;, explained in an interview that sugary soda consumption not only overwhelms the body’s ability to regulate sugar but also speeds up cellular aging in multiple tissues. What’s striking is that these effects show up regardless of age, income, ethnicity, or education level. In other words, nobody gets a free pass—soda’s impact on cellular health is universal.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 data-start="1567" data-end="1612"&gt;More Than Just Sugar: The Hidden Effects&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p data-start="1613" data-end="2011"&gt;Newer research reinforces these findings. A 2021 review in &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em data-start="1672" data-end="1699"&gt;Current Nutrition Reports&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; highlighted how sugary drinks disrupt the gut microbiome, fuel chronic inflammation, and increase oxidative stress. These three biological processes are well-known drivers of premature aging. Taken together, they paint a clear picture: soda isn’t just a guilty pleasure, it’s a catalyst for long-term decline.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 data-start="2012" data-end="2056"&gt;A Short-Term Pleasure, A Long-Term Cost&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p data-start="2057" data-end="2481"&gt;Of course, enjoying a cold soda on a hot day feels harmless—even nostalgic. Many of us grew up associating it with family meals, summer picnics, or celebrations. But as science continues to uncover the hidden costs, nutritionists are urging people to rethink their daily habits. Alternatives like sparkling water with a squeeze of lemon or unsweetened iced tea can deliver the same refreshment without the cellular damage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="code-block code-block-4"&gt;

&lt;ins class="adsbygoogle" data-ad-client="ca-pub-5177416233695826" data-ad-slot="2855453267" data-ad-format="auto" data-full-width-responsive="true"&gt;&lt;/ins&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 data-start="2482" data-end="2519"&gt;Think Twice Before Your Next Sip&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p data-start="2520" data-end="2908" data-is-last-node="" data-is-only-node=""&gt;The occasional soda won’t undo years of healthy living, but making it a regular habit can quietly chip away at your body’s resilience. As researchers remind us, aging is inevitable—but accelerating it through what we drink is not. The next time you find yourself craving that fizzy sweetness, it might be worth pausing to consider: is the momentary satisfaction worth the price of time?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;You might also like:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;div class="saboxplugin-wrap" itemtype="http://schema.org/Person" itemscope itemprop="author"&gt;&lt;div class="saboxplugin-tab"&gt;&lt;div class="saboxplugin-desc"&gt;&lt;div itemprop="description"&gt;&lt;p&gt;David Miller is an entertainment expert with a passion for film, music, and series. With eight years in cultural criticism, he takes you behind the scenes of productions and studios. His energetic style guides you to the next big releases and trending sensations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="clearfix"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

		&lt;/div&gt;

				&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>valleyvanguardonline.com</author><pubDate>Sun, 14 Sep 2025 14:45:54 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMivwFBVV95cUxQNlBDZWFEa3FMYS1VamJYUFpmcWpuQjQ0SUFTRko4bzgwNmtUMV9abjdodENPbS1LSnlRNlBkU3lUMlpDTDdmOXhEVk5HbHBEVG9qa20wb2gzc0J4MWZ0WjhyWm02aFZCU2pYUWItckZJQUo3TnJmNGZHSHlEb0xQekZuODNZeXRTMGNsYWdReDZpV3B0WV82TmJuSEVPaWM3NFNqUkVGSGk2bUNVMk0tUllONmpGd3BHTVVuTmlXTQ</guid></item><item><title>5种非记忆丧失的痴呆症状-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/5-signs-of-dementia-that-are-not-memory-loss/photostory/123879819.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="COQxt" data-ua-type="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dementia, an umbrella term used to describe a range of neurological conditions affecting the brain that worsen over time, is one of the most impactful diseases in the world. This common and disabling disease that affects the brain occurs when brain cells are damaged or die, leading to progressive declines in cognitive functions, mood, behavior, and personality. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/fact-check-are-heart-attacks-caused-by-bacterial-infections/articleshow/123884019.cms"&gt;Fact check: Are heart attacks caused by bacterial infections?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/kidney-health-best-herbal-teas-for-kidney-support-besides-water-and-supplements/amp_etphotostory/123864389.cms"&gt;Kidney health: Best herbal teas for kidney support besides water and supplements&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;With over 55 million people with dementia worldwide currently, nearly 10 million new cases develop each year. The number of people with dementia is growing worldwide and is expected to triple by 2050. Despite the prevalence of the disabling disease, when most people think of dementia, the first thing that comes to mind is memory loss, like forgetting names, appointments, or where things are. While memory decline is very common, dementia involves much more than that. Early on, there are other changes, subtle signals, that often go unnoticed. These can be changes in behaviour, language, perception, coordination, or mood.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr. Bing, MD, MPH, a renowned neurologist with over 170K followers on Instagram, says the same.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Researchers warn that spotting these non-memory signs early can lead to faster diagnosis, better care, and more time to plan. Many dementia types – such as Alzheimer’s, dementia with Lewy bodies, frontotemporal dementia, and vascular dementia – show these symptoms. But because these signs are subtler, they are sometimes ignored or chalked up to stress, age, or mood. That delay in recognizing these non-memory signals means missed opportunities for early treatment, support, and slowing of progression.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But if you know what to watch for, you can help yourself or someone you care about get help sooner. Let’s look at 5 non-memory signs of dementia: what they are, how to spot them, which dementia types tend to show them, and when to talk to a doctor. Recognizing these signs is not about fear – it’s about awareness, so that early support, treatment, or lifestyle changes can make a real difference.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Sun, 14 Sep 2025 14:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi2wFBVV95cUxNRVVCenVVV0NqaGJ4c2tDcy1pMVZ4MlNjc3FsMVRLM1B6X0NIV1lwdVhKV1pYQ3Q3Qmx4cnI2U2d2VWk3MDgwQ0tsSWhyc0xVSks2aU9ycW9IaDdKMDlvWkw2ZlBTS2tjTEVKeDZyejBXSXBlNWZLYzNZVThKZjlyclB5a00xc0ktRDRIRDNGaFhUbWxwUHZVV2paT3ZtaHBPR0xYbjM2Nk5haE1zNG5YVEtnNXhra1FmV1p2dlJCV1dSTFo0ZFFOc1JJVXpVMkpobVUtSkpQM2dZR3PSAeMBQVVfeXFMUGZEYUc1ci1UT2Ztam82Q3ZfTDR0R0U5cUFUcE5CdTdxbEc2UWR1UU53anphbkl6YVRjY05qNDJvYi1rOXNBUnVJdm81bGxsckF6TXIzXzUxdWRvbWoxOTdDVF9Ma243alFOSWIza3M1bUI1eE1Ba3k0NDRSWlhIalpiaGdvQ2dfVmRSUlJFSEkzSmZuamE3NWpTMnMyN05xdlBKaHlfTjAzWFhvQ2NmM0dYVlJvb2NyRU9lRGdJNlE3ZUktQTNfY2xEOWtITE5mQ29udFczakpDWS1vb09HbFJpQnc</guid></item><item><title>在无树岛上意外发现的古老热带雨林- Earth.com</title><link>https://www.earth.com/news/pollen-from-ancient-tropical-forest-accidentally-discovered-on-a-treeless-island/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="page_content__AwOj6"&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Falkland Islands are known today for cool winds, broad grasslands, and very few trees. That modern picture is accurate, but it is not the whole story. Pollen found beneath the capital shows these islands once supported a cool-temperate forest – wet, shaded, and biologically rich.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The clue came from a dark, woody layer uncovered during construction in Stanley. It was not random debris. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was a &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/fossilized-frozen-forest-reveals-climate-impacts-on-ancient-alpine-ecosystems/"&gt;buried forest&lt;/a&gt; bed – plant-heavy sediment preserved in place – holding microscopic grains and real pieces of ancient wood.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-forest-pollen-and-wood-fragments"&gt;Forest pollen and wood fragments&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Scientists collected three kinds of evidence: pollen grains, spores, and chunks of &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/north-americas-oldest-known-pterosaur-eotephradactylus-mcintireae-discovered-arizona/"&gt;fossilized wood&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pollen and spores keep their species-specific shapes for millions of years when they get trapped in wet sediment and then buried. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wood fragments preserve internal features that point to the type of tree and the conditions in which it grew.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This layer is &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/topics/social-sciences/lignite" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;lignitic&lt;/a&gt; – formed as plant material piled up in waterlogged, low-oxygen settings where leaves and twigs do not fully rot. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Over time, that mush compressed into a dense, carbon-rich stratum, likely in a shallow, protected basin near the coast.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-collecting-and-identifying-samples"&gt;Collecting and identifying samples&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;After the discovery, Dr. Zoë Thomas of the &lt;a href="https://www.southampton.ac.uk/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;University of Southampton&lt;/a&gt; hurried to the site with colleagues to salvage fresh samples before they dried and cracked. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The tree remains were so pristinely preserved they looked like driftwood,” recalled Dr. Thomas.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the lab, the team separated tiny grains from the sediment and examined them under high magnification. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The mix showed southern beech (&lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/topics/agricultural-and-biological-sciences/nothofagus" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Nothofagus&lt;/a&gt;) and podocarps – Southern Hemisphere conifers – alongside moisture-loving plants that thrive in soggy ground. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The fossil pollen, spores, and wood paint a much different picture of the ancient environment, providing direct evidence of cool, wet forests,” noted Michael Donovan, collections manager at &lt;a href="https://www.fieldmuseum.org/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Chicago’s Field Museum&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-reading-the-forest-s-pollen-and-wood"&gt;Reading the forest’s pollen and wood&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pollen alone can be misleading because wind can carry it far. That is why the wood matters. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/giant-trees-never-seen-before-up-to-3000-years-old-tessmannia-princeps-tasmania/"&gt;Wood anatomy&lt;/a&gt; – cell sizes, pits, and rays – helps confirm whether pieces came from conifers or broadleaf trees and whether the community matches the pollen record. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Here, it does. The agreement points to a local forest, not distant pollen that drifted in.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Modern relatives of Nothofagus and &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Podocarpus" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;podocarps&lt;/a&gt; form cool, mossy forests in parts of southern Chile and Patagonia. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Their presence in the Falklands’ fossil record supports the idea that the islands once held a wet, shaded habitat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-dating-the-forest-fossils"&gt;Dating the forest fossils&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Radiocarbon dating tops out around 50,000 years, so the team turned to regional comparison. They lined up the Falklands’ pollen ‘cast’ with well-dated South American records. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When the same key pollen types appear and fade in the same order across sites, timelines can be matched.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Those comparisons point to the mid-to-late Cenozoic – tens of millions of years ago – when warmer intervals let rainforests extend to higher latitudes and outlying islands.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wp-block-image"&gt;&lt;figure class="aligncenter size-full"&gt;&lt;a href="https://cff2.earth.com/uploads/2025/09/13202756/ancient-forest_treeless-island_falklands_pollen-discovered_1m.jpg"&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" decoding="async" src="https://cff2.earth.com/uploads/2025/09/13202803/ancient-forest_treeless-island_falklands_pollen-discovered_1s.webp" alt="Selected photomicrographs of fossil pollen produced in an ancient forest by gymnosperm and angiosperm living relatives in the rainforest of southern South America. Credit: Antarctic Science" class="wp-image-1985897" srcset="https://cff2.earth.com/uploads/2025/09/13202803/ancient-forest_treeless-island_falklands_pollen-discovered_1s.webp 300w, https://cff2.earth.com/uploads/2025/09/13202803/ancient-forest_treeless-island_falklands_pollen-discovered_1s-150x150.webp 150w, https://cff2.earth.com/uploads/2025/09/13202803/ancient-forest_treeless-island_falklands_pollen-discovered_1s-32x32.webp 32w" sizes="(max-width: 300px) 100vw, 300px"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;figcaption class="wp-element-caption"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Selected photomicrographs of fossil pollen produced in an ancient forest by gymnosperm and angiosperm living relatives in the rainforest of southern South America. Click image to enlarge. Credit: Antarctic Science&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-pollen-explains-the-disappearing-forest"&gt;Pollen explains the disappearing forest&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Islands get new species in bursts. Seeds and spores ride wind, float on ocean debris, and travel with birds. During milder, wetter stretches, the odds of survival jump. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Once early trees took root in a sheltered, waterlogged basin, they could trap moisture, calm ground-level winds, and gradually build a stable community.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That is a familiar pattern in island biology. Given time and the right conditions, a few arrivals can turn into a functioning forest.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The climate shifted. Cooling trends and glacial cycles brought colder, windier conditions. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Falklands lack high mountains to block strong westerlies or snag extra rainfall, and many soils are thin and peaty. Those factors make it hard for trees to outcompete grasses today.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ecosystems do not just follow latitude. Local wind, rainfall, and topography set the rules. Under the current rules, &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/mountain-greening-threatens-genetic-diversity-of-iconic-plants/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;open grassland&lt;/a&gt; wins across most of the islands.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-why-does-any-of-this-matter"&gt;Why does any of this matter?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fossil evidence gives climate scientists real targets for testing models. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If a model run with mid-to-late &lt;a href="https://ucmp.berkeley.edu/cenozoic/cenozoic.php" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Cenozoic&lt;/a&gt; conditions places a cool-temperate rainforest on the Falklands, that is a sign it is on track. If it does not, something is missing. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These checks turn evidence from a single site into valuable test data.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There is also a wider lesson. Ecosystems can move, shrink, expand, or appear in places that seem unusual by today’s standards. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Falklands’ buried forest shows how temperature, rainfall, and wind can reshuffle living communities over long spans of time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-building-the-case"&gt;Building the case&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fieldwork documented and sampled the lignitic layer in place. Lab work isolated pollen and spores, then identified them under microscopes. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wood pieces were sectioned to reveal diagnostic features. Together, those signals established both habitat and local origin.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For age, researchers matched the Falklands’ pollen sequence to dated South American profiles, tracking the same marker taxa as they rose and fell. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That approach pinned the layer to a deep time window without relying on radiocarbon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-what-have-we-learned"&gt;What have we learned?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;To sum it all up, hidden beneath Stanley on the Falkland Islands lies a pollen record of a cool, wet forest dominated by southern beech and podocarp relatives, growing in a sheltered, waterlogged basin. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The age falls in the mid-to-late Cenozoic, when warmer intervals allowed trees to push farther poleward and onto islands. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This clear snapshot – written in pollen, spores, and wood – adds a useful data point to Earth’s climate history and helps scientists check the tools we use to understand past, present, and future change.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The full study was published in the journal &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cambridge.org/core/journals/antarctic-science/article/evidence-for-a-floristically-diverse-rainforest-on-the-falkland-archipelago-in-the-remote-south-atlantic-during-the-mid-to-late-cenozoic/B4CFF913DD8F1BB43B570E4086C7CF7B" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Antarctic Science&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;—–&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Like what you read? &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/subscribe/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Subscribe to our newsletter&lt;/a&gt; for engaging articles, exclusive content, and the latest updates.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Check us out on &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/earthsnap/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;EarthSnap&lt;/a&gt;, a free app brought to you by &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/author/eralls/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Eric Ralls&lt;/a&gt; and Earth.com.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;—–&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Earth.com</author><pubDate>Sun, 14 Sep 2025 14:07:02 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMirAFBVV95cUxNWDRmcXpXZVZiNEZuMHBpUmVVZXMzTmRYaDAtZ1pfbnF1Y0VxQ1NGVU45djBNMkVRUTJTR1E3dVo2ZUUwSXJEMXlrbXRzU1Jpc1ZOWWQ5WXBjMHRFZ2V5UmwtTGNwSkhxRV80a1lSM0t6TzFRZWl5X3JjQlNpTlFEU3loenpaNjNTRXdETkxKcFFJZ1dyLTktWFlod0pucVRYbmRtS2V1WE45Qnpt</guid></item><item><title>放弃超加工食品可能很难。从这里开始。-《华尔街日报》</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/health/wellness/ditching-ultraprocessed-foods-can-be-hard-heres-where-to-start-c37728d7</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Wall Street Journal</author><pubDate>Sun, 14 Sep 2025 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiqwFBVV95cUxNV254eV8yV3MwV3czSFBtYzhMR2NwTzdkYVhmNFFPaDNyMWZDZkFhbmdqVUNSWUlubEZSU3dNZ1VVeHdheUV1a1o4YlltbzIxSnhoNW50OUNyQjdUN2VYOWdVcm1NakNzd21sNFdnNnFZczZMX1V3cEctQ2FpLUl5RENUN3lEeTloaDB1MmV2NjVRZ2VnN1hMcWxqd3c0dV9pUllvaEtFSUdzeUU</guid></item><item><title>科学家在新研究中揭示了杀死癌细胞的单一运动-每日邮报</title><link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-15088973/single-exercise-kills-breast-cancer-cells-scientists-reveal.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div itemprop="articleBody"&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;It's the most tried and true health advice: regular exercise is key to warding off obesity, aging and chronic diseases. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Mountains of research also shows working out just a few days a week could slash the risk of dying from &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/cancer/index.html" id="mol-d5d8c730-8f1e-11f0-8349-2b5d94e39299"&gt;cancer&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;However, a new study has &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/health/article-15039727/workout-two-decades-life-heart-health-cardio.html"&gt;pinpointed a specific workout routine&lt;/a&gt; shown to slow the growth of cancer cells, even after just one session. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Researchers in Australia recruited women who had survived breast cancer and had them undergo a single bout of either resistance training, such as weightlifting, or high-intensity interval training (HIIT), which involves short, intense bursts of exercise followed by short breaks. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;They found that immediately after one 45-minute resistance training or HIIT routine, participants showed up to 47 percent higher myokines in their blood. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Myokines are proteins released by skeletal muscle cells during exercise that help muscles communicate with the rest of the body. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;They have also been shown to regulate metabolism and suppress molecules that cause inflammation, a key driver in cancer cell formation.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The team estimated that the increased myokines produced may slow cancer growth by 20 to 30 percent.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Researchers in Australia found resistance training and high-intensity interval training (HIIT) may slow cancer cell growth (stock image) &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    
    
    &lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Francesco Bettariga, lead study researcher and PhD student at Edith Cowan University in Australia, told the Daily Mail: 'By demonstrating anti-cancer effects at the cellular level, our results provide a potential explanation for why exercise reduces the risk of cancer progression, recurrence, and mortality. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'While our study has limitations and further in vivo work is needed, these findings highlight how exercise could contribute to improved survival outcomes in people with cancer.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The study, published earlier this summer in the journal &lt;a target="_blank" class="" rel="nofollow" href="https://link.springer.com/article/10.1007/s10549-025-07772-w"&gt;Breast Cancer Research and Treatment&lt;/a&gt;, looked at 32 patients who had been treated for breast cancer, ranging from stage one to stage three, at least four months beforehand. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The largest cancer stage group was stage two (41 percent). &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The average participant age was 59 with a body mass index (BMI) of 28, which is considered overweight but not obese. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Participants in the resistance training group completed eight repetitions of five sets of exercises for major muscle groups. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;These included chest press, seated row, shoulder press, lateral pulldown, leg press, leg extension, leg curl and lunges. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Participants in this group got one to two minutes between sets to rest. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In the HIIT group, participants performed seven 30-second bouts of high-intensity exercise on at least three of the following exercise machines: stationary bike, treadmill, rower and cross-trainer. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;They had three-minute rest periods between sets. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Bettariga told this website: 'We selected two distinct exercise modalities—resistance and aerobic training—because they provide different physiological benefits: resistance training improves muscle strength, while aerobic training enhances cardiorespiratory fitness in order to determine which exercise could drive greater cancer-suppressive effects. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Specifically, we used a high-intensity exercise to determine whether greater intensity could amplify these anti-cancer effects.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Both groups completed about 45 minutes of exercise in total. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Researchers also performed blood tests on participants at three separate times: before working out, immediately following the sessions and 30 minutes after working out. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The team found that completing either the resistance or HIIT regimen just one time increased levels of myokines in participants' blood.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The largest jump was in the myokine IL-6, which increased 47 percent in the HIIT group immediately after exercise. Myokine IL-6 is a protein released from muscles during exercise that plays a crucial role in immune function. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Meanwhile, the resistance group showed a 23 percent increase in decorin, a myokin that regulates tissue growth, and a nine percent increase in IL-6. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The team found myokine levels gradually decreased over time after participants finished working out, though they remained elevated. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Based on results, researchers estimated the myokine levels produced from exercising could reduce the growth of cancer cells by 20 to 30 percent. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Myokines have been shown to suppress inflammatory proteins called cytokines. Cytokines are secreted by immune cells to control inflammation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;However, high cytokine levels can trigger excess inflammation, which damages cell DNA and increases the risk of cancer cells forming. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Breast cancer is one of the most common forms of the disease, striking 311,000 US women every year and killing 42,000 (stock image)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;A recent study in JAMA found that breast cancer rates went up by about 0.79 percent each year during the study from from 2000 to 2019&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Bettariga said: 'We found that both resistance training and HIIT increased the release of myokines with anti-cancer properties after just a single exercise session. We then observed a reduction of up to 30 percent in cancer cell growth in [lab testing]. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'What stood out was that both modalities had comparable effects, suggesting that exercise intensity is the main driver of these anti-cancer changes, rather than the specific type of exercise performed.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Breast cancer strikes 311,000 American women every year and kills 42,000, according to the American cancer society. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;While the disease generally has a high survival rate of 92 percent, that rate can drop as low as 33 percent if cancer cells spread to other areas.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;It's also on the rise among young women, with rates increasing by 0.8 percent every year from 2000 to 2019, &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/health/article-14177967/breast-cancer-rising-doctors-warn-american-women-report.html"&gt;one study suggests&lt;/a&gt;. Experts have tied this rise to hormone-disrupting chemicals and early menstruation, which can increase exposure to hormones like estrogen that can fuel breast cancer. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Though the new study results are promising for breast cancer, it's unclear if they would translate to other forms of the disease. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Bettargia said: 'Breast cancer is the most common cancer among women and the leading cause of cancer-related death in women. Surprisingly, no studies with this specific design had been conducted in this population, making our findings highly relevant to millions of women living with breast cancer.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;There were several limitations, including the small sample size and focusing on only one form of cancer. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Bettariga told this website that the team next plans to investigate these effects in other types of cancer and groups of people with the disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;He said: 'Furthermore, it is now time to examine the effects of regular, long-term exercise programs on these anti-cancer responses. We also aim to explore additional mechanisms particularly the role of the immune system, which plays a crucial part in controlling cancer cell growth.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
            

            
            
            
            
            &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Daily Mail</author><pubDate>Sun, 14 Sep 2025 13:37:10 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMitwFBVV95cUxOYWVZalhsS3AzeXppYUwzZmIxSTRGSDJud2hjeHZNamdDSWVCd3NXaE5BbEViVnM5dGZTVHktcWhadXVVMHFncXJLMmFELXhLV2RfcDVqbnhiaFFrYl9OeVhJd3BNQ0hIYlk3R0JSMndneUFmZ1BZbnVQRzdpbmZMeDdVeG5aRmp2QzktQVAzR2VnUEhaZHZTRURvWGlvTU4xMC1CdnZ3NFhfRmx3MC1TWjhUVG53OTjSAbwBQVVfeXFMTjdmQjUtT01xTVRXRktlMkVfUk9tc1Y2eTZXNGxpUEp3SVhPMXBaTkFSS2kzY05VU1ZHUDZNOFV2QmpZYmlOMWxYaUUzRGtmWlhPMjVneHN5V1dFTU9FREVfTkRvUnl0alRWemEyU242bEpkdHlrN1JwMk45SF80d3Y0aWktZlRGYURXLWF1SjdxTl91MHRmOC1kaUxEWGxQRXFoZEJGUERWcFpVSWlIMXBuMWg2cVVYa0dSTGU</guid></item><item><title>科学家在新研究中揭示了杀死癌细胞的单一运动-每日邮报</title><link>http://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-15088973/single-exercise-kills-breast-cancer-cells-scientists-reveal.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div itemprop="articleBody"&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;It's the most tried and true health advice: regular exercise is key to warding off obesity, aging and chronic diseases. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Mountains of research also shows working out just a few days a week could slash the risk of dying from &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/cancer/index.html" id="mol-d5d8c730-8f1e-11f0-8349-2b5d94e39299"&gt;cancer&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;However, a new study has &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/health/article-15039727/workout-two-decades-life-heart-health-cardio.html"&gt;pinpointed a specific workout routine&lt;/a&gt; shown to slow the growth of cancer cells, even after just one session. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Researchers in Australia recruited women who had survived breast cancer and had them undergo a single bout of either resistance training, such as weightlifting, or high-intensity interval training (HIIT), which involves short, intense bursts of exercise followed by short breaks. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;They found that immediately after one 45-minute resistance or HIIT session, participants showed up to 47 per cent more myokines in their blood. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Myokines are proteins released by skeletal muscle cells during exercise that help muscles communicate with the rest of the body. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;They have also been shown to regulate metabolism and suppress molecules that cause inflammation, a key driver in cancer cell formation.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The team estimated that the increased myokines produced may slow cancer growth by 20 to 30 per cent.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Researchers in Australia found resistance training and high-intensity interval training (HIIT) may slow cancer cell growth&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    
    
    &lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Francesco Bettariga, lead study researcher and PhD student at Edith Cowan University in Australia, told the Daily Mail: 'By demonstrating anti-cancer effects at the cellular level, our results provide a potential explanation for why exercise reduces the risk of cancer progression, recurrence, and mortality. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'While our study has limitations and further in vivo work is needed, these findings highlight how exercise could contribute to improved survival outcomes in people with cancer.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The study, published earlier this summer in the journal &lt;a target="_blank" class="" rel="nofollow" href="https://link.springer.com/article/10.1007/s10549-025-07772-w"&gt;Breast Cancer Research and Treatment&lt;/a&gt;, looked at 32 patients who had been treated for breast cancer, ranging from stage one to stage three, at least four months beforehand. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The largest cancer stage group was stage two (41 per cent). &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The average participant age was 59 with a body mass index (BMI) of 28, which is considered overweight but not obese. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Participants in the resistance training group completed eight repetitions of five sets of exercises for major muscle groups. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;These included chest press, seated rows, shoulder press, lateral pulldowns, leg press, leg extensions, leg curls and lunges. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Participants in this group got one to two minutes between sets to rest. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In the HIIT group, participants performed seven 30-second bouts of high-intensity exercise on at least three of the following exercise machines: stationary bike, treadmill, rower and cross-trainer. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;They had three-minute rest periods between sets. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Bettariga told this website: 'We selected two distinct exercise modalities—resistance and aerobic training—because they provide different physiological benefits: resistance training improves muscle strength, while aerobic training enhances cardio-respiratory fitness in order to determine which exercise could drive greater cancer-suppressive effects. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Specifically, we used a high-intensity exercise to determine whether greater intensity could amplify these anti-cancer effects.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Both groups completed about 45 minutes of exercise in total. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Researchers also performed blood tests on participants at three separate times: before working out, immediately following the sessions and 30 minutes after working out. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The team found that completing either the resistance or HIIT regimen just one time increased levels of myokines in participants' blood.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The largest jump was in the myokine IL-6, which increased 47 per cent in the HIIT group immediately after exercise. IL-6 is a protein released from muscles during exercise that plays a crucial role in immune function. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Meanwhile, the resistance group showed a 23 per cent increase in decorin, a myokin that regulates tissue growth, and a nine per cent increase in IL-6. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The team found myokine levels gradually decreased over time after participants finished working out, though they remained elevated. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Based on results, researchers estimated the myokine levels produced from exercising could reduce the growth of cancer cells by 20 to 30 per cent. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Myokines have been shown to suppress inflammatory proteins called cytokines. Cytokines are secreted by immune cells to control inflammation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;However, high cytokine levels can trigger excess inflammation, which damages cell DNA and increases the risk of cancer cells forming. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Breast cancer is one of the most common forms of the disease, striking 311,000 US women every year and killing 42,000&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;A recent study in JAMA found that breast cancer rates went up by about 0.79 per cent each year from 2000 to 2019&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Bettariga said: 'We found that both resistance training and HIIT increased the release of myokines with anti-cancer properties after just a single exercise session. We then observed a reduction of up to 30 per cent in cancer cell growth in [lab testing]. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'What stood out was that both modalities had comparable effects, suggesting that exercise intensity is the main driver of these anti-cancer changes, rather than the specific type of exercise performed.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Breast cancer strikes 311,000 American women every year and kills 42,000, according to the American Cancer Society. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;While the disease generally has a high survival rate of 92 per cent, that rate can drop as low as 33 per cent if cancer cells spread to other areas.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;It's also on the rise among young women, with rates increasing by 0.8 per cent every year from 2000 to 2019, &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/health/article-14177967/breast-cancer-rising-doctors-warn-american-women-report.html"&gt;one study suggests&lt;/a&gt;. Experts have tied this rise to hormone-disrupting chemicals and early menstruation, which can increase exposure to hormones like estrogen that can fuel breast cancer. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Though the new study results are promising for breast cancer, it's unclear if they would translate to other forms of the disease. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Bettargia said: 'Breast cancer is the most common cancer among women and the leading cause of cancer-related death in women. Surprisingly, no studies with this specific design had been conducted in this population, making our findings highly relevant to millions of women living with breast cancer.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;There were several limitations, including the small sample size and the focus on only one form of cancer. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Bettariga told this website that the team next plans to investigate these effects in other types of cancer and groups of people with the disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;He said: 'It is now time to examine the effects of regular, long-term exercise programs on these anti-cancer responses. We also aim to explore additional mechanisms, particularly the role of the immune system, which plays a crucial part in controlling cancer cell growth.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
            

            
            
            
            
            &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Daily Mail</author><pubDate>Sun, 14 Sep 2025 13:37:10 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMitgFBVV95cUxPdVBYb0p4U011MXl6c2FCcWU0eFQ1NmcyZ1BRRGMyTlRaaWxHbFJYWW9SOURVaVgwSmd6eTRpUjg0X1BfOVYwd3FTQWdpcWdqQjVkOUpnOE5BeTkzR0JoMU1ST3N2dVBmMlc4bk9ueG9xRWJybXljcjJHcW9neXhNLTRGMVQzb0xvYXcyU3NLYTAwaEUxd3Zuc2F4YVpRWURjVEppUGFBZjczQzVRelFfLUhXLUtZQdIBvAFBVV95cUxON2ZCNS1PTXFNVFdGS2UyRV9ST21zVjZ5Nlc0bGlQSndJWE8xcFpOQVJLaTNjTlVTVkdQNk04VXZCalliaU4xbFhpRTNEa2ZaWE8yNWd4c3lXV0VNT0VERV9ORG9SeXRqVFZ6YTJTbjZsSmR0eWs3UnAyTjlIXzR3djRpaS1mVEZhRFctYXVKN3FOX3UwdGY4LWRpTERYbFBFcWhkQkZQRFZwWlVJaUgxcG4xaDZxVVhrR1JMZQ</guid></item><item><title>《每日邮报》揭示了过去100年来最好和最差的饮食时尚……以及始终有效的“老式可靠” --《每日邮报》</title><link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-15063169/Daily-Mail-reveals-best-worst-diet-fads-100-years-old-reliable-works.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div itemprop="articleBody"&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In the US, about 41 percent of the population is overweight or obese; and about 20 percent of Americans are on a diet in a bid to lose that weight or keep their trim figure.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Long before the advent of weight-loss drugs like Ozempic and Wegovy, people turned to strict diets to drop pounds, and dieting in the Western world, specifically focused on weight loss and physique change, began to gain traction in the 19th century, notably with William Banting's influential 1863 diet guide.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Banting, who was a funeral director living in &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/london/index.html" id="mol-9c0d0d50-7e06-11f0-89a6-d1f846923610"&gt;London&lt;/a&gt; during the mid-19th century, claimed to have lost 52 pounds and &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/health/article-15024677/Hidden-body-fat-skinny-ageing-heart.html"&gt;more than 13 inches&lt;/a&gt; from his waist in one year by adhering to a low-carb diet after three decades of struggling with his weight.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;By 1862, at the age of 64, Banting was obese - weighing 202lbs at 5ft 5in with a BMI of 33.6 - so he decided to give up bread, butter, milk, sugar, beer and potatoes and live on mainly animal protein, fruit and non-starchy vegetables. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Astounded by the results, he printed his &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/weight_loss/index.html" id="mol-1b65f430-7e08-11f0-89a6-d1f846923610" class=""&gt;weight loss&lt;/a&gt; secrets in a booklet titled 'Letter On Corpulence, Addressed To The Public,' which is considered one of the first diet guides.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;However, the idea of controlling diet for health purposes has ancient roots, appearing in Ancient &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/greece/index.html" id="mol-b9ce00a0-8906-11f0-aaff-8f9f7f932f69"&gt;Greece&lt;/a&gt; and through religious fasting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The 20th century further popularized dieting as a health and beauty craze, particularly the aesthetic ideal of thinness that emerged in the early 1900s, leading to the creation of the diet culture we know today. And with the accessibility of ingredients and products easier than ever, the variety of diets is vast. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Here DailyMail.com speaks to a number of health experts to get their verdicts on the best and worst diets launched over the past century and the old reliable that has stood the test of time. Surprisingly, none of the diets mention calorie counting, and  instead the experts focus on the content and quality of foods.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Dieting in the Western world, specifically focused on weight loss and physique change, began to gain traction in the 19th century, notably with William Banting's influential 1863 diet guide&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Obesity rates by state in the US as of 2023 - the latest data available&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    
    
    &lt;h2 class="mol-para-with-font mol-style-subhead health-ccox"&gt;THE WORST &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font mol-style-bold"&gt;JUICE CLEANSES: 1/10&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;While juice cleanses have become all the rage over the past decade or so after gaining mainstream popularity in the 1990s and 2000s, many health experts are less excited about the concept. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Unlike other diets, a juice cleanse is a temporary dietary regimen that involves consuming only fruit and vegetable juices for a predetermined period, typically ranging from a few days to a week.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;It is often promoted as a way to detoxify the body, lose weight, and improve overall health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;New York-based personal trainer Natalie Alex told this website: 'More recently overly restrictive "detoxes" or juice cleanses often promise quick fixes but leave people depleted, with results that rarely last. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'These fads tend to ignore balance and sustainability, which is why people so often rebound after them.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Similarly, New York dermatologist Dr Michele Green isn't a fan of juice cleanses and she gives them just a one out of 10. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Unlike other diets, a juice cleanse is a temporary dietary regimen that involves consuming only fruit and vegetable juices for a predetermined period, typically ranging from a few days to a week&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;She added: 'Detox diets, including juice cleanses and liquid cleanses, are also not sustainable and often do not provide enough daily nutrients. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'These extreme diets lack scientific support. Additionally, the body is equipped with mechanisms and organs that effectively flush out potential toxins without the need for detox diets.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The National Center for Complementary and Integrative Health also warns of the dangers of juice cleanses, with some of the side effects including 'dangerous electrolyte imbalances', headaches, fainting, weakness, and dehydration.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font mol-style-bold"&gt;THE KETO DIET: 2/10&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Many health experts Daily Mail spoke to rated the keto diet as one of the worst eating regimens from the past century. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The diet was first introduced in the 1920s as a treatment for epilepsy by Dr Russell Wilder at the Mayo Clinic in Minnesota. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;It was designed to mimic the effects of fasting by drastically reducing carbohydrate intake and increasing fat consumption. This helps to manage epilepsy by inducing a metabolic state called ketosis, when the body burns fat energy instead of glucose. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Ketosis has been shown to have an anti-seizure effect in people with epilepsy, though the mechanism behind the connection is not fully understood. It could be a change in brain chemistry, change in neuronal activity or improvement in cell function. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The diet encourages followers to eat butter, avocado, coconut, bacon, cream, cheese and some nuts but avoid grains, milk, yogurt, most fruits, legumes, potatoes and many vegetables.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;The Keto diet encourages the consumption of meats, butter and cheese&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;According to the Dietitian's Association of Australia, keto diet isn't recommended for the general population as the long-term efficacy and safety of the diet are unknown, having only been studied in the short-term.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Sophie Scott, who is a nutritionist based out of Australia, gave the keto diet a two out of 10 in terms of its effectiveness. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;She told this website: 'Keto forces the body to use fat (or more specifically, ketones) as the main fuel source instead of glucose.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Carbohydrates are severely restricted to around 50g per day (equivalent to two slices of bread and a banana) and fat constitutes 70 percent of this diet.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The American Heart Association also does not recommend the diet for long-term success. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Experts from the organization explain: 'In studies up to six months long, improvements in body weight and blood sugar have been shown with these diets. However, after a year, most improvements were no different from the results of a less restrictive diet. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Restrictions on fruits, whole grains and legumes may result in reduced fiber intake. Additionally, these diets are high in fat without limiting saturated fat. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Consuming high levels of saturated fat and low levels of fiber are both linked to the development of cardiovascular disease.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font mol-style-bold"&gt;SOUTH  BEACH DIET: 3/10&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;&lt;p class="clear"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;The South Beach Diet focuses on eliminating refined carbs and prioritizing healthy fats like olive oil&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The South Beach Diet was developed in the mid-1990s by Dr Arthur Agatston, a cardiologist, to help his patients with heart disease and diabetes. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;It gained widespread popularity in 2003 with the release of his best-selling book, The South Beach Diet, which explained the diet's principles for weight loss and improved health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The diet focuses on eliminating refined carbs and prioritizing healthy fats like olive oil. However, the experts warn that like keto, it can be restrictive and for this reason, they give it a three out of 10.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The first phase, which lasts for 14 days, involves eating three meals and two snacks daily, mainly protein and non-starchy vegetables.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;After that, participants add small amounts of whole grains and fruits, as well as small amounts of alcohol. This phase lasts as long as it takes you to reach your goal weight.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In the final phase, no food is off limits, but participants pay strict attention to serving sizes. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The South Beach Diet says that you'll lose 8lbs to 13lbs during phase one, with most of the weight coming from your midsection. In phase two, it says that you'll likely lose 1lb to 2lbs per week.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;There is no research suggesting that the South Beach diet leads to long-term weight loss.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Sharon Palmer, a dietitian at the Plant-Powered Dietitian, said: 'This diet would be hard to follow in the context of cultural diets, and it reinforces diet culture. I would not recommend this diet overall for weight loss.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mol-para-with-font mol-style-subhead health-ccox"&gt;THE BEST &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font mol-style-bold"&gt;THE MEDITERRANEAN DIET: 9/10&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;The Mediterranean diet is rich in fruit, vegetables, wholegrains, legumes and olive oil, and features moderate amounts of fish and poultry - and the occasional glass of red wine&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Long touted by health experts as the secret to a lengthy, healthy life, the Mediterranean diet has been crowned one of the healthiest nutritional plans for promoting an approach to healthy eating.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The concept of the Mediterranean diet was first coined in the 1960s by American biologist Ancel Keys, but its origins trace back to ancient times. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;It's rich in fruit, vegetables, wholegrains, legumes and olive oil, and features moderate amounts of fish and poultry - and the occasional glass of red wine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The diet eliminates added sugars, refined grains like white breads and pasta, trans fats like in margarine, canola oil and processed meat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Nutritionist Sophie Scott told Daily Mail: 'The diet is a 10 out of 10 because it is more of an eating pattern, rather than a prescriptive diet, which makes it easier to follow consistently than other more restrictive diets.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;She referenced a research paper that found the diet consistently performs well in relation to weight loss, reduction in cardiovascular disease and reduction of depression.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The PREDIMED study, published in the New England Journal of Medicine in 2013, showed the Mediterranean diet group had a third less heart disease, diabetes and stroke than the low-fat group. They also lost a little weight and had less memory loss.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'The benefits can't be narrowed down to one single food or factor but to some general themes,' she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Extra fiber, a diverse range of fruits and vegetables, whole grains and legumes, yoghurts and cheese, small amounts of fish and meat, red wine, nuts and seeds and good quality olive oil all played their part.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'However, the authors believe that the olive oil itself was the most powerful single factor.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Fitness expert Natalie Alex is also a fan of the Mediterranean diet, as she says it is less of a fad and more of a lifestyle. She gives it a nine out of 10. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;She explained: 'It supports both long-term health and enjoyment of food, which is key. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'And on the fitness front, the shift toward higher-protein, strength-supporting nutrition in recent years has been beneficial for people looking to maintain lean mass and metabolic health.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Harvard researchers found that people who followed the DASH diet for 30 years had a 14 percent lower risk of coronary heart disease and strokes&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span class="mol-style-bold"&gt;THE DASH DIET: 8.5/10&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Beloved by many health experts, the DASH diet was introduced in 1997 by NIH-supported research teams and it was designed to reduce high blood pressure. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Studies have since shown that the DASH diet can have positive effects on cardiovascular health and may have other health benefits.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The eating plan encourages eating fruits, vegetables, whole grains, and low-fat dairy products.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;It favors lean sources of protein, like beans and lean meats, and suggests limiting saturated fats and sugar-sweetened food and drinks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Experts at the American Heart Association rate this diet at 8.5 out of 10. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;They explain: 'The DASH-style eating pattern received a perfect score by meeting all of the Association's guidance. These eating patterns are low in salt, added sugar, alcohol, tropical oils and processed foods, and rich in non-starchy vegetables, fruits, whole grains and legumes. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Protein tends to be mostly from plant sources (such as legumes, beans or nuts), along with fish or seafood, lean poultry and meats, and low-fat or fat-free dairy products.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Harvard researchers found that people who followed the diet for 30 years had a 14 percent lower risk of coronary heart disease and strokes compared to people on a standard diet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span&gt;New York cosmetic &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a class="" rel="nofollow noreferrer noopener" target="_blank" href="https://www.michelegreenmd.com/botox-nyc"&gt;dermatologist&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; Dr Michele Green says the DASH diet is also 'excellent' for the skin, as it limits processed sugar and unhealthy fats.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span&gt;'You really notice a glow on this plan,' she adds. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font mol-style-bold"&gt;WEIGHT WATCHERS: 7/10&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Popularized by dozens of celebrities, from Oprah Winfrey to Kate Hudson, Weight Watchers doesn't involve counting calories. Instead, foods are assigned a certain amount of points based on their nutrients&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;At the top of the diet list with many health experts is the old American favorite diet, Weight Watchers. It got a seven out of 10 overall.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Introduced in 1963 by Jean Nidetch in New York, it started as a small social support group for friends to lose weight together and today it has more than 3.4 million subscribers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Popularized by dozens of celebrities, from Oprah Winfrey to Kate Hudson, Weight Watchers doesn't involve counting calories.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Instead, foods are assigned a certain amount of points based on their nutrients, such as fiber, added sugars, protein, and fat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Foods with more unhealthy nutrients like added sugars and fat, and too little of vital compounds like fiber, are assigned more points. Dieters are allotted a specific amount of points to use daily and weekly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Doug Cook, a registered dietitian in Toronto, told US News and World Report: 'Weight Watchers helps people to understand balance in so far that no food is off limits, helping it to be sustainable in the long run. It focuses on wholesome foods like fruits, vegetables, lean proteins, etc.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;A study published in the BMJ involving 740 overweight or obese participants found that those who used Weight Watchers lost the most weight compared to those on other diets, dropping an average of 9.8lbs after 12 weeks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Additionally, in a review of 45 studies, researchers found that after 12 months of Weight Watchers, members lost 2.6 percent more weight than those who received no weight loss guidance or education.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mol-para-with-font mol-style-subhead health-ccox"&gt;THE OLD RELIABLE - 10/10&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Instead of a fad diet or brand, the experts say having a grasp of what eating well looks like is of utmost importance and maintaining a healthy balance&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;When quizzed about which diet has stood the test of time as the 'old reliable,' the health experts revealed a surprising answer: 'just a balanced diet.' &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Instead of a fad diet or costly branded products, they say having a grasp of what eating well looks like is of utmost importance when it comes to keeping in shape. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Los Angeles-based Dr Raj Dasgupta told this website: 'The one approach that never goes out of style is eating a variety of real, unprocessed foods, watching portions, and moving your body. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'It's not flashy, but it's reliable and backed by decades of solid research.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;He recommends stocking up on plenty of fruits and vegetables, lean proteins, whole grains, and healthy fats while limiting ultra-processed foods and added sugars.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Dr Michele Green says from her own experience too, a diet in moderation is the one that has always worked best for her. She says eliminating certain food groups can often lead to people giving up and creating an unhealthy relationship with food. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;She adds: 'While I think it is important to reduce the consumption of sugary foods, sweets do not need to be cut out completely and can be consumed in moderation.' &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Meanwhile, fitness trainer Natalie Alex concludes: 'Looking ahead, I think we'll see less focus on rigid diets and more emphasis on personalized nutrition plans built around someone's lifestyle, preferences, and health needs, instead of strict rules that are hard to follow long-term.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
            

            
            
            
            
            &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Daily Mail</author><pubDate>Sun, 14 Sep 2025 13:35:52 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiwwFBVV95cUxORnAzNExZaXdWZk4tN2ZzdFFmVVJTZzlLV0kzbmU1U1ZFUHNQN1hGMmhtU1FrOG8wR1VOT3VfcFo0dmpFSnNVSXplcmdiMVpvVFB2N1NaSnozb3o4TVdwX3ZVVkxQYjZFc1laaXhJaVVtVlQ2cV8yRkN4NlZITVRnbHl1aUNIOXFiZGRqRWl5T21ZN2lqb3lwdUpyREdFVV95NXNDZ3lOOU5XUGhKR1Y2YXliRjU2ZmhDZlBtYmswb1lPUVHSAcgBQVVfeXFMUEVyZkJFWVBGYWswa3BwdFM5UHdNZGxkcV9raF9tMVEzZmlKMlBjZnp0Ym1VbXJ3SjRWQ0dNN2t6QjZvZ2FFNzNWeTRrV255MUxNRW43Y1F5WlJuRXFSV0tCcE4wMmFYOWJzeGdzcldCX3V3MXhmUUNoV01Xd25iUzE0bEl6VV9mMjRYVVJ1ZFptRXN0WG9NTFNkZFlua1pwdFhzOUhYVUdBeVk1UmhyLUoxT25ZbW1GOG51MlgtbkhGWDZFYlJSeFA</guid></item></channel></rss>