<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>GNews Health</title><link>https://news.google.com/</link><description></description><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>The good news about anxiety - The Washington Post</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMilgFBVV95cUxPXzdIdjVwYWh5LTJJdGdnUFQ1RmxJeFdVRXVwVm0zeGg0WWNnZjZ3bkljTzJ0Q3h3VS1YTTAtLWltLU5RWWgzUFJtTjRDaXhVNkdhU3dnSFVtODk2YWM5dXVqUkEtdHdaNmhWSWRITXNUV2dlTUJOTzFsMEFCeFFvdkItNWZ6U1loZDZEMXBCdnBJajRwdXc?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="meteredContent grid-center"&gt;&lt;div class="teaser-content"&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="6ITLP2JOOZBKPFBMOL2OWBCLL4" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;The first time my improv teacher called me up to act out a scene, my throat clenched and my vision briefly went dim. The thought of performing in front of other people, especially in a way that was meant to be silly, sent my anxiety into the stratosphere.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-subscribe-cta" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="6ZFFVZRRJBDQZKNIQDREGJLXJQ" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;I had signed up for improv to boost my levels of the personality trait of extroversion for a book I was writing about personality change. There was only one problem: My high levels of “neuroticism,” the trait associated with anxiety, immobilized me every time I started to improvise. I felt like everyone could hear my heart pounding; I obsessed over trying to calm down instead of moving the scene forward.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="6ZJS6X7KSNDBFA446ETWRNOYG4" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;For a while, I coped with improv class by trying to will my anxiety away. I got mad at myself for being so nervous during something that was supposed to be fun, and I tried to wave off the butterflies filling my stomach. But it turns out that was the wrong approach. Some psychologists now think a certain amount of anxiety can be useful.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="AAH4HFIJMJARHMXVDZRR7KEKVA" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;A concept called the &lt;a href="https://www.healthline.com/health/yerkes-dodson-law" target="_blank"&gt;Yerkes-Dodson&lt;/a&gt; curve shows that when people have very high levels of anxiety, they don’t tend to perform well. They might be so worried about a big work project that they avoid getting started, for example. But at very low levels of anxiety, performance also suffers: They might be so relaxed that they rush through the project to watch Netflix.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-topic-follow-interstitial" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="ECMW4DD2WNDOJAJ3AGL7ROLPMA" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;“There’s actually the sweet spot in the middle, where anxiety is really adaptive,” or helpful, says Shannon Sauer-Zavala, a clinical psychology professor at the University of Kentucky. At that middle-ground point, anxiety “tells you, ‘This is important, I should pay attention to it, I should prepare for it.’”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="EQ5HMOKLMNFIFOXKD7UJQH6TMY" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Psychologist Tracy Dennis-Tiwary writes in her book &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/Future-Tense-Anxiety-Though-Feels/dp/0063062100" target="_blank"&gt;Future Tense&lt;/a&gt; that anxiety can help narrow attention and heighten focus and detail orientation. It spurs creativity and motivates us to problem-solve. In some studies, people who felt anxious came up with more and better solutions to problems than those who felt calm.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="AZUE45R5TFENJLN5KP5YJUJOXA" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Dennis-Tiwary writes in her book that when her son was diagnosed with a heart condition as a baby, anxiety and worry fueled her efforts to get him help. “Worry pushed me to figure out how to maximize the chances of a successful surgery,” she writes. Her mind racing, she read academic articles about her son’s condition, made lists of questions for his doctors and scoured community forums for information. “In the end,” she writes, “it was the worry that helped us get through.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="KU7TODFIZVA3FK6AMIZO6NWA3A" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Anxiety can be a form of caring, of our minds highlighting what matters. It tells us that accomplishing our goals will require effort, and it pushes us to think about what efforts, exactly, we should take. It motivates us to take action. In one study, people who were somewhat, but not overly, anxious were more likely to pursue follow-up care after a heart transplant — and to survive.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="JYPNQLNHHJHNDBVDAHTZVLG6TQ" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;In other words, you shouldn’t want to live completely free of anxiety, because you need anxiety to get things done.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-header" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;h3 class="wpds-c-iLVUUd wpds-c-iLVUUd-bALvEi-isCenteredLayout-false" data-qa="article-header" data-contentid="DKUY7VDEUJCNJHOLTGEMMZQJUM" data-apitype="header" level="2" id="DKUY7VDEUJCNJHOLTGEMMZQJUM"&gt;Helpful or unhelpful?&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="S3EMFU4DRFDHVFHQIP32GMACMA" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;The line between helpful and unhelpful anxiety is whether it causes what scientists call “functional impairment,” meaning it prevents you from living your life: Doing your job, caring for your family or interacting with other people.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="QEIGNEA5D5C6BJMDUNIEA4TTXI" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;If you feel your worrying is spiraling out of control, Dennis-Tiwary said when I called her, you should make a list of all the things that can go wrong. But also think about all the things that can go right. “Anxiety evolved to help us navigate uncertainty in life,” Dennis-Tiwary told me. “It evolved to help us focus on potential danger in our future. But to also remember that positive outcomes are still possible.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="JCICVNJNNFEJHJBSSRI34NI2OA" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;For me, this was a new way of thinking about anxiety, and by extension, about neuroticism. Which meant if I wanted to deflate my neuroticism the best way to do that would be to listen to my anxiety, rather than to treat it like a pointless affliction and struggle against it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="7M37PRKHWZBNPFIS7PNIJJOZPI" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Anxiety can be almost like a gut instinct, providing information from our subconscious about something bad looming ahead. It can be irrational, but it can also be rational. The trick is to learn from it, then let it move on.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="ZNPJWQEFS5A6JM6SSUJVBXT6SE" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;It’s not just the feeling of anxiety that can be helpful in life. Actually &lt;i&gt;experiencing&lt;/i&gt; a moderate number of stressful situations might be beneficial, as well. Just as you shouldn’t shy away from sometimes feeling anxious, you shouldn’t shy away from situations that might provoke anxiety.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="XMNPE7F5M5CP7B22WFNJSHAQUM" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;“Having a child, getting a new job, winning a sports game or performing in front of people — those are all stressful,” says Jeremy Jamieson, a professor of psychology at the University of Rochester who researches stress. “If we didn’t engage with stress, if we just tried to avoid it, we really wouldn’t do anything that was innovative.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="CPM6OFR7TVB7HCLSEQ3FXQCMZA" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Research on both &lt;a href="https://urldefense.com/v3/__https://escholarship.org/content/qt4b6787gk/qt4b6787gk.pdf__;!!M9LbjjnYNg9jBDflsQ!CBB932IJ9kMjV2Vf7RlLSO7FH8WSXxyFDLNlFOp1MIcDZvu1rVOSTN007IgpUTl4stVjKwr2CeeL4fvoOKcIRBH7$" target="_blank"&gt;humans&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://urldefense.com/v3/__https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/16473950/__;!!M9LbjjnYNg9jBDflsQ!CBB932IJ9kMjV2Vf7RlLSO7FH8WSXxyFDLNlFOp1MIcDZvu1rVOSTN007IgpUTl4stVjKwr2CeeL4fvoOAyJWclW$" target="_blank"&gt;monkeys&lt;/a&gt; has found that enduring a small number of adverse events, such as a loved one’s illness or a parent’s divorce, can result in better mental health than experiencing either lots of adversity — or no adversity at all. Even severe misfortunes, such as bereavement, have an eventual silver lining by contributing to resilience. (Though this number is very approximate, Mark Seery, a psychologist at the University of Buffalo, said his research suggests that five adverse events across a lifetime seems like the happy medium.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="MQSOTDMCZRBTRAK4AN5FZAXQ6Y" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Experience with hardship seems to fortify you for the challenges that inevitably come up in life. Seery compares this “toughening” phenomenon to physical exercise — if you never work out, you’ll never be sore, but you also won’t grow stronger.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-header" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;h3 class="wpds-c-iLVUUd wpds-c-iLVUUd-bALvEi-isCenteredLayout-false" data-qa="article-header" data-contentid="H5QMQXLQHZEB7DNVBYWFAYTNVI" data-apitype="header" level="2" id="H5QMQXLQHZEB7DNVBYWFAYTNVI"&gt;How to cope&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="QFVGZ37KM5FNBHUN4MFUK4WVGM" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;One way to cope with these stressors is to acknowledge that yes, the situation is stressful, but you can handle the stress, because your jitters are giving you fuel. &lt;a href="https://urldefense.com/v3/__https://www.researchgate.net/profile/Brett-Peters/publication/261767554_Rethinking_Butterflies_The_Affective_Physiological_and_Performance_Effects_of_Reappraising_Arousal_During_Social_Evaluation/links/5773d65908aead7ba06e586c/Rethinking-Butterflies-The-Affective-Physiological-and-Performance-Effects-of-Reappraising-Arousal-During-Social-Evaluation.pdf__;!!M9LbjjnYNg9jBDflsQ!CBB932IJ9kMjV2Vf7RlLSO7FH8WSXxyFDLNlFOp1MIcDZvu1rVOSTN007IgpUTl4stVjKwr2CeeL4fvoOK_e1oCd$" target="_blank"&gt;Studies&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://urldefense.com/v3/__https://files.eric.ed.gov/fulltext/ED566260.pdf__;!!M9LbjjnYNg9jBDflsQ!CBB932IJ9kMjV2Vf7RlLSO7FH8WSXxyFDLNlFOp1MIcDZvu1rVOSTN007IgpUTl4stVjKwr2CeeL4fvoOGIZOmJb$" target="_blank"&gt;suggest&lt;/a&gt; that reframing anxiety as a benefit — i.e., anxiety will help me think of the right answer — can help people feel less incapacitated by their &lt;a href="https://urldefense.com/v3/__https://escholarship.org/content/qt9n46p04q/qt9n46p04q_noSplash_350ecfb9ba8515f86d07f5bb36a8f8d5.pdf__;!!M9LbjjnYNg9jBDflsQ!CBB932IJ9kMjV2Vf7RlLSO7FH8WSXxyFDLNlFOp1MIcDZvu1rVOSTN007IgpUTl4stVjKwr2CeeL4fvoOFl6orSc$" target="_blank"&gt;nerves&lt;/a&gt;. When we feel this kind of “good” stress, our heart rate increases and our blood vessels dilate to deliver oxygen to the brain. Our bodies produce anabolic hormones, the kind of hormones that help boost performance. (Meanwhile, “bad” stress occurs when you decide you can’t handle the stressor. In that case, your body floods with hormones like cortisol, which don’t aid performance.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="U6MCJCM62RFXTGJRFX6KZDCIYQ" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Jamieson believes it’s preferable to go into a challenging situation, like a work presentation or first date, feeling a little bit amped than feeling totally calm. You should think to yourself, he says, “My heart’s racing because oxygen is getting to my brain — awesome.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="BLKRVHKQNZGQ5ESJHHGQLHHOX4" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;During the improv “showcase” — a public performance for a few dozen strangers — that took place at the end of the series of improv classes, I could feel my heart drumming and my palms growing icy. This is good, I told myself. This will make me seem more energetic during my performance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="Q7VPCASCSVCVFEATDV4FCVVBNQ" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;We settled into a common type of scene in which someone is extremely unqualified for their job, for which I played a secretary who kept falling asleep at inopportune moments. My fellow improvisers would request to be put through to various big shots, or to have paperwork faxed, and I would dramatically break into a stage-snore.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="ZSYD3VUYHBBIZF523FOIF52AYI" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;I tried to reassure myself that my nerves were lending my performance a kind of manic zaniness. I heard laughs and judged them to be only 60 percent out of pity. Then, our instructor called “scene,” and it was over. Comedy gold? Not quite. But I survived, and I felt proud for having leaped over this hurdle despite my anxiety — and possibly because of it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="5HTVDGQ5FNGCZNBND64QUBO2E4" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;&lt;i&gt;Olga Khazan is the author of “&lt;/i&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/Me-But-Better-Science-Personality/dp/1797192906" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;i&gt;Me, But Better: The Science and Promise of Personality Change&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;i&gt;,” which is being released this month.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 12:31:12 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilgFBVV95cUxPXzdIdjVwYWh5LTJJdGdnUFQ1RmxJeFdVRXVwVm0zeGg0WWNnZjZ3bkljTzJ0Q3h3VS1YTTAtLWltLU5RWWgzUFJtTjRDaXhVNkdhU3dnSFVtODk2YWM5dXVqUkEtdHdaNmhWSWRITXNUV2dlTUJOTzFsMEFCeFFvdkItNWZ6U1loZDZEMXBCdnBJajRwdXc</guid></item><item><title>This Simple Diet Change Could Extend Your Life – Backed by 30 Years of Research - SciTechDaily</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMipgFBVV95cUxQMHBWd2YzQWJBMlpuazliNWlTZUo0ZXhveTBFd1d1Y0NONGd2b3FIV0ctLWk3bVRjcDJzVlB0a3FDdm8tUi1tcVFkSFdRMVZ4M054ZkdfSDMxWkFNVmxGa3VoX3hTbXVqMWZzOHJWdEdDZ1VKdTJmN0s5TXpBY1VMYWo0ZjUxY29jVHRyWGVNSHJtQjFFU1RFUU51RHNlQ01YcThDeDJB?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>SciTechDaily</author><pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 10:34:48 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipgFBVV95cUxQMHBWd2YzQWJBMlpuazliNWlTZUo0ZXhveTBFd1d1Y0NONGd2b3FIV0ctLWk3bVRjcDJzVlB0a3FDdm8tUi1tcVFkSFdRMVZ4M054ZkdfSDMxWkFNVmxGa3VoX3hTbXVqMWZzOHJWdEdDZ1VKdTJmN0s5TXpBY1VMYWo0ZjUxY29jVHRyWGVNSHJtQjFFU1RFUU51RHNlQ01YcThDeDJB</guid></item><item><title>Doctors Are Sharing The Things We Still Don't Know About The Human Body, And It's Fascinating - BuzzFeed</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMif0FVX3lxTE5HX1hUVm04Z1psR2xabXpXUjJCcFFWZWMwcnBEeDFqSkhCZFRYSS1pcm8wMUZMcF84bTdUYnlFOWZpQjZRUWJHLUFQWUpyUzMtNWYyTndsRDFYYnJjT3JmcDhyWEtROGVNLUdYenNWU2xLS2UtQnRCZUJnMUJYMUE?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="subbuzz buzz-width--standard__subbuzz buzz-type--list__subbuzz subbuzz-text
  subbuzz-index-24
  
  
  
  
  " data-keywords="fast fashion" data-module="subbuzz-text"&gt;
  
  &lt;p id="138329100" class="subbuzz-anchor"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



  &lt;h2 class="subbuzz__header subbuzz__header--standard subbuzz__title "&gt;
    

    
      &lt;span class="js-subbuzz__title-text"&gt;I don't know about you guys, but my mind is blown, and now I can't stop thinking about all of the things we simply don't understand. If you're a health professional, what are some things we actually *don't* know about the human body? Let us know in the comments, or you can anonymously share your knowledge using this &lt;a href="https://forms.gle/BJGKEGCk7WnzwQgVA" target="_blank"&gt;form&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/span&gt;
    
  &lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Note: Some submissions have been edited for length and/or clarity.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BuzzFeed</author><pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 10:31:03 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMif0FVX3lxTE5HX1hUVm04Z1psR2xabXpXUjJCcFFWZWMwcnBEeDFqSkhCZFRYSS1pcm8wMUZMcF84bTdUYnlFOWZpQjZRUWJHLUFQWUpyUzMtNWYyTndsRDFYYnJjT3JmcDhyWEtROGVNLUdYenNWU2xLS2UtQnRCZUJnMUJYMUE</guid></item><item><title>How Much You Need To Walk Every Day To Cut Your Risk Of Heart Disease - HuffPost</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMimgFBVV95cUxOZHNOOTR6djE0dE5fT3B1QXpiTGxqbUREaDY3UVBZLTdKMmQ5NTRaUlBzWDFwbVVjZ0NEOHNrOXd0Rkp1ZEZ6Uy1seW1KTDIxNXlNb2RVWVk0dEpURFVhRDhpZnR2dzdqeVNkSWYyVzVpRkFqcy1BdG9tTGhkTS10cnRmMUk5NTdnbWNYQ0FFWEhTNExETWhqTjJn0gGfAUFVX3lxTE5rczZqenRhdXkyMEFYTUNBc2xmMThOY0c1OU1ac2RpRnZISTNZYVNyUEZIS3pZZ1FUd2tZWkJYYjZCbV8taklJYUxFUFBlRTNkVVFWa1R1VGhYUUxLZlVjcmdSbjg3MWxPSi1ZcXNuRmdLVGJwWEduXzRsYnpLdk4zZjdHMmFNSTNqMzlsMHY4Q0JCZlBSbl91aW5UNVhObw?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;section class="entry__content-list js-entry-content js-cet-subunit"&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Walking is a powerful tool for both our physical and mental health ― perhaps even more powerful than we think.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Walking an estimated 21 minutes a day can reduce your risk of heart disease by 30%, according to a &lt;a href="https://www.health.harvard.edu/exercise-and-fitness/walking-for-health" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Harvard Health" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="67d34253e4b0756a721abf18" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.health.harvard.edu/exercise-and-fitness/walking-for-health" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="0"&gt;Harvard Health&lt;/a&gt; special report published in 2017 that &lt;a href="https://www.commwellhealth.org/news/5-surprising-benefits-of-walking" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="has been used often" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="67d34253e4b0756a721abf18" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.commwellhealth.org/news/5-surprising-benefits-of-walking" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="1"&gt;has been used often&lt;/a&gt; to &lt;a href="https://www.wellandgood.com/walking-reduces-heart-disease-risk/" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="underscore the importance of going for a walk" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="67d34253e4b0756a721abf18" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.wellandgood.com/walking-reduces-heart-disease-risk/" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="2"&gt;underscore the importance of going for a walk&lt;/a&gt;. The report also suggests that walking has been “shown to reduce the risk of diabetes and cancer, lower blood pressure and cholesterol, and keep you mentally sharp.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;In other words, walking has serious health benefits, along with being a free workout that doesn’t require any equipment or much planning.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;If that information alone doesn’t convince you to hit the pavement, here are a few other reasons to embrace walking and some advice on how to incorporate more of it into your day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;No matter your age or health history, walking is beneficial.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Walking consistently is a great form of exercise that reduces cardiovascular mortality ... and often correlates to other healthy habits and behaviors,” said &lt;a href="https://my.clevelandclinic.org/staff/23916-tamanna-singh" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Dr. Tamanna Singh" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="67d34253e4b0756a721abf18" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://my.clevelandclinic.org/staff/23916-tamanna-singh" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="3"&gt;Dr. Tamanna Singh&lt;/a&gt;, co-director of the sports cardiology center at Cleveland Clinic.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;And, while walking isn’t associated with the same kind of energy exertion as spin classes or interval runs, it’s just as valuable and can help people of all ages and health backgrounds better their health outcomes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Anyone can benefit from walking,” Singh said. People who have minimal or no cardiovascular risk can prevent disease, while those who deal with things like high blood pressure, high cholesterol, diabetes or obesity can use walking to reach their health goals and prevent future strokes or heart attacks, she added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;In fact, walking is so good for so many different things, the Harvard Health report stated that “the next time you have a medical check-up, don’t be surprised if your doctor hands you a prescription to walk.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure class="cli cli-image js-no-inject"&gt;&lt;p class="cli-image__spacer"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="cli-image__source-wrapper"&gt;&lt;div class="cli-image__credit" aria-label="Image Credit: Sawitree Pamee / EyeEm via Getty Images"&gt;&lt;p class="credit-container"&gt;&lt;span class="credit"&gt;Sawitree Pamee / EyeEm via Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption class="cli-image__caption caption-cli"&gt;Approximately 21 minutes may be the magic number, but short walking bursts each day are beneficial, too.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Walking keeps you from prolonged sitting.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Working from your living room, your kitchen or your office may have its perks (no commuting!) but there are also some disadvantages. Many of us are sitting more than ever because of the current work-from-home lifestyle, and sitting all day can affect our bodies over time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“It’s not so much that chairs are evil and sitting is really bad for you,” Harvard evolutionary biology professor Dan Lieberman &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/entry/sitting-all-day-bad-for-health_l_6022a938c5b6d78d444a1819" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-internal-link" data-vars-item-name="previously told HuffPost" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="67d34253e4b0756a721abf18" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="6022a938c5b6d78d444a1819" data-vars-target-content-type="buzz" data-vars-type="web_internal_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="4"&gt;previously told HuffPost&lt;/a&gt;. “It’s that sitting too much is bad for you if you don’t also exercise.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Singh noted that walking in any capacity keeps you from prolonged sitting, which can only be a health benefit in the long run.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;If you need motivation, try walking with a friend.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Singh said that going for a walk with friends is a great way to create accountability for both you and your walking buddies. Think about it: You’re more likely to lace up your sneakers if your friend is heading over to meet you for a walk you agreed to earlier in the week.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“You’ll each hold each other accountable to developing a walking habit and sticking to it,” Singh said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;And you don’t have to task your friend group with high-stress, quick-paced walks. As long as you get out there, you’re benefiting your body. Plus, if you’re someone who likes to walk and talk, you’ll get some enjoyable conversation and laughter out of a walk with a friend, Singh noted. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You can also listen to music or a podcast on your walk.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you are more of a solo exerciser, Singh suggested that you save a good podcast, audiobook or soundtrack for your walks to make them more enjoyable. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Try telling yourself that you can only listen to these things during your walks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“It’ll get you excited to go on a walk, and [you’ll] get the ‘reward’ of listening to your favorite thing,” Singh said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure class="cli cli-image js-no-inject"&gt;&lt;p class="cli-image__spacer"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="cli-image__source-wrapper"&gt;&lt;div class="cli-image__credit" aria-label="Image Credit: SolStock via Getty Images"&gt;&lt;p class="credit-container"&gt;&lt;span class="credit"&gt;SolStock via Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption class="cli-image__caption caption-cli"&gt;Turn on your favorite podcast to make your walk more interesting.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;If you can’t fit in the full 21 minutes a day, that’s OK.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Between work, errands, family obligations and household chores, life is busy. Taking time for yourself may not be feasible right now and that’s OK. If you can’t fit in the recommended 21 minutes of walking a day, start small. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Even a quick one-minute jaunt pays off,” according to the report by Harvard Health. The report noted that a 2014 study from the University of Utah found that “for every minute of brisk walking that women did throughout the day, they lowered their risk of obesity by 5%.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;So start small. Task yourself with a minute-long walk down your driveway this afternoon, or take that 10-minute work check-in call as you walk around your block. No amount of time is too short.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div id="support-huffpost-entry" class="cli support-huffpost-mid-article primary-cli cli cli-text cli-support-huffpost"&gt;&lt;div class="cli-support-huffpost__content-wrapper"&gt;&lt;h4 class="cli-support-huffpost__title"&gt;Get Our Lifestyle Coverage Ad-Free&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;div class="cli-support-huffpost__container"&gt;&lt;div class="cli-support-huffpost__message-container"&gt;&lt;div class="cli-support-huffpost__message support-huffpost-control"&gt;&lt;p&gt;HuffPost is your trusted source to help you lead a better life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Our reporters rely on research, expert advice and lived experiences. So when you've got questions, you know you can count on our answers. Support our work and &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/support" class="cli-support-huffpost__message__link js-entry-link" data-vars-item-name="enjoy our stories ad-free" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="main" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="/support" data-vars-target-content-type="feed" data-vars-type="web_internal_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="6"&gt;enjoy our stories ad-free&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="cli-support-huffpost__message variation contributor-once-variation"&gt;&lt;p&gt;You've supported HuffPost before, and we'll be honest — we could use your help again. We won't back down from our mission of providing free, fair news during this critical moment. But we can't do it without you.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For the first time, &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/support" class="cli-support-huffpost__message__link js-entry-link" data-vars-item-name="we're offering an ad-free experience" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="main" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="/support" data-vars-target-content-type="feed" data-vars-type="web_internal_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="6"&gt;we're offering an ad-free experience&lt;/a&gt; to qualifying contributors who support our fearless journalism. We hope you'll join us.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="cli-support-huffpost__message variation contributor-canceled-variation"&gt;&lt;p&gt;You've supported HuffPost before, and we'll be honest — we could use your help again. We won't back down from our mission of providing free, fair news during this critical moment. But we can't do it without you.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For the first time, &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/support" class="cli-support-huffpost__message__link js-entry-link" data-vars-item-name="we're offering an ad-free experience" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="main" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="/support" data-vars-target-content-type="feed" data-vars-type="web_internal_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="6"&gt;we're offering an ad-free experience&lt;/a&gt; to qualifying contributors who support our fearless journalism. We hope you'll join us.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;a class="js-entry-link cli-support-huffpost__support-button accent-button" href="https://www.huffpost.com/support" data-vars-item-name-overwritable="support-huffpost" data-vars-item-name="Support HuffPost" data-vars-item-type="button" data-vars-unit-name="main" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="/support" data-vars-target-content-type="feed" data-vars-type="web_internal_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="5"&gt;Support HuffPost&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p class="support-huffpost-login"&gt;Already contributed? &lt;a class="js-entry-link" href="https://login.huffpost.com/login?dest=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.huffpost.com%2Fentry%2Fpreventing-heart-disease-walking-ano_l_67d34253e4b0756a721abf18%3Fhp_auth_done%3D1" data-vars-item-name="Log in to hide these messages" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="67d34253e4b0756a721abf18" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="/login" data-vars-target-content-type="utility" data-vars-type="web_internal_link"&gt;Log in to hide these messages.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Once you feel ready, you can start to incorporate different walking distances and intensities, like speed changes and hills, Singh said. Both of these things, plus “maintaining a consistent habit will likely yield the biggest bang for its buck,” she explained.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>HuffPost</author><pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 07:00:30 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimgFBVV95cUxOZHNOOTR6djE0dE5fT3B1QXpiTGxqbUREaDY3UVBZLTdKMmQ5NTRaUlBzWDFwbVVjZ0NEOHNrOXd0Rkp1ZEZ6Uy1seW1KTDIxNXlNb2RVWVk0dEpURFVhRDhpZnR2dzdqeVNkSWYyVzVpRkFqcy1BdG9tTGhkTS10cnRmMUk5NTdnbWNYQ0FFWEhTNExETWhqTjJn0gGfAUFVX3lxTE5rczZqenRhdXkyMEFYTUNBc2xmMThOY0c1OU1ac2RpRnZISTNZYVNyUEZIS3pZZ1FUd2tZWkJYYjZCbV8taklJYUxFUFBlRTNkVVFWa1R1VGhYUUxLZlVjcmdSbjg3MWxPSi1ZcXNuRmdLVGJwWEduXzRsYnpLdk4zZjdHMmFNSTNqMzlsMHY4Q0JCZlBSbl91aW5UNVhObw</guid></item><item><title>I've spent $300,000 on cosmetic surgeries - these ones ruin your looks - Daily Mail</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiqAFBVV95cUxNclJZU3FDNFdXcVVwUWFaZThPVlFscW1OeGI3d1J5Sm1sckExTHRzYTRBY29neGJQOHJjNXFXd3hMR1hZZENReEhKRkFyTnJpWktvRWJWSXVEUzBsQXpOZ3U1NlJJRmQ5bk51bmtyd1VUS080VVUxSjZuVFMyaDBXQUloel90THAwMkRjSnRJS3lRRGo3X0pVTGNXVTB1Vmt4SDB1SmtsSTg?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div itemprop="articleBody"&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Sandra Lena Silverman knows a thing or two about &lt;a target="_self" href="/health/cosmetic-surgery/index.html" id="mol-61627440-ff55-11ef-8ca4-5f560504ca4b" class=""&gt;cosmetic surgery&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The Miami-based 54-year-old has splashed out $300,000 on more than &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/health/article-14460103/video-Kardashian-family-plastic-surgery.html"&gt;25 procedures&lt;/a&gt; (she's lost count of the exact number) over nearly three decades.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But while Ms Silverman is now regularly complimented for her &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/health/article-14448157/plastic-surgeon-daddy-transformations-surgery-craze.html"&gt;age-defying looks&lt;/a&gt;, it was a long process of trial and error to get the look she wanted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;After doing some minor tweaks in her 20s and 30s - including facials, peels, lasers, &lt;span&gt;Botox, filler, breast augmentation, &lt;/span&gt;rhinoplasty &lt;span&gt;and a vaginal reconstruction - she thought she had been through it all. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span&gt;But then she started feeling especially bad her appearance in her 40s, and when she looked in the mirror, she said it was like 'staring at an old crone, a total Disney witch'. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Ms Silverman is now sharing her insights with Daily Mail readers in the hope that she can prevent people from making the same mistakes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;One in four Americans will undergo some kind of cosmetic work in their lifetime, but some surveys suggest up to six in 10 regret it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Sandra Lena Silverman, who is based in Miami, told DailyMail.com that it was a process of trial and error to look the way she does now at the age of 54&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;&lt;p class="clear"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;The surgery she was most pleased with was her mini facelift, which was done at the same time as a forehead lift, at the age of 47. Above left, before the procedure and right, afterwards &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h2 class="mol-para-with-font mol-style-subhead health-ccox"&gt;&lt;span class="mol-style-italic"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;Vaginal reconstruction left me incontinent&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font mol-style-bold"&gt;PRICE: Up to $20,000 &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Of all of the cosmetic procedures she has tried, Ms Silverman says the vaginal reconstruction she had in her early 40s was the most painful.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Explaining why she opted for the procedure, she says: 'I would argue that my full vaginal reconstruction wasn't cosmetic because my uterus was falling low after the birth of my son, so I actually needed it, but it was the most painful thing I've ever gone through. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'The major issues I faced were incontinence and the fact that I was so loose down there that I couldn't feel anything during sex. It was bad. And not great for my marriage.' &lt;/p&gt;
    
    
    &lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;During the procedure she also had labiaplasty to reduce the size of her labia minora - the skin folds surrounding the urethra and vagina. The entire operation took around six hours.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Although the surgery went well and the results were 'spectacular', Ms Silverman reveals that the recovery was very tough. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;She says: 'I had a catheter for two weeks after the surgery and was prescribed Percocet with Tylenol for the pain, which had the side effect of making me terribly constipated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Words cannot fully describe the pain. Since I had a catheter, I couldn't go to the bathroom, so I had to take [the laxative] MiraLAX. Then I would have explosions. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'I ended up needing to wear a freakin' diaper! Not to mention during that two week period, I had to go to the emergency room three times. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Touching on her own experience with breast implants, Ms Silverman says: 'For my first breast augmentation on my late 20s, the profile was too high and the medium was too large, so I actually ended up looking top-heavy. I eventually got saline implants replaced with silicone and did a breast lift and went smaller and lower'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'My husband was in Las Vegas for much of this, so I was handling it all solo for the most part. Eventually, the doctor changed my pain medication, and that helped a lot. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Once the catheter was out, I was on the mend, but everything down there hurt for a good month.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;While things are '&lt;span&gt;still looking and &lt;/span&gt;feeling great down there' 15 years on, Ms Silverman says for others contemplating the surgery 'if you don't need it, don't do it'.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mol-para-with-font mol-style-subhead health-ccox"&gt;Don't get filler in your 20s and 30s&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font mol-style-bold"&gt;&lt;span class="mol-style-bold"&gt;PRICE:&lt;/span&gt; From $500 to $1,500 per syringe&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Fillers - gel-like substances injected beneath the skin to restore lost volume, smooth lines and enhance facial contours - have become big business because the results are instant with little-to-no down time. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The number of women using fillers has increased close to threefold in the US over the past decade.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In 2010, 1.8 million filler procedures were performed, increasing to 5.3 million in 2023.&lt;/p&gt;
    
    
    &lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The most popular dermal filler brands are Juvederm, Restylane and Sculptra. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;This is because they are made using hyaluronic acid, which is a natural component of the skin, and experts say these brands offer a more natural look.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The most popular areas for dermal fillers include the lips, cheeks, and under-eye areas, and volumes range from 0.25ml for a 'bee sting' look in the lips to up to 3ml per cheek for chiseled cheekbones. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Despite their popularity, Ms Silverman warns against getting fillers too early, as she believes they can age the skin prematurely. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;This is because they can stretch the top layer of skin and users will need to keep replacing this lost volume with yet more filler, leading to a 'puffy' or 'hamster cheek' look. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;She explains: 'Anything that removes fat or stretches out skin is not good for when you age.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Try to stay away from filler in your face when you're in your 20s and 30s.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;She also had one horror story with filler in her lips, where the injector made her look 'like a duck,' so she flags the importance of finding a reputable clinic. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Once damage is done, she says it can take a long time and lots of money to reverse the effects of filler.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Looking back, Ms Silverman says she would have avoided getting filler so early as this led to her needing a facelift.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Now she is older, she is a big fan of the injectables and &lt;span&gt;she has '&lt;/span&gt;gotten them almost everywhere at this point' including in the lips, smile lines, chin, jaw, temples, nose, cheeks, knees, vagina, butt, hands, earlobes, and corners of the mouth.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mol-para-with-font mol-style-subhead health-ccox"&gt;Never do buccal fat removal &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font mol-style-bold"&gt;PRICE: Anywhere from $5,000 to $20,000&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;&lt;p class="clear"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Chrissy Teigen (pictured in May, 2021 on the right) admitted to receiving buccal fat removal in September 2021. Teigen's (pictured in late 2021 on the right) face has a more angular appearance after receiving the procedure&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Buccal fat removal has become a hot procedure over recent years to achieve a more chiseled look. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The procedure involves removing fat pads from inside the cheeks, giving them a more angular face as a result. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Among the most notable A-listers who have had or are &lt;a target="_self" href="/health/article-14044839/plastic-surgeon-celebrities-buccal-fat-removal-surgery.html"&gt;rumored to have had&lt;/a&gt; their buccal fat pads removed is model Chrissy Teigen, who kickstarted a major trend among celebrities and non-celebrities.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;She admitted that she had had her buccal fat removed and also talked about her eyebrow hair transplant.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But other well-known stars including Lea Michele, Bella Hadid, and Anya Taylor-Joy are also believed to have had the procedure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Explaining why she advises against the fashionable tweakment, Ms Silverman says: 'You actually need your buccal fat because as you age, you lose volume in your face.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;With no padding in the cheeks, the beauty expert says people can look too sucked in and gaunt as they get older. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;She warns that then filler is then needed to add volume, and this can change the shape of your face further. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'So make sure that's what you're willing to do,' she concludes. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mol-para-with-font mol-style-subhead health-ccox"&gt;Don't do the 'Y' Lift&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span class="mol-style-bold"&gt;PRICE: Between $2,000 and $7,000 &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The Y Lift, better known as a 'liquid facelift', is a 'facial contouring' technique that uses strategically placed fillers to rejuvenate the face.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;It aim is to restore a youthful 'Y' shape from the cheekbones to the chin, and improve the appearance of wrinkles and sagging skin.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;It can be &lt;span&gt;completed in as little as 30&lt;/span&gt; minutes and the results are immediate, whereas facelifts can take a few weeks to see any results.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But Ms Silverman says getting a Y Lift is something she will 'always regret'. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;She reveals: 'The first time I did it was great - I got filler in the perimeter of my jowls, which was lifting and made me look more sculpted. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'But the second time I did it, I got pie-faced, and by that I mean there was so much filler in my cheeks that I looked completely round, like a pie. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'It caused my skin to stretch and then sag, and it took about two years to fully fix it because the filler goes deep inside the muscle. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'By the time I got my facelift two years later, I still had filler in there.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Ms Silverman said her face looked too rounded after too much filler and she warns it can change the shape of your face for the worse &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h2 class="mol-para-with-font mol-style-subhead health-ccox"&gt;Do LOTS of research before rhinoplasty and breast augmentation&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font mol-style-bold"&gt;&lt;span class="mol-style-bold"&gt;Price for rhinoplasty and breast augmentation: Each treatment f&lt;/span&gt;rom $5,000 to $10,000&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Ms Silverman says that she wishes she had done more research before getting her first nose job but it was before the age of the internet and it was more difficult to find feedback on practitioners.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Because of this, she ended up with a mediocre doctor who took out too much cartilage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;She recalls: '&lt;span&gt;I got my first rhinoplasty in my twenties and &lt;/span&gt;it was honestly underwhelming. I went to a doctor in Baltimore and received his signature style: these itty-bitty noses. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'During our consultation, I described what I wanted, that is a normal size nose, not a teeny tiny one. I trusted he would listen and not take his typical approach with me. I was wrong - UGH! I left his office with a nose that was just... too small.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'I didn't like it. While it was better than what I had started out with, it wasn't what I wanted, and I kicked myself for not going to someone else. The shape of my nose bothered me for years.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Since her first nose job, Ms Silverman has had two more and she is finally happy with the way it looks, describing it as 'fine'. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The beauty expert says the same amount of research needs to be done ahead of getting breast implants. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;To help pick a doctor, she recommends looking at as many before/after photos as possible to get an idea of the results they can offer. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Touching on her own experience with breast implants she adds: 'For my first breast augmentation on my late 20s, the profile was too high and the medium was too large, so I actually ended up looking top-heavy. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'I eventually got saline implants replaced with silicone and did a breast lift and went smaller and lower. Be cautious about going too big or too high.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;With both nose jobs and breast augmentation procedures, Ms Silverman says it is a 'must' to choose &lt;span&gt;a board-certified plastic surgeon who specializes in that specific procedure.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span&gt;She adds: '&lt;/span&gt;DO NOT TAKE ANY SHORTCUTS TO SAVE MONEY! Do your research, as always, and be sure to tell your surgeon exactly what you’re looking for during your consultation.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mol-para-with-font mol-style-subhead health-ccox"&gt;Watch out for facial peels &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font mol-style-bold"&gt;PRICE: Anywhere from $125 to $2,500 &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;When it comes to facial peels, Ms Silverman says she has 'tried them all'.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;These treatments are designed to exfoliate the skin and promote new cell growth to improve skin texture and address various skin issues such as acne and pigmentation.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Ms Silverman's favorites are the retinol and chemical peels that her facialist Mindy Kim offers at her office in the Miami area. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;While she now has her favorites, she says she has '&lt;span&gt;been down some major rabbit holes &lt;/span&gt;with specialists who looked good on the surface but would do things to my face and body that made me look worse, just so I'd come back and spend more with them'. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Again, she says the most important thing is to do thorough research and to pay attention to online reviews.   &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;She also warns that some of the harsher peels require anesthesia and can be 'pretty strong so you look like a burn victim afterward'.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;For the more intense peels, she warns that recovery can take at least a week so you will need to plan accordingly and 'you can't get too many of them because your skin can get very, very thin'.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mol-para-with-font mol-style-subhead health-ccox"&gt;Don't get liposuction... on the knees&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font mol-style-bold"&gt;PRICE: From $3,000 to $6,000&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;&lt;p class="clear"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;LEFT: The bad lipo Ms Silverman did in her knees with sagging afterwards RIGHT: After she had a threading treatment to rectify the issue. The specialized, dissolvable threads work by lifting and tightening the skin&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The first time Ms Silverman tried liposuction on her body was in her 30s, right after she had her son, and she said the experience was 'great'. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But when she went for her second round of lipo in her 40s it proved to be a disaster. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;While getting her stomach done, the doctor said she could get her knees sculpted and Ms Silverman agreed. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But she said it was a decision she went on to regret. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;She explains: 'The lipo doctor also told me that she could liposuction my knees. In the moment, it seemed like a good idea (this was before I'd realized the terrible results on my stomach). &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Oh, if only I could go back in time! She ended up taking out too much fat from my knees, which made them very uneven. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Now, with so much fat gone, the skin on my knees started to sag majorly; I had to get threads (specialized, dissolvable threads to lift and tighten the skin) in them. This is when I also started to get filler in my knees too. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'I had to go back for tweaks about every five months. All in all, my liposuction experience was terrible.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Because of her traumatic lipo experience, Ms Silverman says she would never recommend the treatment on the knees because the fat there is necessary. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;She concludes: '&lt;span&gt;I actually caused more damage by removing the fat when I could have just eaten more protein and done more lunges at the gym. Don't touch your knees.' &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mol-para-with-font mol-style-subhead health-ccox"&gt;And... the surgery she was most pleased with?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Ms Silverman says of all the procedures she's had, she was most pleased with her mini facelift, which was done at the same time as a forehead lift, at the age of 47. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;She got the facelift to help lift sagging skin, something she had unsuccessfully tried to do with fillers in the past.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'The facelift that I'd had done turned out to be great as all the inflammation in my cheeks and under my eyes started to go away&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'The facelift that I'd had done turned out to be great as all the inflammation in my cheeks and under my eyes started to go away,' shes&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'The facelift that I'd had done turned out to be great as all the inflammation in my cheeks and under my eyes started to go away,' she&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'I was starting to look sculpted, and even more lifted than I'd been in my thirties.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Going forward, Ms Silverman says she plans to maintain herself through 'diet, nutrition, working out, and small treatments'.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font mol-style-italic mol-style-bold"&gt;Ms Silverman's book, &lt;a target="_blank" class="" rel="nofollow" href="https://www.amazon.com/Bullshit-Botox-Rebels-Self-Love-Eternal/dp/B0DK62B4ZT"&gt;From Bullshit to Botox: A Rebel's Guide To Self Love And Eternal Yout&lt;/a&gt;h, is out now&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Daily Mail</author><pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 06:08:07 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiqAFBVV95cUxNclJZU3FDNFdXcVVwUWFaZThPVlFscW1OeGI3d1J5Sm1sckExTHRzYTRBY29neGJQOHJjNXFXd3hMR1hZZENReEhKRkFyTnJpWktvRWJWSXVEUzBsQXpOZ3U1NlJJRmQ5bk51bmtyd1VUS080VVUxSjZuVFMyaDBXQUloel90THAwMkRjSnRJS3lRRGo3X0pVTGNXVTB1Vmt4SDB1SmtsSTg</guid></item><item><title>Tragic twist of fate as little girl, 6, with cancer dies from unrelated illness - Daily Mail</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMioAFBVV95cUxOYmpUNjQ2aDU0dmUyTzk3MmhZWXhSTUl4UHNaZEpTR0ZVNnd1OW1mZ1hSMHJrYTFBQTdRbG9HRVRrNEV0ZE1PMnRoTW5MQ2VuR1J2TUx3OGl5Sy16aEc0SnZ4WTRTZ2JublNsdWpoMzFrV203d3JTb0lKdXBBUTI0Sm1CS0FzWko0VWI4Ump1QnRIeFZfektIU1ctUXVtUVdn?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div itemprop="articleBody"&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;A cancer-stricken six-year-old girl from &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/arizona/index.html" id="mol-07659b30-021a-11f0-899a-03e998d49ec3" class="class"&gt;Arizona&lt;/a&gt;, who had just received her final bout of chemotherapy, tragically died after she came down with another, unrelated sickness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Lola Zimmer, 6, died from a fungal infection on March 4, five months after she was diagnosed with Leukemia. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Her long battle with illness began on October 31, 2024, when she went trick-or-treating with parents, Alyssa Aguilar and Drew Zimmer, and little sister, Pheobe. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Shortly after leaving their her home in Flagstaff for an evening of when when the young girl 'collapsed.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'We were heading out the door to go trick-or-treating and she collapsed,' her father, Drew Zimmer, told &lt;a target="_blank" class="class" rel="nofollow" href="https://www.fox5vegas.com/2025/03/14/6-year-old-with-cancer-dies-fungal-infection/"&gt;KPHO&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The worry-riddled parents then took their daughter to a nearby emergency room before she was 'airlifted' to Phoenix Children's Hospital for further treatment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Within 24 hours of arriving at the children's hospital - 150 miles from their home - Lola started on her first round of chemotherapy, a post shared by Lola's grandmother, Salina Aguilar, on &lt;a target="_self" href="/sciencetech/facebook/index.html" id="mol-b378c1d0-0220-11f0-899a-03e998d49ec3" class="class"&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt; reads.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Several months later, on February 24, the Kindergarten student completed her second, and final, round of chemotherapy - 'the consolidation phase,' as her grandmother called it. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'For all we know, she was &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/cancer/index.html" id="mol-0a0a3f40-0223-11f0-899a-03e998d49ec3"&gt;cancer&lt;/a&gt; free after finishing this second round,' she wrote. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Lola Zimmer, 6, died from a fungal infection on March 4, five months after she was dianosed with Leukemia&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;On October 31, 2024, Lola, along with her parents, Alyssa Aguilar (pictured) and Drew Zimmer, and little sister, Pheobe, left her home in Flagstaff for an evening of trick-or-treating when when the young girl 'collapsed'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;However, when Lola's cancer was finally ready to be re-examined her doctors delivered the devastating news. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'She was about to have her bone marrow cells re-tested for cancer cells but tragically unbeknownst to us and the doctors, she had contracted a deadly fungal infection that spread rapidly,' Salina said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Just a day after the doctor's harrowing discovery, Zimmer said Lola's heart stopped and she was no longer able to breathe on her own.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Seeing your daughter on life support unresponsive is really hard, and then having the doctors tell you that the fungal infection she has is untreatable, and having to say goodbye, it's traumatic,' the distraught father said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Only a few days later, the heart-broken family was told their little girl 'wasn't going to make it.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'We were told she wasn't going to make it and to call all of our family to say our final goodbyes to our sweet, precious Lola girl,' her grandmother said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Aguilar suspected the chemo destroyed her daughter's immune system.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'I get frustrated and angry that she could have beat cancer, but she couldn't have beat a fungal infection,' Aguilar said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;As they process the loss, Zimmer and Aguilar have found a new meaning in butterflies and cherries. Both became symbols of hope connected to Lola and now embody the 'fragility of life.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Cherish every moment and tell people you love them,' Zimmer said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Tell your children you love them and kiss them goodnight,' Aguilar added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;The worry-riddled parents then took their daughter to a nearby emergency room before she was 'airlifted' to Phoenix Children's Hospital for further treatment. Pictured: Lola and her parents, Alyssa Aguilar and Drew Zimmer, and her little sister, Pheobe&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Several months later, on February 24, the Kindergarten student completed her second, and final, round of chemothreapy - 'the consolidation phase,' as her grandmother called it&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;However, when Lola's cancer was finally ready to be re-examined her doctors delivered the devastating news - she had contracted a deadly fungal infection. Pictured: Lola and her younger sister Pheobe&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Aguilar's brother, AJ Torres, has since created a &lt;a class="class" rel="nofollow noreferrer noopener" target="_blank" href="https://www.gofundme.com/f/support-lolas-leukemia-treatment"&gt;GoFundMe &lt;/a&gt;fundraiser to help 'support' and 'ease some of the weight' the grieving family now has to bear. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Lola's uncle described his niece as a 'powerhouse, an excellent big sister to Phoebe, and an irreplaceable best friend to my son, Myles.'  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'She loves animals, playing outside, music, dancing, and sometimes defying authority. She is a force, a precious gift to everyone that knows and loves her,' he added on the fundraising page. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;As of Sunday morning they had raised $15,659 of their $25,000 goal. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Daily Mail</author><pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 05:29:26 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMioAFBVV95cUxOYmpUNjQ2aDU0dmUyTzk3MmhZWXhSTUl4UHNaZEpTR0ZVNnd1OW1mZ1hSMHJrYTFBQTdRbG9HRVRrNEV0ZE1PMnRoTW5MQ2VuR1J2TUx3OGl5Sy16aEc0SnZ4WTRTZ2JublNsdWpoMzFrV203d3JTb0lKdXBBUTI0Sm1CS0FzWko0VWI4Ump1QnRIeFZfektIU1ctUXVtUVdn</guid></item><item><title>Newport mum saves son's umbilical cord stem cells as 'back-up' - BBC.com</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiWkFVX3lxTE1DSUJWeXJCOVRqU1B0eFhnejNpd3ZjRkxMUWtSZ3AtUHZTRnIzTlk1eDQwa2ItOEF1bTljTkNaV2ZQUGt4Q1d3TXVZYkhFN1FVUVRkWDNQa0NWZ9IBX0FVX3lxTE5WMC1LQ0VxS0dySHVOZzhPa0JrYmlHSlJrdUZaM0xWX2prTDdkQ2QyYU5ra2RDaGNhUmZoSm9KNWdwa194Ui1lWkFxQVpEYW1YZ2hlZFZaRzlpVjNyYXpR?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article&gt;&lt;p data-component="headline-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 eeiVGB"&gt;&lt;h1 class="sc-518485e5-0 itISwu"&gt;Friend's death prompts woman to save son's umbilical cord stem cells&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 ejjhCR"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="hero-image" class="sc-a34861b-1 jxzoZC"&gt;&lt;img src="/bbcx/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-a34861b-0 cOpVbP hide-when-no-script"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/2cbb/live/9efedcc0-0028-11f0-a94c-6986d2348378.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/2cbb/live/9efedcc0-0028-11f0-a94c-6986d2348378.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/2cbb/live/9efedcc0-0028-11f0-a94c-6986d2348378.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/2cbb/live/9efedcc0-0028-11f0-a94c-6986d2348378.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/2cbb/live/9efedcc0-0028-11f0-a94c-6986d2348378.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/2cbb/live/9efedcc0-0028-11f0-a94c-6986d2348378.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/2cbb/live/9efedcc0-0028-11f0-a94c-6986d2348378.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/2cbb/live/9efedcc0-0028-11f0-a94c-6986d2348378.jpg.webp" loading="eager" alt="Family photo Natalie looking down at newborn baby Arthur in her arms wearing an orange hat. She has brown hair and a blood pressure monitor on her finger and is sat in a hospital bed, with a wooden table and chair beside her." class="sc-a34861b-0 efFcac"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-a34861b-2 hesJxn"&gt;Family photo&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 bdPeAJ"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-8353772e-0 iUqqeb"&gt;The stem cells from baby Arthur's umbilical cord were harvested as soon as he was born&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 dlWCEZ"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;A mum whose friend's death from leukaemia prompted her to bank stem cells from her newborn's umbilical cord has described it as a "back-up" which has brought her reassurance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;Natalie Harrop, 40, from Newport, arranged to have a stem cell harvesting procedure with her baby son Arthur and said it was a "really straightforward" but important process.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;The cells remain banked for the family to use if needed until Arthur turns 25, after which they can decide whether or not to donate them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;Leukaemia &amp;amp; Myeloma Research UK (LMRUK) said stem cells could be used for future treatment of blood cancers and other life-threatening illnesses, and described them as "effective biological health insurance".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 dlWCEZ"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;Ms Harrop, a school wellbeing officer, was inspired to research leukaemia and cancer treatments following the death of her friend and colleague Jacqueline Walsh.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;She described Ms Walsh as "a lovely lady" who was generous with her time, raising money for many different charities. "She touched everybody's hearts," she added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 dlWCEZ"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;One area of research Ms Harrop became interested in was stem cell harvesting, after discovering there were &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.nhsbt.nhs.uk/cord-blood-bank/what-is-cord-blood/" class="sc-c9299ecf-0 beIoQm"&gt;more than a million blood-producing stem cells in the blood within the umbilical cord and placenta&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;Pregnant with her fourth child, Arthur, Ms Harrop discussed the procedure with her partner Gary Hardwick-Bishop, who agreed that they should apply to have it done.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;The procedure involves the cells being retrieved from the umbilical cord after birth, stored and then collected to be banked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 jFCfG"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-a34861b-1 jxzoZC"&gt;&lt;img src="/bbcx/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-a34861b-0 cOpVbP hide-when-no-script"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/bbe6/live/143a4ea0-004e-11f0-b50e-9d086302645f.png.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/bbe6/live/143a4ea0-004e-11f0-b50e-9d086302645f.png.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/bbe6/live/143a4ea0-004e-11f0-b50e-9d086302645f.png.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/bbe6/live/143a4ea0-004e-11f0-b50e-9d086302645f.png.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/bbe6/live/143a4ea0-004e-11f0-b50e-9d086302645f.png.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/bbe6/live/143a4ea0-004e-11f0-b50e-9d086302645f.png.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/bbe6/live/143a4ea0-004e-11f0-b50e-9d086302645f.png.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/bbe6/live/143a4ea0-004e-11f0-b50e-9d086302645f.png.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Natalie Harrop Natalie and Jacqueline smiling as they embrace. Jacqueline has short blonde hair and Natalie has long, darker blonde hair. The photo is tightly cropped around their faces." class="sc-a34861b-0 efFcac"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-a34861b-2 hesJxn"&gt;Natalie Harrop&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 bdPeAJ"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-8353772e-0 iUqqeb"&gt;Natalie Harrop (right) began researching leukaemia treatments when her friend Jacqueline died of the blood cancer&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 dlWCEZ"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;"It feels like you've got a little back-up there, so if anything does come up, we have that on the side if we ever do need it," said Ms Harrop, whose other children are aged eight, 14 and 18.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;"And not just for our family, but for anyone who is a DNA match to Arthur or to me, anybody that needs them."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;Ms Harrop explained there were some criteria they had to meet to be eligible, including having someone in their family who had had cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;"Gary's dad had cancer in the past and recovered, so it was really important to him as well, and my grandad died of cancer when I was young," she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;The mum said she faced "quite a few barriers" and had to "jump through a few hoops" to gather the correct documentation, but added she felt this was due to a lack of awareness among medical professionals and said the process itself was completely non-invasive.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;She now hopes raising awareness about it will make the process more widely considered.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;Ms Harrop recalled one midwife being quite unsure about it and asking if she was "jinxing herself".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;"There's nothing negative that can come from it. If it doesn't work out, it doesn't work out, if the stem cells get damaged, they get damaged, but at least you've tried."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;After seeking out her grandfather's death certificate as part of the application process and seeing his name, Arthur, on it, Ms Harrop said it also prompted the couple to name their baby after him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 jFCfG"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-a34861b-1 jxzoZC"&gt;&lt;img src="/bbcx/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-a34861b-0 cOpVbP hide-when-no-script"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/97c0/live/404f7c20-0050-11f0-b477-a50b7b3e27ff.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/97c0/live/404f7c20-0050-11f0-b477-a50b7b3e27ff.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/97c0/live/404f7c20-0050-11f0-b477-a50b7b3e27ff.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/97c0/live/404f7c20-0050-11f0-b477-a50b7b3e27ff.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/97c0/live/404f7c20-0050-11f0-b477-a50b7b3e27ff.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/97c0/live/404f7c20-0050-11f0-b477-a50b7b3e27ff.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/97c0/live/404f7c20-0050-11f0-b477-a50b7b3e27ff.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/97c0/live/404f7c20-0050-11f0-b477-a50b7b3e27ff.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Family photo Arthur as a newborn baby with his eyes tightly closed, lying on a white sheet. He is wearing a white cardigan and an orange and green knitted hat in the shape of a pumpkin, while holding a blanket which has pumpkins on it. " class="sc-a34861b-0 efFcac"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-a34861b-2 hesJxn"&gt;Family photo&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 bdPeAJ"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-8353772e-0 iUqqeb"&gt;Ms Harrop says she feels reassured knowing Arthur's stem cells are available should they ever need them&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 dlWCEZ"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;Mr Hardwick-Bishop contacted the phlebotomist when Ms Harrop went into labour and Arthur was born at The Grange hospital in Cwmbran, Torfaen, on 31 October 2023 following a "horrendous birth".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;"I ended up having an emergency caesarean, but whether you have a good birth or a bad birth you can still collect the cells, it doesn't really matter," said Ms Harrop.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;The cord and placenta cells were transferred into a freezer, which stayed beside Ms Harrop at the hospital until they were collected and taken to a bank.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;"They sent me a letter and a little certificate as well," she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 dlWCEZ"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;She continued: "Since we kept his stem cells I've done a bit more research and it just seems like it's really difficult when children or adults need stem cells, they're not on hand.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;"Which seems such a shame, when there are so many births daily. It just baffles me there are all these stem cells going to waste."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;LMRUK runs a cord blood banking service, the Model Cell Biobank, and said taking stem cells from a baby's umbilical cord was "effective biological health insurance", providing options for treatment of the child or another member of the family should they need the stem cells in the future because of a serious illness, including blood cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 jFCfG"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-a34861b-1 jxzoZC"&gt;&lt;img src="/bbcx/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-a34861b-0 cOpVbP hide-when-no-script"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/e7ca/live/fb48c7c0-0050-11f0-b477-a50b7b3e27ff.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/e7ca/live/fb48c7c0-0050-11f0-b477-a50b7b3e27ff.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/e7ca/live/fb48c7c0-0050-11f0-b477-a50b7b3e27ff.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/e7ca/live/fb48c7c0-0050-11f0-b477-a50b7b3e27ff.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/e7ca/live/fb48c7c0-0050-11f0-b477-a50b7b3e27ff.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/e7ca/live/fb48c7c0-0050-11f0-b477-a50b7b3e27ff.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/e7ca/live/fb48c7c0-0050-11f0-b477-a50b7b3e27ff.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/e7ca/live/fb48c7c0-0050-11f0-b477-a50b7b3e27ff.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Family photo A family picture at a zoo with giraffes in the background. Gary is bald with a dark beard and moustache, wearing a black puffer coat and holding a toddler with blonde hair, who is wearing a blue cardigan and light green bib. Next to him is a young girl with blonde hair and a tooth gap who is hugging Natalie who has long brown hair and glasses in a black puffer coat. They are all smiling at the camera." class="sc-a34861b-0 efFcac"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-a34861b-2 hesJxn"&gt;Family photo&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 bdPeAJ"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-8353772e-0 iUqqeb"&gt;Natalie Harrop and her partner Gary will have access to Arthur's stem cells should he or anyone who is a DNA match need them for medical treatment&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 dlWCEZ"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;LMRUK recently joined forces with Smart Cells International, the UK's first private stem cell storage company, to procure, process and store cord blood stem cells for qualifying families.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;The service is means-tested and is part-funded for some families, and fully funded for others, such as Ms Harrop's.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;Dr Joanna Tilley, operations director at LMRUK, said stem cells were "vital" in cancer treatment, adding medical research was revealing new potential future uses for them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;Ms Harrop added: "Any new mums considering this, there is absolutely nothing to lose.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;"If Jacki was alive, she was such a funny person and I can just imagine her saying it was amazing, she'd be the first one to be promoting anything like this."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BBC.com</author><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 21:49:28 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiWkFVX3lxTE1DSUJWeXJCOVRqU1B0eFhnejNpd3ZjRkxMUWtSZ3AtUHZTRnIzTlk1eDQwa2ItOEF1bTljTkNaV2ZQUGt4Q1d3TXVZYkhFN1FVUVRkWDNQa0NWZ9IBX0FVX3lxTE5WMC1LQ0VxS0dySHVOZzhPa0JrYmlHSlJrdUZaM0xWX2prTDdkQ2QyYU5ra2RDaGNhUmZoSm9KNWdwa194Ui1lWkFxQVpEYW1YZ2hlZFZaRzlpVjNyYXpR</guid></item><item><title>Newport mum saves son's umbilical cord stem cells as 'back-up' - BBC.com</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiWkFVX3lxTE1DSUJWeXJCOVRqU1B0eFhnejNpd3ZjRkxMUWtSZ3AtUHZTRnIzTlk1eDQwa2ItOEF1bTljTkNaV2ZQUGt4Q1d3TXVZYkhFN1FVUVRkWDNQa0NWZw?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article&gt;&lt;p data-component="headline-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 eeiVGB"&gt;&lt;h1 class="sc-518485e5-0 itISwu"&gt;Friend's death prompts woman to save son's umbilical cord stem cells&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 ejjhCR"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="hero-image" class="sc-a34861b-1 jxzoZC"&gt;&lt;img src="/bbcx/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-a34861b-0 cOpVbP hide-when-no-script"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/2cbb/live/9efedcc0-0028-11f0-a94c-6986d2348378.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/2cbb/live/9efedcc0-0028-11f0-a94c-6986d2348378.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/2cbb/live/9efedcc0-0028-11f0-a94c-6986d2348378.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/2cbb/live/9efedcc0-0028-11f0-a94c-6986d2348378.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/2cbb/live/9efedcc0-0028-11f0-a94c-6986d2348378.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/2cbb/live/9efedcc0-0028-11f0-a94c-6986d2348378.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/2cbb/live/9efedcc0-0028-11f0-a94c-6986d2348378.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/2cbb/live/9efedcc0-0028-11f0-a94c-6986d2348378.jpg.webp" loading="eager" alt="Family photo Natalie looking down at newborn baby Arthur in her arms wearing an orange hat. She has brown hair and a blood pressure monitor on her finger and is sat in a hospital bed, with a wooden table and chair beside her." class="sc-a34861b-0 efFcac"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-a34861b-2 hesJxn"&gt;Family photo&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 bdPeAJ"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-8353772e-0 iUqqeb"&gt;The stem cells from baby Arthur's umbilical cord were harvested as soon as he was born&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 dlWCEZ"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;A mum whose friend's death from leukaemia prompted her to bank stem cells from her newborn's umbilical cord has described it as a "back-up" which has brought her reassurance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;Natalie Harrop, 40, from Newport, arranged to have a stem cell harvesting procedure with her baby son Arthur and said it was a "really straightforward" but important process.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;The cells remain banked for the family to use if needed until Arthur turns 25, after which they can decide whether or not to donate them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;Leukaemia &amp;amp; Myeloma Research UK (LMRUK) said stem cells could be used for future treatment of blood cancers and other life-threatening illnesses, and described them as "effective biological health insurance".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 dlWCEZ"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;Ms Harrop, a school wellbeing officer, was inspired to research leukaemia and cancer treatments following the death of her friend and colleague Jacqueline Walsh.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;She described Ms Walsh as "a lovely lady" who was generous with her time, raising money for many different charities. "She touched everybody's hearts," she added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 dlWCEZ"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;One area of research Ms Harrop became interested in was stem cell harvesting, after discovering there were &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.nhsbt.nhs.uk/cord-blood-bank/what-is-cord-blood/" class="sc-c9299ecf-0 beIoQm"&gt;more than a million blood-producing stem cells in the blood within the umbilical cord and placenta&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;Pregnant with her fourth child, Arthur, Ms Harrop discussed the procedure with her partner Gary Hardwick-Bishop, who agreed that they should apply to have it done.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;The procedure involves the cells being retrieved from the umbilical cord after birth, stored and then collected to be banked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 jFCfG"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-a34861b-1 jxzoZC"&gt;&lt;img src="/bbcx/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-a34861b-0 cOpVbP hide-when-no-script"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/bbe6/live/143a4ea0-004e-11f0-b50e-9d086302645f.png.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/bbe6/live/143a4ea0-004e-11f0-b50e-9d086302645f.png.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/bbe6/live/143a4ea0-004e-11f0-b50e-9d086302645f.png.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/bbe6/live/143a4ea0-004e-11f0-b50e-9d086302645f.png.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/bbe6/live/143a4ea0-004e-11f0-b50e-9d086302645f.png.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/bbe6/live/143a4ea0-004e-11f0-b50e-9d086302645f.png.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/bbe6/live/143a4ea0-004e-11f0-b50e-9d086302645f.png.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/bbe6/live/143a4ea0-004e-11f0-b50e-9d086302645f.png.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Natalie Harrop Natalie and Jacqueline smiling as they embrace. Jacqueline has short blonde hair and Natalie has long, darker blonde hair. The photo is tightly cropped around their faces." class="sc-a34861b-0 efFcac"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-a34861b-2 hesJxn"&gt;Natalie Harrop&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 bdPeAJ"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-8353772e-0 iUqqeb"&gt;Natalie Harrop (right) began researching leukaemia treatments when her friend Jacqueline died of the blood cancer&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 dlWCEZ"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;"It feels like you've got a little back-up there, so if anything does come up, we have that on the side if we ever do need it," said Ms Harrop, whose other children are aged eight, 14 and 18.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;"And not just for our family, but for anyone who is a DNA match to Arthur or to me, anybody that needs them."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;Ms Harrop explained there were some criteria they had to meet to be eligible, including having someone in their family who had had cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;"Gary's dad had cancer in the past and recovered, so it was really important to him as well, and my grandad died of cancer when I was young," she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;The mum said she faced "quite a few barriers" and had to "jump through a few hoops" to gather the correct documentation, but added she felt this was due to a lack of awareness among medical professionals and said the process itself was completely non-invasive.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;She now hopes raising awareness about it will make the process more widely considered.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;Ms Harrop recalled one midwife being quite unsure about it and asking if she was "jinxing herself".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;"There's nothing negative that can come from it. If it doesn't work out, it doesn't work out, if the stem cells get damaged, they get damaged, but at least you've tried."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;After seeking out her grandfather's death certificate as part of the application process and seeing his name, Arthur, on it, Ms Harrop said it also prompted the couple to name their baby after him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 jFCfG"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-a34861b-1 jxzoZC"&gt;&lt;img src="/bbcx/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-a34861b-0 cOpVbP hide-when-no-script"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/97c0/live/404f7c20-0050-11f0-b477-a50b7b3e27ff.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/97c0/live/404f7c20-0050-11f0-b477-a50b7b3e27ff.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/97c0/live/404f7c20-0050-11f0-b477-a50b7b3e27ff.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/97c0/live/404f7c20-0050-11f0-b477-a50b7b3e27ff.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/97c0/live/404f7c20-0050-11f0-b477-a50b7b3e27ff.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/97c0/live/404f7c20-0050-11f0-b477-a50b7b3e27ff.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/97c0/live/404f7c20-0050-11f0-b477-a50b7b3e27ff.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/97c0/live/404f7c20-0050-11f0-b477-a50b7b3e27ff.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Family photo Arthur as a newborn baby with his eyes tightly closed, lying on a white sheet. He is wearing a white cardigan and an orange and green knitted hat in the shape of a pumpkin, while holding a blanket which has pumpkins on it. " class="sc-a34861b-0 efFcac"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-a34861b-2 hesJxn"&gt;Family photo&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 bdPeAJ"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-8353772e-0 iUqqeb"&gt;Ms Harrop says she feels reassured knowing Arthur's stem cells are available should they ever need them&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 dlWCEZ"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;Mr Hardwick-Bishop contacted the phlebotomist when Ms Harrop went into labour and Arthur was born at The Grange hospital in Cwmbran, Torfaen, on 31 October 2023 following a "horrendous birth".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;"I ended up having an emergency caesarean, but whether you have a good birth or a bad birth you can still collect the cells, it doesn't really matter," said Ms Harrop.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;The cord and placenta cells were transferred into a freezer, which stayed beside Ms Harrop at the hospital until they were collected and taken to a bank.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;"They sent me a letter and a little certificate as well," she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 dlWCEZ"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;She continued: "Since we kept his stem cells I've done a bit more research and it just seems like it's really difficult when children or adults need stem cells, they're not on hand.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;"Which seems such a shame, when there are so many births daily. It just baffles me there are all these stem cells going to waste."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;LMRUK runs a cord blood banking service, the Model Cell Biobank, and said taking stem cells from a baby's umbilical cord was "effective biological health insurance", providing options for treatment of the child or another member of the family should they need the stem cells in the future because of a serious illness, including blood cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 jFCfG"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-a34861b-1 jxzoZC"&gt;&lt;img src="/bbcx/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-a34861b-0 cOpVbP hide-when-no-script"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/e7ca/live/fb48c7c0-0050-11f0-b477-a50b7b3e27ff.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/e7ca/live/fb48c7c0-0050-11f0-b477-a50b7b3e27ff.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/e7ca/live/fb48c7c0-0050-11f0-b477-a50b7b3e27ff.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/e7ca/live/fb48c7c0-0050-11f0-b477-a50b7b3e27ff.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/e7ca/live/fb48c7c0-0050-11f0-b477-a50b7b3e27ff.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/e7ca/live/fb48c7c0-0050-11f0-b477-a50b7b3e27ff.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/e7ca/live/fb48c7c0-0050-11f0-b477-a50b7b3e27ff.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/e7ca/live/fb48c7c0-0050-11f0-b477-a50b7b3e27ff.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Family photo A family picture at a zoo with giraffes in the background. Gary is bald with a dark beard and moustache, wearing a black puffer coat and holding a toddler with blonde hair, who is wearing a blue cardigan and light green bib. Next to him is a young girl with blonde hair and a tooth gap who is hugging Natalie who has long brown hair and glasses in a black puffer coat. They are all smiling at the camera." class="sc-a34861b-0 efFcac"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-a34861b-2 hesJxn"&gt;Family photo&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 bdPeAJ"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-8353772e-0 iUqqeb"&gt;Natalie Harrop and her partner Gary will have access to Arthur's stem cells should he or anyone who is a DNA match need them for medical treatment&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 dlWCEZ"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;LMRUK recently joined forces with Smart Cells International, the UK's first private stem cell storage company, to procure, process and store cord blood stem cells for qualifying families.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;The service is means-tested and is part-funded for some families, and fully funded for others, such as Ms Harrop's.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;Dr Joanna Tilley, operations director at LMRUK, said stem cells were "vital" in cancer treatment, adding medical research was revealing new potential future uses for them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;Ms Harrop added: "Any new mums considering this, there is absolutely nothing to lose.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;"If Jacki was alive, she was such a funny person and I can just imagine her saying it was amazing, she'd be the first one to be promoting anything like this."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BBC.com</author><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 21:49:28 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiWkFVX3lxTE1DSUJWeXJCOVRqU1B0eFhnejNpd3ZjRkxMUWtSZ3AtUHZTRnIzTlk1eDQwa2ItOEF1bTljTkNaV2ZQUGt4Q1d3TXVZYkhFN1FVUVRkWDNQa0NWZw</guid></item><item><title>Herpes Virus Linked to Long-Term Brain and Neurological Problems - Neuroscience News</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiakFVX3lxTE51aEd3QjBQMTliTmlKQVM4VUdaRGdtTFdOelZMeHJTSy1OMVV3VEgySTA3NDF1MVJEc1p5XzBFaFZiSHh1RjNzQno5aVV1aHpFWTVHTm1tWE1UQ1F4ZG9nOXVWd2ZxWWxKQlE?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content body-color clearfix link-color-wrap"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary: &lt;/strong&gt;A new study reveals that herpes simplex virus-1 (HSV-1), commonly known for causing cold sores, can travel through the nasal cavity directly to the brain, causing severe and lasting neurological symptoms. In animal experiments, nasal HSV-1 infection led to persistent neurological dysfunction, including anxiety and cognitive impairment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers identified heparanase, a cellular enzyme, as a critical factor in allowing HSV-1 to cause severe, lasting neurological damage. Blocking the activity of this enzyme significantly reduced neurological damage in infected animals, highlighting a possible therapeutic target.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Facts:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class="wp-block-list"&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Neurological Impact:&lt;/strong&gt; Intranasal HSV-1 infections lead to lasting neurological and cognitive impairments.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Role of Heparanase:&lt;/strong&gt; This enzyme facilitates HSV-1-induced brain damage; blocking it reduces neurological consequences.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Global Prevalence:&lt;/strong&gt; Approximately two-thirds of the global population carries HSV-1, emphasizing the potential wide-reaching impact of these findings.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Source: &lt;/strong&gt;University of Illinois&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Herpes simplex virus-1 (HSV-1) is commonly known for causing blisters and sores. But in some cases, the virus can migrate to the eye or nervous system, causing severe, chronic symptoms.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Now, a study from University of Illinois Chicago researchers finds that herpes infection through the nose can lead to anxiety, motor impairment and cognitive issues. The research is the first to show that, by exploiting a cellular enzyme, the virus can produce behavioral symptoms. The finding emphasizes the need for prevention and treatment of a virus carried by billions of people worldwide. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="wp-block-image size-full"&gt;&lt;picture fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" class="wp-image-108156"&gt; &lt;source type="image/webp" srcset="https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/03/hsv1-neurology-neuroscience.jpg.webp 1200w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/03/hsv1-neurology-neuroscience-300x200.jpg.webp 300w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/03/hsv1-neurology-neuroscience-770x513.jpg.webp 770w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/03/hsv1-neurology-neuroscience-1155x770.jpg.webp 1155w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/03/hsv1-neurology-neuroscience-370x247.jpg.webp 370w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/03/hsv1-neurology-neuroscience-293x195.jpg.webp 293w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/03/hsv1-neurology-neuroscience-150x100.jpg.webp 150w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px"&gt;&lt;/source&gt; &lt;img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" src="https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/03/hsv1-neurology-neuroscience.jpg" alt="This shows a head and viruses." srcset="https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/03/hsv1-neurology-neuroscience.jpg 1200w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/03/hsv1-neurology-neuroscience-300x200.jpg 300w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/03/hsv1-neurology-neuroscience-770x513.jpg 770w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/03/hsv1-neurology-neuroscience-1155x770.jpg 1155w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/03/hsv1-neurology-neuroscience-370x247.jpg 370w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/03/hsv1-neurology-neuroscience-293x195.jpg 293w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/03/hsv1-neurology-neuroscience-150x100.jpg 150w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px"&gt; &lt;/picture&gt;&lt;figcaption class="wp-element-caption"&gt;The new research looked at intranasal infection, where viral particles enter the body through the nose and have more direct access to the nervous system. Credit: Neuroscience News&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;The research, published in &lt;em&gt;mBio&lt;/em&gt;, is the latest from the College of Medicine group led by Deepak Shukla, the Marion H. Schenk Esq. Professor in Ophthalmology for Research of the Aging Eye and UIC professor of microbiology and immunology.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shukla’s laboratory previously studied how the virus spreads to the eye and brain and can lead to blindness, encephalitis and other conditions. The new research looked at intranasal infection, where viral particles enter the body through the nose and have more direct access to the nervous system. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“If an infected individual is shedding virus via tears, it could reach the nasal cavity, where it could go more directly to the brain,” Shukla said. “I think it’s underdiagnosed and understudied, but the neurological consequences, we believe, are much more severe than you would normally see with fever blisters or ocular infection.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In animal experiments, the researchers observed high levels of inflammation and neuronal damage just days after HSV-1 infection. For several months after — equivalent to decades of life in humans — infected animals performed more poorly on tests of motor coordination and memory and exhibited more anxiety-like behavior when compared to controls.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“There is definitely nerve damage if you take the intranasal route, and the effects are long-term, which is alarming,” Shukla said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers also studied heparanase, a cellular enzyme the group previously studied for its role in HSV-1 reinfection and long-term effects. Animals with a deactivated gene for heparanase did not show the same neurobehavioral deficits after infection as control animals. That suggests the enzyme mediates some of the virus’ damaging effects in the brain. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“These insights open the door to potential therapeutic approaches to mitigate the effects of neuroinflammation and prevent long-term brain injury caused by viral infections,” said Hemant Borase, a UIC postdoctoral researcher and first author of the study. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Herpes simplex virus-1 is extremely common. The World Health Organization estimates that nearly two-thirds of the global population carry the virus. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The virus reactivates throughout life; it’s a lifelong infection” said Chandrashekhar Patil, research assistant professor in the College of Medicine and co-author of the paper. “So, I think this awareness will be really important among the large population which is carrying this virus.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tibor Valyi-Nagy, professor of pathology, is also a co-author of the paper.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Funding: &lt;/strong&gt;The study was funded by grants from the National Institutes of Health. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;About this neurology research news&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="has-background"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Author: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#e082868c8f8f84a0958983ce858495" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Brian Flood&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Source:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://uic.edu" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;University of Illinois&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Contact: &lt;/strong&gt;Brian Flood – University of Illinois&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Image: &lt;/strong&gt;The image is credited to Neuroscience News&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="has-background"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Original Research: &lt;/strong&gt;Open access.&lt;br&gt;“&lt;a href="https://dx.doi.org/10.1128/mbio.03765-24" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;HPSE-mediated proinflammatory signaling contributes to neurobehavioral deficits following intranasal HSV-1 infection&lt;/a&gt;” by Deepak Shukla et al. &lt;em&gt;mBio&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr class="wp-block-separator has-text-color has-pale-cyan-blue-color has-alpha-channel-opacity has-pale-cyan-blue-background-color has-background"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Abstract&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;HPSE-mediated proinflammatory signaling contributes to neurobehavioral deficits following intranasal HSV-1 infection&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Herpes simplex virus-1 (HSV-1) is a neurotropic virus that can infect the brain, and an uncontrolled infection can lead to a range of diseases, including chronic nerve pain, encephalitis, and neurobehavioral abnormalities.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These outcomes are often severe and have lasting consequences, highlighting the need to identify host factors that contribute to disease severity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; In this study, we report that intranasal HSV-1 infection in murine model, which promotes viral dissemination into the brain, implicates the host protein heparanase (HPSE) as a key mediator of neuroinflammation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Specifically, we observed that the HPSE activity during HSV-1 infection in naïve animals promotes the upregulation of proinflammatory cytokines, enhances microglial activity in the brain, and contributes to cognitive impairment, anxiety, and motor coordination deficits.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Such effects are significantly less detectable in heparanase deficient (&lt;em&gt;Hpse−/&lt;/em&gt;−) mice. Additionally, we found that moderate activation of toll-like receptors (TLRs), particularly in &lt;em&gt;Hpse+/+&lt;/em&gt; mice, may contribute to the activation of the inflammasome pathway.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This, in turn, leads to the activation of caspase-1 (&lt;em&gt;Casp1&lt;/em&gt;) and caspase-3 (&lt;em&gt;Casp3&lt;/em&gt;), which may play a role in nerve function loss.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Our findings position HPSE as a potential therapeutic target for mitigating virus-induced neuroinflammation and neurobehavioral defects.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p class="clear"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Neuroscience News</author><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 21:27:51 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiakFVX3lxTE51aEd3QjBQMTliTmlKQVM4VUdaRGdtTFdOelZMeHJTSy1OMVV3VEgySTA3NDF1MVJEc1p5XzBFaFZiSHh1RjNzQno5aVV1aHpFWTVHTm1tWE1UQ1F4ZG9nOXVWd2ZxWWxKQlE</guid></item><item><title>Zoom Fatigue: Scientists Say Your Face Might Be The Problem - ScienceAlert</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMikAFBVV95cUxNRzVtMXhmWjZKVF95QUJpYzJTRGNQVDFNeU5FZjd1TXMycE50azZQZURZR0hnRzFDYTExTmVvRFJrNjd5UXprMndwR2dzOXQxanp3Sm1sV05rS241c3lZdHF6dDA2SjNfNU1obVRaNGZGRkpoNWpTRUJtRE9kVXhwZDBsWDZUZFhiM1k0MnBiWm4?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Work gatherings are often unpopular events, but many people experience particular discomfort when meetings are conducted by videoconference.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to a new study by a team of researchers led by Chaeyun Lim from Michigan State University, this sentiment, commonly known as "&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/experiment-reveals-a-simple-trick-to-avoid-zoom-fatigue"&gt;Zoom fatigue&lt;/a&gt;" or videoconference fatigue, is linked with dissatisfaction about one's facial appearance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Surveys suggest workers generally &lt;a href="https://www.pewresearch.org/short-reads/2025/01/13/many-remote-workers-say-theyd-be-likely-to-leave-their-job-if-they-could-no-longer-work-from-home/"&gt;prefer remote work&lt;/a&gt; when it's an option, and those who frequently use videoconferencing tend to &lt;a href="https://www.pewresearch.org/short-reads/2022/05/04/as-telework-continues-for-many-u-s-workers-no-sign-of-widespread-zoom-fatigue/"&gt;report little distress&lt;/a&gt; overall.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yet Zoom fatigue is a real phenomenon, and although it could presumably affect anyone, women, and people of color report &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/we-may-have-found-one-of-the-main-reasons-for-zoom-fatigue-and-it-s-affecting-women-more"&gt;higher levels&lt;/a&gt;, as previous research has shown.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While not everyone needs videoconferencing, the technology is important for many industries and individuals, and can help improve efficiency and productivity across a range of scenarios.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Zoom fatigue could pose a significant barrier for the broader adoption of virtual meetings, or VMs, the researchers note. Yet little is still known about the relationship between VM fatigue and facial appearance dissatisfaction, and about how this fatigue affects adoption of videoconferencing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Despite VM fatigue's critical role in shaping workplace interactions and digital inclusion in emerging virtual work environments, its effects on VM adoption – and the mechanisms linking facial appearance concerns, VM fatigue, and VM adoption – remain underexplored," the authors &lt;a href="https://dx.doi.org/10.1371/journal.pone.0312354"&gt;write&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In hopes of addressing that, Lim and her team investigated impression management features – tools in videoconferencing software that let users adjust their appearance by tweaking the video feed of themselves.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The researchers recruited 2,448 US-based workers in various professional, technical, or scientific fields who at least sometimes work remotely and who regularly participate in virtual meetings for work.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A 15-minute survey documented how the volunteers felt about their facial appearance, as well as their thoughts on impression-management behaviors like using touch-up to enhance self video or using video filters or avatars.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lim and her colleagues used structural equation modeling to study the relationships between these factors, finding that subjects who reported higher facial appearance dissatisfaction also experienced higher levels of VM fatigue.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This in turn led to increased use of impression management features to modify the user's appearance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some subjects might have already experienced facial appearance dissatisfaction before developing VM fatigue, but as the researchers point out, there are indications that staring at ourselves on screens can feed this dissatisfaction.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Excessive screen time, engagement with social media, and selective self-presentation through modifying photos before posting them have long been associated with appearance dissatisfaction," they &lt;a href="https://dx.doi.org/10.1371/journal.pone.0312354"&gt;write&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Similarly, the extended amount of time spent on VMs may exacerbate negative perceptions of self-image, as well as concerns of critical evaluation."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_153717" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-153717" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/02/50200577876_5e36f6d987_c.jpg" alt="videoconference on laptop computer screen" class="size-full wp-image-153717" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/02/50200577876_5e36f6d987_c.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/02/50200577876_5e36f6d987_c-600x307.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-153717" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;(&lt;a href="https://www.flickr.com/photos/bryanalexander/50200577876/"&gt;Bryan Alexander/Flickr/CC BY 2.0&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;VM fatigue caused by facial appearance dissatisfaction was also associated with negative perceptions of VMs, such as deeming them not useful, the study revealed – and thus influencing users' opinions about adopting videoconferencing for work meetings.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Turning off self-video has been floated as an effective solution, but it remains impractical for many users, such as those who prefer or feel compelled to monitor their appearance during meetings.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Beyond disturbing workplace interactions and productivity, such negative experiences can create psychological barriers to adopting VM technologies, contributing to technology inequity in the workplace," the team writes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The new study has some significant limitations, the authors note, such as its inability to reveal causal relationships and the recruitment of only workers from the US for the survey.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Future research should recruit subjects from broader cultural contexts, the researchers suggest, and be designed to investigate ways of helping to alleviate VM fatigue.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study was published in &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://journals.plos.org/plosone/article?id=10.1371/journal.pone.0312354"&gt;PLOS One&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 21:01:16 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikAFBVV95cUxNRzVtMXhmWjZKVF95QUJpYzJTRGNQVDFNeU5FZjd1TXMycE50azZQZURZR0hnRzFDYTExTmVvRFJrNjd5UXprMndwR2dzOXQxanp3Sm1sV05rS241c3lZdHF6dDA2SjNfNU1obVRaNGZGRkpoNWpTRUJtRE9kVXhwZDBsWDZUZFhiM1k0MnBiWm4</guid></item><item><title>Brooklyn kitten ID’d as second NYC avian flu victim after contracting virus from another cat - New York Post</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiowFBVV95cUxQbUJMRjU2dWxlU3QtbVJrNzM3R1VuODJMM0FwQUhYLWJGa242QXA3c1BIa2RXRkVvSGFTM2JoYTdGMWcwT0NueElweWc5R1J1LWhZUHg5emhGcU50T0lwVDNySzh1ZGRpeG1RZjdWb2Ffd0VPVFRLSXZKS241MzRGUjhmbmsyNGYzTzZIRTJfWlBaT0ZwaEdOMlpXdzN4blEtUzd3?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="single__content entry-content m-bottom "&gt;
							


&lt;p&gt;A Brooklyn kitten has been identified as the second confirmed feline victim of avian flu in New York City — having contracted the contagion from another infected cat.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Valentino, a 1-year-old domestic shorthair, was technically the &lt;a href="https://nypost.com/2025/02/21/us-news/some-of-nycs-500000-stray-cats-could-already-be-infected-with-bird-flu-and-a-possible-threat-to-humans-activists/"&gt;first cat in the Big Apple to die from the H5N1 virus &lt;/a&gt;after undergoing an emergency euthanasia on Feb. 1, Dr. Natara Loose of The Neighborhood Vet in Bushwick, told The Post.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;His case was only confirmed this week after a second cat, &lt;a href="https://nypost.com/2025/03/14/us-news/two-nyc-cats-dead-from-avian-flu-including-8-month-old-kitten/"&gt;an 8-month-old Upper West Side kitten&lt;/a&gt;, succumbed to the same fate.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;figure class="nyp-slideshow-modal-image wp-block-image aligncenter size-large"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;Valentino is the second confirmed fatality in New York City of avian flu in felines.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“Legitimately, had this little kitten not died recently and had it not been confirmed this week, I would still be in the process, probably for an unknown period of time, of not knowing how Valentino got it or how he died … no one would have put it out there, so it’s good news for the public,” Loose, Valentino’s veterinarian and owner, explained.&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;p id="connatix-outstream-video"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Valentino was put to sleep just 24 hours after he recorded a jaw-dropping 106-degree fever.&lt;/p&gt;


	



&lt;p&gt;The lively little black kitten had been his active and curious self in the days earlier, but Loose became concerned when she noticed he was hiding inside the Bushwick vet office, which he called home.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Valentino — whose condition was already delicate due to diabetes — was put on antibiotics and fluids and checked for multiple infections, but he didn’t respond to anything.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;figure class="nyp-slideshow-modal-image wp-block-image aligncenter size-large"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;Valentino’s health rapidly declined within 24 hours of recording a 106-degree fever. &lt;span class="credit"&gt;theneighborhoodvet/Instagram&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The domestic shorthair was rushed to an animal hospital on Jan. 31 and underwent a procedure, but it was too late.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“I euthanized him and he was here. I’m kissing him,” Loose said in a social media video, indicating she was holding Valentino close when he was put to sleep.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Suspecting her beloved kitten’s cause of death, Loose submitted Valentino for a necropsy, where it was confirmed that every organ of his body was infected by bird flu via tainted food.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Government officials were suspicious, however, because Valentino had not consumed any raw meat — which had caused the deaths of at least 85 cats across the US since 2022.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;figure class="nyp-slideshow-modal-image wp-block-image aligncenter size-large"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;Valentino likely contracted bird flu from another cat, who survived the infection. &lt;span class="credit"&gt;theneighborhoodvet/Instagram&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;p&gt;A second Big Apple feline death last month — which experts believe was caused by ingesting the raw food brand Savage Cat, prompting investigators to question whether any of Loose’s furry patients had a history with the brand.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Further investigation revealed that Valentino had contracted the virus from a third cat, “Cat C,” who had been rushed into The Neighborhood Vet days before Valentino’s death.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“That cat had a mild fever. No respiratory signs, just a little uncomfortable in his belly and went home the next day completely normal,” Loose said.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“I read through the history of the cat and the cat had eaten the same food.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;figure class="nyp-slideshow-modal-image wp-block-image aligncenter size-large"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;Valentino died on Feb. 1 from an emergency euthanasia.  &lt;span class="credit"&gt;theneighborhoodvet/Instagram&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;p&gt;On Friday, Audrey Brady, owner of Savage Cat, told The Post that the company’s ingredients are USDA inspected and are monitored for H5/H7 viruses. The brand’s raw foods were &lt;a href="https://savagecatfood.com/avian-influenza/"&gt;recalled in February after a potential link&lt;/a&gt; to another infection, which was later proven negative.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Though Valentino lives at the vet office, he did not have any direct contact with Cat C, Loose said, leading her to believe the avian flu was transmitted through the air.&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;p&gt;Neither Loose nor any of her employees contracted the avian flu, despite their close contact with Valentino, especially in the heartbreaking moments of his death.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“I think cats-to-human is going to be pretty rare or very, very, very low risk because we were all very direct contact with him,” said Loose.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="comments-inline-cta" data-comment-count data-prompt="What do you think?"&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;There have been no cases of bird flu in humans in New York City, the city health department confirmed.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;There has been no official recall for Savage Cat Foods, though the health department is advising New Yorkers not to feed their pets anything from the brand, or any raw meat or milk products.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="wpcom-liveblog-container"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;						&lt;/div&gt;

												&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>New York Post</author><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiowFBVV95cUxQbUJMRjU2dWxlU3QtbVJrNzM3R1VuODJMM0FwQUhYLWJGa242QXA3c1BIa2RXRkVvSGFTM2JoYTdGMWcwT0NueElweWc5R1J1LWhZUHg5emhGcU50T0lwVDNySzh1ZGRpeG1RZjdWb2Ffd0VPVFRLSXZKS241MzRGUjhmbmsyNGYzTzZIRTJfWlBaT0ZwaEdOMlpXdzN4blEtUzd3</guid></item><item><title>Chocolate could be the next probiotic powerhouse - Earth.com</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiggFBVV95cUxQa3ZkTkNiOWQxLWE3NmZLSFVNM1d6N0Z5TnBDMkVLeFduR1I3alFUUzAxNkw1ZDlVYWZKVXFwMm9DRk9iOUpCTGpMWXV5alJDNmUwMWdONHVqUVpzYkR4Sk4xQVdVN1kxdmFLWEU4ejFBYlZubUpFSlR0X1FLVXFEN0VR?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="page_content__AwOj6"&gt;&lt;p&gt;What if eating chocolate could be more than just a guilty pleasure? What if &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/chocolate-and-cocoa-prices-have-doubled-in-the-past-year-climate-change/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;chocolate&lt;/a&gt;, infused with probiotics, had hidden health benefits beyond the usual antioxidant boost from dark varieties?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Scientists are working on just that. By infusing chocolate with prebiotics and probiotics, they aim to transform it into a functional food. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The goal is to produce a delicious, gut-friendly treat that does more than satisfy cravings. But there’s a challenge: adding health-boosting ingredients can alter texture, moisture, and even protein levels. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The trick is to keep the chocolate as indulgent as ever while making it better for the body.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-probiotics-make-chocolate-healthier"&gt;Probiotics make chocolate healthier&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Probiotics are tiny, beneficial microbes found in yogurt and kimchi that play a vital role in gut health. They help balance bacteria, aid digestion, and even reduce inflammation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But they’re delicate. Stomach acid, heat, and processing can destroy probiotics before they ever reach the intestines, where they do their best work.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Enter prebiotics. These compounds, often dietary fibers, act as food for probiotics, helping them to thrive. Together, they form a powerhouse combination known as synbiotics. The challenge now is to find a way to embed these prebiotics and probiotics into &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/can-chocolate-survive-dna-research-may-help-save-cacao-trees/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;chocolate&lt;/a&gt; without ruining its flavor or texture.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That’s where researchers Smriti Gaur and Shubhi Singh from the Jaypee Institute of Information Technology (&lt;a href="https://www.jiit.ac.in" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;JIIT&lt;/a&gt;) in India stepped in.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Instead of using complex processing methods, they took a different approach – corn and honey. These natural prebiotics were easy to integrate, and eliminated the need for complicated manufacturing techniques.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-experimenting-with-flavor"&gt;Experimenting with flavor &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The research team didn’t stop at a single chocolate &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/cocoa-production-in-africa-is-under-extreme-climate-pressure/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;recipe&lt;/a&gt;. They created five versions. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One was a control – pure chocolate with standard ingredients like cocoa butter, cocoa powder, and milk powder. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The others were synbiotic chocolates, each containing different combinations of prebiotics (corn and honey), probiotics (&lt;em&gt;Lactobacillus acidophilus La-14&lt;/em&gt; or &lt;em&gt;Lactobacillus rhamnosus GG&lt;/em&gt;), and a flavor enhancer – either cinnamon or orange.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Then came the tests. Fat content remained steady across all chocolates, keeping the mouthfeel familiar, but other properties shifted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Orange-flavored chocolate, for example, changed the game. It lowered the pH, increased moisture, and even boosted protein levels compared to the other samples. Scientists believe the citrus elements interacted with the probiotics, enhancing their stability.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-probiotics-change-chocolate-s-texture"&gt;Probiotics change chocolate’s texture&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Texture matters in &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/sustainable-farming-could-save-the-future-of-chocolate/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;chocolate&lt;/a&gt;. The perfect piece should break with a clean snap, not crumble or feel too soft. The synbiotic chocolates, however, lost some of that sharp break. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Additional ingredients disrupted the chocolate’s structure, making it slightly softer. Whether that’s good or bad depends on personal preference. Some might find it more luxurious.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nutritionally, though, the changes were promising. The probiotic-enhanced chocolates had higher antioxidant levels than the control. That means they not only delivered gut-friendly microbes but also an extra dose of protection against oxidative stress.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Storage was another key test. Would the probiotics survive? Over time, microbial counts decreased, but not as much as expected. Even after 125 days, probiotic levels remained high.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This shelf life exceeded that of many other probiotic-infused chocolates that had been tested in past studies, proving that the chosen bacteria strains and prebiotic ingredients contributed to long-term stability.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-the-real-test-is-surviving-digestion"&gt;The real test is surviving digestion&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chocolate infused with probiotics sounds great in theory, but there’s a bigger question: do the probiotics actually make it past the stomach? &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Harsh digestive conditions can destroy beneficial microbes before they reach the intestines, rendering the whole idea useless.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To find out, the researchers simulated human digestion in a lab. The results were encouraging. The probiotics maintained substantial viability for over five hours, meaning they had a strong chance of surviving long enough to benefit gut health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-does-it-still-feel-like-a-treat"&gt;Does it still feel like a treat?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Of course, none of this matters if the &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/new-discovery-will-help-climate-proof-chocolate/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;chocolate&lt;/a&gt; doesn’t taste good. People aren’t likely to choose gut-friendly chocolate if it doesn’t deliver the same rich, satisfying experience. So, the researchers sampled their creations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Personally, we enjoyed the orange-flavored chocolates the most, where the vibrant citrus notes complemented the rich cocoa, and it had a slightly softer texture that made each bite feel more luxurious,” said Gaur.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That’s a promising sign. A probiotic chocolate that doesn’t taste like a “health food” could appeal to a much wider audience. Experimenting with more flavors could make these chocolates even more exciting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-the-future-of-probiotic-chocolate"&gt;The future of probiotic chocolate&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;This study is just the beginning. While the results suggest that synbiotic chocolates can boost gut health and antioxidant levels, there’s still room for improvement. Future research could refine the probiotic strains, adjust texture, and enhance flavors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“In the future, we are excited to explore additional health benefits of these chocolates while thoroughly investigating their sensory and nutritional profiles, with the goal of creating an even more wholesome and enjoyable treat,” said Gaur.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If successful, this could mark a shift in how people see chocolate – not just as a sweet indulgence, but as a functional food. Imagine a world where treating yourself means nourishing your body, too. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study is published in the journal &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://pubs.acs.org/doi/10.1021/acsfoodscitech.4c00741" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;ACS Food Science &amp;amp; Technology&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;—–&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Like what you read? &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/subscribe/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Subscribe to our newsletter&lt;/a&gt; for engaging articles, exclusive content, and the latest updates.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Check us out on &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/earthsnap/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;EarthSnap&lt;/a&gt;, a free app brought to you by &lt;a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/eric-ralls/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Eric Ralls&lt;/a&gt; and Earth.com.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;—–&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Earth.com</author><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 17:39:25 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiggFBVV95cUxQa3ZkTkNiOWQxLWE3NmZLSFVNM1d6N0Z5TnBDMkVLeFduR1I3alFUUzAxNkw1ZDlVYWZKVXFwMm9DRk9iOUpCTGpMWXV5alJDNmUwMWdONHVqUVpzYkR4Sk4xQVdVN1kxdmFLWEU4ejFBYlZubUpFSlR0X1FLVXFEN0VR</guid></item><item><title>Undiscovered cause of Parkinson’s found for first time by scientists in huge breakthrough - The Independent</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMikgFBVV95cUxQczBfcTVnRjlFaFdwVU9UQnRVWWQ3bUNIaHg3Nm02dTg3WloxSTRlR1NQRExLQ0s4d3dkR05qcHJ3Q3pfSGdtMVZZRXNHUG94cGtyRXowalVFa2h6TXp4ZlNzQ1hybm8wSEZFNlVoWDNNckpuT251SGlCSjloSDlnd0J3UWVYSG9OVUp5UDNrb3pndw?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="sc-jbiisr-0 lkPksW sc-jbiisr-1 hiukpJ" id="main"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="hydrate-root sc-10wlkbs-0 cFynzd" data-component="SupportNSCNative" data-loading="lazy" data-theme-name="base-light"&gt;&lt;aside class="sc-hez36s-0 eFDpwi"&gt;&lt;div class="sc-hez36s-1 jkkqcL"&gt;&lt;h3 data-testid="support-nsc-title" class="sc-hez36s-2 dDFcwe"&gt;Your support helps us to tell the story&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;div class="sc-hez36s-8 kqOtlp"&gt;&lt;div class="sc-hez36s-13 bjQKsM"&gt;&lt;div class="sc-aja53j-0 hWxisF sc-hez36s-16 gBaKpR"&gt;&lt;div class="sc-aja53j-6 ifXxYf"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="dropdown-with-gradient-collapsed-content-container" class="sc-aja53j-5 jlvSeZ"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div data-testid="dropdown-with-gradient-collapsed-content" class="sc-aja53j-4 ghJHgZ"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div data-testid="support-nsc-collapsed-content-tablet" class="sc-hez36s-7 bhFQeV"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-1uza6dc-0 gMxIQB"&gt;From reproductive rights to climate change to Big Tech, The Independent is on the ground when the story is developing. Whether it's investigating the financials of Elon Musk's pro-Trump PAC or producing our latest documentary, 'The A Word', which shines a light on the American women fighting for reproductive rights, we know how important it is to parse out the facts from the messaging.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-1uza6dc-0 gMxIQB"&gt;At such a critical moment in US history, we need reporters on the ground. Your donation allows us to keep sending journalists to speak to both sides of the story.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-1uza6dc-0 gMxIQB"&gt;The Independent is trusted by Americans across the entire political spectrum. And unlike many other quality news outlets, we choose not to lock Americans out of our reporting and analysis with paywalls. We believe quality journalism should be available to everyone, paid for by those who can afford it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;strong class="sc-1uza6dc-1 fJIQUi"&gt;Your support makes all the difference.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;button class="sc-aja53j-1 dvfakS sc-aja53j-7 gYsKvs"&gt;&lt;span data-testid="dropdown-with-gradient-dropdown-tablet" class="sc-aja53j-3 CRIit"&gt;&lt;span data-action-type="Read more" class="sc-aja53j-2 ctXiMg"&gt;Read more&lt;/span&gt;&lt;svg class="sc-eaj12q-0 fdygxT sc-culv3z-0 kOpooG sc-a5wy94-0 hgIqfZ"&gt;&lt;use href="#ee6613da15642019"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="/topic/scientists"&gt;Scientists&lt;/a&gt; have made a potentially “life-changing” discovery that could pave the way for new drugs to treat Parkinson’s disease. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Experts have known for several decades that the PINK1 protein is directly linked to Parkinson’s disease – the &lt;a href="/news/uk/home-news/academics-bmj-beijing-symptoms-east-asia-b2709819.html"&gt;fastest growing&lt;/a&gt; neurodegenerative condition in the world.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="article-im-prompt"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Until now, no one has seen what human PINK1 looks like, how PINK1 attaches to the surface of damaged mitochondria inside of cells, or how it is activated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But scientists have now discovered how the mutation switches on and can start using this knowledge to find a way to switch it off and slow the progression of the condition down.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Researchers at the Walter and Eliza Hall Institute, Parkinson’s Disease Research Centre, in Australia, have solved the decades-long mystery.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="taboola-mid-article-thumbnails-ii" class="sc-looa6c-0 kWYnHL"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The findings published in the journal &lt;em&gt;Science &lt;/em&gt;reveal for the first time ever the structure of PINK1 and how it binds to mitochondria – the powerhouse of a cell – and stops it functioning properly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Parkinson’s disease can take years, sometimes decades to diagnose. Often associated with tremors, there are close to 40 symptoms including cognitive impairment, speech issues, body temperature regulation and vision problems. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The neurological condition affects around 153,000 Britons. There is currently no cure for Parkinson’s, although medicine, physiotherapy and surgery can help manage symptoms. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="sc-482ou5-2 lafNeh sc-482ou5-3 fdIcNP image align-center"&gt;&lt;figure class="sc-1cbdeug-0 lkeWpK"&gt;&lt;div data-gallery-length="2" class="sc-482ou5-0 hVSdqv"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.independent.co.uk/2024/02/16/19/1579c6ced0b3815b4ae9d2fc2c3ad0f1Y29udGVudHNlYXJjaGFwaSwxNzA4MTcxODkz-2.74571124.jpg" srcset="https://static.independent.co.uk/2024/02/16/19/1579c6ced0b3815b4ae9d2fc2c3ad0f1Y29udGVudHNlYXJjaGFwaSwxNzA4MTcxODkz-2.74571124.jpg?quality=75&amp;amp;width=320&amp;amp;auto=webp 320w, https://static.independent.co.uk/2024/02/16/19/1579c6ced0b3815b4ae9d2fc2c3ad0f1Y29udGVudHNlYXJjaGFwaSwxNzA4MTcxODkz-2.74571124.jpg?quality=75&amp;amp;width=640&amp;amp;auto=webp 640w" loading="lazy" alt="Some Parkinson’s patients can take more than 20 tablets a day to manage their condition" class="sc-1mc30lb-0 bNNNXy inline-gallery-btn"&gt;&lt;p class="hydrate-root sc-10wlkbs-0 sc-482ou5-1 cFynzd dcZiNS" data-component="AutoGalleryButton" data-theme-name="base-light"&gt;&lt;button class="sc-ohzviw-0 klhTsW inline-gallery-btn" id="trigger-autogallery-187185"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-ohzviw-1 bDzDal"&gt;open image in gallery&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-1cbdeug-1 sc-1cbdeug-3 fWLHSZ hfwDDP"&gt;Some Parkinson’s patients can take more than 20 tablets a day to manage their condition&lt;span class="sc-1cbdeug-7 eUTWtv"&gt; (PA)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;One of the &lt;a href="/news/health/parkinsons-disease-bood-test-symptoms-b2564686.html"&gt;hallmarks of Parkinson’s &lt;/a&gt;is the death of brain cells. Around 50 million cells die and are replaced in the human body every minute. But, unlike other cells in the body, when brain cells die, the rate at which they are replaced is extremely low.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When mitochondria are damaged, they stop making energy and release toxins into the cell. In a healthy person, the damaged cells are disposed of in a process called mitophagy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a person with Parkinson’s and a PINK1 mutation, the mitophagy process no longer functions correctly and toxins accumulate in the cell, eventually killing it. Brain cells need a lot of energy and are especially sensitive to this damage. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In particular, PINK1 has been linked to young-onset Parkinson’s Disease, which affects people under the age of 50. Despite the known link, researchers have previously been unable to visualise the protein or how it works.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“This is a significant milestone for research into &lt;a href="/topic/parkinsons"&gt;Parkinson’s&lt;/a&gt;. It is incredible to finally see PINK1 and understand how it binds to mitochondria,” said Professor David Komander, corresponding author on the study. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Our structure reveals many new ways to change PINK1, essentially switching it on, which will be life-changing for people with Parkinson’s,” he added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lead author on the study, Dr Sylvie Callegari, said PINK1 works in four distinct steps, with the first two steps not having been seen before.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;First, PINK1 senses mitochondrial damage. Then, it attaches to damaged mitochondria. Once attached, it links to a protein called Parkin so that the damaged mitochondria can be recycled.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“This is the first time we’ve seen human PINK1 docked to the surface of damaged mitochondria, and it has uncovered a remarkable array of proteins that act as the docking site. We also saw, for the first time, how mutations present in people with Parkinson’s disease affect human PINK1,” said Dr Callegari.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The idea of using PINK1 as a target for potential drug therapies has long been touted but not yet achieved because the structure of PINK1 and how it attaches to damaged mitochondria were unknown.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The research team hope to use the knowledge to find a drug to slow or &lt;a href="/news/science/parkinsons-people-university-of-oxford-university-of-cambridge-bordeaux-b2522960.html"&gt;stop Parkinson’s&lt;/a&gt; in people with a PINK1 mutation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Researchers in the UK also believe the discovery could lead to better drug design. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Consultant neurologist Dr Richard Ellis said: “It is a crucial step towards understanding the impact of PINK1 in Parkinson’s disease. These observations may hopefully create new opportunities for developing novel strategies for slowing the progression of Parkinson’s disease.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr Zhi Yao, research scientist, Life Arc, said: “A robust understanding of these aspects could present a significant opportunity for accelerating drug discovery for Parkinson's disease and potentially other neurodegenerative conditions too.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Becky Jones, research communications manager at Parkinson’s UK, said: “Changes in the PINK1 have long been linked to Parkinson’s, and a specific mutation in the gene that contains the instructions for making the protein are known to cause a rare inherited form of the condition.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="taboola-mid-article-thumbnails-iii" class="sc-looa6c-0 kWYnHL"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“It’s encouraging to see this research, which will help us understand how changes in PINK1 might be causing damage to dopamine-producing brain cells in people with Parkinson’s. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“This knowledge unlocks future avenues for better drug design and discovery of a treatment that could slow or even stop Parkinson’s progression. This is vital, as despite it being the fastest growing neurological condition in the world, we don’t yet have any drug treatments that can do this.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Independent</author><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 17:12:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikgFBVV95cUxQczBfcTVnRjlFaFdwVU9UQnRVWWQ3bUNIaHg3Nm02dTg3WloxSTRlR1NQRExLQ0s4d3dkR05qcHJ3Q3pfSGdtMVZZRXNHUG94cGtyRXowalVFa2h6TXp4ZlNzQ1hybm8wSEZFNlVoWDNNckpuT251SGlCSjloSDlnd0J3UWVYSG9OVUp5UDNrb3pndw</guid></item><item><title>What Happens to Your Body When You Take CoQ10 Regularly - EatingWell</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMibEFVX3lxTE9iRFFLaC01a3pXTUlHYXVzWlRiNm1FMEw0Y3dDMlp3VENDRDJMVnFiempVY0xOclRmMC1Db1lzTEZfcUxETjNJek9lMVR4REg5aHZfN0ltdTh1NHFvdEE3aW1xYmVrZG9TQWRBeA?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-page_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-page mntl-block structured-content" data-sc-sticky-offset="90" data-sc-ad-label-height="24" data-sc-ad-track-spacing="100" data-sc-min-track-height="250" data-sc-max-track-height="600" data-sc-breakpoint="50em" data-sc-load-immediate="4" data-sc-content-positions="[1, 1250, 1550, 1950, 2350, 2750, 3150, 3550, 3950]" data-bind-scroll-on-start="true"&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-block_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-callout mntl-sc-block-universal-callout theme-generic" data-tracking-id="mntl-sc-block-callout" data-tracking-container="true"&gt; &lt;h3 class="mntl-sc-block-universal-callout__heading"&gt;Key Takeaways&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;div class="mntl-sc-block-universal-callout__body"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Coenzyme Q10 is naturally produced by the body and found in some foods. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;CoQ10 may increase energy, reduce cellular damage and possibly improve heart health. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;It is safe for most people except those who are pregnant or breastfeeding. It can also interact with some medications.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_2-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Coenzyme Q10 is a substance that’s naturally present in every organ in the body. It’s also found in some foods and is available in supplement form.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="1"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;CoQ10 supplements claim to have many health benefits, including increasing energy, keeping your cells healthy, promoting heart health, improving physical performance, preventing migraines and more. Because our natural CoQ10 levels decline with age, it’s also a popular supplement for longevity.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="2"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_3-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_4-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; If you’re curious about CoQ10, here’s what you need to know about its potential health benefits, side effects and risks.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_5-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_7-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-may-increase-energy"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_8-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; May Increase Energy &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_9-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; CoQ10 plays an essential role in energy production. It works by helping our bodies produce a substance called adenosine triphosphate (ATP), which our cells use for energy, explains &lt;a href="https://fullwellfertility.com/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1" rel="nofollow"&gt;Ayla Barmmer, M.S., RD, LDN&lt;/a&gt;, a registered dietitian and founder and CEO of the supplement company FullWell. Studies have investigated the effect of CoQ10 supplementation on energy levels with promising results. For instance, one meta-analysis of 13 studies found that taking a CoQ10 supplement reduced fatigue compared to a placebo.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="3"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_10-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-may-reduce-cell-damage"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_11-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; May Reduce Cell Damage &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_12-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; CoQ10 may keep your cells healthy in several ways. The first is by acting as an &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/2051586/best-antioxidant-rich-foods/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;antioxidant&lt;/a&gt;. “Antioxidants are like peacekeepers that stabilize free radicals in several ways, including giving the frantic free radical molecules an extra electron,” says Barmmer. That’s not all. “CoQ10 acts as a free radical scavenger, helping to protect cells from damage and reducing inflammation,” says&lt;a href="https://nutritiondigested.com/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="2" rel="nofollow"&gt; Amy Brownstein, M.S., RDN&lt;/a&gt;, a registered dietitian and owner of Nutrition Digested. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_13-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_15-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-might-improve-heart-health"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_16-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; Might Improve Heart Health &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_17-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Heart disease is the leading cause of death in the United States. So, it’s no surprise that supplements touting their heart-health benefits are a popular choice. “CoQ10 is especially important for heart health because the heart requires a lot of energy to pump blood effectively,” says Barmmer. “By supporting energy production and helping to manage oxidative stress, CoQ10 may help maintain healthy heart function.”
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_18-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_19-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; As encouraging as that is in theory, the National Institutes of Health points out that there is very little research on CoQ10’s ability to prevent heart disease and that the research that does exist is not conclusive.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="4"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; In addition, a systematic review of 11 studies concludes that there is no evidence, one way or the other, to suggest that it may guard against heart failure.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="5"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_20-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_21-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; On the upside, the NIH says that there is some evidence that it may protect against complications from heart surgery. Some research has also shown that it may help reduce blood pressure. However, more study is needed. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_22-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_24-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-recommended-dosage"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_25-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; Recommended Dosage  &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_26-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; “Supplements are available in a wide range of doses, typically from 30 to 600 milligrams,” says Barmmer. There’s no single established dose that’s best for everyone. However, many studies have used dosages in the 100 to 200 milligram range. But don’t wing it. “It’s best to follow your health practitioner’s recommendations for individualized advice,” says Barmmer.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_27-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_29-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-potential-side-effects-and-precautions"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_30-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; Potential Side Effects and Precautions &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_31-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Side effects are possible with any medication or supplement, including CoQ10. However, older research has shown that doses of 900 milligrams per day were as well-tolerated as a placebo.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="6"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt; Side effects can occur but are usually mild. “Some people may experience digestive issues, dizziness, insomnia, headaches or skin rashes when taking CoQ10,” says&lt;a href="https://inutritioncenter.com/about/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1" rel="nofollow"&gt; Vanessa Imus, M.S., RDN&lt;/a&gt;, a registered dietitian and owner of Integrated Nutrition for Weight Loss. Insomnia has also been reported. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_32-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_33-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Despite CoQ10’s solid safety record, it may not be suitable for people who are pregnant or breastfeeding. “Since research on its safety during pregnancy is limited, it’s generally recommended to discontinue when pregnancy is confirmed,” says Barmmer. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_34-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_35-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Additionally, medication interactions are possible when taking CoQ10. “Those who are diabetic or are on blood pressure-lowering meds should use caution, as it could lower blood sugar and blood pressure,” says Imus. Other medications, like blood thinners and chemotherapy drugs, can also interact with CoQ10 supplements. Before adding CoQ10 to your routine, be sure to review all your medications and supplements with your health care provider.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_36-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-the-bottom-line"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_37-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; The Bottom Line &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_38-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; As we age, our bodies naturally produce less CoQ10. So, it’s easy to assume a supplement will help you feel younger, healthier and more vibrant. However, research on CoQ10 is still evolving. The best evidence is for its ability to increase energy and reduce cellular damage. It may also lower blood pressure and protect against complications from heart surgery, but more study is needed. CoQ10 has mild side effects and is safe for most people (except for those who are pregnant or breastfeeding). However, it can interact with certain medications, especially blood thinners and chemotherapy drugs and may also be problematic for anybody taking medication to lower their blood sugar or blood pressure. As with any supplement, speak with your health care professional before adding CoQ10 to your regimen to make sure it’s safe for you.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_39-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="mntl-sc-block_40-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-faq mntl-sc-block-universal-faq"&gt;&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-faqs-92e608d5-0fa5-496b-9799-2dcd7fb6d977"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;h2 class="mntl-sc-block-universal-faq__title"&gt;Frequently Asked Questions&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block-universal-faq__content_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block-universal-faq__content mntl-accordion js-accordion"&gt;
&lt;li class="accordion__item js-accordion-item " data-ordinal="1"&gt;
&lt;p tabindex="0" class="accordion__header js-accordion-trigger" id="mntl-accordion__item_1-0-section-0"&gt;
&lt;svg class="icon icon-chevron accordion__icon"&gt;
&lt;use xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xlink:href="#icon-chevron" href="#icon-chevron"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;
&lt;/svg&gt;
&lt;span class="accordion__title"&gt;What are the benefits of taking CoQ10?&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="accordion__body"&gt;
&lt;div id="mntl-accordion__content_1-0" class="comp mntl-accordion__content"&gt; &lt;div class="faq-accordion__item-answer"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;CoQ10 is a powerful antioxidant that reduces oxidative stress and protects against cellular damage. Research finds that taking CoQ10 supplements may increase energy, protect your cells from damage and possibly improve heart health.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="accordion__item js-accordion-item " data-ordinal="2"&gt;
&lt;p tabindex="0" class="accordion__header js-accordion-trigger" id="mntl-accordion__item_2-0-section-1"&gt;
&lt;svg class="icon icon-chevron accordion__icon"&gt;
&lt;use xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xlink:href="#icon-chevron" href="#icon-chevron"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;
&lt;/svg&gt;
&lt;span class="accordion__title"&gt;Is it OK to take CoQ10 every day?&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="accordion__body"&gt;
&lt;div id="mntl-accordion__content_2-0" class="comp mntl-accordion__content"&gt; &lt;div class="faq-accordion__item-answer"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yes, taking CoQ10 every day has been shown to be safe for most healthy adults. However, it’s unknown if it is safe for people who are pregnant or breastfeeding, due to a lack of research.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="accordion__item js-accordion-item " data-ordinal="3"&gt;
&lt;p tabindex="0" class="accordion__header js-accordion-trigger" id="mntl-accordion__item_3-0-section-2"&gt;
&lt;svg class="icon icon-chevron accordion__icon"&gt;
&lt;use xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xlink:href="#icon-chevron" href="#icon-chevron"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;
&lt;/svg&gt;
&lt;span class="accordion__title"&gt;What is coenzyme Q10 used for?&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="accordion__body"&gt;
&lt;div id="mntl-accordion__content_3-0" class="comp mntl-accordion__content"&gt; &lt;div class="faq-accordion__item-answer"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;CoQ10 is a supplement that may help boost energy levels and promote cellular and cardiovascular health. Since the body’s natural CoQ10 levels decline with age, it is also a popular supplement for longevity. People also take it to improve physical performance, prevent migraines and ease muscle pain from cholesterol-lowering medications.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>EatingWell</author><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMibEFVX3lxTE9iRFFLaC01a3pXTUlHYXVzWlRiNm1FMEw0Y3dDMlp3VENDRDJMVnFiempVY0xOclRmMC1Db1lzTEZfcUxETjNJek9lMVR4REg5aHZfN0ltdTh1NHFvdEE3aW1xYmVrZG9TQWRBeA</guid></item><item><title>Keeping With Kennedy’s Advice, Measles Patients Turn to Unproven Treatments - The New York Times</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMid0FVX3lxTE85VnRIUjQ0SWhaV3ZBWTZVSDZId2E0enQweC11S0xldE4wWUxScXJFN0NjZFA0b0tJdWJRTjBHY3VCai1SanNoU3NXQkxRR3p1RHNXUU9CVnJsZ21QRjBCZjlaLV9qSU5QSkRfWndfMkRjM1AyMjNR?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="css-s99gbd StoryBodyCompanionColumn" data-testid="companionColumn-0"&gt;&lt;div class="css-53u6y8"&gt;&lt;p class="css-at9mc1 evys1bk0"&gt;Struggling to contain a raging measles epidemic in West Texas, public health officials increasingly worry that residents are relying on unproven remedies endorsed by Robert F. Kennedy Jr., the health secretary, and postponing doctor visits until the illness has worsened.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="css-at9mc1 evys1bk0"&gt;Hospitals and officials &lt;a class="css-yywogo" href="https://www.facebook.com/story.php?story_fbid=1193400659464206&amp;amp;id=100063828481984&amp;amp;_rd" title="" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;sounded an alarm this week&lt;/a&gt;, issuing a notice explaining which measles symptoms warranted immediate medical attention and stressing the importance of timely treatment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="css-at9mc1 evys1bk0"&gt;&lt;strong class="css-8qgvsz ebyp5n10"&gt;“&lt;/strong&gt;I’m worried we have kids and parents that are taking all of these other medications and then delaying care,” said Katherine Wells, director of public health in Lubbock, Texas, where many of the sickest children in this outbreak have been hospitalized.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="css-at9mc1 evys1bk0"&gt;Some seriously ill children had been given alternative remedies like cod liver oil, she added. “If they’re so, so sick and have low oxygen levels, they should have been in the hospital a day or two earlier,” she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="css-s99gbd StoryBodyCompanionColumn" data-testid="companionColumn-1"&gt;&lt;div class="css-53u6y8"&gt;&lt;p class="css-at9mc1 evys1bk0"&gt;The growing outbreak has spread to nearly 260&lt;strong class="css-8qgvsz ebyp5n10"&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;people in Texas. So far, 34 patients have been hospitalized, and one child has died. In neighboring New Mexico counties, the virus has sickened 35 and hospitalized two. Two cases in Oklahoma have also been &lt;a class="css-yywogo" href="https://oklahoma.gov/health/news---events/newsroom/2025/first-cases-of-measles-in-oklahoma-reported.html" title="" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;linked to the outbreak&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="css-at9mc1 evys1bk0"&gt;Texas health officials believe the true number of cases is far higher. In all, there have been 301 measles cases in the United States this year, the highest number since 2019, the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention reported on Friday.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The New York Times</author><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 16:09:35 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMid0FVX3lxTE85VnRIUjQ0SWhaV3ZBWTZVSDZId2E0enQweC11S0xldE4wWUxScXJFN0NjZFA0b0tJdWJRTjBHY3VCai1SanNoU3NXQkxRR3p1RHNXUU9CVnJsZ21QRjBCZjlaLV9qSU5QSkRfWndfMkRjM1AyMjNR</guid></item><item><title>Cancer Vaccines Are Suddenly Looking Extremely Promising - Futurism</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiaEFVX3lxTE1KdG1DaGV0S2sxUm1YZFhvSEYyazhpSUREaUFfaVp6VWtyN29mNl85VlZHOE9XVllkcXBpVERHc19TZ3NpaEExRXN0QVJUdUF0ZHVVVGpRN0xFTU9UT1I3c3N6eVFsY0ZD?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;section id="incArticle" class="post-content z-50 w-full p-3 space-y-4 bg-white border lg:-mt-6 md:p-4 md:border-gray-900 lg:ml-3 lg:w-2/3 font-b text-3"&gt;&lt;div class="space-y-4 lg:space-y-0"&gt;&lt;p class="block text-xs text-gray-500 uppercase lg:hidden font-c"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Image by Getty / Futurism&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;With the help of mRNA technology proven effective during the COVID pandemic, researchers are now closer than ever to creating viable cancer vaccines.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In an &lt;a href="https://www.wired.com/story/wired-health-lennard-lee-cancer-vaccines/" class="underline hover:text-neoscope hover:no-underline transition-all duration-200 ease-in-out"&gt;interview with &lt;em&gt;Wired&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, Lennard Lee, an oncologist with the United Kingdom's National Health Service (NHS) working on mRNA cancer vaccines, says he believes the groundbreaking research may prove to be a "silver lining" in the brutal COVID-19 pandemic.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Before COVID, as Lee told the magazine, "cancer vaccines weren’t a proper field of research."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Pretty much every clinical trial had failed," the NHS oncologist said. "With the pandemic, however, we proved that mRNA vaccines were possible."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As with mRNA COVID vaccines, the logistics of these potential new cancer inoculations work by "giving the body instructions" to fight troublesome cells, as Lee detailed, ultimately providing the immune system with a how-to manual on fighting cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Going from mRNA Covid vaccines to mRNA cancer vaccines is straightforward," he told &lt;em&gt;Wired&lt;/em&gt;. "Same fridges, same protocol, same drug, just a different patient."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Instead of the one-size-fits-all approach taken with the widespread usage of mRNA COVID jabs, however, these new cancer vaccines will be personalized for each individual cancer patient.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"In the current trials," Lee elucidated, "we do a biopsy of the patient, sequence the tissue, send it to the pharmaceutical company, and they design a personalized vaccine that’s bespoke to that patient’s cancer."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"That vaccine is not suitable for anyone else," he recounted to the magazine. "It’s like science fiction."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to Lee, breakthrough cancer vaccine innovation came on the heels of the UK's rapid infrastructure-building during the COVID pandemic, which saw the country "open and deliver clinical trials" much faster than anyone would have expected.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As COVID began winding down in 2022, Lee and his colleagues set up the Cancer Vaccine Launch Pad, a post-pandemic pet project that segued mRNA research into the arena of oncology. Not long after, "the dominoes started falling very quickly" as that project and others around the world rapidly progressed towards cancer vaccines. One NHS trial seeking to stop skin cancer from coming back was completed a year early — something that's "completely unheard of," Lee said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The NHS oncologist told &lt;em&gt;Wired&lt;/em&gt; that the results from that trial should come out by the end of this year or the beginning of 2026. If it was successful, Lee told &lt;em&gt;Wired&lt;/em&gt;, he and his team "will have invented the first approved personalized mRNA vaccine — an impressive feat indeed, especially this soon after the technology was deployed at scale during the pandemic.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=""&gt;&lt;strong&gt;More on the cancer vax: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://futurism.com/neoscope/first-ovarian-cancer-vaccine" class="underline hover:text-neoscope hover:no-underline transition-all duration-200 ease-in-out"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Groundbreaking Ovarian Cancer Vaccine at an "Exciting" Moment, Lead Scientist Says&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Futurism</author><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 16:00:25 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiaEFVX3lxTE1KdG1DaGV0S2sxUm1YZFhvSEYyazhpSUREaUFfaVp6VWtyN29mNl85VlZHOE9XVllkcXBpVERHc19TZ3NpaEExRXN0QVJUdUF0ZHVVVGpRN0xFTU9UT1I3c3N6eVFsY0ZD</guid></item><item><title>Cancer Vaccines Are Suddenly Looking Extremely Promising - Yahoo</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMijAFBVV95cUxQbVRjempMLWliYjlBd0szZ2JyOUsxTE44c0xlYlZES1VOc1JrbkhfX0dlOU5VdldaSURpYTF3NkQtdC1OQnNpZ0lsZFJ4dXBVZ2thd3lkTlZ5WWhlQ3BCNXd1N2FsLUtwaVFEQnpMYnIwYklKbW5LTTZERWxsbUoxNUlqNFNrVEtrb3BHbQ?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="" data-article-body="true"&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;With the help of mRNA technology proven effective during the COVID pandemic, researchers are now closer than ever to creating viable cancer vaccines.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;In an &lt;a href="https://www.wired.com/story/wired-health-lennard-lee-cancer-vaccines/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:interview with Wired;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;interview with &lt;em&gt;Wired&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, Lennard Lee, an oncologist with the United Kingdom's National Health Service (NHS) working on mRNA cancer vaccines, says he believes the groundbreaking research may prove to be a "silver lining" in the brutal COVID-19 pandemic.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Before COVID, as Lee told the magazine, "cancer vaccines weren’t a proper field of research."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;"Pretty much every clinical trial had failed," the NHS oncologist said. "With the pandemic, however, we proved that mRNA vaccines were possible."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;As with mRNA COVID vaccines, the logistics of these potential new cancer inoculations work by "giving the body instructions" to fight troublesome cells, as Lee detailed, ultimately providing the immune system with a how-to manual on fighting cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;"Going from mRNA Covid vaccines to mRNA cancer vaccines is straightforward," he told &lt;em&gt;Wired&lt;/em&gt;. "Same fridges, same protocol, same drug, just a different patient."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Instead of the one-size-fits-all approach taken with the widespread usage of mRNA COVID jabs, however, these new cancer vaccines will be personalized for each individual cancer patient.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;"In the current trials," Lee elucidated, "we do a biopsy of the patient, sequence the tissue, send it to the pharmaceutical company, and they design a personalized vaccine that’s bespoke to that patient’s cancer."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;"That vaccine is not suitable for anyone else," he recounted to the magazine. "It’s like science fiction."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;According to Lee, breakthrough cancer vaccine innovation came on the heels of the UK's rapid infrastructure-building during the COVID pandemic, which saw the country "open and deliver clinical trials" much faster than anyone would have expected.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;As COVID began winding down in 2022, Lee and his colleagues set up the Cancer Vaccine Launch Pad, a post-pandemic pet project that segued mRNA research into the arena of oncology. Not long after, "the dominoes started falling very quickly" as that project and others around the world rapidly progressed towards cancer vaccines. One NHS trial seeking to stop skin cancer from coming back was completed a year early — something that's "completely unheard of," Lee said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The NHS oncologist told &lt;em&gt;Wired&lt;/em&gt; that the results from that trial should come out by the end of this year or the beginning of 2026. If it was successful, Lee told &lt;em&gt;Wired&lt;/em&gt;, he and his team "will have invented the first approved personalized mRNA vaccine — an impressive feat indeed, especially this soon after the technology was deployed at scale during the pandemic.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;More on the cancer vax: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://futurism.com/neoscope/first-ovarian-cancer-vaccine" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk='slk:Groundbreaking Ovarian Cancer Vaccine at an "Exciting" Moment, Lead Scientist Says;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas' class="link "&gt;&lt;em&gt;Groundbreaking Ovarian Cancer Vaccine at an "Exciting" Moment, Lead Scientist Says&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Yahoo</author><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 16:00:25 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijAFBVV95cUxQbVRjempMLWliYjlBd0szZ2JyOUsxTE44c0xlYlZES1VOc1JrbkhfX0dlOU5VdldaSURpYTF3NkQtdC1OQnNpZ0lsZFJ4dXBVZ2thd3lkTlZ5WWhlQ3BCNXd1N2FsLUtwaVFEQnpMYnIwYklKbW5LTTZERWxsbUoxNUlqNFNrVEtrb3BHbQ</guid></item><item><title>My Friend Swears She Saw My Husband Cheating On Me. But She Only Spotted One, Uh, Body Part. - Slate</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMihAFBVV95cUxPanlYWm1lcnhvVGJseVZHcGpTN00zb3lodjlnZzVNTGFpckhIaXFHclNJTHpTaXBkZmxYZGxGUlhweW44b1VoRS1ITUlFZVFXeU1RTHh3MDlsZHlEUUpLdFZZYlQ3VlhacWQ5NHJDNUlzTmdnaFkxNzdYZEZ2dlhPSjdhU2c?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article__content" itemprop="mainEntityOfPage"&gt;
          &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="18" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cm89dbj13002cw0kr0bxt1c3j@published"&gt;&lt;em&gt;How to Do It is Slate’s sex advice column. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Have a question? &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLSdx34-uOijrCIKqMdw5hnyYahSJBKa4AaSzDCu1nfcpmd3IjA/viewform"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Send it to Jessica and Rich here&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt; It’s anonymous!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="5" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cm89dfddt002r3b724pt8kxpf@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dear How to Do It,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="44" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cm89df4em002g3b729btxpe5m@published"&gt;My best friend “Megan” recently attended a sex party. Not long afterward, she called to tell me she was “pretty sure” my husband “Dave” is cheating on me. Except, the story she told me is so insane and unbelievable that I don’t know what think.&lt;/p&gt;



  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="108" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cm89dfjo6002w3b72bh2uz2bx@published"&gt;When I asked her what would make her think he was cheating, she said that the invitation to the party requested all the women arrive ahead of the men for the purpose of a game called “Who’s Who.” When she got there, the hosts had the women assemble in the living room where a sheet with a hole cut in it was hung to completely cover the living room doorway. Then when the men arrived, they took turns putting their dicks through the hole in the sheet and the women tried to guess who each man was before the party began. Megan said my husband’s name came up three times!&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="43" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cm89df4i4002h3b72mge4mup3@published"&gt;Dave and I do not have an open marriage, nor do we attend those kinds of events, so there is no other conclusion to draw other than my husband must be cheating on me. How do I go about confronting him with this revelation?&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="2" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cm89df4lm002i3b72j0ljqmb0@published"&gt;—Game Over&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="3" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cm89df4os002j3b72m7vywstj@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dear Game Over,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="70" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cm89dhugh00373b725fujido4@published"&gt;I don’t know what kind of party this was, but from your question, it seems like both first and last names came up during the guessing segment. That is extremely indiscreet for a sex party, but if there’s any ambiguity at all, your first step should be checking with Megan to make sure it was indeed your husband Dave who was identified (there are a lot of people named “Dave.”)&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="87" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cm89mevoq000l3b72py1wlau5@published"&gt;I have to tell you that this scenario is, at minimum, unconventional. I’ve never heard of this game, I’m not sure how or why it’s played (is the gag that the partygoers have seen these dicks before, but not generally in their flaccid state, so that’s the challenge?). Could Megan have information that she’s not sharing with you? Could it be that she knows Dave is cheating on you but has changed key (or perhaps all) the details in the story to protect herself? It’s all confusing.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="72" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cm89mf77b000p3b72mfif0c9w@published"&gt;I’m going to recommend getting more information out of Megan. Can she describe any of the dicks attributed to Dave? Maybe there’s more to tease out of this that will help clear things up. Can Megan put you in touch with someone else who was there and may have a different perspective/better means of articulating the scenario? It’s really tough to present someone with a story this convoluted as evidence of wrongdoing.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="128" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cm89df4wx002l3b72q6je1dwf@published"&gt;If and when (emphasis on the if) you are &lt;em&gt;sure&lt;/em&gt; sure, I think the best and most direct way to go about doing this is to tell him what you heard. Instead of introducing it as ironclad proof that he’s cheating on you, set up the scenario much as you did in this letter: Your friend (whether you want to identify Megan or not is your call) went to a sex party, and Dave’s name was mentioned several times as a possible attendee. Ask him why and listen to his answer. It might help to, ahead of confronting him, think about how he might explain himself out of the situation or even possible scenarios in which he isn’t cheating. I can’t think of any, but maybe you can.&lt;/p&gt;


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="186" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cm89df500002m3b72vpfat7dn@published"&gt;The idea is to be prepared and not accept bullshit, but also not to get so wrapped up in Megan’s story that you can’t receive Dave’s. He might have a verifiable alibi! If he doesn’t, there’s some chance he’ll confess when presented with the evidence. If the conversation gets too heated to continue but you are unconvinced of an explanation he’s trotted out, let him know that you don’t believe him and that you’ll pick this conversation up later. It’s astounding to consider that your partner would be so brazen as to cheat on you at sex parties that are close enough to your circle (in proximity and social overlap) that your best friend would also be in this scene, but some people really are that brazen. I worry that if he’s willing to do that, he’ll also lie right to your face and never come clean. You can’t make someone tell you the truth, but you can let him know that you don’t believe his lies. Now is the time to consider what this, if true, will mean for your relationship and your own future.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="1" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cm89dtypr003j3b72rjf8ujf2@published"&gt;&lt;span class="slate-paragraph--tombstone"&gt;—Rich&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;h3 class="subhead subhead--none" data-uri="slate.com/_components/subhead/instances/cm89dudyg003x3b72wf6bfgzu@published"&gt;
&lt;p class="subhead__marker"&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
More Advice From Slate

&lt;/h3&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="94" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cm89dbj13002fw0krcyfcc5wf@published"&gt;The other day, I was looking for my cat under my son’s bed and I found a number of really strange “things.” Not sex toys, like … unidentified objects next to a bottle of olive oil he’d apparently been using for lube. We eventually found out that he was anally masturbating with them. There’s no shame in that, but we want him to be safe, and don’t think he should be using random found objects as sex toys! &lt;a href="https://slate.com/human-interest/2023/09/anal-masturbation-sex-education-teen-advice.html"&gt;Is there a way we can talk to him about this without making him feel ashamed?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;h3 class="subhead subhead--none" data-uri="slate.com/_components/subhead/instances/cm89dxsl000423b727dg19dh2@published"&gt;
&lt;p class="subhead__marker"&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
Send Us Your Questions About the Workplace!

&lt;/h3&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="37" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cm89dxz6h00463b727wx004j5@published"&gt;The columnists behind our new advice column, &lt;a href="https://slate.com/advice/good-job"&gt;Good Job&lt;/a&gt;, want to help you navigate your social dynamics at work. Does your colleague constantly bug you after hours? Has an ill-advised work romance gone awry? &lt;a href="https://forms.gle/DEVPsiDdnLHQVX7h7"&gt;Ask us your question here&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;

  

&lt;/div&gt;

      &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Slate</author><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihAFBVV95cUxPanlYWm1lcnhvVGJseVZHcGpTN00zb3lodjlnZzVNTGFpckhIaXFHclNJTHpTaXBkZmxYZGxGUlhweW44b1VoRS1ITUlFZVFXeU1RTHh3MDlsZHlEUUpLdFZZYlQ3VlhacWQ5NHJDNUlzTmdnaFkxNzdYZEZ2dlhPSjdhU2c</guid></item><item><title>The #1 Spice to Help Lower Blood Sugar, According to a Dietitian - EatingWell</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMickFVX3lxTE44Yjg2UVZfMnNnSjlTby1hcVhtMTllUkVzam1iR1NJQ1NRRlFoY0F0SmYwLWN2MGYxcFdYNkRWTmkwTm9sek9BbFB4NEdTNlZfUU10TlkxQjFJa1NwcVpORkdlQUhBWGVIYTVPMWJvVWRJdw?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-page_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-page mntl-block structured-content" data-sc-sticky-offset="90" data-sc-ad-label-height="24" data-sc-ad-track-spacing="100" data-sc-min-track-height="250" data-sc-max-track-height="600" data-sc-breakpoint="50em" data-sc-load-immediate="4" data-sc-content-positions="[1, 1250, 1550, 1950, 2350, 2750, 3150, 3550, 3950]" data-bind-scroll-on-start="true"&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-block_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-callout mntl-sc-block-universal-callout theme-generic" data-tracking-id="mntl-sc-block-callout" data-tracking-container="true"&gt; &lt;h3 class="mntl-sc-block-universal-callout__heading"&gt;Key Takeaways&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;div class="mntl-sc-block-universal-callout__body"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Polyphenol-rich ginger is our pick for the best spice to help lower blood sugar.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ginger can also positively influence your cholesterol levels.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;High blood sugar over a prolonged period may lead to diabetes or prediabetes.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_2-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; The benefits of spices go beyond making food taste good. They have bona fide health properties, too. And when it comes to reducing blood sugar and improving insulin resistance, &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/8051448/different-types-of-cinnamon/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;cinnamon&lt;/a&gt; is perhaps the most commonly recommended spice to do just that. But as delicious as it is, if you’re solely focused on cinnamon, you may be missing out on other spices to add to your routine that can also be effective. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_3-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_4-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Learn about the No. 1 spice to lower your blood sugar, diabetes-friendly recipes to try starring the spice and other ways to manage your blood sugar levels. And guess what: our pick is just as warming as cinnamon—it's ginger.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_5-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_7-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-how-ginger-helps-lower-blood-sugar"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_8-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; How Ginger Helps Lower Blood Sugar &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_9-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Ginger tops our list for its potent blood sugar benefits. Ginger packs powerful polyphenols like gingerol, which combat inflammation, something that may indirectly help balance blood sugar, says &lt;a href="https://www.spicespicebaby.com/about/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Kanchan Koya, Ph.D.&lt;/a&gt;, author of the &lt;em&gt;Spice Spice Baby &lt;/em&gt;cookbook. “&lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/inflammation-myths-to-stop-believing-8740999" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;Inflammation&lt;/a&gt; has been linked to insulin resistance and poor blood sugar control. Therefore, balancing inflammation with spices like ginger may have a beneficial effect on blood sugar,” she says, adding that more studies are needed to confirm the connection.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_10-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_11-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Much of the research supporting the use of ginger has been done with ginger supplementation. This is different from using ginger in recipes. However, the results on ginger and blood sugar are interesting and promising. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_12-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_13-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; In a review and meta-analysis published in &lt;em&gt;Nutrients&lt;/em&gt; in 2024, researchers investigated the effects of common herbs and spices found in the Mediterranean diet—black cumin, clove, parsley, saffron, thyme, ginger, black pepper, rosemary, turmeric, basil, oregano and cinnamon—on blood sugar in people with type 2 diabetes.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="3"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; They measured fasting blood glucose levels, glycated hemoglobin (A1C) and insulin concentrations. Ginger, curcurmin, saffron and cinnamon lowered fasting blood sugar significantly, while black cumin and ginger reduced A1C and decreased insulin levels. Supplemental ginger (doses ranged from 600 to 3,000 milligrams per day) was the only spice that had a significant impact on all three outcomes that were measured. To compare, 1,000 mg of ginger is about ½ teaspoon of ground ginger or 1 teaspoon of grated raw ginger. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_14-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_16-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_17-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; “Some research indicates that ginger can positively impact blood sugars by improving insulin sensitivity and slowing down the digestion of carbohydrates, which leads to less of a spike in blood sugars after a meal,” says &lt;a href="https://www.topnutritioncoaching.com/dietitians/colette-micko" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1" rel="nofollow"&gt;Colette Micko, RD&lt;/a&gt;, a registered dietitian and diabetes educator at Top Nutrition Coaching. That research was a meta-analysis of 10 studies published in &lt;em&gt;Evidence-Based Complementary and Alternative Medicine&lt;/em&gt; in 2018.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="4"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Ginger may inhibit enzymes that play a role in the digestion and absorption of carbohydrates, as well as impact pathways related to glucose metabolism and protect beta cells (insulin-producing cells in the pancreas), the authors of that study point out.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_18-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_19-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Ginger presents additional benefits, Micko notes, “Many people who have prediabetes and diabetes are at high risk of cardiovascular disease, and ginger has been shown to positively impact cholesterol levels.”
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_20-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_21-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; While we don’t have much clinical data examining the effect of culinary use of ginger, Koya notes that cooking with the spice can only help. “There is little downside to using ginger, so I say why not incorporate it for those beneficial polyphenols, anti-inflammatory and digestion-boosting effects,” she says. The one caution is &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/what-is-acid-reflux-8760717" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;if you have heartburn&lt;/a&gt;, as large amounts of ginger can aggravate symptoms, Koya adds.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_22-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_23-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Consuming a variety of plants—including herbs and spices—is an important strategy to help prevent diabetes or manage blood sugar if you have the condition. “Herbs and spices add flavor and variety. They also have inflammation-reducing potential,” says Micko. In addition, herbs and spices contain no added sodium or fat, important factors to consider if you have diabetes and need to pay extra attention to your heart health.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_24-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_25-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Yet, keep in mind that simply adding one spice or herb to your diet without making other changes will not magically lower your blood sugar. That’s where that recommendation to consume a variety of herbs, spices and other plant foods, like vegetables, fruits, legumes, nuts and seeds is key when you’re putting together a blood-sugar-friendly diet.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_26-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_28-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-what-is-high-blood-sugar"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_29-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; What Is High Blood Sugar?  &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_30-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; High blood sugar, also known as hyperglycemia, is defined as having blood sugar that is higher than normal. Over time, high blood sugar can lead to a diagnosis of prediabetes or diabetes. In people who have been diagnosed with diabetes, high blood sugar can occur for many reasons, according to the American Diabetes Association (ADA).&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="1"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_31-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_32-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;li&gt;If you have type 1 diabetes and you didn’t take enough insulin.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;If you have type 2 diabetes, you have insulin resistance and your cells are not taking up blood sugar from your bloodstream as they should. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Because you ate more or moved less—or a combination of both. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Due to physical stress from an illness, such as a cold or flu.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Due to psychological stress.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Due to the dawn phenomenon, a surge of hormones that occurs in the early morning.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_33-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_34-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; These are just some of the reasons you may experience high blood sugar. Chronically high blood sugars in people with diabetes are dangerous and can increase the risk of complications such as heart disease, kidney disease and nerve damage (neuropathy). Extremely high blood sugar can result in diabetic ketoacidosis (more common in people with type 1 diabetes), a life-threatening emergency, per the ADA.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="2"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_35-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_37-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-other-ways-to-lower-blood-sugar"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_38-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; Other Ways to Lower Blood Sugar &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_39-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Lifestyle factors such as regular exercise, stress management, adequate sleep and smoking cessation are also important strategies that assist in lowering blood sugars, notes the American Heart Association.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="5"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_40-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_41-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Two positive changes you can make today is get adequate sleep tonight and find ways to move more in your day, particularly after eating. “Aiming for at least seven hours of sleep per night has been shown to positively impact blood sugar, metabolism and overall health,” Micko says. “Walking 10 to 15 minutes after eating has been shown to greatly reduce post-meal blood sugar levels by increasing insulin sensitivity,” she adds.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_42-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_44-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-ginger-recipes-to-try"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_45-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; Ginger Recipes to Try  &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_46-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; There are so many opportunities to add ginger to the foods you enjoy. Combine ginger with foods high in fiber, which is a key ingredient in blood sugar management, notes the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="6"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Fiber is the indigestible part of carbohydrate found in plants (fruit, vegetables, nuts, seeds, legumes and whole grains), which promotes digestive regularity and feelings of fullness, contributes to gut health and reduces blood sugar spikes. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_47-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_49-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_51-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-the-bottom-line"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_52-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; The Bottom Line  &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_53-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Ginger may assist in reducing blood sugars by improving insulin sensitivity and reducing inflammation. However, keep in mind that ginger is not meant to replace medication, and it won’t magically reduce blood sugar on its own. Instead, use ginger alongside lifestyle modifications, such as eating a plant-forward diet, regular exercise, stress management and adequate sleep. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_54-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_55-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Your best bet is to add ginger to the food you eat, such as smoothies, oats, salad dressings, vegetable bowls, meat marinades and more. If you are curious about ginger supplementation, talk to your health care provider or registered dietitian.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_56-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>EatingWell</author><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMickFVX3lxTE44Yjg2UVZfMnNnSjlTby1hcVhtMTllUkVzam1iR1NJQ1NRRlFoY0F0SmYwLWN2MGYxcFdYNkRWTmkwTm9sek9BbFB4NEdTNlZfUU10TlkxQjFJa1NwcVpORkdlQUhBWGVIYTVPMWJvVWRJdw</guid></item><item><title>7 tips to burn calories faster - DNA India</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMilwFBVV95cUxQQlJxTEY0ek9WdjB4SjN1SHJRZWhtMks3QUc2elpKWU5CS2NVWXlkMXhWb0xtMTlQV09mWmc1SFYtbkZ5ZHNPV05FcWt4Uy1PVDJ1NlhLN2FqQ0JxdVNENzBqMmp6eGNuWmxDR1FlZkt0SE9KUjZwZUN5X25rWGoyYjFUUk9LYy1xN0VkNmRrTEl3cmRhNktr0gGXAUFVX3lxTFBCUnFMRjR6T1Z2MHhKM3VIclFlaG0ySzdBRzZ6WkpZTkJLY1VZeWQxeFZvTG0xOVBXT2ZaZzVIVi1uRnlkc09XTkVxa3hTLU9UMnU2WEs3YWpDQnF1U0Q3MGoyanp4Y25abENHUWVmS3RIT0pSNnBlQ3lfbmtYajJiMVRST0tjLXE3RWQ2ZGtMSXdyZGE2S2s?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="textBoxData"&gt;&lt;p animate-in="fade-in" animate-in-delay="0.0s" animate-in-duration="0.0s"&gt;High stress raises cortisol, which can lead to fat storage, so try relaxation techniques like yoga or meditation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>DNA India</author><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 15:36:46 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilwFBVV95cUxQQlJxTEY0ek9WdjB4SjN1SHJRZWhtMks3QUc2elpKWU5CS2NVWXlkMXhWb0xtMTlQV09mWmc1SFYtbkZ5ZHNPV05FcWt4Uy1PVDJ1NlhLN2FqQ0JxdVNENzBqMmp6eGNuWmxDR1FlZkt0SE9KUjZwZUN5X25rWGoyYjFUUk9LYy1xN0VkNmRrTEl3cmRhNktr0gGXAUFVX3lxTFBCUnFMRjR6T1Z2MHhKM3VIclFlaG0ySzdBRzZ6WkpZTkJLY1VZeWQxeFZvTG0xOVBXT2ZaZzVIVi1uRnlkc09XTkVxa3hTLU9UMnU2WEs3YWpDQnF1U0Q3MGoyanp4Y25abENHUWVmS3RIT0pSNnBlQ3lfbmtYajJiMVRST0tjLXE3RWQ2ZGtMSXdyZGE2S2s</guid></item><item><title>Newborn babies exposed to measles in Texas hospital amid outbreak - mySA</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMingFBVV95cUxPWUR4M1NMOVdBd045WjlGY3NjM2FTQ1lDSGpmSE1hZUF0b3JlcDJlMkJBWm9wZHAyckZoUDFvaEFENWwwNDIxVk5wT25qZDBxTHRmem9NR2wtNmw3SnNNSUdSbFAwcVNYQ2RTZjQwQlZRMnBxOVFpOEVXYUVZaG5lQjV3TExWTHRZUlpSZGhZSVp0UXZFODFmVW5GNGtNZw?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href="https://www.mysanantonio.com/news/local/article/measles-outbreak-texas-oklahoma-new-mexico-20221891.php" data-link="native" class=""&gt;fast-growing measles outbreak&lt;/a&gt; continues to impact lives across Texas and has now reached newborn babies at a hospital in West Texas. Infants as young as three days old are receiving antibody injections to help their bodies fight the virus due to possible exposure, &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/texas-measles-outbreak-hospital-newborn-babies-exposed-rcna196519" data-link="native" target="_blank" rel="noopener" class=""&gt;according to a NBC News report&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hospital staff are reportedly scrambling with damage control efforts after new moms, newborn babies and their families were exposed to measles at University Medical Center Children’s Hospital in Lubbock Wednesday, March 12. NBC reported a woman who gave birth at the hospital was infected with measles, and "doctors didn't realize until the young mother had been admitted and in labor." &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Others were unknowingly exposed to the virus, "one of the most contagious in the world," according to NBC. Measles can cause serious health complications, especially in children younger than 5 years old, according to the &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/measles/about/index.html" data-link="native" target="_blank" rel="noopener" class=""&gt;Centers for Disease Control and Prevention&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Medical staff began "implementing emergency masking policies" and giving babies barely three days old injections of immunoglobulin, "an antibody that helps their fragile immune system fight off infections." NBC reported that a 2021 study "found the therapy to be highly effective in protecting exposed newborns."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;The exact number of people exposed to the virus has not been confirmed, and it's unclear when the woman tested positive for measles, NBC reported. Considering the virus can live in the air or on surfaces for up to two hours, health officials are working to contact everyone who may have been exposed to this patient. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href="https://www.mysanantonio.com/news/local/article/texas-measles-outbreak-san-antonio-20184311.php" data-link="native" target="_blank" rel="noopener" class=""&gt;measles outbreak&lt;/a&gt; has now spread to 11 Texas counties, according to the Texas Department of State Health Services (DSHS). Recently, the outbreak was &lt;a href="https://www.mysanantonio.com/news/local/article/measles-outbreak-texas-oklahoma-new-mexico-20221891.php" data-link="native" target="_blank" rel="noopener" class=""&gt;linked to a death in New Mexico&lt;/a&gt; and cases in Oklahoma, according to reports issued by health departments in each state. Texas' case count is now at 259 as of Friday, March 14, &lt;a href="https://www.mysanantonio.com/news/local/article/measles-texas-20213617.php" data-link="native" class=""&gt;an increase from 223 on Tuesday&lt;/a&gt;, March 11.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>mySA</author><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 15:33:36 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMingFBVV95cUxPWUR4M1NMOVdBd045WjlGY3NjM2FTQ1lDSGpmSE1hZUF0b3JlcDJlMkJBWm9wZHAyckZoUDFvaEFENWwwNDIxVk5wT25qZDBxTHRmem9NR2wtNmw3SnNNSUdSbFAwcVNYQ2RTZjQwQlZRMnBxOVFpOEVXYUVZaG5lQjV3TExWTHRZUlpSZGhZSVp0UXZFODFmVW5GNGtNZw</guid></item><item><title>Man notices strange symptom while eating sandwich, now has few month to live: ‘Am I not chewing it properly’ - Hindustan Times</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMi-AFBVV95cUxPcTQwWjExUHIxSm8yZHUxdmlYR3JOT3ItcHd5WlB1clZfM293QVFzVkgzeWFTMU1GVlJlRUdjYUJmOTFaS3hWWnBjck1OempBbG93XzZlTjE1RHV1VjdfZmZQYmxrMFh1SGtlejdmWGZ6bUdfak5KamlZel9FbWVjQm9QLTVsQ2dvUnlIZVVSODM3RlhUcllFVWllQkl1Yk1ELUdNZlBFdHBUbTFXSHJyN1NqRndfWkROQnoyR2xyZDNXeFZRUTNEZk45U0l1QU9oM0hpX1lPSFdBNHRxa0lhdXNfVVJHZGtOdVRvblpCTE5mdXpOelkzOQ?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="detail " dataid="/trending/man-notices-strange-symptom-while-eating-sandwich-now-has-few-month-to-live-am-i-not-chewing-it-properly-101742033433074.html"&gt; &lt;div class="storyParagraphFigure"&gt; &lt;p&gt;What seemed like a routine meal turned into a life-changing moment for Des Longstaff, 39. Struggling to swallow a bacon and sausage sandwich, he sought medical help—only to be diagnosed with advanced stage-four oesophageal adenocarcinoma, an aggressive cancer that has spread to his liver, reported the &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/uk-news/i-noticed-weird-symptom-eating-34866366" target="_blank" class="manualbacklink"&gt;Mirror&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;figure class=""&gt; &lt;span class=""&gt; &lt;picture&gt; &lt;source media="(max-width:767px)" srcset="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/03/15/550x309/akjbakcna_1742034086265_1742034091076.png" alt=" He visited a doctor, who advised him to undergo an endoscopy.(Pexel)" title=" He visited a doctor, who advised him to undergo an endoscopy.(Pexel)"&gt;&lt;/source&gt; &lt;img src="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/03/15/550x309/akjbakcna_1742034086265_1742034091076.png" alt=" He visited a doctor, who advised him to undergo an endoscopy.(Pexel)" title=" He visited a doctor, who advised him to undergo an endoscopy.(Pexel)"&gt; &lt;/picture&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;figcaption&gt;He visited a doctor, who advised him to undergo an endoscopy.(Pexel)&lt;/figcaption&gt; &lt;/figure&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;p id="readMoreFTUser"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The landscape contractor, determined to prolong his time with his five-year-old son, is now exploring alternative treatments to fight the disease. According to Cancer Research UK, oesophageal cancer at this stage is typically incurable, but Longstaff is seeking every possible option to extend his life.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p id="shortEntryContainer"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="mt10 mb10 htEchoArticlePromo"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="predictorShow mb20" data-vars-predictor="true" data-vars-quiz="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="quizShow mb20" data-vars-minimized="false" data-vars-predictor="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Recalling the moment he first noticed something was wrong, he told &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.bristolpost.co.uk/news/health/dad-battling-silent-killer-months-10025270" target="_blank" class="manualbacklink"&gt;BristolLive&lt;/a&gt;: “I am a landscaper by trade, and I was doing a job for one of my friends when his partner made me a bacon and sausage sandwich. When I was eating it – I hadn’t put any sauce on or anything – it sort of got lodged in my oesophagus, and I had a good pint of water, but it still wouldn’t budge.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;“It was to the point where you’re thinking you’re choking. I thought to myself, ‘Am I not chewing it properly?’”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;Diagnosis&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Following this incident, Longstaff visited a doctor, who advised him to undergo an endoscopy. However, before the procedure could take place, he began vomiting blood and later noticed blood in his stool. He was immediately sent to the hospital, where a 35cm tumour was discovered in his lower oesophagus on Christmas Eve.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Initially, he had hoped for keyhole surgery to remove the tumour, but further scans revealed that the cancer had already spread to his liver, severely limiting his treatment options.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Longstaff has since begun immunotherapy to help his body’s white blood cells fight the cancer, along with another form of chemotherapy. However, he acknowledges that these treatments are not curative. “It is palliative, and it is to keep me comfortable so I don’t die straight away,” he said.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;“I couldn’t have knocked it back. It is something to attack the cancer; otherwise, it is going to spread all over the place. The NHS has only given me 12 months to live.”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;His mother, Tracy, has launched a GoFundMe campaign to raise money for treatment in Germany, where he hopes to receive specialised care. “Des is unable to work and will not be able to for the foreseeable future. We are exploring new treatments in Germany to give Des the best chance of a five-year-plus life expectancy,” she wrote.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The fundraiser has already collected over £31,000, with the targeted amount set at £43,000. The proposed treatment, which costs €52,000 (approximately &lt;span class="webrupee"&gt;₹&lt;/span&gt;46.5 lakh), involves a combination of therapies aimed at targeting the cancerous cells in his liver.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Longstaff remains hopeful about the medical approach in Germany, explaining, “They have a totally different outlook. They have one of the best treatment plans over there, and there is no such thing as terminal. If you are terminal, you are riddled with it, but I’m not. It has stayed localised, and at the moment, I have two small dots, and they are going to turn into tumours if I am not careful.”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Detailing the treatment plan, he shared, “So the idea is to go to Germany, where they are going to target the liver. It is basically an injection going into the liver that will give me the highest dose of chemotherapy, but it will only target those two dots. They are going to cut off the main artery to the main tumour in my oesophagus and let that die for five days.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;“They will then cut it out and scrape around my diaphragm and around my stomach lining, but they will build the stomach lining up by putting mesh a…&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Hindustan Times</author><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 15:00:20 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi-AFBVV95cUxPcTQwWjExUHIxSm8yZHUxdmlYR3JOT3ItcHd5WlB1clZfM293QVFzVkgzeWFTMU1GVlJlRUdjYUJmOTFaS3hWWnBjck1OempBbG93XzZlTjE1RHV1VjdfZmZQYmxrMFh1SGtlejdmWGZ6bUdfak5KamlZel9FbWVjQm9QLTVsQ2dvUnlIZVVSODM3RlhUcllFVWllQkl1Yk1ELUdNZlBFdHBUbTFXSHJyN1NqRndfWkROQnoyR2xyZDNXeFZRUTNEZk45U0l1QU9oM0hpX1lPSFdBNHRxa0lhdXNfVVJHZGtOdVRvblpCTE5mdXpOelkzOQ</guid></item><item><title>Opioid orphans: Grandparents struggle to raise children left behind - The Seattle Times</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiwAFBVV95cUxOV1NPQmMzX3pHYUdZUkN4d2pyMG5XdXpjTDRHbWJmSWE0ekNBX2JtZVdNYnR4cDQwRXRPVDR0YnJ4MWdXcnQ0WTNxTlR5V3FGVXlSOHNwUXdsUlVqdWJxUkM1WmRJeWZYR2V5bUlPeU1ySEJEdFZhYlVaUXZ2LUZFNlJaYUh0UUpuTHFab2tyZ29qTzc3cHUyVm5yQXVxX2dVcUo2TXk2RUJzNUo3Nm5keGdtZVlqSXQ4UE1mOG1KTXc?oc=5</link><description>&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiwAFBVV95cUxOV1NPQmMzX3pHYUdZUkN4d2pyMG5XdXpjTDRHbWJmSWE0ekNBX2JtZVdNYnR4cDQwRXRPVDR0YnJ4MWdXcnQ0WTNxTlR5V3FGVXlSOHNwUXdsUlVqdWJxUkM1WmRJeWZYR2V5bUlPeU1ySEJEdFZhYlVaUXZ2LUZFNlJaYUh0UUpuTHFab2tyZ29qTzc3cHUyVm5yQXVxX2dVcUo2TXk2RUJzNUo3Nm5keGdtZVlqSXQ4UE1mOG1KTXc?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;Opioid orphans: Grandparents struggle to raise children left behind&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Seattle Times&lt;/font&gt;</description><author>The Seattle Times</author><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiwAFBVV95cUxOV1NPQmMzX3pHYUdZUkN4d2pyMG5XdXpjTDRHbWJmSWE0ekNBX2JtZVdNYnR4cDQwRXRPVDR0YnJ4MWdXcnQ0WTNxTlR5V3FGVXlSOHNwUXdsUlVqdWJxUkM1WmRJeWZYR2V5bUlPeU1ySEJEdFZhYlVaUXZ2LUZFNlJaYUh0UUpuTHFab2tyZ29qTzc3cHUyVm5yQXVxX2dVcUo2TXk2RUJzNUo3Nm5keGdtZVlqSXQ4UE1mOG1KTXc</guid></item><item><title>Oregon health Q&amp;A: Will COVID-19 vaccines be updated again in coming months? - OregonLive</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMivAFBVV95cUxNNERVOWlaRXFscHFPTnZHanp5RXNHNGdYTkRobkRVVWZVQVllM2kzY01BRUxqVFBhdUw2RTFrSFllZ3dYMkZkWlpZa1hqSXlvaFBlb2l1dTM2VWllQ1dJOEk0NktPMlVyaGszWGkzX2hxV2NTcFB1Q2NJOEpWNVJuZTdWUFJOUUFIdVV1VVZwR19vM1dkU3dnZ25Nd3Y1S0UzZ0Z2cnlGbXRIanFldkJNQUgwbmRvSk83UmJSQ9IB0AFBVV95cUxONnNqWElQYkxmRlUwanpmUTN6WTkyMmpMcnpVNENOVDAydzBVWlZHZ0tManl1WkhKX2ctb1RXNzBWUmpsQUNSRm1nYVdyQVZzczlrYWtPOWdCTGlPd3pBWElySzFqNlQyR3lGZllldDNqTVpwSG5FN1hLSEE4amZhd3dCY2F1RzAzd3I1OEF6OHgxb2szSUtWdXd3bEI3MG5SS1ppVlRBTS1qQUl1VjQ0dHAtMy1SVnF0akVZLW8xTlRCUVdlOXNjdWs3MWQ5MktF?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content "&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="6YQMATDUTJA3PK5WFG3JECWBCA"&gt;Questions are answered by experts at the Oregon Health Authority, other state agencies or community partners. Questions and answers are republished by permission.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-1"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="LXOCGKRCGZDS3ILHABDUMYVFNU"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Q: &lt;/b&gt;I know I need to wait six months for my next COVID-19 shot. In my case it will be the end of March. Will the COVID shots available be updated again, or will they be the same formula I received before? &lt;i&gt;– April, Eugene&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-2"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="VEKOTLFQKNAVNPNXH63OJD5H6Y"&gt;&lt;b&gt;A: &lt;/b&gt;The additional dose(s) of the 2024-2025 COVID-19 vaccine available to people ages 65+ or those with compromised immune systems are exactly the same as those available last fall and throughout the 2024-2025 respiratory virus season. However, we do expect COVID vaccines may be updated with a new formula next fall for the 2025-2026 season.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-3"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="IUI3NI42NZBR7JN3IESS3SR4ZY"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Q: &lt;/b&gt;I am a 67-year-old woman who, as a child, had mumps and was vaccinated for measles and rubella. Do I need an MMR booster (measles, mumps and rubella)? I am overweight, diabetic, asthmatic, and I just had open heart surgery. &lt;i&gt;– Claudia, Gaston&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-4"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="JP7WT2RKONGUVJWZ36O2HN6LDQ"&gt;&lt;b&gt;A: &lt;/b&gt;Claudia, one dose of measles-containing vaccine is recommended for persons of your age. However, if you got it during 1963-1968, you &lt;i&gt;might&lt;/i&gt; have gotten a formulation (“killed” or “inactivated” vaccine) that was less effective, and you can consider getting the current MMR vaccine. The other measles vaccine available to you at that time was very effective and should protect you for life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-5"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="OZ7CKFKQWZGAJO4KDNME6FPIKA"&gt;If you have your original vaccination records, you can show it to your provider who can tell you which version you got. Alternatively, if you want to play it safe, getting one dose of today’s MMR vaccine is perfectly fine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-6" class="middleParagraph"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="73CPQKIWRVHF3BAOYJ5DWWN6BU"&gt;We don’t recommend additional doses based on the underlying conditions you mention.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-7"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="DWFU6VWA6VBA5K2TTV6D5AV5CE"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Q:&lt;/b&gt; Is the Texas measles outbreak “rubella” or the other measles? I had rubella in the 1970s here in Portland, as an 11 year old. I was immunized for the other during childhood. Which measles is this? &lt;i&gt;– Jennifer, Portland&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-8"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="K3J4ZLAZOZAKNL2IVBTQI2776A"&gt;&lt;b&gt;A: &lt;/b&gt;We know, it can be confusing! The scientific term for measles is actually “rubeola” (pronounced “roo-be-OH-lah”) which is circulating in &lt;a href="https://links-2.govdelivery.com/CL0/https:%2F%2Fwww.dshs.texas.gov%2Fnews-alerts%2Fmeasles-outbreak-2025%3Futm_medium=email%26utm_source=govdelivery/1/0101019591cda6f1-da624835-415c-4d4d-8aed-c0117ce589da-000000/ZjW9GCdmoNO63jOY2xiPEQ8f1_D_Y0bkfBpFF3nk948=396" rel="" target="_blank" title="https://nam10.safelinks.protection.outlook.com/?url=https%3A%2F%2Flinks-2.govdelivery.com%2FCL0%2Fhttps%3A%252F%252Fwww.dshs.texas.gov%252Fnews-alerts%252Fmeasles-outbreak-2025%253Futm_medium%3Demail%2526utm_source%3Dgovdelivery%2F1%2F0101019591cda6f1-da624835-415c-4d4d-8aed-c0117ce589da-000000%2FZjW9GCdmoNO63jOY2xiPEQ8f1_D_Y0bkfBpFF3nk948%3D396&amp;amp;data=05%7C02%7Ctbottomly%40oregonian.com%7C93785e8794e5431ab35b08dd628569d7%7C1fe6294574e64203848fb9b82929f9d4%7C0%7C0%7C638775047374790662%7CUnknown%7CTWFpbGZsb3d8eyJFbXB0eU1hcGkiOnRydWUsIlYiOiIwLjAuMDAwMCIsIlAiOiJXaW4zMiIsIkFOIjoiTWFpbCIsIldUIjoyfQ%3D%3D%7C0%7C%7C%7C&amp;amp;sdata=md%2BOovtH5C9kkP68h3mj4yg1rsHoQeDVy%2BpLVIZuSUQ%3D&amp;amp;reserved=0"&gt;Texas&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://links-2.govdelivery.com/CL0/https:%2F%2Fwww.nmhealth.org%2Fabout%2Ferd%2Fideb%2Fmog%2F%3Futm_medium=email%26utm_source=govdelivery/1/0101019591cda6f1-da624835-415c-4d4d-8aed-c0117ce589da-000000/vdwZejlglmk2j28_Ul-_QHblABShM2U2SE1_bFB8ptU=396" rel="" target="_blank" title="https://nam10.safelinks.protection.outlook.com/?url=https%3A%2F%2Flinks-2.govdelivery.com%2FCL0%2Fhttps%3A%252F%252Fwww.nmhealth.org%252Fabout%252Ferd%252Fideb%252Fmog%252F%253Futm_medium%3Demail%2526utm_source%3Dgovdelivery%2F1%2F0101019591cda6f1-da624835-415c-4d4d-8aed-c0117ce589da-000000%2FvdwZejlglmk2j28_Ul-_QHblABShM2U2SE1_bFB8ptU%3D396&amp;amp;data=05%7C02%7Ctbottomly%40oregonian.com%7C93785e8794e5431ab35b08dd628569d7%7C1fe6294574e64203848fb9b82929f9d4%7C0%7C0%7C638775047374806687%7CUnknown%7CTWFpbGZsb3d8eyJFbXB0eU1hcGkiOnRydWUsIlYiOiIwLjAuMDAwMCIsIlAiOiJXaW4zMiIsIkFOIjoiTWFpbCIsIldUIjoyfQ%3D%3D%7C0%7C%7C%7C&amp;amp;sdata=7oaE8pYxT1nemtcf%2FotB7SZ73s%2FPqlbTYeTGV%2B2MsYM%3D&amp;amp;reserved=0"&gt;New Mexico&lt;/a&gt; right now. Cases in the U.S. are imported from abroad regularly and sometimes cause outbreaks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-9"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="BLZEWEPZNRGKPBMRD3EXADIDZQ"&gt;Rubella, however, is the scientific term for &lt;a href="https://links-2.govdelivery.com/CL0/https:%2F%2Fwww.cdc.gov%2Frubella%2Fabout%2Findex.html%3Futm_medium=email%26utm_source=govdelivery/1/0101019591cda6f1-da624835-415c-4d4d-8aed-c0117ce589da-000000/PBUc1BtZcO4k3LVaXbinEcyUIu_4m35F4qos0my2LyI=396" rel="" target="_blank" title="https://nam10.safelinks.protection.outlook.com/?url=https%3A%2F%2Flinks-2.govdelivery.com%2FCL0%2Fhttps%3A%252F%252Fwww.cdc.gov%252Frubella%252Fabout%252Findex.html%253Futm_medium%3Demail%2526utm_source%3Dgovdelivery%2F1%2F0101019591cda6f1-da624835-415c-4d4d-8aed-c0117ce589da-000000%2FPBUc1BtZcO4k3LVaXbinEcyUIu_4m35F4qos0my2LyI%3D396&amp;amp;data=05%7C02%7Ctbottomly%40oregonian.com%7C93785e8794e5431ab35b08dd628569d7%7C1fe6294574e64203848fb9b82929f9d4%7C0%7C0%7C638775047374821394%7CUnknown%7CTWFpbGZsb3d8eyJFbXB0eU1hcGkiOnRydWUsIlYiOiIwLjAuMDAwMCIsIlAiOiJXaW4zMiIsIkFOIjoiTWFpbCIsIldUIjoyfQ%3D%3D%7C0%7C%7C%7C&amp;amp;sdata=TPCAPubOvM6ZTS5AreyaUkFvLXlWjckIBdgOQg2Qlio%3D&amp;amp;reserved=0"&gt;German measles&lt;/a&gt;, which is pronounced “roo-BELL-ah.” Rubella is associated with birth defects and was eliminated from the Americas in 2009. We almost never see rubella in the U.S. anymore and, if we did, it would be a big deal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-10"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="BN5WUXFTIBAM7IINV3J7HSCNHI"&gt;&lt;i&gt;If you have questions about health topics for the Oregon Health Authority, &lt;/i&gt;&lt;a href="https://links-2.govdelivery.com/CL0/https:%2F%2Fapp.smartsheet.com%2Fb%2Fform%2Fdd321356940e488c99854ff14e80b503%3Futm_medium=email%26utm_source=govdelivery/2/010101944d41fe7a-ace2b35b-c505-4e7a-8738-d2e1035e7e69-000000/PdYGlLTPRVS-F1_LT7bwvkeh17nLQOBs7RdXGfThCKo=387" rel="" target="_blank" title="https://nam10.safelinks.protection.outlook.com/?url=https%3A%2F%2Flinks-2.govdelivery.com%2FCL0%2Fhttps%3A%252F%252Fapp.smartsheet.com%252Fb%252Fform%252Fdd321356940e488c99854ff14e80b503%253Futm_medium%3Demail%2526utm_source%3Dgovdelivery%2F2%2F010101944d41fe7a-ace2b35b-c505-4e7a-8738-d2e1035e7e69-000000%2FPdYGlLTPRVS-F1_LT7bwvkeh17nLQOBs7RdXGfThCKo%3D387&amp;amp;data=05%7C02%7Cdvattiat%40oregonian.com%7C9155014ee7974fc901e408dd47090ba8%7C1fe6294574e64203848fb9b82929f9d4%7C0%7C0%7C638744826359692907%7CUnknown%7CTWFpbGZsb3d8eyJFbXB0eU1hcGkiOnRydWUsIlYiOiIwLjAuMDAwMCIsIlAiOiJXaW4zMiIsIkFOIjoiTWFpbCIsIldUIjoyfQ%3D%3D%7C0%7C%7C%7C&amp;amp;sdata=RXSQ8KA2iG3Dmkq785P9f64APUGV0%2BWUL4nCyBP0g2M%3D&amp;amp;reserved=0"&gt;&lt;i&gt;submit your question here&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;i&gt;. Although the agency is unable to answer every question, it will try to address those of interest to a broad audience. Please understand that OHA is unable to provide specific medical advice for personal medical conditions.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-11"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="D2FFFUUHDNE7FLAPG2RNIRNHXY"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-12"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>OregonLive</author><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMivAFBVV95cUxNNERVOWlaRXFscHFPTnZHanp5RXNHNGdYTkRobkRVVWZVQVllM2kzY01BRUxqVFBhdUw2RTFrSFllZ3dYMkZkWlpZa1hqSXlvaFBlb2l1dTM2VWllQ1dJOEk0NktPMlVyaGszWGkzX2hxV2NTcFB1Q2NJOEpWNVJuZTdWUFJOUUFIdVV1VVZwR19vM1dkU3dnZ25Nd3Y1S0UzZ0Z2cnlGbXRIanFldkJNQUgwbmRvSk83UmJSQ9IB0AFBVV95cUxONnNqWElQYkxmRlUwanpmUTN6WTkyMmpMcnpVNENOVDAydzBVWlZHZ0tManl1WkhKX2ctb1RXNzBWUmpsQUNSRm1nYVdyQVZzczlrYWtPOWdCTGlPd3pBWElySzFqNlQyR3lGZllldDNqTVpwSG5FN1hLSEE4amZhd3dCY2F1RzAzd3I1OEF6OHgxb2szSUtWdXd3bEI3MG5SS1ppVlRBTS1qQUl1VjQ0dHAtMy1SVnF0akVZLW8xTlRCUVdlOXNjdWs3MWQ5MktF</guid></item><item><title>4 foods a top nutrition expert avoids at all costs, and one sweet treat he eats regularly - Fortune</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiiwFBVV95cUxNTHFhWkF1empTNU1OYm5aRzVnd2hzcWxrUkpGS0RnLW1HVVlfNExQbnZ6b3NYMXRuRDFIeW9vZGNaeUZoNWxQWnBNWWZJREgtdFBnbUtlbjFlOV9OalFJcm44dXFqQlI5aDRfaUlrLXZNckdhRDc4cFAtZlZBOUtWVmxBamQ1M0FqNmh3?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div data-cy="article-image" class="sc-fac7c12f-7 ifTevn"&gt;&lt;img alt="happy african american man holding plate of chips and eating snacks from potatoes on yellow isolated background, guy in white t-shirt eats fast food" data-content-placement="primary_image" fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" data-nimg="1" class="impression-element" sizes="100vw" srcset="https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/GettyImages-1498169169-e1741985171634.jpg?w=320&amp;amp;q=75 320w, https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/GettyImages-1498169169-e1741985171634.jpg?w=384&amp;amp;q=75 384w, https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/GettyImages-1498169169-e1741985171634.jpg?w=480&amp;amp;q=75 480w, https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/GettyImages-1498169169-e1741985171634.jpg?w=576&amp;amp;q=75 576w, https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/GettyImages-1498169169-e1741985171634.jpg?w=768&amp;amp;q=75 768w, https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/GettyImages-1498169169-e1741985171634.jpg?w=1024&amp;amp;q=75 1024w, https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/GettyImages-1498169169-e1741985171634.jpg?w=1280&amp;amp;q=75 1280w, https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/GettyImages-1498169169-e1741985171634.jpg?w=1440&amp;amp;q=75 1440w" src="https://fortune.com/img-assets/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/GettyImages-1498169169-e1741985171634.jpg?w=1440&amp;amp;q=75"&gt;&lt;p data-cy="caption" class="sc-13b6974d-9 dKtuAn"&gt;The mixture of fat, sugars, and salt combined with a texture that almost dissolves in your mouth can make it hard to stop eating certain foods.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-cy="credit" class="sc-13b6974d-10 hbPqHz"&gt;Getty Images&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Fortune</author><pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 13:42:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiwFBVV95cUxNTHFhWkF1empTNU1OYm5aRzVnd2hzcWxrUkpGS0RnLW1HVVlfNExQbnZ6b3NYMXRuRDFIeW9vZGNaeUZoNWxQWnBNWWZJREgtdFBnbUtlbjFlOV9OalFJcm44dXFqQlI5aDRfaUlrLXZNckdhRDc4cFAtZlZBOUtWVmxBamQ1M0FqNmh3</guid></item></channel></rss>