<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>GNews Health</title><link>https://news.google.com/</link><description></description><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>科学家如何揭示季节性情感障碍背后的生物学-《卫报》</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/society/2025/nov/02/how-to-beat-the-winter-blues-seasonal-affective-disorder</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body-commercial-selector article-body-viewer-selector dcr-hdpgoq"&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-15rw6c2"&gt;F&lt;/span&gt;or some, the darkening days of autumn bring more than the annual ritual of reviving woolly jumpers and turning on the central heating. As the evenings close in and the mornings grow murky, energy ebbs and a heavy sadness settles in.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Although seasonal affective disorder (Sad) was only formally recognised by psychiatrists in the 1980s, the link between the seasons, mood and vitality has long been observed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="sign-in-gate"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The Yellow Emperor’s Classic of Medicine – a Chinese text from roughly 300BC – described how the seasons affect all living things. It advised that in winter, one should “retire early and get up with the sunrise”, keeping “desires and mental activity quiet and subdued, as if keeping a happy secret”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Today, scientists are rediscovering how closely tuned our biology is to the seasons. According to Dr Cathy Wyse, a chancellor’s research fellow at the University of Edinburgh, the biggest advance over the past decade “has been the realisation that seasonal changes in human mood are probably endogenous – that they’re part of our physiology”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Large-scale resources such as &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/science/2025/apr/18/uk-biobank-is-safely-sharing-health-data-to-drive-medical-research" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;the UK Biobank&lt;/a&gt; have transformed this area of research, allowing scientists to track seasonal patterns across hundreds of thousands of people over many years – something that was previously impossible.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;However, where to draw the line between normal winter sluggishness and clinical depression is not straightforward. Sad is recognised as a subtype of major depression or bipolar disorder, defined by its predictable seasonal pattern: symptoms typically begin in autumn or winter and lift in spring. Alongside typical signs of depression, people often sleep longer, feel lethargic and want to eat more, particularly carbohydrates.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The triggers of these changes are still being investigated, but they are almost certainly linked to reduced daylight. Light is the key regulator of our internal body or circadian clock, influencing the timing of hormone release, alertness and mood. Without sufficient daylight – especially when combined with too much artificial light in the evenings – these rhythms can drift out of sync with the external world.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="4bd39955-f577-4324-88ab-06658bf4a4f5" data-spacefinder-role="inline" data-spacefinder-type="model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.ImageBlockElement" class="dcr-173mewl"&gt;&lt;figcaption data-spacefinder-role="inline" class="dcr-fd61eq"&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-1inf02i"&gt;&lt;svg viewbox="0 0 18 13"&gt;&lt;path d="M18 3.5v8l-1.5 1.5h-15l-1.5-1.5v-8l1.5-1.5h3.5l2-2h4l2 2h3.5l1.5 1.5zm-9 7.5c1.9 0 3.5-1.6 3.5-3.5s-1.6-3.5-3.5-3.5-3.5 1.6-3.5 3.5 1.6 3.5 3.5 3.5z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-1qvd3m6"&gt;Amish people in the US, who spend more time outdoors and less time exposed to artificial light at night, have some of the lowest Sad rates among Caucasian populations.&lt;/span&gt; Photograph: Evelyn Hockstein/Reuters&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Some people may be more sensitive to this shift than others. Wyse and her colleagues are studying seasonal effects in &lt;a href="https://www.heliosbd.com/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;bipolar disorder&lt;/a&gt;, where manic episodes often peak in spring and depression tends to be more common in the darker months. “We suspect that people with bipolar disorder may be very sensitive to light and seasonal cues, and that’s triggering their symptoms,” said Wyse.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Even among those without clinical depression, many people experience a milder seasonal dip in mood, known as subsyndromal Sad or “the winter blues”. In the UK, an estimated one in five people are affected, though only about 2% experience full Sad.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Yet, seasonal biology extends far beyond mood. Researchers have found fluctuations in the expression of &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/ncomms8000" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;more than 4,000 protein-coding genes&lt;/a&gt; in white blood cells and fat, along with changes in the cellular composition of blood itself across the year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Wyse and her colleagues recently analysed four years of UK Biobank sleep data from half a million people. “We found that in winter, people tended to sleep longer and had increased sleeplessness – their sleep wasn’t so good as in the summer,” said Wyse, who will present these findings at the British Sleep Society conference in Brighton next week.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;However natural these seasonal changes may be, society still expects people to carry on as normal. Few of us can hibernate, however tempting that may sound. The most effective antidote to the winter slump is light. Bright light therapy remains the gold standard for treating Sad, though timing and dosage are critical (see below). For those unable to manage a daily session in front of a light box, natural sunlight is a powerful substitute.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="aae49198-892e-44fa-813c-7151b7917e50" data-spacefinder-role="showcase" data-spacefinder-type="model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.ImageBlockElement" class="dcr-5h0uf4"&gt;&lt;figcaption data-spacefinder-role="inline" class="dcr-9ktzqp"&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-1inf02i"&gt;&lt;svg viewbox="0 0 18 13"&gt;&lt;path d="M18 3.5v8l-1.5 1.5h-15l-1.5-1.5v-8l1.5-1.5h3.5l2-2h4l2 2h3.5l1.5 1.5zm-9 7.5c1.9 0 3.5-1.6 3.5-3.5s-1.6-3.5-3.5-3.5-3.5 1.6-3.5 3.5 1.6 3.5 3.5 3.5z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-1qvd3m6"&gt;‘Early morning light is especially powerful in resetting the circadian clock.’&lt;/span&gt; Photograph: Rebecca Cole/The Guardian&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Studies of Amish communities in the US – who spend more time outdoors and less time exposed to bright artificial light at night – show some of the lowest Sad rates recorded among Caucasian populations. By contrast, the prevalence in New York is about 4.7%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Exposure to bright, natural light early in the day helps to synchronise the circadian clock and suppress lingering melatonin, a night-time hormone that may make a person feel groggy. Light also has a direct alerting effect: one study found that an hour of blue-enriched light boosted reaction times more than the equivalent of two cups of coffee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;But light isn’t the whole story. Cognitive behavioural therapy tailored for Sad can be &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/25859764/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;as effective as light therapy&lt;/a&gt;, helping people reframe their relationship with winter rather than just manage symptoms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Winter will come regardless. By shifting how we think about it, we can reclaim some joy from the darker months.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="how-to-beat-the-winter-blues" class="dcr-12ibh7f"&gt;How to beat the winter blues&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;footer class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;&lt;ul class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;
 &lt;li class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;
  &lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Seek the morning sun: &lt;/strong&gt;Even on grey days, step outside as early as possible. Daylight resets your circadian clock, improves alertness and suppresses melatonin. Early morning light is especially powerful.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
 &lt;li class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;
  &lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Try a light box: &lt;/strong&gt;Brightness levels are measured in lux. A typical Sad lamp will emit light at about 10,000 lux – 20 to 40 times brighter than typical office lighting, and roughly equivalent to outdoor light on an overcast summer’s day. Sit in front of it for 20–30 minutes soon after waking.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
 &lt;li class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;
  &lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Check your sleep habits: &lt;/strong&gt;Stick to regular sleep and wake times, avoid screens late at night and keep evening lighting warm and dim. This helps prevent your internal rhythms from drifting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
 &lt;li class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;
  &lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Get outside – properly:&lt;/strong&gt; Even on a cloudy day in&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;January, outdoor light is roughly 10 times brighter than indoors. Aim for at least an hour a day, ideally combining it with something enjoyable: a walk, a coffee in the park or a kick-about with friends.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
 &lt;li class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;
  &lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Plan winter pleasures: &lt;/strong&gt;Reframe thoughts such as “I hate winter” into “winter is harder, but I can plan around it”. Embrace cosy rituals, such as candles, hot chocolate or warm baths and schedule social or outdoor activities, such as cold-water dips or winter hikes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
 &lt;li class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;
  &lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Know when to seek help: &lt;/strong&gt;If mood, sleep or motivation problems persist for weeks or interfere with daily life, speak to a GP or mental health professional. Sad is treatable.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span data-dcr-style="bullet"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; In the UK, the charity &lt;a href="https://www.mind.org.uk/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;Mind&lt;/a&gt; is available on 0300 123 3393 and &lt;a href="https://www.childline.org.uk/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;Childline&lt;/a&gt; on 0800 1111. In the US, call or text &lt;a href="https://www.mhanational.org/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;Mental Health America&lt;/a&gt; at 988 or chat 988lifeline.org. In Australia, support is available at &lt;a href="https://www.beyondblue.org.au/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;Beyond Blue&lt;/a&gt; on 1300 22 4636, &lt;a href="https://www.lifeline.org.au/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;Lifeline&lt;/a&gt; on 13 11 14, and at &lt;a href="https://mensline.org.au/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;MensLine&lt;/a&gt; on 1300 789 978&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/footer&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Guardian</author><pubDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2025 13:12:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipwFBVV95cUxOanVwWWVsYk1wSlprWTRKSEVjYi1faWMyNE1LdFFFZjlraElzTFZKN2Q1aFJwSnNFdnotVm0yY0l5SVNINXRrTTRRTWk3eFdPa3YtNjJDTjYySkJTVzBjTzE3d0JTZ1U0T0xyMHFtSmtTNjc4MmhDbmV6a1VnU2dYX1BhaENid2RZU1MyOXBrWWdlaTRYRFhxMzVlMjkwaUZlNVFKU1Fmdw</guid></item><item><title>营养学家实际上是在乞求你吃这些营养素，因为这种情况已经成为一种合法的健康危机- BuzzFeed</title><link>https://www.buzzfeed.com/juliekendrick/shortfall-nutrients-scary-sc</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="subbuzz buzz-width--standard__subbuzz buzz-type--long__subbuzz subbuzz-text
  subbuzz-index-11
  
  
  
  
  " data-keywords="fast fashion" data-module="subbuzz-text"&gt;
  
  &lt;p id="139570610" class="subbuzz-anchor"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;





&lt;p&gt;All this talk of shortfalls might leave you wondering if it’s at all possible to keep yourself well nourished these days. But if you’re reaching for a bottle of multivitamins right to supplement the gaps, you may want to slow your roll, experts said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Registered dietician nutritionist &lt;a href="https://www.mpmnutrition.com/about" target="_blank" data-skimlinks-tracking="7965912" data-affiliate="true"&gt;Marissa Karp&lt;/a&gt; had this advice: “While supplements can help us bridge the gap and serve as an insurance policy, they aren’t a replacement for eating nourishing foods. If you aren’t already eating well, moving your body, drinking water and managing your stress, don’t waste money on supplements. Taking supplements and then eating processed foods is not the same as eating a whole foods diet and using supplements to help ensure you’re getting enough.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She offered this example of the joy of whole foods: “When you eat an avocado, it’s not just about the potassium or dietary fiber, but the synergy of the nutrients working together. It’s how the fat and fiber in the avocado slow down your gastric emptying and help keep you fuller longer. It’s also about how satisfying it tastes.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Staying well-nourished is much simpler than you might think, Walker said. “We don’t need extreme diets or supplements to fill these nutrient gaps, but simple, intentional dietary shifts that can make a significant impact. By increasing whole foods like fruits, vegetables, whole grains, legumes, nuts, seeds, dairy and lean proteins, you can improve your intake of these critical shortfall nutrients, leading to better long-term health and disease prevention.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This article originally appeared on&lt;/em&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/entry/shortfall-nutrients_l_67e43ec0e4b0e572f646b037" target="_blank" data-skimlinks-tracking="7965912"&gt;&lt;em&gt;HuffPost.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BuzzFeed</author><pubDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2025 12:31:02 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMidkFVX3lxTE83Vm93SE4zMEdpWTlSZG5ESm9yeUpMc1ZrbHlJLUI0Sl82ekxTOHB2SU1mYzB2cTktMGZ3SG5qUXhNb09odTlranZjRW1fM3RPMjhlUS1iMWFsdE8wUC1kaWxhbVdySFVCWHBkeVBIcnVXcXlsUUE</guid></item><item><title>叛徒明星Elyn Wyn感谢“异常解剖学” - BBC</title><link>https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/c8dr4y51qd6o</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article&gt;&lt;p data-component="headline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 hNbOGD"&gt;&lt;h1 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 idLnWK"&gt;Traitors star is 'grateful for abnormal anatomy'&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="byline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="byline-new" class="sc-7bfdb3c2-0 fYJjWP"&gt;&lt;span data-testid="byline-new-contributors" class="sc-7bfdb3c2-11 ljQVMv"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="byline-new-contributors-contributor-0" class="sc-7bfdb3c2-5 xGeVU"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="sc-7bfdb3c2-7 djOqvY"&gt;Lena-Zaharah Mohammed&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-testid="byline-new-contributors-contributor-0-role-location" class="sc-7bfdb3c2-8 gvcwmG"&gt;BBC Wales&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 gtLOOD"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="hero-image" class="sc-5340b511-1 cMIbKV"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20251021-134202-667692b2c6-web-2.32.2-1/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 gUePlo hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/d17f/live/a94431b0-b646-11f0-9374-1f3a24e94d38.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/d17f/live/a94431b0-b646-11f0-9374-1f3a24e94d38.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/d17f/live/a94431b0-b646-11f0-9374-1f3a24e94d38.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/d17f/live/a94431b0-b646-11f0-9374-1f3a24e94d38.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/d17f/live/a94431b0-b646-11f0-9374-1f3a24e94d38.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/d17f/live/a94431b0-b646-11f0-9374-1f3a24e94d38.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/d17f/live/a94431b0-b646-11f0-9374-1f3a24e94d38.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/d17f/live/a94431b0-b646-11f0-9374-1f3a24e94d38.jpg.webp" loading="eager" alt="BBC/PA A brown haired woman staring down the barrel of the camera with a slight smirk. She is wearing black clothes with an 'E' shaped necklace. The background is busy with castles and birds." class="sc-5340b511-0 hLdNfA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 jVqbAn"&gt;BBC/PA&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;Elen has previously called on the Welsh government to offer more funding, better information and greater sensitivity to women's health&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The Traitors star and Welsh opera singer Elen Wyn says she is "grateful to have an abnormal anatomy" as it ultimately led to her endometriosis diagnosis. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Appearing on &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://feeds.acast.com/public/shows/its-not-just-a-period" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;the podcast It's Not JUST a Period!&lt;/a&gt;, the 25-year-old from Anglesey said doctors discovered she had only one "abnormally big kidney... two wombs and two cervixes".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The condition, known as uterus didelphys, occurs when the uterus fails to fuse during development in the womb and it affects about &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.toplinemd.com/doral-beach-gynecology/uterus-didelphys-what-are-the-causes-and-right-treatments/" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;0.3% of women&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;This results in a double uterus, which may also have two cervixes and two vaginal canals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Despite living with the condition her whole life, the recent discovery has left Elen with "so many questions" such as "why do [both the wombs] bleed at the same time?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The star of &lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/p0db9b2t/episodes/player" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;The Traitors Series 3&lt;/a&gt;, who was eliminated on episode two, &lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/articles/cgq91e88lepo" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;previously told the BBC&lt;/a&gt; that the pain she suffered was comparable to that of "barbed wire around her stomach".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;When her periods began aged 14, she frequently missed school and sat out of sports because of her discomfort.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;During her 10-year wait for an endometriosis diagnosis, Elen, originally from Llanfair-yng-Nghornwy, was regularly told it was "just a period", that she had a low pain threshold and on one occasion, was &lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/articles/cgq91e88lepo" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;laughed at by a GP&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Elen began suspecting she had endometriosis after watching other people talk about it on TikTok, yet the full extent of her complex condition came to light in a "terrifying" way.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;After her second ultrasound, a doctor assumed she knew she only had one kidney, which she did not. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;She was referred for an internal ultrasound and recalled feeling extremely anxious when a nurse couldn't locate her cervix and more staff were called in for second opinions. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"So many people were just looking at this screen inside of me and they just didn't understand," she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;At first, doctors denied she had &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.nhs.uk/conditions/endometriosis/" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;endometriosis&lt;/a&gt; - a condition where tissue similar to the womb's lining grows elsewhere in the body - but told her that her anatomy looked "very different" and referred her for an urgent MRI scan. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 hNbOGD"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 gXmhTb"&gt;'So many questions'&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;When doctors were trying to make sense of her uterus didelphys, they questioned whether she had two periods a month, which she hadn't.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"They asked me 'do you use tampons or pads?' and I said both.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"They asked me if I insert a tampon, do I continue to bleed, and I said no," she recalled.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"So it's all normal except from my two wombs."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Elen admitted she was still baffled by the discovery, leaving her with "so many questions".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"What I don't understand is if I have two wombs... why do they bleed at the same time?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"Are they just in sync?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"I'm kind of grateful that I do have an abnormal anatomy because otherwise I wouldn't have found out I had stage 4 endometriosis." &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;After years of being made to feel dramatic and "constantly gaslit", Elen said the diagnosis was something she "really needed".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 hNbOGD"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 gXmhTb"&gt;What is uterus didelphys?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Uterus didelphys is a rare congenital condition that develops before birth, when the two tubes that normally form a single uterus fail to fuse properly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Instead, two separate wombs are created - each with its own cervix - and, in some cases, a double vaginal canal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;People with a double uterus are at &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://my.clevelandclinic.org/health/diseases/23301-uterus-didelphys" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;increased risk of miscarriage and preterm birth but can have healthy pregnancies&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Some symptoms include:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class="sc-6f869981-0 diUlgm"&gt;&lt;li class="sc-734a601e-0 cRgahm"&gt;Pain during sex&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="sc-734a601e-0 cRgahm"&gt;Painful cramping before and during your period&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="sc-734a601e-0 cRgahm"&gt;Heavy bleeding during your period&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="sc-734a601e-0 cRgahm"&gt;Leaking blood when using a tampon (tampon is only in one vaginal canal and not the other)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="sc-734a601e-0 cRgahm"&gt;Frequent miscarriages&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="sc-734a601e-0 cRgahm"&gt;Premature labour&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Now that Elen has received her diagnosis, she is waiting for a laparoscopy to surgically remove the endometriosis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;After nine months believing she was on the waiting list, estimated to be six to eight months long, she asked for an update and discovered she was "never referred".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;She has now been added to the list, but feels it means the clock has restarted in her bid to get the answers she needs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BBC</author><pubDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2025 11:51:21 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiWkFVX3lxTE93MUJIenNTWTVqSjRFNU5GMHhWamRXVVlzRnExWHFETDVHdDVIWjZoWklmU210eml2R0Vqa0NNVG15ZmdJX2dOQU1xb3cwM2pOUnk5MjNhSDl3UdIBX0FVX3lxTE5Wem5rLVk5ZWZyVjZWVkMzeDAxVUhsUVBkakZSTHlwbm41ZXJ2Q2s2RnZ0UmpIekVJSlU2Z0trZkczYktPaEQ1OFJmSHpTTXVTWW1MWlRXaGpzU243STUw</guid></item><item><title>这位母亲有三个自闭症孩子。她花了成千上万的钱在虚假的希望上。’-《华盛顿邮报》</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/health/2025/11/02/autism-alternative-treatments-leucovorin/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text subtype-from-the-source grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="AEP5S6AO5RDCHGF3YHNVW6VUDM" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;ROCHESTER HILLS, Mich. — Wrangling three children with autism consumed Dana Paduchowski’s days in a chaotic swirl, her weeks dissolving into a blur of routines and meltdowns. When the house finally quieted at night, the mother would stay awake for hours scouring the internet for a magic treatment that didn’t exist.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2025 11:31:52 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilAFBVV95cUxOWmctelpnbEZZckdpa09zZkwzRVdseHcxM2w3SE1CT01rTWJSeWZqSk9tS2dESTVETnoyY2JOdDNXSEVuOWdSZjN1RTAyUThkbjN3cVp0eV9TbE9vWWpkUmZNTmRXWFhER0tlWms0dmNUS3V6a2FJQ2ZTU3BySHZnWVlkMDlVd3BGcE94eGlQMm1KWTE0</guid></item><item><title>让你闻起来更有吸引力的食物- BBC</title><link>https://www.bbc.com/future/article/20251031-the-foods-that-make-you-smell-more-attractive</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="sc-85f9acf9-0 kfxpiP"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Other vegetables have a very unique effect on our smell. The asparagus plant produces &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S003194221300352X?via=ihub" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;a compound called the asparagusic acid&lt;/a&gt; and, when it's digested by your body, it releases sulphur compounds too. &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://muse.jhu.edu/article/533914" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;It's these chemicals&lt;/a&gt;, such as methanethiol and dimethyl sulphide, that make your sweat and your pee smell a certain way. Sulphur compounds are very volatile, so they easily disperse in the air. That's why they're so easy to smell from the toilet bowl. This smell usually lasts &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://ascpt.onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/psp4.12264" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;more than five hours&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Not everybody produces this smell, although studies about this &lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.bbc.com/future/article/20140818-mystery-of-asparagus-and-urine" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;keep &lt;/a&gt;&lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.bbc.com/future/article/20140818-mystery-of-asparagus-and-urine" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;coming up with different findings&lt;/a&gt;. In the 1950s, research seemed to suggest that fewer than 50% of people produce the tell-tale asparagus pee odour, while in 2010, researchers found more than 90% of test participants did. So it’s not clear cut. And not everybody can perceive the stink: the ability to smell one's pungent &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://academic.oup.com/chemse/article/36/1/9/442551?login=false" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;asparagus-smelling pee seems to be down to genetics&lt;/a&gt; too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;However, when it comes to fruit and vegetables more widely, eating more of them can lead to a more attractive scent. &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S1090513816301933" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;A 2017 study in Australia&lt;/a&gt; found that men who had consumed more fruit and vegetables were significantly associated with smelling better – more fruity, floral and sweet. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The study also notes, interestingly, when people have to rate people's faces, slightly yellower skin rich in carotenoid – a molecule from carrots, pumpkins, tomatoes and papayas and others – is also found to be more attractive. But the same study suggests that people consuming diets with a little bit of fat, meat, egg, and tofu intake were also associated with more pleasant-smelling sweat. Carb-heavy diets produced the least sexy of scents. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 gXmhTb"&gt;&lt;span id="meat-and-fish" class="sc-d16436d-0 gCPVhV"&gt;&lt;b id="meat-and-fish" class="sc-d16436d-0 gnUCoQ"&gt;Meat and fish&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Meat and fish can also produce a distinct body odour as animal proteins are broken down by the body into amino acids and fats, which are then excreted through sweat – where they interact with skin bacteria.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BBC</author><pubDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikwFBVV95cUxNakprX2xSVmdrUVR3Z21GWnRiRnFhS2Q0YW90Q3IzVW03NUk1U3lfQkdFanVSNG5mZTA4SHRLVDlHcm1RMkNVcXhDcEJBbHJsYm9lZi1BRDF6Mk93TDJza0cwU20ycGtmVWQtQnZxYnpBVUdlbFlmZkpXanpBcDRjYTkwa0lDekhYcFZYUHRzazcxSXc</guid></item><item><title>以下是您应该（或不应该）在全身冰浴中浸泡的原因-有线</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/is-cold-plunging-good-for-you/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="body__inner-container"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="lead-in-text-callout"&gt;Cold plunging at&lt;/span&gt; the gym or having a chilly shower at home has become a popular practice in recent years. But is all the self-inflicted freezing really that good for you? With the promise of boosting your mood, providing mental clarity, and reducing muscle soreness post-workout, it may sound enticing, but it’s not for everyone. Aside from making your teeth chatter, there are the notable negatives as well as its positives to consider.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;Tasked with the challenge of testing the &lt;a href="https://www.wired.com/story/best-cold-plunge-tubs/" target="_blank"&gt;latest cold-plunge pools&lt;/a&gt; earlier this year, I reluctantly jumped on the bandwagon. With my adrenaline pumping and my endorphins having a disco post-plunge, I was hooked and have since became an ice bath advocate. But as with every wellness craze, it’s worth keeping up with the ever-changing advice on best practices. Keen to find out more, I asked Gary Brecka, top biohacker and founder of &lt;a data-offer-url="https://www.theultimatehuman.com/" class="external-link" data-event-click='{"element":"ExternalLink","outgoingURL":"https://cna.st/affiliate-link/VDkSwjASRpoWbh7jFFq7H1EGwVjShzD22fmppo1hRHX5MmtKR7XuHmt35Nnxq7CjQFWEQ1TgaXqkBwP5pnW22Ujfa7cjW2ePSJJtykV6HkLSCdCDMaiNujN2urahUWkKvLQ6Bydw1Y9zHp9Wysur87VnuMj4QU6B4ERoc3yKyfv376DtkyyoS4VdqGoHv88TjEiAfhMHjFkTunEgkZCtfRBz5YCiqxv4C9Rtjurt7aZQChpyXWJGT2rFixqBKC7f1c5EGJHq7EuwZksL9C3bk"}' href="https://cna.st/affiliate-link/VDkSwjASRpoWbh7jFFq7H1EGwVjShzD22fmppo1hRHX5MmtKR7XuHmt35Nnxq7CjQFWEQ1TgaXqkBwP5pnW22Ujfa7cjW2ePSJJtykV6HkLSCdCDMaiNujN2urahUWkKvLQ6Bydw1Y9zHp9Wysur87VnuMj4QU6B4ERoc3yKyfv376DtkyyoS4VdqGoHv88TjEiAfhMHjFkTunEgkZCtfRBz5YCiqxv4C9Rtjurt7aZQChpyXWJGT2rFixqBKC7f1c5EGJHq7EuwZksL9C3bk" rel="sponsored" target="_blank"&gt;The Ultimate Human&lt;/a&gt;, for advice on how to cold plunge for maximum benefit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;Whether you’re a seasoned pro or a newbie wondering what all the fuss is about, take a deep, calming breath and jump right in. Find options for your own ice bath in the WIRED guide to the &lt;a href="https://www.wired.com/story/best-cold-plunge-tubs/" target="_blank"&gt;best cold-plunge tubs&lt;/a&gt;, with designs from the likes of &lt;a data-offer-url="https://polarmonkeys.com/products/brainpod?" class="external-link" data-event-click='{"element":"ExternalLink","outgoingURL":"https://cna.st/affiliate-link/7zscoHCrWNbASLQN1h2KUpoPrCLRtaQ4fEKh71zYwvRYxB5GyD6mKp2NZBgXNebLjuYnTL2hWeka8kjLFEkL5MVuAErfuC7C3aR6jZUxdsZtf7QpkYwhZKzgqJ9rJtF3S4MhhaVpoVwcKfZrMA24yMRDvEMkDS2vGLUtrAAjDx352GRWF7sWzfC4k7tgB7m6W9WXUvoyihLZ2KLG7JsFhszh8HfBtXsDedcK2DbmkjpUPHZiq2iNutRdxX5kjt8HP7jfKf2awHyZmrvJN9psgFnP7dZ2H57vHQa"}' href="https://cna.st/affiliate-link/7zscoHCrWNbASLQN1h2KUpoPrCLRtaQ4fEKh71zYwvRYxB5GyD6mKp2NZBgXNebLjuYnTL2hWeka8kjLFEkL5MVuAErfuC7C3aR6jZUxdsZtf7QpkYwhZKzgqJ9rJtF3S4MhhaVpoVwcKfZrMA24yMRDvEMkDS2vGLUtrAAjDx352GRWF7sWzfC4k7tgB7m6W9WXUvoyihLZ2KLG7JsFhszh8HfBtXsDedcK2DbmkjpUPHZiq2iNutRdxX5kjt8HP7jfKf2awHyZmrvJN9psgFnP7dZ2H57vHQa" rel="sponsored" target="_blank"&gt;PolarMonkeys&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a data-offer-url="https://www.amazon.co.uk/CalmMax-Athletes-Portable-Therapy-Outdoor/dp/B0CTK27RS5?" class="external-link" data-event-click='{"element":"ExternalLink","outgoingURL":"https://cna.st/affiliate-link/5a1FMimJbzYezMeMToA4fa2KPpoGk6a3mjMwdfkBSx8vqeN5ZYTnYXCCPjYH6EcN1Byfudtbuz74NZYpgiVk57gSvZfgNc65uYMruFBT5rVMtuYv2U1cHFegNekE4Wp9woqTBv37r6pHdP7EKvnkaMbiUU6rrmm9ohfMjWZwMh2aYYMsjvnxVi14HHedngy4t3ELoSCerfabpaBf2WeuDMeXMsqw2LDeG4r8EKAcbZJQUTVbRmoPK88b8fYDECJ72xZjpKHmazfB9cXgcnp7bsgm1Kitm2W8MD4pAtfaQJhrRxihRQy89kbLfnAk5yAD2A3w6LCqMaGsiJG2QeiN4jQ"}' href="https://cna.st/affiliate-link/5a1FMimJbzYezMeMToA4fa2KPpoGk6a3mjMwdfkBSx8vqeN5ZYTnYXCCPjYH6EcN1Byfudtbuz74NZYpgiVk57gSvZfgNc65uYMruFBT5rVMtuYv2U1cHFegNekE4Wp9woqTBv37r6pHdP7EKvnkaMbiUU6rrmm9ohfMjWZwMh2aYYMsjvnxVi14HHedngy4t3ELoSCerfabpaBf2WeuDMeXMsqw2LDeG4r8EKAcbZJQUTVbRmoPK88b8fYDECJ72xZjpKHmazfB9cXgcnp7bsgm1Kitm2W8MD4pAtfaQJhrRxihRQy89kbLfnAk5yAD2A3w6LCqMaGsiJG2QeiN4jQ" rel="sponsored" target="_blank" data-aps-asin="B0CTK27RS5" data-aps-asc-tag="w050b-20"&gt;CalmMax&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a data-offer-url="https://plunge.com/products/plunge?" class="external-link" data-event-click='{"element":"ExternalLink","outgoingURL":"https://cna.st/affiliate-link/AUmSbTSfyktbrSrBKbpwFxNMcdd1vukjCDSHder9QRM9oqS3iFWcbcCEDv7CodPPhD1MM2aPiCFEAPmnBtDFjkTF2h8JpxygFX6xcVCVmTrhBRdvyyP3GgX4tLhLVXiShJGV55Aa1cDausWBFbRuNVt4N5cQuz1Vn8auFBhUEsFkq7GbRM2uvUePoaSG333428NsDUKEgocnhXYhN1fdwBuN3fAXV28kb9RGrAR1ey2C1gBGmtLou1sdWxwqmbNJTC1WhPcbpNfDUBKUqiUQcBDQ"}' href="https://cna.st/affiliate-link/AUmSbTSfyktbrSrBKbpwFxNMcdd1vukjCDSHder9QRM9oqS3iFWcbcCEDv7CodPPhD1MM2aPiCFEAPmnBtDFjkTF2h8JpxygFX6xcVCVmTrhBRdvyyP3GgX4tLhLVXiShJGV55Aa1cDausWBFbRuNVt4N5cQuz1Vn8auFBhUEsFkq7GbRM2uvUePoaSG333428NsDUKEgocnhXYhN1fdwBuN3fAXV28kb9RGrAR1ey2C1gBGmtLou1sdWxwqmbNJTC1WhPcbpNfDUBKUqiUQcBDQ" rel="sponsored" target="_blank"&gt;Plunge&lt;/a&gt;, and more.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="TableOfContentWrapper-jDOHAN fhKwHR table-of-content"&gt;&lt;div data="[object Object]" class="AccordionWrapper-hsYVHT bgMFty"&gt;&lt;div class="AccordionItemWrapper-eWlGuu eNwKZf"&gt;&lt;div class="AccordionContainer-foSklP iRHdCZ"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="accordion-item-container" class="AccordionItemContainer-ywYcO eQgPvY"&gt;&lt;p class="AccordionItemContainerLabel-ioTxOM diANax"&gt;Jump to Section&lt;/p&gt;&lt;button class="BaseButton-lbLhfD ButtonWrapper-igqDZ gTIqfM hKIiJv button button--utility AccordionItemContainerButton-eSsfaw cSYOvq" data-event-click='{"element":"Button"}' data-testid="Button" role="button" type="button"&gt;&lt;span class="ButtonLabel-cyWivE hvohFn button__label"&gt;AccordionItemContainerButton&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p id="what-is-cold-plunging" tabindex="-1"&gt;&lt;h2 class="paywall"&gt;What Is Cold Plunging?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;Whether it’s in the sea, a lake, or an ice bath at your local gym or at home, cold plunging means immersing your body in water that is 39 to 59 defrees Fahrenheit (4 to 15 Celsius). If you don’t have a gym membership and don’t fancy stripping down to your bathing suit at the local lake, an indoor bathtub filled with icy cold water will do. “You don’t need an expensive set up,” says Brecka. “A bathtub with ice works. A horse trough in the backyard works. Dedicated plunge pools are convenient, but you’ll get benefits no matter how you create cold exposure. It’s consistency that matters more than equipment.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Container-VgtPr ekoLDG"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;So how long do you cold plunge and what temperature should a cold plunge be? Brecka suggests two to six minutes as the ideal time. It’s long enough to activate the nervous system and short enough to stay safe. If you’re new to cold plunging, however, under a minute is plenty.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="is-cold-plunge-good-for-you" tabindex="-1"&gt;&lt;h2 class="paywall"&gt;Is Cold Plunging Good for You?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;“What are the benefits of cold plunging?” is the million dollar question you’re probably asking yourself, right as you're staring into the tub (along with “Why don’t you just have a warm cookie and hot chocolate instead?” which is what I often hear my inner child say.) Brecka suggests persevering for maximum benefit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;“We do a plunge because cold exposure activates your nervous system, improves circulation, and helps your body adapt to stress,” he says. “Cold plunging is not about powering through the shock, it’s about letting that shock drive physiological change.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;Some studies show benefits for cold plunging, including from &lt;a href="https://www.health.harvard.edu/staying-healthy/research-highlights-health-benefits-from-cold-water-immersions?" target="_blank"&gt;Harvard Medical School&lt;/a&gt;. While &lt;a data-offer-url="https://sncs-prod-external.mayo.edu/hometown-health/speaking-of-health/cold-plunge-after-workouts" class="external-link" data-event-click='{"element":"ExternalLink","outgoingURL":"https://sncs-prod-external.mayo.edu/hometown-health/speaking-of-health/cold-plunge-after-workouts"}' href="https://sncs-prod-external.mayo.edu/hometown-health/speaking-of-health/cold-plunge-after-workouts" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;those studies are encouraging&lt;/a&gt;, however, they are not conclusive, and their effects vary considerably across the board.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>WIRED</author><pubDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiakFVX3lxTE5TcUpweTloWm9YTWM3MldlRWY4Q01TN3NPVXVKT2M4UjhmOWk2bnBzSVVRVmZ1OFgwZENlVVpTOVVBQW9JWmJqOUUtSk9JLWVacUZWZXFEbzgwUFdsMm02c0JrUnMya19PTnc</guid></item><item><title>研究表明，运动使女性在心脏健康方面优于男性|健康-印度斯坦时报</title><link>https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/study-says-exercise-gives-women-this-one-edge-over-men-when-it-comes-to-heart-health-101762066922101.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="detail " dataid="/lifestyle/health/study-says-exercise-gives-women-this-one-edge-over-men-when-it-comes-to-heart-health-101762066922101.html"&gt; &lt;div class="storyParagraphFigure"&gt; &lt;p&gt;One of the fundamental pillars of safeguarding &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/cardiac-surgeon-explains-how-to-choose-the-right-cooking-oils-for-heart-health-101761816473497.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="heart health"&gt;heart health&lt;/a&gt; is exercising. It keeps the heart pumping efficiently and keeps the cardiovascular system resilient. From &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/topic/blood-pressure" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="blood pressure"&gt;blood pressure&lt;/a&gt; levels to weight management, there are ample benefits. But did you know the amount of exercise needed for better heart health benefits differs from person to person? One way this distinction appears is sex-based.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;figure class=""&gt; &lt;span class=""&gt; &lt;picture&gt; &lt;source media="(max-width:767px)" srcset="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/11/02/550x309/cyclling_1759048029799_1762067276470.jpg" alt="Men even when they exercise as much as women may not reap the same rewards. (Freepik)" title="Men even when they exercise as much as women may not reap the same rewards. (Freepik)"&gt;&lt;/source&gt; &lt;img src="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/11/02/550x309/cyclling_1759048029799_1762067276470.jpg" alt="Men even when they exercise as much as women may not reap the same rewards. (Freepik)" title="Men even when they exercise as much as women may not reap the same rewards. (Freepik)"&gt; &lt;/picture&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;figcaption&gt;Men even when they exercise as much as women may not reap the same rewards. (Freepik)&lt;/figcaption&gt; &lt;/figure&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;p id="readMoreFTUser"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;ALSO READ: &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/take-the-stairs-over-lift-study-reveals-just-3-minutes-of-daily-movement-can-reduce-heart-attack-and-stroke-risk-101754563066677.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="Take the stairs over lift: Study reveals just 3 minutes of daily movement can reduce heart attack and stroke risk"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Take the stairs over lift: Study reveals just 3 minutes of daily movement can reduce heart attack and stroke risk&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="mt-10 mb-10 htEchoRecirculationWidget"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="predictorShow mb20" data-vars-predictor="true" data-vars-quiz="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="quizShow mb20" data-vars-minimized="false" data-vars-predictor="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;A &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s44161-025-00732-z" target="_blank" class="backlink" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="study"&gt;study&lt;/a&gt; published in the journal of Nature Cardiovascular Research on October 27, 2025, unveiled this difference in how men and women gain heart health benefits from exercise. Turns out, women may gain the same level of heart protection as men with nearly half the amount of activity as men. The study examined wearable device data from around 85,000 adults.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;What did the study find?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Women who exercised for almost 250 minutes a week, which is approximately 35 minutes a day, showed a 30 percent lower risk of developing heart disease. But here's the difference. For men to achieve the same heart protection from exercise of 30 percent lower risk, they need to do exercises for around 530 minutes a week.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;This is not solely for preventing heart diseases, but also the same is applicable for mitigating heart disease complications as well. Women with heart disease who met the recommended activity levels gained the advantage of a whopping 70 percent lower death reduction, compared to those women who stayed inactive. But when men did the same amount and duration of exercise, their risk reduction was only around 19 percent.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;It sheds light on the global recommended activity levels, which are often general and not sex specific. The same 150 minutes of moderate to vigorous activity per week is relevant for everyone, despite gender. But this study serves as an eye-opener, suggesting that exercise's benefits are effective not based on how long one works out but on how the body responds to the activity. This is particularly critical as men and women have greatly different biological responses and systems.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;Why do women's bodies respond differently?&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;figure class="inlineIMG"&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;img data-src="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/10/08/original/1049_1759934877054.jpg" class="lazy" src="https://images.hindustantimes.com/default/550x309.jpg" alt="Muscle type and hormones help women gain better heart health benefits. (Picture credit: Freepik)" title="Muscle type and hormones help women gain better heart health benefits. (Picture credit: Freepik)"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;figcaption&gt;Muscle type and hormones help women gain better heart health benefits. (Picture credit: Freepik)&lt;/figcaption&gt; &lt;/figure&gt; &lt;p&gt;The reason why women have an extra advantage here is due to the hormones and muscle composition. Estrogen, which is a sex hormone, is more common in women, causes fat metabolism when one is exercising. This is essentially an energy process where the body uses fat as fuel during exercise rather than relying on sugar. When fat for energy is used, it puts less pressure on the heart. This is why women have better heart health with less activity. Women also have more endurance-oriented muscle fibres (type I), unlike men, who have more power-oriented muscle fibres (type II).&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;All these biological variations make it possible for women to reap better rewards for cardiovascular health. For women, their hormones and muscles help them gain more benefits.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Note to readers: This article is for informational purposes only and not a substitute for professional medical advice. Always seek the advice of your doctor with any questions about a medical condition.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Hindustan Times</author><pubDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2025 07:47:16 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi6AFBVV95cUxORzlzMDctTWhObkRYUmYwNFBsZDV2VXlnQk5ETklhbVc4Nk5hMElQTFg3WkIzMHpzQzRxU3dIN21fUVlPT3Q2bktNc09URzhiQW1ZUnF0TTdZZ0FCckkxblY2MnpNMlU1aTlndm5DYVFIWVNTQ2hLUjAwTTJ3RGJNemRES2xRcUY3MlNvTlZFNDVmbEhuUERTbGdMUXgzd2pRbktXUWdFSkV2NDMxU3R2M0RKRE5DUHd1V01NQzR4RDdnMnFIVUdLMTlJZHo5dzhfb0ppWHN1b0gyaUVsd3VhVjZER0dUWUhj0gHuAUFVX3lxTE5zMkhSQk5NYnlJN29DZWR2a1lIcW1tX192U2FTbUhRSExCRGlLZ21fdWQyOUxuRUtpOS1iZWRZeTNSVVJualUtNTJ2Z0VPTnhlNnFXX1hXb0o0dHFwdlF1ZWF3Q2g4WHlPeFlYdWxsMkFodGw5RDlDR1RoRk50Yl9pWlRpdC01NllwNnVEemtpVXNQOEJEMTF4OWQzakk3VXhzUDNiV25SUXpFTFE3R2h2dE9EVldPS3B0WDZKM0EzTEgtWVh5VG01Z1I2dDQxcWNFVF9CM0ZUb0o1ZzhDQ3VrX2I4V2ZxZDRDUUtzOHc</guid></item><item><title>自然逆转心脏病：领先心脏病专家的21天生活方式计划-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/reversing-heart-disease-naturally-the-21-day-lifestyle-plan-from-a-leading-cardiologist/articleshow/125028384.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Heart disease is still the leading cause of death worldwide, but what if one of the world's top cardiologists told you it was possible to greatly improve your heart health naturally in just 21 days? Renowned cardiologist Dr. Aseem Malhotra, along with an award-winning health campaigner, developed a science-backed approach based on lifestyle changes that support cardiovascular health without any medication. In the Ultimate Human Podcast with Gary Brecka, Dr. Malhotra shares how heart health can improve drastically within 21 days if a person follows the steps outlined below.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="3"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="4"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;The motivation behind this approach&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr. Malhotra's journey within the NHS began when he faced a concerning paradox: patients admitted with heart attacks were being served unhealthy hospital food, while he performed emergency procedures. This sparked his lifelong commitment to advocating for nutrition and lifestyle as foundational to heart health. In a 2013 BBC article, Dr. Malhotra said, "I mend hearts. Then I see my patients served junk food by our hospitals." This troubling trend persists worldwide, which explains why heart disease is still on the rise.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="9"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="lOvcW vdo_embedd"&gt;&lt;div class="k7lcu"&gt;&lt;p class="efT4r"&gt;Why are women more at risk for heart disease?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="11"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;He emphasizes that modern medicine has often overlooked the simple power of foods, exercise, stress management, and sleep. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While medications such as statins are widely prescribed, Dr. Malhotra notes their benefits are marginal compared to lifestyle changes, which can rapidly improve heart health and overall well-being.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="15"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="16"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;The 21-day heart health reset&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="18"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr. Malhotra's 21-day solution provides actionable, sustainable steps to reset your metabolism, reduce inflammation, and protect your arteries. The core principle is adopting a low-carbohydrate Mediterranean-style diet focused on whole, minimally processed foods: vegetables, nuts, seeds, virgin olive oil, and lean proteins.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="21"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;He advises avoiding sugar, refined carbohydrates, fruit juices, and ultra-processed foods for at least three weeks. This phase helps stabilize blood sugar, lower triglycerides, and improve insulin sensitivity—all key factors in reducing cardiovascular risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="23"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Motion and exercise&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="25"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="26"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Physical activity is another pillar of the reset. Dr. Malhotra recommends a daily brisk walk of 30 minutes. The goal is consistent movement, not extreme gym workouts. Regular walking improves blood flow, aids weight control, and enhances heart and lung function, forming a foundation for cardiovascular longevity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="30"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Meditation for reducing stress&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="32"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="33"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stress is a major contributor to heart disease, and meditation, especially Rajyoga meditation, plays a vital role. Studies suggest it may even reverse artery blockages by reducing inflammation and calming the nervous system. Spending time each day on mindful breathing limits stress hormones that damage blood vessels, helping prevent heart attacks and strokes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="36"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Sleep and quality recovery&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="38"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="39"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sleep is often underestimated but crucial for heart health. Dr. Malhotra recommends 7–8 hours of quality sleep each night. Proper rest regulates blood pressure and inflammation, aiding the repair and maintenance of the cardiovascular system.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="41"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="42"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Beyond diet and exercise: Building a healthy environment and habits&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="44"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;While personal responsibility is important, Dr. Malhotra stresses the need for an environment that supports healthy choices. Junk food marketing and the easy availability of processed meals often work against individuals. He advocates for systemic change alongside individual lifestyle shifts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="48"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;He also notes that approximately 67% of what many people consume daily falls into the highly processed category, which typically contains additives, preservatives, colorings, and flavor enhancers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="50"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thumb rule to check processed foods:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="52"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;If a product has more than five ingredients, it is likely ultra-processed and best avoided. Dr. Malhotra emphasizes that mounting scientific evidence links an ultra-processed diet to increased risk of diseases such as cancer, depression, and overall mortality.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="55"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="56"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Scientific evidence and impact&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr. Malhotra’s approach is grounded in research. Meta-analyses and clinical trials confirm that reducing carbohydrate intake, cutting sugar, and adopting a Mediterranean diet significantly lowers heart disease risk markers within weeks. Stress reduction techniques also have anti-inflammatory and cardiovascular benefits.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="58"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;He further notes that cholesterol alone is an incomplete marker of heart disease risk. Insulin resistance, triglycerides, inflammation, and lifestyle factors are stronger predictors—and all are modifiable through diet and lifestyle changes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="62"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="63"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Tips to get started today&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="65"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Eat real food: Fill your plate with vegetables, healthy fats such as olive oil and nuts, and moderate protein. Avoid sugary drinks, sweets, and processed snacks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="67"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Daily walk: Aim for a brisk 30-minute walk every day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="69"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Meditate: Spend 20–40 minutes a day practicing focused breathing or Rajyoga meditation to calm the mind and heart.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="72"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sleep well: Maintain a pattern that allows 7–8 hours of quality sleep each night.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="74"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr. Aseem Malhotra’s message is one of hope and empowerment: heart health is not about pills or procedures. It’s about embracing a lifestyle that allows your body to heal and function as it was designed to. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="76"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Times of India</author><pubDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2025 03:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihgJBVV95cUxObk9IWnBKbkNVQ05XMHdSQnV3NUN5c1ZoRm1oLWNrUmZ3cXRTTTZNa0tVd1RaX0N1Y3hiNVRFTF82WlZPRWN1dV84Qkw1QVRpb2FlWjM5MEJodHh2TTdIQVUxTW1wY1BXTXZWX2paNnBVM2NkdjB1dDdvUktZMTVVaTJZWW5nTjhGXzZ1cHc3UGctdTNpaU9NdGNYSVNEa1FFUnl2dlJtRDU3NTQ4Z3pGWC0wT3oyY0d4Y2hvSEQzRWtrWXdmaGZxaE9mZVJCakszUnVCcXRsdEtfN2RoZ2dGb0Fqcjh4Y3MwTElkV3E5QWUtSkVoazRhWmZFcTRqZjFKWkdmV1p3</guid></item><item><title>我是一名传染病医生。以下是当我在飞机上坐在怀疑接种疫苗的人旁边时发生的事情。- Yahoo News UK</title><link>https://uk.news.yahoo.com/im-infectious-disease-doctor-heres-023104848.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="" data-article-body="true"&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;It’s hard to believe that infectious diseases have become a political litmus test, but they are now very much part of the “with us or against us” mental sorting more and more people seem to be doing these days. And the topic seems to be everywhere. Do you think the U.S. should continue &lt;a href="https://www.thelancet.com/journals/lancet/article/PIIS0140-6736(25)01186-9/fulltext" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:funding aid programs for diseases such as AIDS, TB and malaria;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;funding aid programs for diseases such as AIDS, TB and malaria&lt;/a&gt;? Are you pleased or horrified about &lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2025/09/03/us/florida-vaccine-mandates.html" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Florida’s plans to undo school vaccine mandates;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Florida’s plans to undo school vaccine mandates&lt;/a&gt;? Do you seek out or steer clear of the annual flu vaccine?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;As someone who recently completed 15 years of post-college training to become an infectious diseases physician-scientist, I can’t avoid these conversations. I just wish I knew the magic words to reach people willing to jettison decades of evidence and research for something they read online.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;I am proud of my work and committed to my profession. Yet in a country polarized by everything from the &lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2025/09/16/us/politics/trump-kirk-free-speech-hate-speech-left.html" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:response to the abhorrent assassination of Charlie Kirk;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;response to the abhorrent assassination of Charlie Kirk&lt;/a&gt; to &lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2025/09/15/health/rfk-jr-hhs-vaccine-committee-members.html" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:RFK Jr.’s abrupt reconfiguration of the nation’s vaccine advisory committee;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;RFK Jr.’s abrupt reconfiguration of the nation’s vaccine advisory committee&lt;/a&gt;, I hesitated to share my occupation with the talkative young man I was recently seated next to on a flight.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;When the inevitable career question came up, he jumped right in. Despite the early hour and lack of sleep, with no viable exit option, I decided to face the challenge, though I braced for the worst.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Lyme disease was first on the list. We were flying out of Connecticut, after all.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“You’ve never heard that Lyme disease was created as a bioterrorism weapon?” I had not (because &lt;a href="https://www.jci.org/articles/view/21681" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:it wasn’t;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;it wasn’t&lt;/a&gt;). Somehow, in between the hours caring for patients, researching disease pathogenesis and staying up to date on the literature in my field, I had missed this infectious disease conspiracy du jour.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“It’s called Lyme because that’s where they released it.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;No. Old Lyme, Connecticut, is where epidemiologists realized that patients’ symptoms coincided with recent tick bites and then confirmed that local ticks carried the disease-causing bacteria.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“You can’t cure it; it was made to weaponize.” Actually, we have very &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/lyme/hcp/clinical-care/index.html" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:effective antibiotics;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;effective antibiotics&lt;/a&gt; to kill the bacteria (though some people can develop a &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/lyme/signs-symptoms/chronic-symptoms-and-lyme-disease.html" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:complex post-treatment Lyme disease syndrome;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;complex post-treatment Lyme disease syndrome&lt;/a&gt;). I’m not a military strategist, but I can’t imagine that indiscriminately infecting outdoor enthusiasts with a non-deadly, treatable disease that requires transmission via a slow-feeding arthropod would be an ideal bioterrorism plan.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“But why is it spreading so fast now?”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Climate change, expanding tick habitats and food sources, and a lack of winters that kill them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;He laughed. “So in your ‘profesh’ opinion, Lyme disease as a bioterrorism weapon is a bunch of horseshit?”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Yes. That I do agree with.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;We moved on to the next obvious infectious disease topic: COVID-19. I gave him space. He wasn’t sparring with a lack of respect, nor was I. We opened up about experiencing the pandemic in completely different ways. He described how hard it was being forced to get vaccinated, feeling coerced to keep his job but fearing the vaccine’s purported harms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;I shared my experience working in the hospital. I told him how I had witnessed numerous people die alone, and how the vaccine was a true savior. He believed it was only old people who had died. I told him I had seen enough young, healthy people become debilitated that I would never make that bet, not in that pandemic or the next one. In fact, by September 2023, &lt;a href="https://data.cdc.gov/National-Center-for-Health-Statistics/Provisional-COVID-19-Deaths-by-Sex-and-Age/9bhg-hcku/data_preview" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:more than 25,000 18-39-year-olds had died from COVID in the U.S.;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;more than 25,000 18-39-year-olds had died from COVID in the U.S.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;I tried to hear his concerns. I admitted that my passion for science and what I had experienced as a physician may have made me unfairly dismissive of people whose primary concerns were being stuck at home unable to pay rent or educate their children. I acknowledged that there’s always a small chance that some people might experience an adverse reaction to any medical intervention, be it a vaccine or over-the-counter drug, and I can understand why that makes some people hesitate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;But I also reiterated the rigor of the scientific process involved in developing treatments, reviewing safety data, and ultimately making clinical recommendations. I told him that mRNA vaccines are neither new — &lt;a href="https://www.niaid.nih.gov/diseases-conditions/decades-making-mrna-covid-19-vaccines" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:they’ve been in development for decades;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;they’ve been in development for decades&lt;/a&gt; — nor a government-led conspiracy to genetically manipulate the population. The reference to “genetic material” may lead to misconceptions, but mRNA does not enter the cell nucleus, where our DNA resides. Our cells do not even possess the molecular machinery capable of turning mRNA into DNA. That’s &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/covid/vaccines/how-they-work.html#:~:text=How%20mRNA%20COVID%2D19%20vaccines%20work" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:fact;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;fact&lt;/a&gt;, not just my “profesh” opinion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;It felt real, the effort to hear and speak to each other. And I learned things from him, too. In response to my insistence that his infection-related conspiracy theories were nothing but that, he admitted, “Yeah, you’re probably right.” Then he added, with a smile on his face, “But conspiracies are a lot more fun.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Conspiracies are a lot more fun&lt;/em&gt;. Maybe vaccine or disease origin conspiracies are fun — if you’re young and healthy, if you’re bored, if you’re motivated to access a community that promises you “inside information.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;But for the population as a whole, they are unbelievably dangerous. Conspiracy theories are why a &lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2025/03/10/health/measles-texas-kennedy-fox.html" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:measles outbreak took hold in the U.S. this year;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;measles outbreak took hold in the U.S. this year&lt;/a&gt;, why &lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2025/08/09/us/gunman-cdc-shooting-vaccines.html" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:CDC employees were targeted in a workplace shooting;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;CDC employees were targeted in a workplace shooting&lt;/a&gt;. They are why &lt;a href="https://www.science.org/content/article/fighting-ebola-hard-congo-fake-news-makes-it-harder" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Ebola outbreaks are hard to contain;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Ebola outbreaks are hard to contain&lt;/a&gt;, why &lt;a href="https://www.pbs.org/newshour/health/the-world-nearly-beat-polio-but-fake-records-misinformation-and-missteps-aided-its-comeback" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:polio vaccine workers are killed;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;polio vaccine workers are killed&lt;/a&gt; abroad.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;By the time our flight was over, our conversation had covered a wide geographic and political space. The experience left me with genuine hope that we could maintain trust in each other and reminded me that scientists and physicians cannot give up on having these conversations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“With COVID, vaccines, Lyme disease, any of it — I’m not your enemy,” I told my seatmate as we were getting ready to disembark. “And I know you’re not the enemy, either.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“True,” he agreed. “But they always want to make someone your enemy.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Exactly&lt;/em&gt;. That is what conspiracy theories require. That is why we have to talk to each other. See me as a person. And I will do the same.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;I am not your enemy. Neither is science.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Morgan Goheen, M.D., Ph.D., works at Yale School of Medicine as a research scientist and board-certified infectious diseases physician, and she is a Public Voices Fellow of The OpEd Project in Partnership with Yale University.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;em&gt;This article originally appeared on &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/entry/infectious-disease-doctor-anti-vaccine-airplane_n_68d2e961e4b03fb4d93463e7" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:HuffPost;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;HuffPost&lt;/a&gt; in October 2025.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Also in Goodful: &lt;a href="https://www.buzzfeed.com/carolinebologna/12-things-millennials-do-that-gen-z-hates?utm_source=yahoo-recirc-links" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk='slk:12 Things Millennials Do That Gen Z Says Give Them The Ultimate "Ick";elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas' class="link "&gt;12 Things Millennials Do That Gen Z Says Give Them The Ultimate "Ick"&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Also in Goodful: &lt;a href="https://www.buzzfeed.com/lizmrichardson/doctors-health-warning-signs-symptoms-shouldnt-ignore?utm_source=yahoo-recirc-links" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Doctors And Nurses Are Revealing The &amp;quot;Small&amp;quot; Health Signs You Should Never Ignore, And It's Shocking;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Doctors And Nurses Are Revealing The "Small" Health Signs You Should Never Ignore, And It's Shocking&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Also in Goodful: &lt;a href="https://www.buzzfeed.com/dannicaramirez/older-adults-are-sharing-the-difficult-truths-about-aging-fs?utm_source=yahoo-recirc-links" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk='slk:"Young People Would Be Surprised By This": 21 "Hard To Swallow" Truths About Getting Older That No One Talks About;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas' class="link "&gt;"Young People Would Be Surprised By This": 21 "Hard To Swallow" Truths About Getting Older That No One Talks About&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.buzzfeed.com/morgangoheen/infectious-disease-doctor-anti-vaccine-airplane?utm_source=yahoo-recirc-links" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Read it on BuzzFeed.com;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Read it on BuzzFeed.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Yahoo News UK</author><pubDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2025 02:31:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigAFBVV95cUxPQm5WdkdzT3k5ZGJXQmlXUmxvUGdfc0VBc1UyTXNWZl9SQzI2ZGRtUXhxUU54YmZsbnFtNTRqNDJKMHYyTWNBcGxvcGMyY3lyV2FRX2ZSVy1qN1lYWEFHbDJqUExBSnEzZ1VpenByaEJjcDNXRDBZSVVFNDNaWF9YNg</guid></item><item><title>我是一名传染病医生。以下是当我在飞机上坐在怀疑接种疫苗的人旁边时发生的事情。- Yahoo News Australia</title><link>https://au.news.yahoo.com/im-infectious-disease-doctor-heres-023104848.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="" data-article-body="true"&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;It’s hard to believe that infectious diseases have become a political litmus test, but they are now very much part of the “with us or against us” mental sorting more and more people seem to be doing these days. And the topic seems to be everywhere. Do you think the U.S. should continue &lt;a href="https://www.thelancet.com/journals/lancet/article/PIIS0140-6736(25)01186-9/fulltext" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:funding aid programs for diseases such as AIDS, TB and malaria;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;funding aid programs for diseases such as AIDS, TB and malaria&lt;/a&gt;? Are you pleased or horrified about &lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2025/09/03/us/florida-vaccine-mandates.html" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Florida’s plans to undo school vaccine mandates;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Florida’s plans to undo school vaccine mandates&lt;/a&gt;? Do you seek out or steer clear of the annual flu vaccine?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;As someone who recently completed 15 years of post-college training to become an infectious diseases physician-scientist, I can’t avoid these conversations. I just wish I knew the magic words to reach people willing to jettison decades of evidence and research for something they read online.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;I am proud of my work and committed to my profession. Yet in a country polarized by everything from the &lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2025/09/16/us/politics/trump-kirk-free-speech-hate-speech-left.html" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:response to the abhorrent assassination of Charlie Kirk;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;response to the abhorrent assassination of Charlie Kirk&lt;/a&gt; to &lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2025/09/15/health/rfk-jr-hhs-vaccine-committee-members.html" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:RFK Jr.’s abrupt reconfiguration of the nation’s vaccine advisory committee;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;RFK Jr.’s abrupt reconfiguration of the nation’s vaccine advisory committee&lt;/a&gt;, I hesitated to share my occupation with the talkative young man I was recently seated next to on a flight.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;When the inevitable career question came up, he jumped right in. Despite the early hour and lack of sleep, with no viable exit option, I decided to face the challenge, though I braced for the worst.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Lyme disease was first on the list. We were flying out of Connecticut, after all.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“You’ve never heard that Lyme disease was created as a bioterrorism weapon?” I had not (because &lt;a href="https://www.jci.org/articles/view/21681" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:it wasn’t;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;it wasn’t&lt;/a&gt;). Somehow, in between the hours caring for patients, researching disease pathogenesis and staying up to date on the literature in my field, I had missed this infectious disease conspiracy du jour.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“It’s called Lyme because that’s where they released it.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;No. Old Lyme, Connecticut, is where epidemiologists realized that patients’ symptoms coincided with recent tick bites and then confirmed that local ticks carried the disease-causing bacteria.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“You can’t cure it; it was made to weaponize.” Actually, we have very &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/lyme/hcp/clinical-care/index.html" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:effective antibiotics;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;effective antibiotics&lt;/a&gt; to kill the bacteria (though some people can develop a &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/lyme/signs-symptoms/chronic-symptoms-and-lyme-disease.html" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:complex post-treatment Lyme disease syndrome;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;complex post-treatment Lyme disease syndrome&lt;/a&gt;). I’m not a military strategist, but I can’t imagine that indiscriminately infecting outdoor enthusiasts with a non-deadly, treatable disease that requires transmission via a slow-feeding arthropod would be an ideal bioterrorism plan.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“But why is it spreading so fast now?”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Climate change, expanding tick habitats and food sources, and a lack of winters that kill them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;He laughed. “So in your ‘profesh’ opinion, Lyme disease as a bioterrorism weapon is a bunch of horseshit?”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Yes. That I do agree with.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;We moved on to the next obvious infectious disease topic: COVID-19. I gave him space. He wasn’t sparring with a lack of respect, nor was I. We opened up about experiencing the pandemic in completely different ways. He described how hard it was being forced to get vaccinated, feeling coerced to keep his job but fearing the vaccine’s purported harms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;I shared my experience working in the hospital. I told him how I had witnessed numerous people die alone, and how the vaccine was a true savior. He believed it was only old people who had died. I told him I had seen enough young, healthy people become debilitated that I would never make that bet, not in that pandemic or the next one. In fact, by September 2023, &lt;a href="https://data.cdc.gov/National-Center-for-Health-Statistics/Provisional-COVID-19-Deaths-by-Sex-and-Age/9bhg-hcku/data_preview" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:more than 25,000 18-39-year-olds had died from COVID in the U.S.;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;more than 25,000 18-39-year-olds had died from COVID in the U.S.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;I tried to hear his concerns. I admitted that my passion for science and what I had experienced as a physician may have made me unfairly dismissive of people whose primary concerns were being stuck at home unable to pay rent or educate their children. I acknowledged that there’s always a small chance that some people might experience an adverse reaction to any medical intervention, be it a vaccine or over-the-counter drug, and I can understand why that makes some people hesitate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;But I also reiterated the rigor of the scientific process involved in developing treatments, reviewing safety data, and ultimately making clinical recommendations. I told him that mRNA vaccines are neither new — &lt;a href="https://www.niaid.nih.gov/diseases-conditions/decades-making-mrna-covid-19-vaccines" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:they’ve been in development for decades;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;they’ve been in development for decades&lt;/a&gt; — nor a government-led conspiracy to genetically manipulate the population. The reference to “genetic material” may lead to misconceptions, but mRNA does not enter the cell nucleus, where our DNA resides. Our cells do not even possess the molecular machinery capable of turning mRNA into DNA. That’s &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/covid/vaccines/how-they-work.html#:~:text=How%20mRNA%20COVID%2D19%20vaccines%20work" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:fact;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;fact&lt;/a&gt;, not just my “profesh” opinion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;It felt real, the effort to hear and speak to each other. And I learned things from him, too. In response to my insistence that his infection-related conspiracy theories were nothing but that, he admitted, “Yeah, you’re probably right.” Then he added, with a smile on his face, “But conspiracies are a lot more fun.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Conspiracies are a lot more fun&lt;/em&gt;. Maybe vaccine or disease origin conspiracies are fun — if you’re young and healthy, if you’re bored, if you’re motivated to access a community that promises you “inside information.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;But for the population as a whole, they are unbelievably dangerous. Conspiracy theories are why a &lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2025/03/10/health/measles-texas-kennedy-fox.html" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:measles outbreak took hold in the U.S. this year;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;measles outbreak took hold in the U.S. this year&lt;/a&gt;, why &lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2025/08/09/us/gunman-cdc-shooting-vaccines.html" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:CDC employees were targeted in a workplace shooting;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;CDC employees were targeted in a workplace shooting&lt;/a&gt;. They are why &lt;a href="https://www.science.org/content/article/fighting-ebola-hard-congo-fake-news-makes-it-harder" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Ebola outbreaks are hard to contain;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Ebola outbreaks are hard to contain&lt;/a&gt;, why &lt;a href="https://www.pbs.org/newshour/health/the-world-nearly-beat-polio-but-fake-records-misinformation-and-missteps-aided-its-comeback" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:polio vaccine workers are killed;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;polio vaccine workers are killed&lt;/a&gt; abroad.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;By the time our flight was over, our conversation had covered a wide geographic and political space. The experience left me with genuine hope that we could maintain trust in each other and reminded me that scientists and physicians cannot give up on having these conversations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“With COVID, vaccines, Lyme disease, any of it — I’m not your enemy,” I told my seatmate as we were getting ready to disembark. “And I know you’re not the enemy, either.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“True,” he agreed. “But they always want to make someone your enemy.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Exactly&lt;/em&gt;. That is what conspiracy theories require. That is why we have to talk to each other. See me as a person. And I will do the same.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;I am not your enemy. Neither is science.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Morgan Goheen, M.D., Ph.D., works at Yale School of Medicine as a research scientist and board-certified infectious diseases physician, and she is a Public Voices Fellow of The OpEd Project in Partnership with Yale University.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;em&gt;This article originally appeared on &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/entry/infectious-disease-doctor-anti-vaccine-airplane_n_68d2e961e4b03fb4d93463e7" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:HuffPost;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;HuffPost&lt;/a&gt; in October 2025.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Also in Goodful: &lt;a href="https://www.buzzfeed.com/abbyzinman/gross-girl-hygiene-trivia-quiz?utm_source=yahoo-recirc-links" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:If You Don't Pass This Extremely Easy Hygiene Test, You're Officially Stinkier Than The Average Human;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;If You Don't Pass This Extremely Easy Hygiene Test, You're Officially Stinkier Than The Average Human&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Also in Goodful: &lt;a href="https://www.buzzfeed.com/lizmrichardson/doctors-bad-health-habits-mistakes?utm_source=yahoo-recirc-links" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:&amp;quot;It's Very Serious&amp;quot;: 15 &amp;quot;Bad&amp;quot; Health Habits You Probably Do Allll The Time (But Really Shouldn't), Straight From Doctors And Nurses;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;"It's Very Serious": 15 "Bad" Health Habits You Probably Do Allll The Time (But Really Shouldn't), Straight From Doctors And Nurses&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Also in Goodful: &lt;a href="https://www.buzzfeed.com/lizmrichardson/doctors-health-warning-signs-symptoms-shouldnt-ignore?utm_source=yahoo-recirc-links" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Doctors And Nurses Are Revealing The &amp;quot;Small&amp;quot; Health Signs You Should Never Ignore, And It's Shocking;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Doctors And Nurses Are Revealing The "Small" Health Signs You Should Never Ignore, And It's Shocking&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.buzzfeed.com/morgangoheen/infectious-disease-doctor-anti-vaccine-airplane?utm_source=yahoo-recirc-links" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Read it on BuzzFeed.com;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Read it on BuzzFeed.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Yahoo News Australia</author><pubDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2025 02:31:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigAFBVV95cUxNMC1xOXg2NmtHX2N2bjNtb3ZsMmI5V3J2WExMYUNpMUJWelBKdWdfenZBNWNpNjV0RXhUWWRVUldULWVkVThxUlN6azdWNkxRQzFKWEYxWHFrUlp3Wnk5aXA0b1NBbVFLQTNHdXctNDAzWk9ZQlhqbWVsam9KRnJGeg</guid></item><item><title>研究人员在发现可能增加ALS风险的被忽视因素后发出警告： “潜在相关” -雅虎</title><link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/articles/researchers-issue-warning-discovering-overlooked-010000764.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="" data-article-body="true"&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Research has revealed a link between the mining and burning of dirty fuels and the development of &lt;a href="https://www.mayoclinic.org/diseases-conditions/amyotrophic-lateral-sclerosis/symptoms-causes/syc-20354022" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:amyotrophic lateral sclerosis;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;amyotrophic lateral sclerosis&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="mb-4 text-lg font-bold"&gt;What's happening?&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;As &lt;a href="https://abcnews.go.com/Health/exposure-mining-fossil-fuel-linked-als-new-research/story?id=126254429&amp;amp;utm_source=instagram&amp;amp;utm_medium=social&amp;amp;utm_campaign=likeshopme&amp;amp;utm_content=www.instagram.com/p/DPtNC0kk0t7" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:ABC News;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;ABC News&lt;/a&gt; observed, the study, published in the journal &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0013935125014835?via%3Dihub" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Environmental Research;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Environmental Research&lt;/a&gt;, found that long-term exposure to sulfur dioxide — a pollutant released during the combustion of oil and gas and during mining activity — increases the risk of developing ALS.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;At an ALS clinic in New Brunswick, Canada, doctors noticed a spike in cases. In response, lead author Daniel Saucier launched a study comparing 304 individuals with the disease to 1,207 healthy individuals, all of the same age and sex. The research used records of environmental pollutants connected to the participants' areas of residence.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Saucier, who holds a master's degree in diagnostic methods for ALS, told ABC that "it looked like air pollution was potentially related to the increased cases of ALS in New Brunswick, with sulfur dioxide appearing to be the one that had a significant association of ALS."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The study found that people exposed to sulfur dioxide over long periods had a 23% higher risk of developing ALS.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;According to Saucier, while burning dirty fuels releases sulfur dioxide, so does "anything that has to do with mining activities."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;All study areas met Canada's &lt;a href="https://ccme.ca/en/air-quality-report" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:clean air guidelines;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;clean air guidelines&lt;/a&gt;, yet the research identified a significant health association between sulfur dioxide exposure and ALS risk. The authors concluded that preventive strategies will be needed to protect public health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="mb-4 text-lg font-bold"&gt;Why is air pollution concerning?&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Harmful pollutants such as sulfur dioxide are released during the extraction and use of coal, oil, and gas. While these fuels remain central to global energy production, their by-products pose serious risks to workers, communities, and the environment, especially in industrial zones.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Beyond sulfur dioxide, many other industrial carbon pollutants contribute to rising global temperatures. A warmer planet intensifies natural disasters, sea-level rise, and other health impacts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="mb-4 text-lg font-bold"&gt;What can be done about air pollution?&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;With new technologies emerging that reduce or eliminate the need to mine and burn dirty fuels, many workplace and public safety concerns can be avoided. For example, &lt;a href="https://guide.thecooldown.com/actions/install-solar-panels/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:solar panels;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;solar panels&lt;/a&gt; generate electricity without releasing harmful pollutants.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Additionally, rising health concerns from exposure to pollution drive a growing demand for cleaner energy. Advocating for solar, wind, hydro, and nuclear energy shows policymakers that the public truly cares about these issues.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Cleaner energy is also becoming increasingly popular and more affordable. A LUT University study concluded that a complete transition is &lt;a href="https://www.lut.fi/en/news/researchers-agree-world-can-reach-100-renewable-energy-system-2050" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:feasible;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;feasible&lt;/a&gt; and could occur before 2050.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;As the world relies more on renewable energy sources, health risks will decrease as heat-trapping pollutants are reduced.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Smaller steps, such as reducing your environmental footprint, are also a great place to start.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Switching from gas-guzzling cars to electric vehicles, turning off lights and appliances when not in use, and eating more plant-based meals are all helpful lifestyle changes that can reduce pollution and the demand for dirty fuels.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Join our &lt;a href="https://www.thecooldown.com/tech-newsletter/?rec0rX1mps1JFgqJm" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:free newsletter;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;free newsletter&lt;/a&gt; for weekly updates on the latest innovations &lt;strong&gt;improving our lives&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;shaping our future&lt;/strong&gt;, and don't miss &lt;a href="https://rb.gy/ivhzmj" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:this cool list;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;this cool list&lt;/a&gt; of easy ways to help yourself while helping the planet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Yahoo</author><pubDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2025 01:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMioAFBVV95cUxOUU54QnE4SC1GcmtIVlotX0lrUUZiUkhoMVZvT1ZWNFZpM0hoc0VYVndkUnFiR3l2Nnk2RHZGaXctUnhHXzNXcDNtUjgwVVQ2LXhGaXBBNkh6U1liX1dVVDdqWVp4OExrNTlBclM2OWgtMjNJRUtOc2NaMFZoT1AyOTBzZFVpN0tvUmhDUDRWNjZpMU9EVF9qYVJiak1lSFNx</guid></item><item><title>分子：在俄罗斯TikTok上疯传的危险减肥药物- BBC</title><link>https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/c201xe61x0lo</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article&gt;&lt;p data-component="headline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 hNbOGD"&gt;&lt;h1 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 idLnWK"&gt;Young Russians are being seduced by a cheap, dangerous weight-loss pill called Molecule&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="byline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="byline-new" class="sc-7bfdb3c2-0 fYJjWP"&gt;&lt;span data-testid="byline-new-contributors" class="sc-7bfdb3c2-11 ljQVMv"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="byline-new-contributors-contributor-0" class="sc-7bfdb3c2-5 xGeVU"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="sc-7bfdb3c2-7 djOqvY"&gt;Sofya Volyanova&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-testid="byline-new-contributors-contributor-0-role-location" class="sc-7bfdb3c2-8 gvcwmG"&gt;BBC News Russian &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 gtLOOD"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="hero-image" class="sc-5340b511-1 cMIbKV"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20251021-134202-667692b2c6-web-2.32.2-1/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 gUePlo hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/20b3/live/a281fad0-b3e7-11f0-a1d0-d5a6c9e4c42e.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/20b3/live/a281fad0-b3e7-11f0-a1d0-d5a6c9e4c42e.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/20b3/live/a281fad0-b3e7-11f0-a1d0-d5a6c9e4c42e.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/20b3/live/a281fad0-b3e7-11f0-a1d0-d5a6c9e4c42e.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/20b3/live/a281fad0-b3e7-11f0-a1d0-d5a6c9e4c42e.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/20b3/live/a281fad0-b3e7-11f0-a1d0-d5a6c9e4c42e.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/20b3/live/a281fad0-b3e7-11f0-a1d0-d5a6c9e4c42e.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/20b3/live/a281fad0-b3e7-11f0-a1d0-d5a6c9e4c42e.jpg.webp" loading="eager" alt="Maria 22-year-old Maria suffered serious side effects after trying the unlicensed weight loss drug promoted on TikTok" class="sc-5340b511-0 hLdNfA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 jVqbAn"&gt;Maria&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;22-year-old Maria suffered serious side effects after trying the unlicensed weight loss drug promoted on TikTok&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Molecule, a pill promising rapid weight loss, went viral on Russian TikTok earlier this year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Young people's feeds started filling up with captions like "Take Molecule and forget food exists", and "Do you want to sit in the back of the class in oversized clothes?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Clips showed fridges lined with blue boxes featuring holograms and "Molecule Plus" labels.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The orders began piling in, as teenagers shared their "weight-loss journeys" on social media.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;But there was a catch.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Maria, 22, had purchased the pill from a popular online retailer. She took two pills per day and, after two weeks, says her mouth dried up and she completely lost her appetite.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"I had absolutely no desire to eat, let alone drink. I was nervous. I was constantly biting my lips and chewing my cheeks."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Maria developed severe anxiety and began having negative thoughts. "These pills were having a profound effect on my psyche," she says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Maria, who lives in St Petersburg, says she wasn't prepared for such severe side effects.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Other TikTok users mentioned dilated pupils, tremors and insomnia. And at least three schoolchildren are reported to have ended up in hospital.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 gXrNRM"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 cMIbKV"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20251021-134202-667692b2c6-web-2.32.2-1/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 gUePlo hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/d2b6/live/989a97f0-b100-11f0-9c44-b9209ab0e9f0.png.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/d2b6/live/989a97f0-b100-11f0-9c44-b9209ab0e9f0.png.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/d2b6/live/989a97f0-b100-11f0-9c44-b9209ab0e9f0.png.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/d2b6/live/989a97f0-b100-11f0-9c44-b9209ab0e9f0.png.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/d2b6/live/989a97f0-b100-11f0-9c44-b9209ab0e9f0.png.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/d2b6/live/989a97f0-b100-11f0-9c44-b9209ab0e9f0.png.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/d2b6/live/989a97f0-b100-11f0-9c44-b9209ab0e9f0.png.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/d2b6/live/989a97f0-b100-11f0-9c44-b9209ab0e9f0.png.webp" loading="lazy" alt="TikTok Clips shared on TikTok show fridges lined with soft drinks and blue boxes of Molecule" class="sc-5340b511-0 hLdNfA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 jVqbAn"&gt;TikTok&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;Clips shared on TikTok show fridges lined with soft drinks and blue boxes of Molecule&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;In April, a schoolgirl in Chita, Siberia, needed hospital care after overdosing on Molecule. According to local reports, she was trying to lose weight quickly, in time for the summer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The mother of another schoolgirl told local media her daughter was admitted to intensive care after taking several pills at once.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;And in May, a 13-year-old boy from St Petersburg needed hospital care after experiencing hallucinations and panic attacks. He had reportedly asked a friend to buy him the pill because he was being teased at school about his weight.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 hNbOGD"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 gXmhTb"&gt;Substance banned in UK, EU and US&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The packaging for Molecule pills often lists "natural ingredients" such as dandelion root and fennel seed extract.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;But earlier this year, journalists at the Russian newspaper Izvestiya submitted pills they had purchased online for testing and found they contained a substance called sibutramine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 gXrNRM"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 cMIbKV"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20251021-134202-667692b2c6-web-2.32.2-1/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 gUePlo hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/6753/live/7fd5a6b0-b100-11f0-9c44-b9209ab0e9f0.png.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/6753/live/7fd5a6b0-b100-11f0-9c44-b9209ab0e9f0.png.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/6753/live/7fd5a6b0-b100-11f0-9c44-b9209ab0e9f0.png.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/6753/live/7fd5a6b0-b100-11f0-9c44-b9209ab0e9f0.png.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/6753/live/7fd5a6b0-b100-11f0-9c44-b9209ab0e9f0.png.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/6753/live/7fd5a6b0-b100-11f0-9c44-b9209ab0e9f0.png.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/6753/live/7fd5a6b0-b100-11f0-9c44-b9209ab0e9f0.png.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/6753/live/7fd5a6b0-b100-11f0-9c44-b9209ab0e9f0.png.webp" loading="lazy" alt="TikTok The pills contain substance called sibutramine, which is banned in many countries" class="sc-5340b511-0 hLdNfA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 jVqbAn"&gt;TikTok&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;The pills contain a substance called sibutramine, which is banned in many countries&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;First used as an antidepressant in the 1980s and later as an appetite suppressant, studies later found sibutramine increased the risk of heart attacks and strokes - while only slightly promoting weight loss.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;It was banned in the US in 2010, and is also &lt;a target="_self" href="http://news.bbc.co.uk/1/hi/health/8473555.stm" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;illegal in the UK&lt;/a&gt;, EU, China and other countries.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;In Russia, it is still used to treat obesity, but available only to adults and by prescription. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Purchasing and selling sibutramine without a prescription is a criminal offence. But that hasn't stopped individuals and small businesses from selling it online - often in higher doses than legal medication - and without requiring prescriptions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The unlicensed pills cost about £6-7 ($8-9) for a 20-day supply - much cheaper than recognised weight-loss injections like Ozempic, which on the Russian market sell for £40-160 ($50-210) per monthly pen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"Self-administration of this drug is very unsafe," says endocrinologist Ksenia Solovieva from St Petersburg, warning of potential overdose risks, "because we do not know how much of the active ingredient such 'dietary supplements' may contain".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 gXrNRM"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 cMIbKV"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20251021-134202-667692b2c6-web-2.32.2-1/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 gUePlo hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/6e9c/live/4ff1bdf0-b0fe-11f0-aa13-0b0479f6f42a.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/6e9c/live/4ff1bdf0-b0fe-11f0-aa13-0b0479f6f42a.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/6e9c/live/4ff1bdf0-b0fe-11f0-aa13-0b0479f6f42a.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/6e9c/live/4ff1bdf0-b0fe-11f0-aa13-0b0479f6f42a.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/6e9c/live/4ff1bdf0-b0fe-11f0-aa13-0b0479f6f42a.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/6e9c/live/4ff1bdf0-b0fe-11f0-aa13-0b0479f6f42a.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/6e9c/live/4ff1bdf0-b0fe-11f0-aa13-0b0479f6f42a.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/6e9c/live/4ff1bdf0-b0fe-11f0-aa13-0b0479f6f42a.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="TikTok Teenagers and young people showing unlicensed weight loss pills sold as dietary supplements from popular marketplaces on their TikTok accounts" class="sc-5340b511-0 hLdNfA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 jVqbAn"&gt;TikTok&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;Teenagers and young people order unlicensed weight loss pills sold as dietary supplements from popular marketplaces&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Russians regularly receive prison sentences for purchasing and reselling Molecule pills. But it's proving difficult for authorities to get a grip on the drug being sold illegally.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;In April, the government-backed Safe Internet League reported the growing trend involving young people to the authorities - prompting several major online marketplaces to remove Molecule from sale. But it soon began appearing online under a new name, Atom, in near-identical packaging.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;A law was recently passed allowing authorities to block websites selling "unregistered dietary supplements" without a court order - but sellers have been getting around this by categorising them as "sports nutrition" instead.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;On TikTok, you can find retailers selling Molecule under listings that look like they are for muesli, biscuits and even lightbulbs. And some retailers aren't even trying to hide it any more.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;A few weeks ago, the BBC found Molecule listings on a popular Russian online marketplace. When approached for comment, the site said it had promptly removed any products containing sibutramine. But it admitted it was difficult to find and remove listings that didn't explicitly mention sibutramine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;If you do manage to get your hands on Molecule, it's hard to know exactly what you're getting - and it's unclear where the pills are being manufactured.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The BBC found some sellers with production certificates from factories in Guangzhou and Henan, in China. Others claim to be sourcing the pills from Germany.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Some packets state they were produced in Remagen in Germany - but the BBC has discovered there is no such company listed at the address given.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Certain Kazakh vendors selling Molecule to Russians told the BBC they bought stock from friends or warehouses in the capital Astana but couldn't name the original supplier.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;ul class="sc-6f869981-0 diUlgm"&gt;&lt;li class="sc-734a601e-0 cRgahm"&gt;&lt;i id="details-of-support-with-eating-disorders-in-the-uk-are-available-at" class="sc-d16436d-0 iVdNuz"&gt;Details of support with eating disorders in the UK are available at &lt;/i&gt;&lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/articles/2DRkg4JC7SLT3B7hlrn6DKN/information-and-support-eating-disorders" class="sc-f9178328-0 kgTYQp"&gt;&lt;i id="bbc-action-line" class="sc-d16436d-0 iVdNuz"&gt;BBC Action Line&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;i id="" class="sc-d16436d-0 iVdNuz"&gt; &lt;/i&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Meanwhile, online eating-disorder communities have become spaces where Molecule is promoted, with users relying on hashtags and coded terms to slip past moderation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Ms Solovieva says Molecule is particularly harmful when taken by young people who already have eating disorders. For those in or near relapse, an easily available appetite suppressant can be seriously dangerous, she says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Anna Enina, a Russian influencer with millions of followers who herself has admitted using unlicensed weight-loss pills in the past, publicly warned her subscribers: "As someone who has struggled with an eating disorder... the consequences will be dire. You'll regret it tenfold."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;Maria from St Petersburg now discourages others from trying Molecule&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Twenty-two-year old Maria suffered bad side effects, and is one of those who regrets it. After taking too many Molecule pills, she was sent to hospital.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Now she discourages other young women and girls from taking the pills in weight-loss forums. She even reached out to one teenage user's parents to alert them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;But Molecule remains popular online.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;And every video that appears on Maria's TikTok feed is a reminder of the pills that made her sick.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BBC</author><pubDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2025 00:07:32 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiWkFVX3lxTE9HTnFadmdrU2NCVXZrTGR6YmFJeXlrYkJMQTEta2RjLXFES0R1UXczWkMzSnNCNmFEUkd0LWsyYm4xY3dGbmRDLXpyVFhsNHQxcGVWbVV5bE91QdIBX0FVX3lxTE1HNjYyYmtHbVFIRXlBSXkzUEFFaGdxaWVqNDRvVzdCRWtkS0p4NmdpX1gyQ21IU1gxcTdIdndhM2ZTRXM1Wm5tSnF5NzhNaklFaTFYbS1La1RDekVhTGVv</guid></item><item><title>牙医警告口干：了解其含义、症状和治疗方法-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/dentists-warn-about-dry-mouth-know-its-meaning-symptoms-and-treatment/articleshow/125023971.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;div class="MwN2O"&gt;&lt;div class="vdo_embedd"&gt; &lt;div class="T22zO"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you have been checking off on your hydration goals daily and yet feel constantly dry in the mouth, then you could likely have dry mouth. Also known as Xerostomia, this is an oral health condition that reduces saliva flow, leading to various symptoms including bad breath, rapid tooth decay and more. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="3"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="4"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;How common is Dry Mouth?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to dentists, the condition is more common than you think. Dry Mouth affects about one in five people, as per the &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://my.clevelandclinic.org/health/diseases/10902-dry-mouth-xerostomia" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="_blank" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;Cleveland Clinic&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;. However, Dr Kourosh Maddahi, a dentist at Dion Health in California shared with NBC Select, that the condition is underdiagnosed as people often mistake it with dehydration. And the longer it remains undiagnosed the more damage it creates for your oral health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="8"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="lOvcW vdo_embedd"&gt;&lt;div class="k7lcu"&gt;&lt;p class="efT4r"&gt;6 Home remedies to get rid of bad breath&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="10"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;A 2023 report by the &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.ada.org/resources/ada-library/oral-health-topics/xerostomia#:~:text=Severity%20of%20dry%20mouth%20symptoms,22%25%20of%20the%20global%20population." rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;American Dental Association&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; stated that dry mouth affects about 10 to 26 per cent of men and 10 to 33 per cent of women. Globally, about 22 per cent of the population is estimated to have xerostomia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="16"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;How would you know if you have dry mouth? Check for these symptoms and follow the treatments mentioned below!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="18"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="19"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Dry Mouth: What are the common symptoms?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="20"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.ada.org/resources/ada-library/oral-health-topics/xerostomia#:~:text=Severity%20of%20dry%20mouth%20symptoms,22%25%20of%20the%20global%20population." rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="_blank" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;American Dental Association&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; states that xerostomia can cause the following symptoms:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="24"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Burning feeling in the mouth&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="26"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Problems in chewing, swallowing, tasting or speaking&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="28"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Altered taste&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="30"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dry or sore throat&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="32"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mouth Sores&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="34"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bad breath&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="36"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cracked or peeling lips&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="38"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;If any of these symptoms persist for long, consulting a professional for diagnosis is advised.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="41"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="42"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Dry Mouth: What are the treatments?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The first step in the treatment is of course consulting with a dentist who can examine the severity of the condition and assess the decay. Most treatments for dry mouth consist of over-the-counter products such as mouthwashes, gels, chewing gums and lozenges. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="44"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, sometimes longer lifestyle changes such as avoiding certain food items and drinks are also required. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="46"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="47"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Understanding dry mouth or xerostomia&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="48"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;In simple words, dry mouth is a condition that makes the mouth feel dry due to an inadequate amount of saliva. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="51"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The most frequent causes of the condition are the use of certain medications. As per a 2018 study published in the &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/29071719/" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="_blank" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;Journal of the American Geriatrics Society&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, urologic medications, antidepressants and psycholeptics were associated with dry mouth in adults. Additionally, chemotherapy or head and neck cancer radiotherapy can also cause the condition as they directly cause toxicity to salivary glands and oral tissues. And, tobacco and cannabis use can also accelerate it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="56"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dry mouth can be damaging to oral health because of the changes it causes to the amount and consistency of saliva in the mouth. Saliva is a natural antibiotic in the mouth and protects it from bacteria, acts as a lubricant, and cleans plaque and other particles from teeth. It also remineralises tooth enamel as it is packed with calcium and phosphate, making the teeth resistant to decay. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="58"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;With a lack of saliva in the mouth, all the symptoms of dry mouth can amp up the progression of the condition and lead to more damage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="60"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Note:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; The information provided in this article is for educational purposes only and is not intended as medical advice. Always consult with a healthcare professional before starting any new medication or treatment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="63"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="65"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Times of India</author><pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 23:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi_gFBVV95cUxQNUN3cGgtSXQ0WDVldG1YQXJGMzNwOEs2eXdQcThWV1NQUmN3V0Z0YzBHaHI0cmpzMzZnYVE1UTJ6UV9zbW45X0g4SUN5aDBXc2toNXVya0tlazFQTjVFSkFHcmJ0RlR4LW8xZnJLTk8wZW1OTzhXbjNLeTRvNGk5T0QtMzNqdXZHM3o4eDNXazJwWVY2Wl96aXhNdGMtSUdXX2dwX2tZNWZJU1dhQnhYb3FoX1Z5T0Q1ZTdfdU1oQmM4RF9mTk9VTFBxTHVGOWhnZWlmS0J3NGtYZm52WXlTZ25xYk5Ja2V3UW96YmJpcThsWENhRTFESmZ4WVluQdIBgwJBVV95cUxNX0xsQVYycGUzYTlUSkY1NjM4Z1gtOEVSWGJSbkhWVk9zbnJWTm9QVzB3ckR2Z3FVWWQwVTVaSG5sSDd4NWU4ekJ6ZnllTmR0M29lbloyQVoySG80VGRLYXhZSU5rMVhRNVlGZWtzZWRRbER3dXh6cm1wS19SS0M0T25TUmNWRTdnVUVPZ1hJaUlYVmdjeFBMdll5R2hLNXk5WFF2Q1RxMjZMWmFqb2hLd1VyTFhkemZaYWNVYjRXa1hlcHV2TkNlM3B2d1lDdm92YV96S1FCbkl0R3piR0NtMnlXNEpqM1F0c0xucC1KQ3BDSVNVUkh5a25Kb2RnWFBaZkNF</guid></item><item><title>科学家发现大麻使用与表观遗传变化有关-雅虎</title><link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/articles/cannabis-linked-epigenetic-changes-scientists-215447890.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="" data-article-body="true"&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Cannabis use may leave lasting fingerprints on the human body, a study of over 1,000 adults published in 2023 suggests – not in our DNA code itself, but in how that code is expressed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;US researchers found it may cause changes in the &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/epigenetic-changes" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:epigenome;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;epigenome&lt;/a&gt;, which acts like a set of switches that activate or deactivate genes involved in how our bodies function; findings that were validated by a systematic literature review &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.drugalcdep.2024.111401" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:published in 2024;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;published in 2024&lt;/a&gt; by researchers in Portugal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;"We observed associations between cumulative marijuana use and multiple epigenetic markers across time," epidemiologist Lifang Hou from Northwestern University &lt;a href="https://news.feinberg.northwestern.edu/2023/07/18/marijuana-use-linked-to-epigenetic-changes/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:explained;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;explained&lt;/a&gt; of his team's findings in 2023.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/cannabis-can-leave-a-distinct-mark-on-your-dna-study-reveals?utm_source=SA_article&amp;amp;utm_campaign=related_link" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Cannabis Can Leave a Distinct Mark on Your DNA, Study Reveals;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Cannabis Can Leave a Distinct Mark on Your DNA, Study Reveals&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cannabis_(drug)" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Cannabis;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Cannabis&lt;/a&gt; is a &lt;a href="https://www.yahoo.com/news/cannabis-rising-across-us-except-025456334.html" data-ylk="slk:commonly used substance in the US;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas;outcm:mb_qualified_link;_E:mb_qualified_link;ct:story;" class="link  yahoo-link"&gt;commonly used substance in the US&lt;/a&gt;, with nearly half of Americans having tried it at least once, Hou and team report in their &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1038/s41380-023-02106-y" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:published paper;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;published paper&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Some US states and &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/australia-s-capital-just-legalised-recreational-marijuana-in-defiance-of-federal-laws" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:other countries;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;other countries&lt;/a&gt; have made cannabis use legal, but we still &lt;a href="https://www.yahoo.com/news/discovery-helps-explain-cannabis-triggers-220057665.html" data-ylk="slk:don't fully understand;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas;outcm:mb_qualified_link;_E:mb_qualified_link;ct:story;" class="link  yahoo-link"&gt;don't fully understand&lt;/a&gt; its &lt;a href="https://www.yahoo.com/news/male-cannabis-users-seem-show-090056205.html" data-ylk="slk:effects on our health;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas;outcm:mb_qualified_link;_E:mb_qualified_link;ct:story;" class="link  yahoo-link"&gt;effects on our health&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;To investigate this, the researchers analyzed data from a long-running health study that had tracked around 1,000 adults over two decades.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Participants, who were between 18 and 30 years old when the study began, were surveyed about their cannabis use over the years and gave blood samples at the 15- and 20-year marks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Using these blood samples from five years apart, Hou and her team looked at the &lt;a class="link " href="https://www.sciencealert.com/epigenetic-changes" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:epigenetic changes;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas"&gt;epigenetic changes&lt;/a&gt;, specifically &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/DNA_methylation" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:DNA methylation;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;DNA methylation&lt;/a&gt; levels, of people who had used cannabis recently or for a long time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The addition or removal of &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Methyl_group" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:methyl groups;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;methyl groups&lt;/a&gt; from DNA is one of the most studied epigenetic modifications.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="relative mb-4"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="relative text-sm mt-1 pr-2.5"&gt;&lt;p&gt;When epigenetic factors, which can come from other genes or the environment inside a cell or beyond, recruit a methyl group, it changes the expression of our genes. (ttsz/iStock/Getty Images)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Without changing the genomic sequence, DNA methylation affects how easily cells 'read' and interpret genes, much like someone covering up key lines in your set of instructions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Environmental and lifestyle factors can trigger these methylation changes, which can be &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/heres-how-events-in-your-grandparents-lives-could-affect-your-genes" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:passed to future generations;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;passed to future generations&lt;/a&gt;, and blood &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Biomarker" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:biomarkers;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;biomarkers&lt;/a&gt; can provide information about both recent and historical exposures.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;"We previously identified associations between marijuana use and the aging process as captured through DNA methylation," Hou &lt;a href="https://news.feinberg.northwestern.edu/2023/07/18/marijuana-use-linked-to-epigenetic-changes/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:said;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;said&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;"We wanted to further explore whether specific epigenetic factors were associated with marijuana and whether these factors are related to health outcomes."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="relative mb-4"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="relative text-sm mt-1 pr-2.5"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Environmental and lifestyle factors can trigger methylation changes, which can be passed to future generations. (&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.canva.com/photos/MADYNemcmnI/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Monkey Business Images/Canva;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Monkey Business Images/Canva&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The comprehensive data on the participants' cannabis use allowed the researchers to estimate cumulative use over time as well as recent use and compare it with DNA methylation markers in their blood for analysis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;They found numerous DNA methylation markers in the 15-year blood samples, 22 that were associated with recent use, and 31 associated with cumulative cannabis use.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;In the samples taken at the 20-year point, they identified 132 markers linked to recent use and 16 linked to cumulative use.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="relative mb-4"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="relative text-sm mt-1 pr-2.5"&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;"Interestingly, we consistently identified one marker that has previously been associated with tobacco use," Hou &lt;a href="https://news.feinberg.northwestern.edu/2023/07/18/marijuana-use-linked-to-epigenetic-changes/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:explained;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;explained&lt;/a&gt;, "suggesting a potential shared epigenetic regulation between tobacco and marijuana use."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Multiple epigenetic changes associated with cannabis use had previously been linked to things like &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cell_proliferation" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:cellular proliferation;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;cellular proliferation&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.mycancergenome.org/content/pathways/hormone-signaling/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:hormone signaling;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;hormone signaling&lt;/a&gt;, infections, neurological disorders like &lt;a class="link " href="https://www.sciencealert.com/schizophrenia" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:schizophrenia;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas"&gt;schizophrenia&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.mayoclinic.org/diseases-conditions/bipolar-disorder/symptoms-causes/syc-20355955" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:bipolar disorder;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;bipolar disorder&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Substance_use_disorder" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:substance use disorders;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;substance use disorders&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;It's important to note that this study doesn't prove that cannabis directly causes these changes or causes health problems.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="relative mb-4"&gt;&lt;a data-ylk="ct:story;elm:img;itc:0;" class="stretched-box" href="https://www.sciencealert.com/spark-into-space-comp" rel="noopener noreferrer nofollow" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;figcaption class="relative text-sm mt-1 pr-2.5"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Win a $10,000 Space Coast Adventure Holiday&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;"This research has provided novel insights into the association between marijuana use and epigenetic factors," &lt;a href="https://news.feinberg.northwestern.edu/2023/07/18/marijuana-use-linked-to-epigenetic-changes/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:said;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;said &lt;/a&gt;epidemiologist Drew Nannini from Northwestern University.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;"Additional studies are needed to determine whether these associations are consistently observed in different populations. Moreover, studies examining the effect of marijuana on age-related health outcomes may provide further insight into the long-term effect of marijuana on health."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The study has been published in &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1038/s41380-023-02106-y" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Molecular Psychiatry;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;&lt;em&gt;Molecular Psychiatry&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;em&gt;An earlier version of this article was published in July 2023.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="mb-4 text-lg font-bold"&gt;Related News&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Yahoo</author><pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 21:54:47 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMinAFBVV95cUxObFJpVTdBbUJidTZEeDhSWG1CNktUT3RMX1JIYmU0dTN6UHRPeVNxckQyX3dEX0pLeHFGWFFGQ0tWMGI3NzMwSnI4M0V6Z2xoWTBqalVONmpCWlltak5XVHI0UWJRSTQtUlRIMnVFRmFrOXRSV3QzZy1SdHBlYU9mcWF2SWZYcWdTLWctOEdVREM5MWU2ODA2ZFhiVzY</guid></item><item><title>根据心理学， 8种创造性技能可以让你的大脑年轻7岁- VegOut</title><link>https://vegoutmag.com/things-to-do/z-8-creative-skills-that-may-keep-your-brain-7-years-younger-according-to-psychology/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="page__content mt-4"&gt;
							&lt;p&gt;We all want to stay sharp as we move through life.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’ve written a lot about mental fitness before, but this one struck me personally. A new international study found that people who regularly engage in creative practices have brains that look &lt;em&gt;seven years younger&lt;/em&gt; than their actual age. Seven years. That’s not small.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The researchers, from the Max Planck Institute for Empirical Aesthetics, used neuroimaging data to study brain “age gaps.” They discovered that adults who frequently &lt;a href="https://www.aesthetics.mpg.de/en/research/research-group-neural-circuits-consciousness-and-cognition/news/news-detailseite/article/creative-minds-younger-brains-new-study-shows-creative-experiences-delay-brain-aging.html?.com"&gt;take part in creative activities&lt;/a&gt; such as music, writing, dance, or crafts tend to show younger neural profiles than their peers. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That means creativity isn’t just about expression; it’s a kind of brain exercise. Below are eight creative skills that may literally keep your brain younger, backed by psychology and science, with a few observations from my own experience thrown in.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;1) Playing a musical instrument&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If there’s one creative activity that shows up again and again in brain-aging research, it’s music.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When you play an instrument, you’re not just moving your hands; you’re processing pitch, rhythm, timing, and emotion. You’re reading or remembering notes, coordinating muscle movement, and listening closely for feedback. That’s multiple brain regions working together in real time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A 2024 &lt;em&gt;eLife&lt;/em&gt; paper found that musicians tend to &lt;a href="https://www.eurekalert.org/news-releases/1100848?.com"&gt;maintain stronger white-matter integrity&lt;/a&gt; and higher neural efficiency in older age.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I started revisiting my old music-blogger roots and picked up a ukulele last year. I won’t be winning any Grammys, but the process of learning new chords and strumming patterns feels like mental yoga. It forces focus and flexibility in equal measure.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Even 10 to 15 minutes of practice a few times a week can make a difference. The goal isn’t mastery; it’s engagement.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;2) Visual arts (painting, drawing, digital art)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If music isn’t your thing, pick up a pencil. Or a stylus.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Visual arts such as painting, drawing, sculpting, or even digital illustration light up brain regions tied to spatial awareness, visual memory, and creative planning. Studies show that people who regularly engage in artistic expression have &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41591-025-00063-3?.com"&gt;better cognitive flexibility&lt;/a&gt; and stronger emotional regulation. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;During a trip to Costa Rica a few years ago, I took a one-day outdoor sketching class. I was awful at it. But here’s what surprised me: focusing on the interplay of light and shadow, seeing how colors shift at different times of day, it changed how I noticed the world afterward.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Creativity rewires perception. That’s what keeps the brain young; it keeps it curious.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;3) Dance and movement arts&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ever noticed how dancers seem ageless? There’s science behind that.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dancing doesn’t just engage the body; it stimulates the cerebellum, hippocampus, and motor cortex, all areas tied to coordination and memory. Tango dancers, in particular, have shown&lt;a href="https://www.smithsonianmag.com/smart-news/creative-hobbies-could-help-keep-your-brain-young-180987476/?.com"&gt; slower cognitive decline&lt;/a&gt; compared to non-dancers. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dance blends rhythm, movement, emotion, and improvisation. It’s one of the most “whole-brain” creative practices out there.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’m not naturally coordinated, but a few summers ago, I joined a friend for a salsa class in Los Angeles. Between laughing at my two left feet and trying to follow the beat, I realized how alive I felt. My brain was firing on all cylinders, anticipating, reacting, adapting.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You don’t have to join a dance troupe. Even a weekly class, or moving freely to your favorite song in your living room, counts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;4) Photography and visual composition&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Photography gets overlooked in the creative skill conversation, but it shouldn’t.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When you compose a shot, you’re making a thousand micro-decisions: where to focus, what to include, what to leave out. You’re adjusting light, color, and angle. You’re engaging visual-spatial reasoning, memory, and intuition simultaneously.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’ve been doing street photography around Los Angeles lately. Carrying a camera changes the way I walk. I’m scanning for patterns, reflections, small stories in motion. It’s not just about taking a photo; it’s about learning to &lt;em&gt;see&lt;/em&gt;. That mental habit of curiosity keeps the brain active and alert.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you’re new to it, start with your phone. Limit yourself to one theme, say, reflections or textures, and shoot three photos a day. It’s like mindfulness training with a creative edge.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;5) Improvisational writing or storytelling&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Writing is another powerful way to keep your brain elastic.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But here’s the key. It has to be creative writing, not just work emails or to-do lists. When you write stories, poems, or reflective essays, you’re engaging what psychologists call &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Divergent_thinking?.com"&gt;divergent thinking&lt;/a&gt;, the ability to generate many ideas from one prompt. That’s one of the cognitive abilities most strongly linked to creative intelligence. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When I travel, I sometimes write short micro-stories about the people I meet, a cab driver in Bangkok, a barista in Lisbon, a musician in Oaxaca. It’s not about publishing them; it’s about connecting dots and seeing meaning in small moments.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Want to try it? Open your notes app, pick a random object near you, and write a short story that begins with, “This object has a secret.” Don’t edit yourself. Just write for five minutes. Your prefrontal cortex will thank you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;6) Strategic games or creative gaming&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let’s clear something up. Video games, board games, and puzzles can be good for your brain if they’re strategic or creative.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A 2024 review of over 20 studies found that people who regularly played complex games like chess, strategy video games, or world-building sims had &lt;a href="https://www.realsimple.com/how-creative-hobbies-keep-your-brain-young-11836947?.com"&gt;improved cognitive flexibility&lt;/a&gt; and delayed signs of brain aging. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The reason? Strategy games demand decision-making, pattern recognition, and adaptation, all cognitive skills that tend to decline with age if left unchallenged.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When I was traveling in Japan, a friend introduced me to Go. I didn’t know the rules, but once I started, I was hooked. The strategic depth is unreal. You think ten moves ahead, and it humbles you every time. That’s what the brain thrives on, challenge with feedback.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So yes, if you play thoughtful games regularly, it’s not wasting time. It’s brain training disguised as fun.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;7) Crafting or building things (DIY)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you prefer something tangible, crafting and DIY projects are gold.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These activities such as woodworking, sewing, gardening, or building furniture combine problem-solving with fine motor control. Research from the Mayo Clinic found that older adults who frequently engaged in hands-on creative activities had &lt;a href="https://time.com/3814104/adults-arts-and-crafts/?.com"&gt;a 30 percent lower risk&lt;/a&gt; of developing mild cognitive impairment. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Last year I built a small bookshelf for my vegan cookbook collection. It took twice as long as expected, and the paint job wasn’t perfect, but I noticed how mentally stimulating it was. I had to plan, measure, visualize, and adjust. Every mistake was a mini-lesson in spatial reasoning.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The satisfaction you get when you finish something with your hands isn’t just emotional; it’s neurological. It tells your brain, “We can still learn new tricks.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;8) Multimodal creative mixing (combining skills)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This last one is where things get interesting.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Researchers call it &lt;a href="https://arxiv.org/abs/1508.00073?.com"&gt;cross-domain creativity&lt;/a&gt;, combining two or more creative modes, like music and art, or photography and writing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;People who engage in multimodal creative projects show higher integration between brain networks that don’t usually talk to each other. That cross-activation is believed to buffer against cognitive aging.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For example, I once challenged myself to write a short instrumental track, photograph an image that matched its mood, and write a short essay connecting the two. It was clumsy, but it was fun. And the mental engagement was next-level.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The point isn’t perfection; it’s exploration. Try mixing two creative hobbies you already enjoy. You’ll stretch different neural circuits at once, which is exactly what the science says keeps the brain youthful.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;How to start if you feel “non-creative”&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here’s the secret: creativity isn’t a talent; it’s a muscle.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can build it gradually by choosing small, doable actions:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Play a short piece on an instrument you already have at home.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sketch one object from your day before bed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Take one creative photo a day for a week.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Journal using prompts like “What did I notice today that I usually ignore?”&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Learn a simple dance routine on YouTube.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Build or repair something small with your hands.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Blend two of the above.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The goal is to engage curiosity, not to perform.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After a few weeks, you’ll likely notice your attention feels sharper, your mood lighter, and your perspective wider. Those are all signs that your brain is adapting, and that’s exactly what keeps it youthful.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;My takeaway&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As someone who writes about psychology and decision-making, I find this body of research oddly reassuring. It means our hobbies aren’t distractions from real life; they’re part of maintaining it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The older I get, the more I realize creativity isn’t about making art; it’s about staying awake to the world. It’s how we keep seeing beauty in small things, keep questioning, keep inventing. And it just so happens that those same habits might help our brains stay seven years younger.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, whatever creative spark you’ve been ignoring, pick it up. Nurture it. Let it grow messy and unpredictable.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Your future self and your brain will thank you for it.&lt;/p&gt;
						&lt;/div&gt;
					&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>VegOut</author><pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 19:33:41 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMivAFBVV95cUxOandEUG5PQjE2bklUam91Z200clFpRDBJX0xVMFlmSTRkQ1pvVnBCSzhYdS1rT3poVDBwMjhPREtDTTQ0b012SjlRTFFQNGNIbUtaV2Z2cm15SXY0UkdZTFM5RUs5cW5Eb0Z0c0RMMmJieWdyRWlndDRKckYzUWNnaW5ST3JuREF3LTJIZnNBTVJVZkZTb1F3Slg2S1JSdHdLcHhXcGlUSjRvUzk5UmJHOUpZUm1veUoydGIxWg</guid></item><item><title>研究表明，美国50岁以下人群的憩室炎激增-upi.com</title><link>https://www.upi.com/Health_News/2025/11/01/gut-disorder-younger-adults/4041762021999/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="stph_caption"&gt;Younger adults increasingly are experiencing diverticulitis, a gut disorder that more commonly occurs later in life. Photo by Adobe Stock/HealthDay News&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;article itemprop="articleBody"&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Younger adults are developing a severe gut disorder at increasing rates, according to a new study.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There's been a troubling surge in severe diverticulitis among Americans younger than 50, researchers from UCLA and Vanderbilt University recently reported.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They found that the proportion of patients younger than 50 admitted to the hospital with severe diverticulitis increased by more than half, rising from just under 19% in 2005 to more than 28% in 2020.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"We're seeing a significant shift in who is being hospitalized for severe diverticulitis," said lead researcher Shineui Kim, a fourth-year medical student at the &lt;a href="https://www.upi.com/topic/David_Geffen/" target="_blank" title="David Geffen" class="tpstyle"&gt;David Geffen&lt;/a&gt; School of Medicine at UCLA.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"This condition was traditionally thought of as a disease of older adults, but our data shows that younger Americans are increasingly affected, and often with more complicated presentations," Kim said in a news release.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Diverticulitis involves small pouches that form at weak spots along the wall of the colon. In severe cases, these pouches can become infected or torn, resulting in potentially life-threatening complications.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For the new study, researchers analyzed records of more than 5.2 million hospitalizations in the U.S.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Of these patients, about 16% were "early-onset" cases occurring in people younger than 50. The number of these cases that involved severe diverticulitis rose by 52% during the study period.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;However, treatment strategies also have evolved.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The proportion of younger patients requiring surgical removal of part of the colon to treat their diverticulitis dropped from nearly 35% to around 20%, showing that doctors are successfully using more conservative approaches to treat serious cases, Kim said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The study found that younger diverticulitis patients tended to die less often and have shorter hospital stays and lower hospitalization costs compared to older patients.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;However, they also were more likely to require complicated procedures, with 29% higher odds of needing to remove part of the colon and 58% higher odds of requiring abscess drainage, researchers found.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"While younger patients generally have better survival outcomes and shorter hospitalizations, they're paradoxically more likely to need invasive interventions," Kim said. "This suggests their disease may be more aggressive or that treatment approaches differ based on patient age and overall health status."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It's not clear why more younger adults are developing diverticulitis, but researchers noted the trend dovetails with an increased risk of colon cancer among this age group.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Little is known about why we're seeing this increase in younger patients," Kim said. "We urgently need additional research to determine what's driving these trends whether it's dietary factors, lifestyle changes, obesity rates or other environmental influences."
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;People can lower their risk of diverticulitis by increasing the amount of fiber in their diet. Only surgery can remove pouches that have already developed in the colon, according to Harvard Medical School&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The new study appears in the journal &lt;a href="https://journals.lww.com/dcrjournal/abstract/2025/05000/national_trends_in_hospital_admissions,.13.aspx" target="_blank"&gt;Diseases in the Colon &amp;amp; Rectum&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;More information&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Harvard Medical School has more on &lt;a href="https://www.health.harvard.edu/diseases-and-conditions/diverticulosis-and-diverticulitis-a-to-z" target="_blank"&gt;diverticulitis&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Copyright © 2025 HealthDay. All rights reserved.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img class="lazy" data-src="https://www.upi.com/img/healthday.jpg"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;/article&gt;
					&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>upi.com</author><pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 18:57:22 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijgFBVV95cUxQaGRNQ0MxX1VaanV2WUtWNW1RZlFKcmhYTmljbnNhUDRLZU9sMEJ1ZDJMTTdPcEVBOTdITmNWS1k0a3NndDZyU2hTVzFpQ3RKVjVjeGh1aWFvbmdnQ3A3VmtkdTlsOEVlU1VldUdRdEJzeHhRTFBmWHVzREZCS2dhTzFFTWJZalBmQmw0ekJn</guid></item><item><title>以下是医生目前看到的4种最常见的新冠肺炎症状-雅虎</title><link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/articles/4-most-common-covid-symptoms-182500971.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="" data-article-body="true"&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.yahoo.com/news/articles/most-common-covid-19-symptoms-102500122.html" data-ylk="slk:COVID-19;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas;outcm:mb_qualified_link;_E:mb_qualified_link;ct:story;" class="link  yahoo-link"&gt;COVID-19&lt;/a&gt; turns six this fall. While we may wish it didn't, the good news is that we're much more informed about the illness once considered mysterious, including its ever-changing symptoms.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Each year and season, the COVID variants change," says &lt;a href="https://www.stonybrook.edu/experts/profile/sharon-nachman" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Dr. Sharon Nachman, MD;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dr. Sharon Nachman, MD&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, the chief of pediatric infectious diseases at Stony Brook Children's Hospital. "As a result, often the symptoms change as well. In some years, we see mainly cough, while in others, we see severe &lt;a href="https://www.yahoo.com/lifestyle/7-reasons-why-throat-might-110000086.html" data-ylk="slk:sore throat;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas;outcm:mb_qualified_link;_E:mb_qualified_link;ct:story;" class="link  yahoo-link"&gt;sore throat&lt;/a&gt;."&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;None of these symptoms sounds like a good time, but sick happens. So, what are the most common COVID-19 symptoms right now? We asked doctors to share what they're seeing and hearing from patients about COVID-19 symptoms going into November 2025.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;🩺&lt;a href="https://parade.com/newsletters/healthy-now-2" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:SIGN UP for Parade’s health newsletter with expert-approved tips, healthy eats, exercises, news &amp;amp; more to help you stay healthy &amp;amp; feel your best self;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;SIGN UP for Parade’s health newsletter with expert-approved tips, healthy eats, exercises, news &amp;amp; more to help you stay healthy &amp;amp; feel your best self&lt;/a&gt;💊&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="relative mb-4"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;h2 class="mb-4 text-xl font-bold md:text-2xl"&gt;What Are the Most Common COVID-19 Symptoms in November 2025?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;COVID-19 has evolved, but honestly, many physicians are seeing more of the same. "The most common symptoms are fatigue and fever," says &lt;a href="https://familydoctor.org/media_ambassadors/michael-richardson/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Dr. Michael Richardson, MD;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dr. Michael Richardson, MD&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, a family physician.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;He reports that other top COVID-19 symptoms in November 2025 include:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class="mb-4"&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Shortness of breath (in severe cases)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Scratchy &lt;a href="https://www.yahoo.com/news/articles/most-common-covid-19-symptoms-102500122.html" data-ylk='slk:"razorblade" throats;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas;outcm:mb_qualified_link;_E:mb_qualified_link;ct:story;' class="link  yahoo-link"&gt;"razorblade" throats&lt;/a&gt; were common during the summer of 2025. Some physicians &lt;a href="https://www.yahoo.com/news/articles/most-common-covid-19-symptoms-102500122.html" data-ylk="slk:are noticing less;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas;outcm:mb_qualified_link;_E:mb_qualified_link;ct:story;" class="link  yahoo-link"&gt;are noticing less&lt;/a&gt; of this symptom, but others say it's alive and well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;"We are hearing specifically about severe knifelike sore throat with far less cough as the primary symptom," says Dr. Nachman, who practices on Long Island in New York. "That is not to say that we don’t also expect fever, body aches and cough to occur, but rather we are seeing more throat complaints than in prior seasons."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Thankfully, some other dangerous symptoms and side effects of COVID-19 aren't as prevalent in the fall of 2025. "While we are still seeing some COVID pneumonia, it is much less common than in prior years," says &lt;a href="https://memorialhermann.org/doctors" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Dr. Linda Yancey, MD;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dr. Linda Yancey, MD&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, an infectious disease specialist with Memorial Hermann Health System.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Also, doctors continue to see far less of two other symptoms once considered COVID-19 hallmarks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;"Early strains of COVID used to make people lose their sense of taste or smell, but that symptom is significantly less common today," says &lt;a href="https://www.medicalofficesofmanhattan.com/our-team/dr-michael-dosik/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Dr. Michael Dosik, MD;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dr. Michael Dosik, MD&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, a primary care physician with Medical Offices of Manhattan and contributor to &lt;a href="https://www.labfinder.com" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:labfinder.com;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;labfinder.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;If you &lt;em&gt;do &lt;/em&gt;experience a loss of taste and smell, it's a telltale sign you probably have COVID-19. However, there's only one way to tell for sure whether you have COVID-19, the flu or RSV (or none of the above).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;"The best way to distinguish between them is by testing," Dr. Richardson clarifies. "All of them share similar symptoms."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Luckily, as COVID-19 has evolved, so have we. "Tests come back within minutes, helping to guide treatment plans and to discuss with families the possibility of [preventative strategies] for the household members," Dr. Nachman shares. "This is especially true for &lt;a href="https://www.yahoo.com/news/articles/experts-warn-look-flu-symptoms-145000937.html" data-ylk="slk:flu;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas;outcm:mb_qualified_link;_E:mb_qualified_link;ct:story;" class="link  yahoo-link"&gt;flu&lt;/a&gt;, where we have several easily available medications that people in close contact with flu can take to successfully prevent their own illness."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.yahoo.com/news/articles/covid-had-startling-impact-brains-212500799.html" data-ylk="slk:COVID Had a Startling Impact on Our Brains, New Research Says—Here’s What a Neurologist Wants You To Do;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas;outcm:mb_qualified_link;_E:mb_qualified_link;ct:story;" class="link  yahoo-link"&gt;COVID Had a Startling Impact on Our Brains, New Research Says—Here’s What a Neurologist Wants You To Do&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mb-4 text-xl font-bold md:text-2xl"&gt;Do We Really Need Another COVID Booster?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;It's a common question, especially amid new federal guidelines—and at times, conflicting state policies. However, doctors remain firm that getting a COVID-19 booster is safe, effective and an excellent defense against severe illness from the virus.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;"All adults would benefit from a &lt;a href="https://www.yahoo.com/news/doctors-begging-patients-65-extra-202500816.html" data-ylk="slk:COVID booster;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas;outcm:mb_qualified_link;_E:mb_qualified_link;ct:story;" class="link  yahoo-link"&gt;COVID booster&lt;/a&gt;," Dr. Richardson says. "Like the flu shot, the COVID booster changes and is targeted to the current strain of the illness. Getting the booster will protect you from serious side effects if you do encounter COVID."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;He urges people to speak with their family physician if they have questions about the COVID-19 booster. Dr. Nachman also suggests having a close discussion with your medical provider, who knows your medical history, including your age and underlying conditions (like diabetes and lung disease), you have that might put you at a greater risk for severe illness and hospitalization.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;"In general, it's important to recognize that these vaccines will help prevent hospitalization and emergency room visits, but not every trace of illnesses," Dr. Nachman says. "So, yes, it will be important to get these vaccines."&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;When should you get your COVID-19 booster? If you're reading this in November 2025, there's no time like the present!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;"Now is a good time to get a COVID booster," Dr. Yancey urges. "Though most cases are mild, you can spare yourself a week of fever and cough, and you will be protecting your at-risk friends and family."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://health.yahoo.com/conditions/immune-system/articles/immunologists-people-over-50-adopt-182500882.html" data-ylk="slk:Immunologists Are Begging People Over 50 To Start Doing This 1 Daily Habit ASAP;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas;outcm:mb_qualified_link;_E:mb_qualified_link;ct:story;" class="link  yahoo-link"&gt;Immunologists Are Begging People Over 50 To Start Doing This 1 Daily Habit ASAP&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mb-4 text-xl font-bold md:text-2xl"&gt;What's the Best Way To Treat COVID?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;First, make sure you actually have COVID-19. "It’s important to be cautious and get an at-home COVID test to see if you have an active infection and need to isolate," Dr. Richardson explains. "Then, depending on the results, you should isolate or wear a mask. If the test is negative, you should check again the next day if you are still having symptoms."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;If you're positive, tell hustle culture to take a seat. "The best thing to do when you have COVID or any viral illness is rest and stay hydrated," Dr. Dosik explains. "Your body is fighting a battle internally, and so you shouldn’t do anything to stress it externally. Using acetaminophen or NSAIDs such as ibuprofen can be useful to reduce high fevers and for pain relief to get you through the worst of the illness."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;FWIW, your colleagues and boss should thank you for calling out.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;"If ill, please try to stay home from work," Dr. Nachman advises. "It does not matter if you have RSV, the flu or COVID. You are highly contagious and likely to pass these viral illnesses to your co-workers."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.yahoo.com/news/articles/experts-warn-look-flu-symptoms-145000937.html" data-ylk="slk:These Are the Most Common Symptoms of the Flu That Doctors Are Seeing Right Now;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas;outcm:mb_qualified_link;_E:mb_qualified_link;ct:story;" class="link  yahoo-link"&gt;These Are the Most Common Symptoms of the Flu That Doctors Are Seeing Right Now&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mb-4 text-xl font-bold md:text-2xl"&gt;What Protects You From COVID?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The basics still apply. "No surprises here: The best way to not get sick is to vaccinate, don’t share straws or drink from others' cups, try to stay a few feet away from someone who is coughing and wash your hands," Dr. Nachman says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;She reiterates that the vaccine can help prevent ER visits and hospitalizations. Cringe all you want at the idea of social distancing—it remains a best practice if someone near you seems sick. Respiratory viruses can spread through the air. The precise distance these germs can travel depends on the illness, but you likely don't know what the person near you in the grocery store has.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;"Some pathogens on things like door knobs or can easily pass when sharing drinks, so common sense always helps," she adds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Dr. Yancey notes that wearing a mask in crowded public spaces can also reduce viral spread. Ideally, you aren't standing next to someone who is sick and contagious at the grocery store because they stayed home—and you're doing the same.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;"If you aren’t feeling well, stay home," Dr. Richardson urges. "This will help you feel better faster and will also help by not spreading the illness to others...Before going back into the world, make sure you have been fever-free for the last 24 hours."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;As for all of those &lt;a href="https://www.yahoo.com/lifestyle/want-live-100-one-vitamin-112500554.html" data-ylk="slk:vitamins;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas;outcm:mb_qualified_link;_E:mb_qualified_link;ct:story;" class="link  yahoo-link"&gt;vitamins&lt;/a&gt; and supplements that promise to boost immunity? One-click buy with caution. "There is no conclusive data on the use of vitamins, over-the-counter supplements or anything that comes to us with just a personal recommendation," Dr. Nachman reports.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Up Next:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.yahoo.com/news/articles/daily-habit-might-quietly-reducing-145000084.html" data-ylk="slk:Related: The Surprising Daily Habit That Can Make Your Vaccine Less Effective;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas;outcm:mb_qualified_link;_E:mb_qualified_link;ct:story;" class="link  yahoo-link"&gt;Related: The Surprising Daily Habit That Can Make Your Vaccine Less Effective&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mb-4 text-xl font-bold md:text-2xl"&gt;Sources:&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;i&gt;This story was originally reported by &lt;a href="https://parade.com/health/most-common-covid-symptoms-november-2025" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Parade;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Parade&lt;/a&gt; on Nov 1, 2025, where it first appeared in the &lt;a href="https://parade.com/health" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Health &amp;amp; Wellness;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Health &amp;amp; Wellness&lt;/a&gt; section. Add Parade as a &lt;a href="https://google.com/preferences/source?q=parade.com" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Preferred Source by clicking here.;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Preferred Source by clicking here.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Yahoo</author><pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 18:25:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihgFBVV95cUxPZV9QMHlQc3h2NjRxMXNKaHFhZVlHVkJkeGp0ajltc1lZYXJZcHF0TWNaVHgtVVFQaktfdWx0a2tiWm1oeGdYakdOd3didWk3ZUNjR0JnSHVPbVl6RmQzaWhtQm9SRE5TM3FZTVM2VUt3aUROWkVHckV6R3NIQVJfMDlRSThudw</guid></item><item><title>Ichilov医院的第二名医生麻疹检测呈阳性-以色列国家新闻</title><link>https://www.israelnationalnews.com/news/417136</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-content-inside article-content" id="articleContent" data-v-2a4c3726 data-v-e580db1b-s&gt;&lt;p id="intext-1" class="sideInf" data-v-2a4c3726 data-v-e580db1b-s data-v-4bdf62d7&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-v-2a4c3726 data-v-e580db1b-s&gt;Israel's Health Ministry on Saturday evening announced that a second doctor from Ichilov Hospital has contracted measles after treating an unvaccinated child for the disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-v-2a4c3726 data-v-e580db1b-s&gt;The doctor, who is vaccinated, tested positive for measles after treating an unvaccinated child.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-v-2a4c3726 data-v-e580db1b-s&gt;Both doctors are in isolation until the end of the contagious period, and their condition is mild.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-v-2a4c3726 data-v-e580db1b-s&gt;One dose of the measles vaccine provides 93-95% of people with protection; two doses will provide 97% of people with protection against developing measles. Since the start of the outbreak earlier this year, infants and toddlers have died of measles. Seven of them were completely unvaccinated, while one infant girl, who died at age 13 months after contracting measles at the age of 11 months, was vaccinated for everything else but was not yet of age to receive the measles vaccine when she was infected with the virus.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="intext-2" class="sideInf" data-v-2a4c3726 data-v-e580db1b-s data-v-4bdf62d7&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-v-2a4c3726 data-v-e580db1b-s&gt;The Health Ministry urged the public to get vaccinated, stating: “The Health Ministry reiterates its call for the public to get vaccinated - measles is a preventable disease with a safe and effective vaccine.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-v-2a4c3726 data-v-e580db1b-s&gt;On Friday, the Ministry announced that a doctor at Ichilov Hospital had contracted measles after treating an unvaccinated child who was sick with the disease. It was emphasized that the doctor was vaccinated and that this unusual incident is under review. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="z396inn" class="" data-v-2a4c3726 data-v-e580db1b-s&gt;



&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Israel National News</author><pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 18:24:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiWkFVX3lxTFBjeXhybkdrSTVXdUNia044a05CUFJIaENBaHFWZWxxSnp1VEpiSDQ1T2k2QktIWjlheW0zZUNCdGVhUmk0VTJJTnJHX3VkZTY4QUxPaWR5Yl94dw</guid></item><item><title>您呼吸的空气可能会对您的大脑产生什么影响-《纽约时报》</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/11/01/health/alzheimers-dementia-air-pollution.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The New York Times</author><pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 16:48:40 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihwFBVV95cUxNUUhjYnlMRjQ2UmpyRkNfeFRCQ1NBamV0SHBVbjhPeUNiMXBvRjFoRktoZkhEdnlheE5jRV9oNFNURF9NcUFTbXZQVTFvem9WT3JZV1JqX3QyT2FSQVJfUDExVlZabFhFNy1tanVOUjB3WXNZNXpQUjFpZGw2cGJucEZ2N2hlVk0</guid></item><item><title>我以为我的女儿肥胖，因为她不肯停止进食……我惊讶地发现了真正的原因--《每日邮报》</title><link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-15221787/daughters-bullied-weight-rare-genetic-disorder-bardet-biedl-syndrome.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div itemprop="articleBody"&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;A mother-of-two has revealed how her daughter's mysterious weight gain was a sign of a rare genetic disorder. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;As Ciara Keown's four-year-old daughter, Harper, entered pre-K, she began suffering meltdowns over fitting into her clothes and shoes. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Despite being 'very lean' as a toddler, Harper had packed on 30 pounds within just a few months due to an insatiable appetite. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Keown and her husband had &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/health/article-14735335/man-weight-loss-transformation-without-ozempic.html"&gt;struggled with their own weight&lt;/a&gt; since they were kids, and the parents assumed Harper was following in their footsteps.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'We just thought it was our bad habits rubbing off on her,' Keown told the Daily Mail.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The family visited an obesity clinic near their home in Chattanooga, &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/tennessee/index.html" id="mol-94e667a0-b052-11f0-a33a-a5006d5ef6f4" class=""&gt;Tennessee&lt;/a&gt;, which counseled them on dietary swaps and other lifestyle changes, but Harper's weight continued to climb.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;By the time she was seven, she weighed over 100 pounds, twice as much as a typical second grader. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Children would push her down on the playground and call her 'fat,' forcing the family to pull her out of school. 'She shut down during that time,' Keown said. 'No kid should have to go through that.' &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Harper (left) and Luna Keown were both diagnosed with the rare genetic disorder Bardet-Biedl syndrome (BBS), which leads to an insatiable appetite and uncontrolled weight gain&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    
    
    &lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Unable to explain the weight gain despite diet and exercise, the clinic suggested Harper undergo genetic testing last year, which revealed she had Bardet-Biedl syndrome (BBS), a rare condition affecting just under 5,000 Americans that causes weight gain and constant, insatiable hunger. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The condition usually manifests early in childhood and progresses over time and affects nearly every major organ, eventually leading to vision loss, kidney failure and developmental delays. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Further testing showed Harper's younger sister, Luna, also had BBS, though she hadn't yet displayed symptoms, and both of their parents were carriers for the mutated genes that cause the condition.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Keown said: '[The doctor] was just mind-blown. She was like, "I've never heard of this before."'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;BBS is caused by mutations in one of at least 24 different genes, most commonly BBS1 and BBS10, which provide instructions for the formation of cilia, hairlike structures on cells that help them relay sensory information like light, sound, smell and taste.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;These mutations cause a dysfunction of the brain's melanocortin-4 receptor (MC4R) pathway, which controls hunger and satiety. If the receptor is mutated, it cannot communicate to the brain that the body is full, leading to uncontrolled eating. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Like Harper, most patients start gaining excess weight around three to five years old, which continues into adulthood, often despite dietary changes and exercise. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Luna also started to gain weight around age four, jumping from 30 to 80 pounds within a few months, more than double the weight of the average preschooler.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;After their diagnosis, the girls were put on topiramate (known as Topamax), an anticonvulsant used off-label for weight loss, and Vyvanse, a stimulant used to treat ADHD and binge eating disorder, to help slow their ravenous hunger.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;They also take setmelanotide, a daily injection under the brand name Imcivree that targets the dysfunctional MC4R pathway. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'It's a complete gamechanger,' Keown told the Daily Mail.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Harper, pictured here, weighed 108 pounds by the time she was seven years old, and she endured bullying so bad that her family was forced to pull her out of school&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Luna (left) and Harper are pictured earlier this year with their mother Ciara (right) after losing weight with medication and lifestyle changes&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;With the help of the medications, as well as dietary swaps and exercise, Harper has lost 30 pounds so far and Luna has lost 10 in the last year. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Since losing the weight, Harper has regained the confidence to return to school, where she most enjoys spending time with her friends. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Keown said: 'She's braver now, like she'll stand up for herself now, whereas in kindergarten, she wouldn't stand up for herself. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'She's not had any problems. She absolutely loves [school].'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;While the girls have lost weight, BBS still affects multiple major organ systems, leaving them with a team of about 10 specialists between the two of them. Luna is in the early stages of chronic kidney disease, while BBS has attacked Harper's liver. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In children, kidney disease can lead to growth issues, cognitive problems, anemia and incontinence. If it progresses, a kidney transplant may be necessary. And children who suffer from liver diseases may experience fatigue, nausea, a swollen abdomen, jaundice and itching.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;About half of children in liver failure will eventually need a transplant.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'We live in and out of doctor's [offices],' Keown said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The girls both have accommodations at school for their condition, including extra time during tests due to dyslexia, which BBS raises the risk of, additional restroom breaks due to kidney issues and rest time from gym class. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The Keown family is now working to spread awareness of BBS and connect with other families across the US. Harper has even helped other children with the condition work up the courage for their daily Imcivree shots. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Keown said: 'It's just one step at a time. I was scared at first, but it's not a death sentence, so when [other] moms reach out, I try to express that to them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'I've heard stories of remission, so I really just want the girls to go into that. I want them to be able to to be able to manage all of this on on their own. I want them to be able just to handle this, be healthy, not have to have to have many doctors, just regular checkups every now and then in the future.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Daily Mail</author><pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 16:07:10 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiwwFBVV95cUxPc3BROTJ3UjRJbGpIWWptRHV0c0JBN1NRZWRkdGdsN1JYMXdEbjQxREtia1FIVFVnWlBXUFoybER3Q28yNHNjR0g4MnJnRFJ5VGZ4ZXFEVW9DM2NYUzhkQ0tpSW51YUFXcmVaY09YRndVZXRiZUEtekoxMnljMzJhd3dCeElNdll5T3VsM3Awa3luSHcyVFdJckMwLWVOQ3BsYkIycW5pQWFHcTdPVnVTVmpYSGlZY09ReE1EUlZQMXZuZUnSAcgBQVVfeXFMUG9mXzZTWmljV3Z3aFdocVJ0aXdGOWEyMlNEZXMtNTUxbk05RVJyQWFmVy0wSXpRTC14TDVPalMwNjJzWmN0dXgzVEtVV3VtR3RkQ28wQzNOSUpSeDJid2JsTFJKWnF2UldUVTdVZzdjVHVDVUpaazJycGs1QXRrQzllTlh4aVU0cXNHRWJsMEVxVDRIMkJPSUJxTnh4VkR1Um5RTXp1VUdBckFjcW1HcFYzaW9CSWZTQWRLaW14ZlQ5YTUySEFYaWg</guid></item><item><title>得知女儿体重增加的原因，我感到震惊-每日邮报</title><link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-15221787/daughters-bullied-weight-rare-genetic-disorder-bardet-biedl-syndrome.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div itemprop="articleBody"&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;A mother-of-two has revealed how her daughter's mysterious weight gain was a sign of a rare genetic disorder. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;As Ciara Keown's four-year-old daughter, Harper, entered pre-K, she began suffering meltdowns over fitting into her clothes and shoes. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Despite being 'very lean' as a toddler, Harper had packed on 30 pounds within just a few months due to an insatiable appetite. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Keown and her husband had &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/health/article-14735335/man-weight-loss-transformation-without-ozempic.html"&gt;struggled with their own weight&lt;/a&gt; since they were kids, and the parents assumed Harper was following in their footsteps.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'We just thought it was our bad habits rubbing off on her,' Keown told the Daily Mail.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The family visited an obesity clinic near their home in Chattanooga, &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/tennessee/index.html" id="mol-94e667a0-b052-11f0-a33a-a5006d5ef6f4" class=""&gt;Tennessee&lt;/a&gt;, which counseled them on dietary swaps and other lifestyle changes, but Harper's weight continued to climb.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;By the time she was seven, she weighed over 100 pounds, twice as much as a typical second grader. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Children would push her down on the playground and call her 'fat,' forcing the family to pull her out of school. 'She shut down during that time,' Keown said. 'No kid should have to go through that.' &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Harper (left) and Luna Keown were both diagnosed with the rare genetic disorder Bardet-Biedl syndrome (BBS), which leads to an insatiable appetite and uncontrolled weight gain&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    
    
    &lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Unable to explain the weight gain despite diet and exercise, the clinic suggested Harper undergo genetic testing last year, which revealed she had Bardet-Biedl syndrome (BBS), a rare condition affecting just under 5,000 Americans that causes weight gain and constant, insatiable hunger. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The condition usually manifests early in childhood and progresses over time and affects nearly every major organ, eventually leading to vision loss, kidney failure and developmental delays. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Further testing showed Harper's younger sister, Luna, also had BBS, though she hadn't yet displayed symptoms, and both of their parents were carriers for the mutated genes that cause the condition.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Keown said: '[The doctor] was just mind-blown. She was like, "I've never heard of this before."'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;BBS is caused by mutations in one of at least 24 different genes, most commonly BBS1 and BBS10, which provide instructions for the formation of cilia, hairlike structures on cells that help them relay sensory information like light, sound, smell and taste.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;These mutations cause a dysfunction of the brain's melanocortin-4 receptor (MC4R) pathway, which controls hunger and satiety. If the receptor is mutated, it cannot communicate to the brain that the body is full, leading to uncontrolled eating. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Like Harper, most patients start gaining excess weight around three to five years old, which continues into adulthood, often despite dietary changes and exercise. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Luna also started to gain weight around age four, jumping from 30 to 80 pounds within a few months, more than double the weight of the average preschooler.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;After their diagnosis, the girls were put on topiramate (known as Topamax), an anticonvulsant used off-label for weight loss, and Vyvanse, a stimulant used to treat ADHD and binge eating disorder, to help slow their ravenous hunger.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;They also take setmelanotide, a daily injection under the brand name Imcivree that targets the dysfunctional MC4R pathway. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'It's a complete gamechanger,' Keown told the Daily Mail.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Harper, pictured here, weighed 108 pounds by the time she was seven years old, and she endured bullying so bad that her family was forced to pull her out of school&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Luna (left) and Harper are pictured earlier this year with their mother Ciara (right) after losing weight with medication and lifestyle changes&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;With the help of the medications, as well as dietary swaps and exercise, Harper has lost 30 pounds so far and Luna has lost 10 in the last year. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Since losing the weight, Harper has regained the confidence to return to school, where she most enjoys spending time with her friends. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Keown said: 'She's braver now, like she'll stand up for herself now, whereas in kindergarten, she wouldn't stand up for herself. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'She's not had any problems. She absolutely loves [school].'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;While the girls have lost weight, BBS still affects multiple major organ systems, leaving them with a team of about 10 specialists between the two of them. Luna is in the early stages of chronic kidney disease, while BBS has attacked Harper's liver. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In children, kidney disease can lead to growth issues, cognitive problems, anemia and incontinence. If it progresses, a kidney transplant may be necessary. And children who suffer from liver diseases may experience fatigue, nausea, a swollen abdomen, jaundice and itching.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;About half of children in liver failure will eventually need a transplant.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'We live in and out of doctor's [offices],' Keown said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The girls both have accommodations at school for their condition, including extra time during tests due to dyslexia, which BBS raises the risk of, additional restroom breaks due to kidney issues and rest time from gym class. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The Keown family is now working to spread awareness of BBS and connect with other families across the US. Harper has even helped other children with the condition work up the courage for their daily Imcivree shots. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Keown said: 'It's just one step at a time. I was scared at first, but it's not a death sentence, so when [other] moms reach out, I try to express that to them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'I've heard stories of remission, so I really just want the girls to go into that. I want them to be able to to be able to manage all of this on on their own. I want them to be able just to handle this, be healthy, not have to have to have many doctors, just regular checkups every now and then in the future.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Daily Mail</author><pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 16:07:10 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiwwFBVV95cUxPc3BROTJ3UjRJbGpIWWptRHV0c0JBN1NRZWRkdGdsN1JYMXdEbjQxREtia1FIVFVnWlBXUFoybER3Q28yNHNjR0g4MnJnRFJ5VGZ4ZXFEVW9DM2NYUzhkQ0tpSW51YUFXcmVaY09YRndVZXRiZUEtekoxMnljMzJhd3dCeElNdll5T3VsM3Awa3luSHcyVFdJckMwLWVOQ3BsYkIycW5pQWFHcTdPVnVTVmpYSGlZY09ReE1EUlZQMXZuZUk</guid></item><item><title>狗在多大程度上减轻了我们的压力？ -《华盛顿邮报》</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/podcasts/post-reports/how-much-do-dogs-reduce-our-stress/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-hEgojh wpds-c-hEgojh-ikjuZWZ-css PodcastCarousel_storyCard__hJIce"&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" alt="Impromptu" src="https://www.washingtonpost.com/wp-apps/imrs.php?src=https%3A%2F%2Fpodcast.posttv.com%2Fseries%2F20250401%2Ft_1743515158922_name_impromptu_main_900x300_copy.jpg&amp;amp;w=400"&gt;&lt;p class="PodcastCarousel_storyDesc__ZCeG0"&gt;Smart when you need it, fun when you want it — with hosts who feel like friends.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 16:04:09 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikgFBVV95cUxPT3lsOHpfWktMalc4UzdSS2RNalpIREF0MHFzaEZqY052T1oySElpZUFIRGJzY0J5UjNESGlQS2c5aXlmOC1JYnNtMTJIc2o2aWFhb3R0Y2pOSjRJY3VDTEE1STZxazhaNVJ4RkJzWURKckVyRkk2LUlnTm9uYkp5UDdiMlp5bjNZT1pucHlLT3JGUQ</guid></item></channel></rss>