<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>GNews Health</title><link>https://news.google.com/</link><description></description><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>Top plastic surgeon reveals types of people who should NEVER get plastic surgery - Daily Mail</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMingFBVV95cUxQVHkydkpVZGlCclRYV2xFV1dNZWFoRDNPOUpQOGpJaXRrb2dlSkxKN2FVLWhlaWtfS3V1N0RzVlJrX0Etekd5dTViV0dnaVE1bU9oRzR6X0d2ZmdUUEhuN0p6YVpTRm5RODNudWc3Q0VoalpnVVZmY3ZFX0tYeDRqZmxIZXpHb2ltcHlzN1hoLTNIdkw5OW5Za3ZMNUs0UdIBowFBVV95cUxPMXNoVDBKems4OExiVGhqaFN5djRBWmxCV1NOQlU4RWtJQXhDeGZvbExxZXU1S3JPc1JxVy1wX2pxbHZaMVM4X2dPNmxoUWNFemdzeWRCUmZzWmh0cG4wVTYwZ2Y5UEpfLVppSklmU1NBMHMtZVRYRFVhdC1yNVZFX2pBWGdnYkZHYXRua2MyZkpLakVoamQyVmpxS0RfM1hvZ3Q4?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div itemprop="articleBody"&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Hundreds of thousands of people a year go under the knife for plastic surgery - whether it's for bigger boobs, a smaller nose or even to look like their favorite celebrity. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;And while most people are fine to &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/health/article-13664679/hair-transplants-veneers-plastic-surgeries-Trump-family-bill.html"&gt;shell out thousands of dollars for the traits they desire&lt;/a&gt;, not everyone is a good candidate for cosmetic procedures. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Typically, doctors advise people who are very young, suffer from health conditions such as heart disease and &lt;a target="_self" href="/health/diabetes/index.html" id="mol-93c0ead0-0666-11f0-97cf-e7043735ec11"&gt;diabetes&lt;/a&gt; or people who have had past surgical complications to avoid an elective operation. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Now, Dr Charles Lee, a board-certified plastic surgeon in Beverly Hills, has revealed why certain people shouldn't get plastic surgery.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span class="mol-style-bold"&gt;Below, DailyMail.com details the people Dr Lee says should avoid cosmetic procedures and why. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mol-para-with-font mol-style-subhead health-ccox"&gt;People with body dysmorphia &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Nearly two percent of Americans have been diagnosed with body dysmorphic disorder as of 2024&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Body dysmorphic disorder is a mental health condition that causes you to excessively and obsessively criticize perceived defects or flaws in your appearance that are usually minor or non-existent. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The person's fixation is far beyond the typical dissatisfaction people may have - like wanting to lose 5lbs - and can cause a person to constantly feel embarrassed, ashamed and anxious to the point they avoid social situations. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="mol-img-group floatRHS"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Dr Charles Lee, a board certified plastic surgeon explained why certain people should not get plastic surgery&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Nearly two percent of Americans have been diagnosed with BDD as of 2024, according to National Alliance of Eating Disorders. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;As a result, people suffering from body dysmorphia may seek out plastic surgery as a solution to fix their imperfections, but in one &lt;a class="" rel="nofollow noreferrer noopener" target="_blank" href="https://www.tiktok.com/@drlee90210/video/7130480675517517098?lang=en"&gt;TikTok video&lt;/a&gt;, Dr Lee advises them not to do so. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The expert explained: 'So someone who looks at a perfectly normal part of their body but they see a big problem, you're not going to get that fixed with surgery that really needs to be taken care of.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Instead of plastic surgery, doctors suggest seeking out mental health professionals who can help evaluate the situation and suggest appropriate treatment such as therapy and medications. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mol-para-with-font mol-style-subhead health-ccox"&gt;Control freaks and perfectionists&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Dr Lee added that people who are extremely particular in life and cannot bear slight asymmetries should not undergo procedures. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Perfectionists and control freaks tend to have a strong drive for flawlessness, which can lead to unrealistic expectations about the outcome of plastic surgery.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But, there is always a risk of complications or flaws when it comes to cosmetic procedures.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In cases of a rhinoplasty (nose job) and eyelid surgery, it is normal to expect a bit of unevenness. However this may cause extreme disappointment among perfectionists - causing them to book more appointments and procedures.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Dr Lee added that people who are extremely particular in life and cannot bear slight asymmetries should not undergo procedures&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    
    
    &lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Dr Lee explained: 'Surgery is not that precise, and if you can't accept a few millimeters off here and there, you should not get plastic surgery, especially the more precise procedures, such as rhinoplasty or eyelid surgery. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'A fraction of a millimeter can be seen, but a surgeon can't necessarily correct all that, plus we have some asymmetries that cannot be corrected as well.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The specialist also noted plastic surgery requires a 'lot of patience and a lot of ability to accept the unknown'.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;He added: 'You're going to be swollen for a while. You're going to heal a certain way. Nobody can predict exactly how the outcome is going to be. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'We have a general idea, but it's in the 95 percent precision rate and that last five  percent is kind of random and you have to be willing to accept that. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'And you may not know for six months, 12 months, sometimes two years, what the final result is.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mol-para-with-font mol-style-subhead health-ccox"&gt;People with delusional expectations  &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Over the last few years, social media has convinced people that plastic surgery can completely 'fix' their problems and make them look perfect. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Dr Lee highlighted that people who have a tendency to bleed easily during surgery should avoid an elective operation&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But Dr Lee says this is unrealistic and people shouldn't expect instant gratification. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;It's important to understand it is impossible for plastic surgery to completely alter facial and bodily structures. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The surgeon revealed: 'I've had a lot of cosmetic surgery myself. I had rhinoplasty, chin implant, whatever. I can't go into surgery expecting to look like Tom Cruise, no matter how much surgery I get.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;He also emphasized it is extremely important for patients to be grounded in reality as plastic surgery ideally cannot reverse signs of aging, improve relationships or alter any negative thought patterns about your body.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mol-para-with-font mol-style-subhead health-ccox"&gt;Easy bleeders&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Lastly, Dr Lee highlighted that people who have a tendency to bleed easily or excessively should opt out of elective surgeries.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;He explained that 'one in 10 people' have a tendency to bleed during surgery and while those with milder conditions, such as vitamin K deficiency, should treat those before seeking treatment, but other 'severe bleeders' need to be careful. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Conditions such as hemophilia - a condition where blood does not clot - and Von Willebrand disease - a genetic bleeding disorder caused by low levels of a clotting protein - may lead to prolonged and difficult-to-control bleeding. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;An accumulation of cigarette smoke in the chest can also cause issues during the healing process&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Frequent cigarette smoking and excessive alcohol consumption can also cause issues.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Alcohol can cause blood to thin and an accumulation of cigarette smoke in the chest can lead to complications during the healing process. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Dr Lee explained: 'The big thing that we worry about related to bleeding during surgery is substance abuse, including cigarettes.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'That's a huge one, because cigarette smoke and other smoke, but cigarette in particular has nicotine and carbon monoxide, tar, things that really clog up the oxygen flow to the healing areas and that can cause necrosis, meaning tissue death, poor scarring and a bad outcome. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'So you really should not smoke for almost any of these elective procedures. Alcohol, there's another one. Red wine causes bleeding.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Other types of alcohol can prolong the swelling phase, and sometimes, if it's swollen for too long of a period, you're not going to get a good result.' &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Daily Mail</author><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 20:12:01 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMingFBVV95cUxQVHkydkpVZGlCclRYV2xFV1dNZWFoRDNPOUpQOGpJaXRrb2dlSkxKN2FVLWhlaWtfS3V1N0RzVlJrX0Etekd5dTViV0dnaVE1bU9oRzR6X0d2ZmdUUEhuN0p6YVpTRm5RODNudWc3Q0VoalpnVVZmY3ZFX0tYeDRqZmxIZXpHb2ltcHlzN1hoLTNIdkw5OW5Za3ZMNUs0UdIBowFBVV95cUxPMXNoVDBKems4OExiVGhqaFN5djRBWmxCV1NOQlU4RWtJQXhDeGZvbExxZXU1S3JPc1JxVy1wX2pxbHZaMVM4X2dPNmxoUWNFemdzeWRCUmZzWmh0cG4wVTYwZ2Y5UEpfLVppSklmU1NBMHMtZVRYRFVhdC1yNVZFX2pBWGdnYkZHYXRua2MyZkpLakVoamQyVmpxS0RfM1hvZ3Q4</guid></item><item><title>A Massive New Study About Seed Oils May Change How You Eat - AOL</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMib0FVX3lxTE8zTm5DQU1uemtMckxhN2JvTmdwRmpROWxhZ3gzUnhsbWl6SnljZ1Zrclk1NkxWRUF0VE1KVHEzMGdxcVpYSFdOVHlzUXFTLVg3OUVlMHlwVFg0Ym1rVndVblFFVzdKUEk3bFBvZ08zbw?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="caas-body"&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure"&gt;&lt;p class="caption-wrapper caption-aligned-with-image"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption-collapse"&gt;&lt;span class="caption"&gt;What the Science Says on Dietary Fat&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="photo-credit"&gt;Lisovskaya&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;i&gt;"Hearst Magazines and Yahoo may earn commission or revenue on some items through these links."&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ONE OF THE&lt;/strong&gt; most divisive nutrition topics right now—and &lt;a href="https://www.menshealth.com/nutrition/a63448441/red-dye-number-three-ban/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:there;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;there&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.menshealth.com/nutrition/a64161967/artificial-dyes-ban-rfk/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:are;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;are&lt;/a&gt; &lt;em&gt;a &lt;a href="https://www.menshealth.com/nutrition/a63603209/is-beef-tallow-actually-good-for-you/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:lot;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;lot&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; of &lt;a href="https://www.menshealth.com/nutrition/a45997622/is-raw-milk-good-for-you/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:them;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;them&lt;/a&gt;—is fat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most of the recent arguments have centered on the supposed dangers of &lt;a href="https://www.menshealth.com/nutrition/a63240441/are-seed-oils-actually-bad-for-you/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:seed oils;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;seed oils&lt;/a&gt;. Now, &lt;a href="https://www.menshealth.com/nutrition/a35103720/saturated-fat-good-or-bad/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:saturated fats;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;saturated fats&lt;/a&gt; like butter and even beef tallow have entered the chat. The two topics are linked: The anti-seed-oils faction has turned to saturated fats as a replacement, based on the belief that these fats are more “natural.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Which brings us to a new study &lt;a href="https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jamainternalmedicine/article-abstract/2831265" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:in JAMA Internal Medicine;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;in &lt;em&gt;JAMA Internal Medicine&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, which looked at the association between varying consumption levels of either butter or plant-based oils (aka seed oils), and mortality levels, &lt;a href="https://www.menshealth.com/health/a63096101/signs-of-heart-disease-in-men/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:heart disease;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;heart disease&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href="https://www.menshealth.com/health/a43774213/good-news-about-cancer/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:cancer;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;cancer&lt;/a&gt; incidence over the long term.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Using data from the &lt;a href="https://nurseshealthstudy.org/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Nurse’s Health Study;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Nurse’s Health Study&lt;/a&gt;, a large-scale study started in 1976, researchers analyzed the dietary habits of more than 220,000 adults. They collected the data through participants’ food frequency recalls to determine the amount of butter and/or plant-based oils in the participants’ diets over the course of roughly 30 years. (Researchers included safflower, soybean, corn, canola, and olive oils in the “plant-based” oils group.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The results were consistent with what previous research has already shown: People who ate the most butter had a 12% higher risk of developing cancer, and a 15% higher risk for all-cause mortality.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Conversely, the subjects who ate the most plant-based oils had a 16% lower risk for all-cause mortality, a 6% lower risk of death from heart disease, and 11% lower risk for cancer, which compounded the more plant-based oils were consumed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Researchers also found that substituting just 10 grams of butter a day—which is less than a tablespoon—for plant-based oil, &lt;a href="https://www.massgeneralbrigham.org/en/about/newsroom/press-releases/dietary-habits-study-suggests-more-plant-oils-less-butter-lead-to-better-health" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:led to a 17% reduction in cancer deaths and all-cause mortality;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;led to a 17% reduction in cancer deaths and all-cause mortality&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These conclusions seem aligned with what other studies have found.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However—and this is a big HOWEVER—there are some caveats.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;First, it’s virtually impossible to draw a definitive link between specific diets—&lt;em&gt;especially&lt;/em&gt; in a population—and health outcomes over time. Scientists just can’t keep people in a controlled lab environment for years of their lives. For long-term research like this, we have to rely on self-reported food intake, and at least some of that data may be inaccurate: People can forget, omit, or even lie about what they’ve been eating.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Second, other factors may muddle the link. People who eat more butter, for instance, may also do more of &lt;em&gt;other&lt;/em&gt; things that increase their risk for disease. They may eat a more processed diet, be more sedentary, or be more likely &lt;a href="https://www.menshealth.com/health/a35213467/quitting-cigarettes-how-i-did-it/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:to smoke;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;to smoke&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Third, people's diets tend to change over time. (While researchers had participants fill out food frequency forms every four years, is this enough data to show the true nature of each person’s intake? Maybe or maybe not.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Good Food, Bad Diet&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class="link rapid-noclick-resp rapid-with-clickid etailiffa-link athena-button" href="https://www.amazon.com/dp/1982137509?tag=syn-yahoo-20&amp;amp;ascsubtag=%5Bartid%7C2141.a.64255411%5Bsrc%7Cyahoo-us" data-i13n="elm:affiliate_link;elmt:premonetized" rel="sponsored" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:$12.05 at amazon.com;elm:affiliate_link;elmt:premonetized;itc:0;sec:content-canvas"&gt;$12.05 at amazon.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fourth, all of the participants in the study were nurses. Do they represent the general population? Also maybe or maybe not.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Despite the potential flaws in nutrition research as a whole, dietitians like myself look for reproducible effects and patterns. If we keep getting the same results over a series of similar studies, it’s likely that there is a true effect happening. In this case, it’s highly likely that a diet high in saturated fats is associated with a greater risk for disease and death.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This doesn’t mean we all need to avoid saturated fat; it simply means that a diet containing a mix of fats is probably the best for health (with the exception of trans fats, which are definitely harmful).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This means favoring unsaturated fats (including seed oils like canola and soybean) &lt;em&gt;and&lt;/em&gt; adding in some saturated fats like butter.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Balance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It might not be the next hot food trend, but it’s the most effective and sustainable.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You Might Also Like&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>AOL</author><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 15:35:10 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMib0FVX3lxTE8zTm5DQU1uemtMckxhN2JvTmdwRmpROWxhZ3gzUnhsbWl6SnljZ1Zrclk1NkxWRUF0VE1KVHEzMGdxcVpYSFdOVHlzUXFTLVg3OUVlMHlwVFg0Ym1rVndVblFFVzdKUEk3bFBvZ08zbw</guid></item><item><title>Oregon Man Sues Pet Food Company for Allegedly Killing His Cats With Bird Flu - Gizmodo</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMirAFBVV95cUxQQjlkR0wzVjk4cVJWblJTNlhfUmgwRFlOYUUycTh1bzFlZHltZndzbi1XeVd4YUJyZkVrenNWaGU0eXJYVzFmUHhMUFREd1hJM01RUFpjMDFjOXBvYXFVMDczYTlqOXg1OHlkTHZPX25iLXhSX21KaGVsdUVtV3BORXFSd3Q2ek5NbjFSaXEwMFdzQU1pYWlucUQwNkNEd0Qtd000Wkt0R251ZEVY?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content prose dark:prose-invert lg:prose-lg lg:leading-[29px] font-serif max-w-none"&gt;
              
              
              &lt;p&gt;A man in Oregon filed a lawsuit against Wild Coast Pet Food this week after his cat died from bird flu. The suit alleges the company misled consumers when it sold raw chicken cat food as healthy, failing to acknowledge potential risks, such as potential death from the consumption of H5N1-infected food.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The lawsuit, filed by Tim Hanson, seeks just under $8,000 in damages which covers compensation for veterinarian bills and legal fees, according to &lt;a href="https://www.ktvb.com/article/news/regional/portland-man-sues-wild-coast-pet-food-cat-dies-bird-flu/283-983181c4-2d7f-4549-8239-6e72d29d4386"&gt;KTVB 7&lt;/a&gt; in Oregon. Hanson adopted his cat Kira in 2021 and told the news outlet he typically feeds his cats raw food like the chicken that killed his cat because “I believe in the health benefits of it.” It’s not entirely clear what health benefits Hanson believes can come from raw chicken.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Hanson told KTVB 7 he bought the Wild Coast Pet Foods brand cat food in January but one day in early February Kira stopped eating. Hanson told the news outlet he brought her to the vet on Feb. 5 and a few days later tests confirmed Kira had bird flu.  Kira was so sick she had to be euthanized on Feb. 9.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Wild Coast, which is based in Washington, issued a recall on March 1 for its 16 oz and 24 oz frozen Boneless Free Range Chicken Formula raw pet food for cats. The food was sold in Washington and Oregon.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The warning from the recall, which was posted on the FDA’s website:&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;People who fed pets the recalled products should watch for symptoms of bird flu in their pets, including fever, lethargy, low appetite, reddened or inflamed eyes, discharge from the eyes and nose, difficulty breathing, and neurological signs like tremors, stiff body movements, seizure, lack of coordination, or blindness. People with pets exhibiting these signs after feeding this product should contact their veterinarian.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt; &lt;p&gt;The spread of bird flu has been devastating for many cat owners, as they seem to be the most susceptible among domestic animals outside birds to H5N1. Many cats from New York to Oregon have been documented to have died from the disease and there are likely many more deaths that are going undetected.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;No humans in the U.S. have contracted bird flu from eating food, at least as far as health authorities can tell. But it does appear that cats are getting it from the consumption of raw food. U.S. health agencies have tested both milk and beef and it appears both are safe for human consumption even with the presence of bird flu as long as the milk is pasteurized and the beef is cooked to at least medium.&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;p&gt;There’s also no evidence of human-to-human spread of the bird flu in the U.S. but there is concern a mutation could allow that to happen. There have been 70 cases of H5N1 documented in Americans with one death. Forty-one of those cases have been tied to dairy cattle, 24 have been traced to poultry farms, two cases are from backyard flocks and wild birds, and three cases are still unknown sources.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Wild Coast didn’t respond to questions emailed Friday. Gizmodo will update this post if we hear back.&lt;/p&gt;
                          &lt;/div&gt;

            &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Gizmodo</author><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 14:43:28 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMirAFBVV95cUxQQjlkR0wzVjk4cVJWblJTNlhfUmgwRFlOYUUycTh1bzFlZHltZndzbi1XeVd4YUJyZkVrenNWaGU0eXJYVzFmUHhMUFREd1hJM01RUFpjMDFjOXBvYXFVMDczYTlqOXg1OHlkTHZPX25iLXhSX21KaGVsdUVtV3BORXFSd3Q2ek5NbjFSaXEwMFdzQU1pYWlucUQwNkNEd0Qtd000Wkt0R251ZEVY</guid></item><item><title>Parkinson's Gut Bacteria Link Suggests an Unexpected, Simple Treatment - ScienceAlert</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMingFBVV95cUxNb0J5Zms2anJFakFMLXFITllyc3BxUk8xT3VyZk5YZFJ1ZWExTnlqVmxhSDdfdU9jNnpjS1RtbnZncmxJQnI0VFc5LTI0MFJoTTJnSzQxdGd3d1JLVnE0S3BRXzJhMFNHd01fYTVXVEFTMzF1YTVTT1JLQnJNcFN1LTE5TUg5ZnNwMnpBRUdtSFZGTDdpdnA4Q1VtbnQ3UQ?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Researchers have suspected for&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/new-evidence-suggests-parkinson-s-might-start-in-the-gut-before-spreading-to-the-brain"&gt; some time&lt;/a&gt; that the link between our gut and brain plays a role in the development of  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/go/IYl" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73029" data-postid="155632" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;Parkinson's&lt;/a&gt; disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A recent study identified gut microbes likely to be involved and linked them with decreased &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Riboflavin"&gt;riboflavin&lt;/a&gt; ( &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/what-are-vitamins-and-do-we-really-need-to-take-them" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73116" data-postid="155632" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;vitamin&lt;/a&gt; B2) and &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Biotin"&gt;biotin&lt;/a&gt; (vitamin B7), pointing the way to an unexpectedly &lt;a href="https://youtu.be/9wuwZbPf0Vs"&gt;simple treatment that may help&lt;/a&gt;: B  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/what-are-vitamins-and-do-we-really-need-to-take-them" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73116" data-postid="155632" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;vitamins&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Supplementation of riboflavin and/or biotin is likely to be beneficial in a subset of Parkinson's disease patients, in which gut dysbiosis plays pivotal roles," Nagoya University medical researcher Hiroshi Nishiwaki and colleagues &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1038/s41531-024-00724-z"&gt;wrote&lt;/a&gt; in their paper published in May 2024.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="aspect-w-16 aspect-h-9 youtube-iframe relative"&gt;&lt;iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/9wuwZbPf0Vs?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen&gt;VIDEO&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The neurodegenerative disease impacts &lt;a href="https://www.who.int/news-room/fact-sheets/detail/parkinson-disease"&gt;almost 10 million people globally&lt;/a&gt;, who at best can hope for &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/this-is-the-first-time-drug-shows-signs-of-slowing-parkinsons-disease"&gt;therapies that slow and alleviate symptoms&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Symptoms typically begin with constipation and sleep problems, up to 20 years before progressing into dementia and the debilitating loss of muscle control.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/changes-in-gut-bacteria-are-present-long-before-signs-of-parkinsons-appear"&gt;Previous research&lt;/a&gt; found people with Parkinson's disease also experience changes in their microbiome long before other signs appear.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_131231" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-131231" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/06/SHakingHandPIckingUpGlass-1.jpg" alt="Hands picking up a glass" class="size-full wp-image-131231" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/06/SHakingHandPIckingUpGlass-1.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/06/SHakingHandPIckingUpGlass-1-533x415.jpg 533w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/06/SHakingHandPIckingUpGlass-1-600x467.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-131231" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Parkinson's disease impacts almost 10 million people globally. (&lt;a href="https://www.canva.com/photos/MAEGCRiWJIk/"&gt;pixelshot/Canva Pro&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Analyzing fecal samples from 94 patients with Parkinson's disease and 73 relatively healthy controls in Japan, Nishiwaki and team compared their results with data from China, Taiwan, Germany, and the US.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While different groups of bacteria were involved in the different countries examined, they all influenced pathways that synthesize B vitamins in the body.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The researchers found the changes in gut bacteria communities were associated with a decrease in &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Riboflavin"&gt;riboflavin&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Biotin"&gt;biotin&lt;/a&gt; in people with Parkinson's disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_145467" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-145467" class="wp-caption aligncenter"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/12/ParkinsonsGutBVitamins642.jpg" alt="Graphic of human gut-brain connection and B vitamins" class="size-full wp-image-145467" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/12/ParkinsonsGutBVitamins642.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/12/ParkinsonsGutBVitamins642-603x415.jpg 603w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/12/ParkinsonsGutBVitamins642-600x413.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-145467" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;In Parkinson's disease, a reduction in the gut bacteria of genes responsible for synthesizing the essential B vitamins B2 and B7 was found. (&lt;a href="https://www.nagoya-u.ac.jp/researchinfo/result-en/2024/06/20240618-01.html"&gt;Reiko Matsushita&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nishiwaki and colleagues then showed the lack of B vitamins was linked to a decrease in &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Short-chain_fatty_acid"&gt;short-chain fatty acids&lt;/a&gt; (SCFAs) and &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Polyamine"&gt;polyamines&lt;/a&gt;: molecules that help create a healthy mucus layer in the intestines.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Deficiencies in polyamines and SCFAs could lead to thinning of the intestinal mucus layer, increasing intestinal permeability, both of which have been observed in Parkinson's disease," Nishiwaki &lt;a href="https://www.nagoya-u.ac.jp/researchinfo/result-en/2024/06/20240618-01.html"&gt;explains&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_131227" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-131227" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/06/GraphicOfParkinsonsVitaminBConnection642.jpg" alt="A graphic depicting the process of gut bacteria depleting B vitamins and leading to symptoms of Parkinson's disease" class="wp-image-131227 size-full" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/06/GraphicOfParkinsonsVitaminBConnection642.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/06/GraphicOfParkinsonsVitaminBConnection642-280x415.jpg 280w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/06/GraphicOfParkinsonsVitaminBConnection642-600x888.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-131227" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Summary of findings from the study and speculations from previous research. (Nishiwaki et al., &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1038/s41531-024-00724-z"&gt;&lt;em&gt;npj Parkinson's Disease&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, 2024)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;They suspect the weakened protective layer exposes the intestinal nervous system to more of the toxins we now encounter more regularly. These include &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/dry-cleaning-chemical-could-be-major-cause-of-parkinsons-scientists-warn"&gt;cleaning chemicals,&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/two-pathways-to-parkinsons-could-point-to-a-single-way-to-prevent-it"&gt;pesticides&lt;/a&gt;, and herbicides.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Such toxins lead to the overproduction of α-synuclein fibrils – molecules &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.nbd.2024.106411"&gt;known to amass&lt;/a&gt; in &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/new-test-detects-parkinsons-7-years-before-most-symptoms-show"&gt;dopamine-producing cells&lt;/a&gt; in the &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/scientists-pinpoint-exactly-which-brain-cells-die-in-parkinson-s-disease"&gt;substantia nigra&lt;/a&gt; part of our brains, and increased nervous system inflammation, eventually leading to the more debilitating motor and dementia symptoms of Parkinson's.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A &lt;a href="https://www.scielo.br/j/bjmbr/a/BM4WLJBtjxF8Cx3wFsjFhKb/?lang=en"&gt;2003 study&lt;/a&gt; found high doses of riboflavin can assist in recovering some motor functions in patients who also eliminated red meat from their diets.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So it's possible that high doses of vitamin B may prevent some of the damage, Nishiwaki and team propose.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_131228" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-131228" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/06/VitaminBInBlood642.jpg" alt="Illustration of a vitamin B2 molecule in the blood. " class="size-medium wp-image-131228" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/06/VitaminBInBlood642.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/06/VitaminBInBlood642-628x415.jpg 628w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/06/VitaminBInBlood642-600x396.jpg 600w" sizes="auto, (max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-131228" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Illustration of a riboflavin (B2) molecule in the blood. (Nemes Laszlo/Science Photo Library/Getty Images)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;This all suggests ensuring patients have healthy gut microbiomes may also prove protective, as would &lt;a href="https://www.hopkinsmedicine.org/health/conditions-and-diseases/parkinsons-disease/can-environmental-toxins-cause-parkinson-disease"&gt;reducing the toxic pollutants&lt;/a&gt; in our environment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Of course, with such a complicated chain of events involved in Parkinson's disease, not all patients likely experience the same causes, so each individual would need to be assessed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"We could perform gut microbiota analysis on patients or conduct fecal metabolite analysis," &lt;a href="https://www.nagoya-u.ac.jp/researchinfo/result-en/2024/06/20240618-01.html"&gt;explains&lt;/a&gt; Nishiwak.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Using these findings, we could identify individuals with specific deficiencies and administer oral riboflavin and biotin supplements to those with decreased levels, potentially creating an effective treatment."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This research was published in &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1038/s41531-024-00724-z"&gt;&lt;em&gt;npj Parkinson's Disease&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;An earlier version of this article was published in June 2024.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 13:02:24 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMingFBVV95cUxNb0J5Zms2anJFakFMLXFITllyc3BxUk8xT3VyZk5YZFJ1ZWExTnlqVmxhSDdfdU9jNnpjS1RtbnZncmxJQnI0VFc5LTI0MFJoTTJnSzQxdGd3d1JLVnE0S3BRXzJhMFNHd01fYTVXVEFTMzF1YTVTT1JLQnJNcFN1LTE5TUg5ZnNwMnpBRUdtSFZGTDdpdnA4Q1VtbnQ3UQ</guid></item><item><title>Flu activity still high as COVID-19 causes nearly 40 deaths a week - Dayton Daily News</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMizAFBVV95cUxNM2l0T3JmS2dva19tYzlRcHNmYks0emJzWHg5TzMtMy16Slh3UkpPLW9nb3drbEhwM1AwZlNROURUMEgtUGc3UG1zMllTQnRJOUM1Y0F5b0Q4WHRkcHoydVJwYnc0OEVGRVVRYzBtTzVSY29aNjVWM0R6dzdXMFVSUk5WU3JGTGwyQ1F6WUs2dldOMWdlanJscVdsVzM5bnljcnFQU3FPLThjVWtSMFZFcVR5SkJtVUtiX2t2UG50QkJmMVM5MW9iVFFzRDI?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="c-contentElements" data-start-index="0"&gt;&lt;p class="story-text " data-index="1"&gt;In late January, Ohio was seeing about 5,500 flu cases a week, Vanderhoff said, but now the state is down to fewer than 3,000 cases.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="story-text " data-index="2"&gt;There were 1,024 flu-related hospitalizations reported in the most recent week of data in Ohio, which is about a 25.7% decline over the previous week, according to ODH. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="story-text " data-index="4"&gt;Over the past two weeks, the state has sharp declines in hospitalizations, Vanderhoff said. Hospitalizations, outpatient visits and trips to the emergency for flu-like illnesses still remain above the five-year average, but they continue to decline. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="story-text " data-index="5"&gt;The flu season will continue until the middle of May, so experts say people should still take precautions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="story-subscription__placeholder subscription-promo b-margin-bottom-d40-m20"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="story-text " data-index="7"&gt;“Typically the flu season runs from October to May, so we’re still in the midst of the traditional season,” Dan Suffoletto, public information manager for Public Health - Dayton &amp;amp; Montgomery County, said earlier this month.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="story-nativo_placeholder--moap b-clear-both is-deferred"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="story-text " data-index="9"&gt;“It’s still very important if people are having signs and symptoms of the flu to stay home if they’re sick to help reduce the spread,” Suffoletto said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="story-text " data-index="10"&gt;Flu-like symptoms also accounted for 5.37% of outpatient visits last week, according to ODH, which was down by 19%. Emergency department visits for flu-like illnesses were just under 2% of all hospital visits, while emergency department visits for general, none specific symptoms that could be flu or cold-like illnesses were at 12.9% of visits.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="story-text " data-index="11"&gt;Locally, Montgomery County has had 1,033 flu-related hospitalizations this season, which is about 6.6% of all of Ohio’s flu hospitalizations, according to ODH.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="story-text " data-index="12"&gt;Butler County has had 375 flu-related hospitalizations and Clark County has had 287; both are totals for this flu season.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="story-text " data-index="13"&gt;Influenza A continues to be the most prevalent of the flu cases nationally, which is often considered to be worse than influenza B as the symptoms are more severe, according to the &lt;a href="https://health.clevelandclinic.org/flu-a-vs-flu-b" target="_blank"&gt;Cleveland Clinic&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="is-deferred MP03 arc_ad b-margin-bottom-d30-m20 "&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="is-deferred RP09 arc_ad b-margin-bottom-d30-m20 "&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="story-text " data-index="17"&gt;COVID-19 is also still a threat that needs to be taken seriously, Vanderhoff said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="story-text " data-index="18"&gt;“It continues to claim too many lives,” Vanderhoff said. “Over the past three weeks, we have averaged about 40 deaths in Ohio per week.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="story-text " data-index="19"&gt;There were 24 COVID-related deaths reported in the most recent week of data, which is down from 34 deaths the week before and 44 before then, according to ODH.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="story-text " data-index="20"&gt;The three-week average for COVID-related hospitalizations is 135 hospitalizations statewide.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="story-text " data-index="21"&gt;Nationwide, 0.9% of the deaths in the U.S. are related to COVID-19, according to the Centers for Disease Control, which also says the rate of COVID-related hospitalizations is 2.1 hospitalizations per 100,000 people.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="story-text " data-index="23"&gt;If people have not yet received the updated COVID-19 shot, Vanderhoff said they should consider getting the updated vaccine, especially those who are 65 or older.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="story-text " data-index="24"&gt;“It offers the best chance for protection,” Vanderhoff said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="story-text " data-index="25"&gt;Respiratory syncytial virus, or RSV, is another common respiratory virus active this season that infects the nose, throat and lungs. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="story-text " data-index="26"&gt;“RSV was another concern earlier in the winter, but thankfully, we have seen a sharp decline in cases and hospitalizations in recent weeks,” Vanderhoff said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="story-text " data-index="27"&gt;COVID-19 and flu shots are available at most doctor’s offices and pharmacies. For more information or to find a location, visit &lt;a href="https://www.vaccines.gov/en/" target="_blank"&gt;vaccines.gov&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="is-deferred HP03 arc_ad b-margin-bottom-d30-m20 "&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="story-text " data-index="31"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Dayton Daily News</author><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 12:17:48 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMizAFBVV95cUxNM2l0T3JmS2dva19tYzlRcHNmYks0emJzWHg5TzMtMy16Slh3UkpPLW9nb3drbEhwM1AwZlNROURUMEgtUGc3UG1zMllTQnRJOUM1Y0F5b0Q4WHRkcHoydVJwYnc0OEVGRVVRYzBtTzVSY29aNjVWM0R6dzdXMFVSUk5WU3JGTGwyQ1F6WUs2dldOMWdlanJscVdsVzM5bnljcnFQU3FPLThjVWtSMFZFcVR5SkJtVUtiX2t2UG50QkJmMVM5MW9iVFFzRDI</guid></item><item><title>Kennedy praises cell phone bans in schools, for science-backed and tenuous reasons - NBC News</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMijgFBVV95cUxQSElwekJlQW93eFBoZDNFNW11c01wZVJkS3VHZVVFeEl1d29jQ25iYWFmTlZnWTZkUEItRmRnazlucUljdTBWclRfZTBHMzFneTNhX2YtN1JLNnBQSDdJMWRqbXN6bWllWlpIZ3NKLS00T3ZERFAtT0lqSXJyMkdNVGFOa21EcjB5cEF2Y1B30gFWQVVfeXFMUGpjLXhJVkFyZWVJckcxWVp1VkY2WGp3OVRVWXhYQVRnSmdSN2tSNWNfV1ZlaWNuYWRPWkpFU3EzUFdwcTRDNG9VVnV6NE1zVHRTaEJQM3c?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body__content"&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;Health and Human Services secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr. took aim at a new target this week as part of his “Make America Healthy Again” agenda: cell phones in schools.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;In &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/video/6370269070112" target="_blank"&gt;an interview with “Fox &amp;amp; Friends”&lt;/a&gt; on Thursday, Kennedy praised &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/politics-news/state-lawmakers-bills-ban-cellphones-schools-rcna187309" target="_blank"&gt;cell phone restrictions in schools&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/rfk-jr-health-stances-vaccines-fluoride-raw-milk-rcna180244" target="_blank"&gt;listed health hazards&lt;/a&gt; that he said were linked to phone use among children and teens  — some backed by scientific research, others less so.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="taboolaReadMoreBelow"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;Kennedy cited established links between social media use and depression and poor school performance. But he also suggested that cell phones “produce electromagnetic radiation, which has been shown to do neurological damage to kids when it’s around them all day, and to cause cellular damage and even cancer.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;Studies have found that excessive use of social media via smartphones can &lt;a href="https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jamapsychiatry/fullarticle/2749480" target="_blank"&gt;negatively impact teens’ mental health&lt;/a&gt;, elevating their risk of depression and anxiety. Scientists have also long understood that cell phone use in school &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC11894741/" target="_blank"&gt;can lead to poor academic performance&lt;/a&gt;, including &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S0747563213003993" target="_blank"&gt;lower grades&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;However, the bulk of research so far has found no association between cell phone use and cancer, nor evidence that cell phones damage DNA. Cell phones emit radio frequency radiation, which has far less energy than ionizing radiation, such as that released by medical X-rays.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;Kennedy’s statements follow a pattern of his, in which he mixes misinformation with scientific fact. Some of the issues he has highlighted &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/kennedy-first-month-health-secretary-vaccines-food-additives-rcna196042" target="_blank"&gt;during his first five-plus weeks in office&lt;/a&gt;, such as reducing chronic disease in children and warning of the dangers of ultraprocessed food, have broad support among the public and many scientists. But certain factors Kennedy blames for those problems and some of his proposed solutions — such as substituting &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/influencers-claim-beef-tallow-health-beauty-benefits-not-necessarily-e-rcna195206" target="_blank"&gt;beef tallow&lt;/a&gt; for seed oils in fast food — are not backed by research.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;So, too, for cell phones in schools. Restricting their use is an issue leaders have embraced on both sides of the aisle. Vivek Murthy, while he was surgeon general under the Biden Administration last year, &lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2024/06/17/opinion/social-media-health-warning.html" target="_blank"&gt;called on schools to get rid of phones in the classroom&lt;/a&gt;. Nine states have already enacted such &lt;a href="https://www.kff.org/mental-health/issue-brief/a-look-at-state-efforts-to-ban-cellphones-in-schools-and-implications-for-youth-mental-health/" target="_blank"&gt;bans or restrictions&lt;/a&gt;, and 15 states and Washington, D.C. have introduced legislation to do so, according to KFF, a nonprofit health think tank.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;“Both in red states and blue states, there’s a lot of concern about kids and cell phones, so I do think that there is bipartisan support on this,” said Annette Campbell Anderson, deputy director of the Johns Hopkins Center for Safe and Healthy Schools.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;However, there’s no reason to fear a cancer risk from using your cell phone at this time, said Jerrold Bushberg, a clinical professor of radiation oncology at the University of California, Davis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;“There’s a lot of low-quality research in the literature that, if you wanted to collect all that and put it together, it would look very damning,” he said. “There are many activist groups out there that promote those studies and say that that’s the truth.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;An HHS spokesperson did not respond to a request for comment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="body-heading"&gt;What Kennedy says, and what studies say&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;Kennedy has made repeated, unsubstantiated claims about the physical harms of cell phone use in the past, including &lt;a href="https://open.spotify.com/episode/3DQfcTY4viyXsIXQ89NXvg" target="_blank"&gt;on Joe Rogan’s podcast&lt;/a&gt; last year. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;At his confirmation hearing in January, Kennedy also told Sen. Andy Kim, D-N.J., that he stood by his past statements that WiFi radiation causes cancer, saying that he had “won a case in front of the Court of Appeals against the FCC on that very issue.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;The anti-vaccine group that Kennedy founded, Children’s Health Defense, challenged the Federal Communications Commission’s decision not to review its 1996 health and safety guidelines for wireless-based technologies. An appeals court &lt;a href="https://www.fcc.gov/ecfs/search/search-filings/filing/1041748778173" target="_blank"&gt;ruled in favor of the plaintiffs&lt;/a&gt; and ordered the FCC to explain how its guidelines protect against potentially harmful health effects. However, that case was about health issues unrelated to cancer, and the court did not take a position on the potential health effects of cell phone radiation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;Research thus far has been “very reassuring” about cell phone safety, Bushberg said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;Most studies have examined whether exposure to radiation from cell phones could increase the risk of brain tumors, given that people often hold their phone by their head while talking. But overall brain cancer rates haven’t risen as cell phones have become more widely used. And &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/34974237/" target="_blank"&gt;a large study&lt;/a&gt; among children found no association between wireless phone use and brain tumors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="recommended-intersection-ref" data-activity-map="recommended-article-body-recommended" data-testid="recommended-wrapper"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="recommended-intersection-ref" data-activity-map="recommended-article-body-recommended" data-testid="recommended-wrapper"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;The &lt;a href="https://www.cancer.gov/about-cancer/causes-prevention/risk/radiation/cell-phones-fact-sheet" target="_blank"&gt;National Cancer Institute&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.fda.gov/radiation-emitting-products/cell-phones/do-cell-phones-pose-health-hazard" target="_blank"&gt;Food and Drug Administration&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.epa.gov/radtown/non-ionizing-radiation-wireless-technology" target="_blank"&gt;Environmental Protection Agency&lt;/a&gt; — agencies that Kennedy now oversees — have all said there’s not enough scientific evidence to associate cell phone use with cancer. However, the International Agency for Research on Cancer has classified radio frequency radiation as possibly carcinogenic, meaning it cannot rule out a causal link. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;Several questions remain, said David McCormick, a biology professor at Illinois Institute of Technology.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;“I think it’s fairly clear that Mr. Kennedy doesn’t necessarily pay much attention to the bulk of the scientific data that is out there. That said, it’s not impossible that there are health effects from people using cell phones,” he said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;In a &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/29217849/" target="_blank"&gt;2017 study&lt;/a&gt;, McCormick and his fellow researchers exposed rodents to &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/29217848/" target="_blank"&gt;radio frequency radiation&lt;/a&gt; and found a possible increased rate of certain tumors — however, findings in lab animals don’t necessarily apply to humans, given the many biological differences, and the studies contained limitations that prevented the researchers from drawing conclusions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;A decade earlier, a &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/17636416/" target="_blank"&gt;study looked at cell phone use&lt;/a&gt; among more than 5,000 people with brain tumors and found a possible increased risk of tumors in the 10% who used their phones the most. But the research relied on people’s memories about past phone use, which aren’t always reliable, so its results (like those of similar studies) are hard to interpret.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;Cell phone use has also changed in recent years, McCormick said, which could affect exposure. Whereas studies thus far have mainly looked at the effects of 2G or 3G mobile signals, higher-frequency 5G networks are common today. And people now text as much if not more than they call, so there’s potentially less radiation near the brain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="body-heading"&gt;The pros and cons of cell phone bans&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;Despite bipartisan support for cell phone restrictions in schools, plenty of disagreement persists as to precisely what those rules should look like. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;Phones can have life-saving benefits — for instance, by allowing children to call 911 — so some parents worry that outright bans could jeopardize their child’s safety. Anderson said policymakers have to weigh those concerns against risks to kids’ mental health and their ability to focus in the classroom. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;“Part of what schools are trying to do is figure out how to wrest back control over what happened in their school climates because of the phone — everything from using the phone to tape fights and incidents that happen in schools to kids using them to make TikToks,” she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;The right approach likely differs from school to school, she added — for instance, in schools where cell phones are the only internet-connected device, a ban may make less sense. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;In his interview on Thursday, Kennedy applauded Virginia Gov. Glenn Youngkin, who last year issued an executive order directing the state’s education department to &lt;a href="https://www.governor.virginia.gov/newsroom/news-releases/2024/july/name-1030522-en.html" target="_blank"&gt;draft guidance for public schools to restrict or eliminate phone use&lt;/a&gt; and set aside $500,000 to fund those efforts. Kennedy visited a Virginia high school on Monday that adopted the change, which he said students and teachers there have welcomed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;“The states that are doing this have found that it is a much healthier environment when kids are not using cell phones in schools,” Kennedy said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;However, prior to becoming HHS secretary, Kennedy suggested that although he personally supports getting phones out of schools, parents and teachers should make their own decisions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="endmark body-graf"&gt;“Do we really want the government to decide when, where, and how we communicate?” he &lt;a href="https://x.com/RobertKennedyJr/status/1710023376360632465" target="_blank"&gt;wrote on X&lt;/a&gt; in 2023.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>NBC News</author><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijgFBVV95cUxQSElwekJlQW93eFBoZDNFNW11c01wZVJkS3VHZVVFeEl1d29jQ25iYWFmTlZnWTZkUEItRmRnazlucUljdTBWclRfZTBHMzFneTNhX2YtN1JLNnBQSDdJMWRqbXN6bWllWlpIZ3NKLS00T3ZERFAtT0lqSXJyMkdNVGFOa21EcjB5cEF2Y1B30gFWQVVfeXFMUGpjLXhJVkFyZWVJckcxWVp1VkY2WGp3OVRVWXhYQVRnSmdSN2tSNWNfV1ZlaWNuYWRPWkpFU3EzUFdwcTRDNG9VVnV6NE1zVHRTaEJQM3c</guid></item><item><title>Allergy sufferers expected to have worse season than usual: See pollen maps - USA TODAY</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiowFBVV95cUxNSEIxVkh4SzRuWncxNlBBd3BieGhGUW5jTVJVbmJJUzlubTlOb0IyTjZXelktVDJlVVI4LVB4OHBKaTA3WWNWLTk1eGYzc1FZZm1FQkd6UjJNMk9CY1V6TTVRa240cl9zNzFkanNqbnplNTctNzhjY3RzSzR2MXR2SVduaURVTExzcWR6RlVuNkZuMTdFWnFsbWZfa28tdERXTEgw?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="gnt_ar_b"&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;For trees and flowers, early spring might be wonderful, but for allergy sufferers, it can be awful.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;Springtime has arrived two weeks earlier than usual in several Midwest states this year, according to the &lt;a href="https://www.usanpn.org/data/maps/spring" data-t-l=":b|z|k|${u}" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;USA National Phenology Network&lt;/a&gt; at the University of Arizona. In the mid-Atlantic and northeast regions, it arrived just over a week ahead of schedule. For those in the western U.S., depending on where you live, spring can arrive anywhere from two weeks earlier to a week later in California, Arizona, and Nevada.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;According to the &lt;a href="https://www.climate.gov/news-features/understanding-climate/us-climate-outlook-march-2025#:~:text=On%20February%2028%2C%20CPC%20released,exception%20of%20in%20the%20Northeast." data-t-l=":b|z|k|${u}" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;Climate Prediction Center&lt;/a&gt;, much of the country's southern and eastern regions are expected to experience temperatures far above average, which means an increase in pollen levels due to blossoming trees. That’s bad news for people with seasonal allergies ‒ about &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/nchs/products/databriefs/db460.htm" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" data-t-l=":b|z|k|${u}" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;1 in 4 adults&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/nchs/products/databriefs/db459.htm" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" data-t-l=":b|z|k|${u}" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;1 in 5 children&lt;/a&gt; in the U.S.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="gnt_ar_b_h2"&gt;States where spring sprang earlier than usual&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;The USA National Phenology Network's map below shows the springtime leaf activity earlier than average (in red tones) and later than average (blue tones) this year:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Unable to view our graphics? &lt;a href="/story/graphics/2025/03/22/allergy-season-spring-pollen-symptoms/82568198007/" data-t-l=":b|e|k|${u}" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;Click here to see them.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;According to a recent &lt;a href="https://aafa.org/asthma-allergy-research/allergy-capitals/" data-t-l=":b|z|k|${u}" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;study&lt;/a&gt; by the &lt;a href="https://aafa.org/" data-t-l=":b|z|k|${u}" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;Asthma and Allergy Foundation of America&lt;/a&gt;, eight cities in California saw large increases in their allergy rankings as a result of a "grass and weed pollen explosion," which the foundation says was intensified by heavy rains that year that spurred plant growth. New Orleans also jumped considerably, going from 34th place the previous year to second in 2025.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="gnt_ar_b_h2"&gt;Where are pollen counts at their highest?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;As warm spring temperatures expand throughout the United States, pollen levels are rising. Pollen counts forecasted on March 20, the first official day of spring:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="gnt_ar_b_h2"&gt;Why does pollen cause allergies?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;Plants, trees and grass release pollen in the springtime to fertilize other plants of the same species. The powdery particles drift in the air and are easily inhaled.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;In some people, inhaling pollen causes their immune systems to overreact. The immune system sees the pollen as a danger and releases antibodies that attack the allergens. This leads to the release of histamines into the blood. Histamines trigger runny noses, itchy eyes and other allergy symptoms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="gnt_ar_b_h2"&gt;How pollen affects your body&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;h2 class="gnt_ar_b_h2"&gt;How to help stop the allergy symptoms&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;Reducing your exposure to pollen allergens and identifying seasonal triggers might help ease your symptoms. You can do the following to decrease your reaction:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;&lt;em&gt;This story was updated to add new information.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_s gnt_ar_s0"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_s gnt_ar_s25"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_s gnt_ar_s50"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_s gnt_ar_s75"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_s gnt_ar_s100"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>USA TODAY</author><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 10:53:11 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiowFBVV95cUxNSEIxVkh4SzRuWncxNlBBd3BieGhGUW5jTVJVbmJJUzlubTlOb0IyTjZXelktVDJlVVI4LVB4OHBKaTA3WWNWLTk1eGYzc1FZZm1FQkd6UjJNMk9CY1V6TTVRa240cl9zNzFkanNqbnplNTctNzhjY3RzSzR2MXR2SVduaURVTExzcWR6RlVuNkZuMTdFWnFsbWZfa28tdERXTEgw</guid></item><item><title>The truth about ‘condoms for Gaza’: DOGE canceled $33 million USAID contract treating 350,000 HIV patients - Fortune</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMingFBVV95cUxQeWVGYTJyOVVFOFhkSFNFQWg3T1RZcVhQdlR3bk1leFJrU200UDloWGtOMDVjaDdPZGVHbWFkMzdTVTdhNDlfSmZmYkh2dnc3bWhubXhFREJVd0E5bnhzTWxzQXBnWDNqUThjSU9CZ05OZ0FMUk15QnpYd0FuY001R0pYbloySEV3b0I0TFFjS3lkNGRPV2tucFBqempsdw?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Fortune</author><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMingFBVV95cUxQeWVGYTJyOVVFOFhkSFNFQWg3T1RZcVhQdlR3bk1leFJrU200UDloWGtOMDVjaDdPZGVHbWFkMzdTVTdhNDlfSmZmYkh2dnc3bWhubXhFREJVd0E5bnhzTWxzQXBnWDNqUThjSU9CZ05OZ0FMUk15QnpYd0FuY001R0pYbloySEV3b0I0TFFjS3lkNGRPV2tucFBqempsdw</guid></item><item><title>I’ve been walking with a weight vest for 5K every day — here's what happened to my body - Tom's Guide</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMixAFBVV95cUxONjJCamJTYnVvRTlBRjNPZnVhOVlPQ1pQdl81ZTFxdXhqOXdHazFibllSQml1UGNzWFo4TmU2b2NZYTNOVlZFelZjYzNNWmwteUpXSE5aenNONzBzbDhaeXVHeEpLSWNtQmNTd213ZkxfTUFtRzhpaGNfRl82YmMxOEQ1Z1FiRVpxZlU4RVBfWVJlNzVKaEc1Uk04NG5jczNUZFVZRHlkQ3FMWFAyZHZaSU9MTnF4b1A4c2RXWVR1VWFqR2NG?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="article-body" class="text-copy bodyCopy auto"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Weight vests are a great way to add intensity to workouts. I’d always opt for a weighted vest over some of the &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.tomsguide.com/best-picks/best-ankle-weights" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.tomsguide.com/best-picks/best-ankle-weights"&gt;best ankle weights&lt;/a&gt; while walking, as ankle weights can put unnecessary pressure on the lower-body joints.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="ad-unit-1" class="ad-unit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That said, I never exercise with a weight vest, so I wanted to ease myself in with a 5K walk each day while wearing one to see what, if anything, happened to my body. And with that, I bought a basic &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://target.georiot.com/Proxy.ashx?tsid=45724&amp;amp;GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Famazon.com%2Fs%3Fk%3Dweight%2Bvest%26crid%3D2AOJSWG8OSLA5%26sprefix%3Dweight%2Bvest%2B%252Caps%252C328%26ref%3Dnb_sb_noss_2%26tag%3Dhawk-future-20%26ascsubtag%3Dtomsguide-us-1029602330739201023-20" target="_blank" rel="sponsored noopener" data-url="https://www.amazon.com/s?k=weight+vest&amp;amp;crid=2AOJSWG8OSLA5&amp;amp;sprefix=weight+vest+%2Caps%2C328&amp;amp;ref=nb_sb_noss_2" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="hawklinks" data-placeholder-url="https://target.georiot.com/Proxy.ashx?tsid=45724&amp;amp;GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Famazon.com%2Fs%3Fk%3Dweight%2Bvest%26crid%3D2AOJSWG8OSLA5%26sprefix%3Dweight%2Bvest%2B%252Caps%252C328%26ref%3Dnb_sb_noss_2%26tag%3Dhawk-future-20%26ascsubtag%3Dhawk-custom-tracking-20" data-google-interstitial="false" data-merchant-name="Amazon US" data-merchant-id="1471" data-merchant-network="Amazon" data-merchant-url="amazon.com"&gt;adjustable weight vest from Amazon&lt;/a&gt;, strapped it on and got walking. Here’s what happened.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="article-body__section" id="section-what-is-a-weight-vest"&gt;&lt;span&gt;What is a weight vest?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;figure class="van-image-figure inline-layout" data-bordeaux-image-check&gt;&lt;figcaption itemprop="caption description" class=" inline-layout"&gt;&lt;span class="credit" itemprop="copyrightHolder"&gt;(Image credit: 5.11 Tactical)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;A &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.tomsguide.com/reviews/5-11-tactical-tactec-trainer-weight-vest" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.tomsguide.com/reviews/5-11-tactical-tactec-trainer-weight-vest"&gt;weight vest&lt;/a&gt; is exactly as it sounds — a vest that you can strap around your chest like a jacket and add weight to, increasing the amount of resistance you experience during a workout. During walks or runs, it may make you feel heavier, and during strength exercises, it can make the moves feel even tougher to complete.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There are many different types of weight vests, as my colleague found out when he &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.tomsguide.com/news/i-worked-out-with-a-weight-vest-for-a-week-and-it-kicked-my-ass" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.tomsguide.com/news/i-worked-out-with-a-weight-vest-for-a-week-and-it-kicked-my-ass"&gt;exercised with a weight vest for a week&lt;/a&gt; back in 2021. But the idea is simple: secure weights to your front and back and get to work. From a &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.tomsguide.com/wellness/fitness/i-just-tried-the-chelsea-crossfit-workout-and-it-strengthens-your-entire-body-with-just-3-bodyweight-exercises" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.tomsguide.com/wellness/fitness/i-just-tried-the-chelsea-crossfit-workout-and-it-strengthens-your-entire-body-with-just-3-bodyweight-exercises"&gt;CrossFit WOD&lt;/a&gt; to walking or &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.tomsguide.com/wellness/fitness/calisthenics-coach-says-this-is-the-20-minute-workout-you-need-to-build-full-body-strength-and-boost-fitness" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.tomsguide.com/wellness/fitness/calisthenics-coach-says-this-is-the-20-minute-workout-you-need-to-build-full-body-strength-and-boost-fitness"&gt;calisthenics&lt;/a&gt;, a weight vest can add intensity without breaking the bank on gym kit like dumbbells or kettlebells.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="ad-unit-2" class="ad-unit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="i-walked-5k-every-day-with-a-weight-vest-for-a-week-here-s-what-happened-3"&gt;I walked 5K every day with a weight vest for a week — here's what happened&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Unlike my colleague, I wasn’t planning on performing strength exercises wearing the vest throughout the week, so brushing moves like squats, push-ups, and lunges aside, I added slightly more weight than I would have otherwise; I opted for 16 lbs (roughly 7kg).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="article-body__section" id="section-i-walked-slower-and-my-daily-walk-felt-more-challenging"&gt;&lt;span&gt;I walked slower — and my daily walk felt more challenging &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Although my arms weren’t weighed down I certainly noticed the additional 7kg. For reference, I weigh roughly 57kg (around 125 lbs) and reach 5”2 in height.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Although this isn’t an enormous amount of weight to add to your daily walk, it made me feel a little sluggish, and I certainly got a sweat on, especially when walking uphill. It definitely made my walk feel more challenging on my legs and core muscles, and I had to focus on bracing my stomach to prevent my lower back from taking the strain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I took a few more hills than usual and found myself puffing as I strode along with my dog. It’s a simple way to add gentle conditioning to walks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="article-body__section" id="section-my-balance-felt-off"&gt;&lt;span&gt;My balance felt off &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;As my colleague also reported, my balance felt slightly off from the change in weight distribution. However, the vest is strapped evenly around the torso rather than isolated to the wrists or ankles, so it doesn't put too much pressure on my joints. I also chose to avoid high-intensity or sudden changes in movement (think burpees), so it didn’t pose too much of a problem.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Had I opted for rucking — adding weight to a backpack on your back — I believe this would have put more pressure on my back, particularly the upper trapezius muscles that sit along either side of the neck.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="article-body__section" id="section-my-fitness-tracker-picked-up-on-the-difference"&gt;&lt;span&gt;My fitness tracker picked up on the difference&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’m a brisk walker, and with 7kg strapped to my torso, this brought a morning cardio element to my day. I noticed my calorie count was slightly higher, but I don’t check &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.tomsguide.com/features/i-just-did-a-500-calorie-hiit-workout-heres-how-many-calories-i-really-burned" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.tomsguide.com/features/i-just-did-a-500-calorie-hiit-workout-heres-how-many-calories-i-really-burned"&gt;calorie burn &lt;/a&gt;while I walk, as it can be an unreliable metric to track.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I have a competitive streak, so &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.tomsguide.com/features/i-closed-my-apple-watch-rings-for-an-entire-week-heres-what-i-learned" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.tomsguide.com/features/i-closed-my-apple-watch-rings-for-an-entire-week-heres-what-i-learned"&gt;closing my Apple ring&lt;/a&gt;s serves as a daily motivator for me; I tend to look at my overall movement for the day rather than individual workouts and their associated metrics — unless I’m going for a run and want to check my time and splits.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cumulative energy expenditure, known as &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.tomsguide.com/features/non-exercise-activity-thermogenesis-why-neat-could-help-you-burn-more-calories" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.tomsguide.com/features/non-exercise-activity-thermogenesis-why-neat-could-help-you-burn-more-calories"&gt;NEAT&lt;/a&gt; (Non-Exercise Activity Thermogenesis), is a great way to naturally &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.tomsguide.com/features/non-exercise-activity-thermogenesis-why-neat-could-help-you-burn-more-calories" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.tomsguide.com/features/non-exercise-activity-thermogenesis-why-neat-could-help-you-burn-more-calories"&gt;burn calories &lt;/a&gt;and &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.tomsguide.com/news/boost-your-metabolism-without-dieting-heres-how" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.tomsguide.com/news/boost-your-metabolism-without-dieting-heres-how"&gt;boost your metabolism. &lt;/a&gt;Walking with a weight vest just helped to ramp things up a little.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For example, I noticed my heart rate increase with the intensity of the exercise without resorting to HIIT or running. That’s not to say it increased to the same level it would if I were out jogging, but &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://digitalrepository.unm.edu/educ_hess_etds/58/" target="_blank" data-url="https://digitalrepository.unm.edu/educ_hess_etds/58/" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;studies &lt;/a&gt;have suggested that a weight vest can boost VO2 max during treadmill walks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Whether you choose to go rucking or walk with a weighted vest, you can combine low-impact resistance training with endurance and improve your daily energy expenditure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="article-body__section" id="section-it-still-felt-meditative"&gt;&lt;span&gt;It still felt meditative&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;figure class="van-image-figure inline-layout" data-bordeaux-image-check&gt;&lt;figcaption itemprop="caption description" class=" inline-layout"&gt;&lt;span class="credit" itemprop="copyrightHolder"&gt;(Image credit: Shutterstock)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;But don’t forget, walking can also benefit your mental health. I recently started making a 5K walk a non-negotiable part of my routine, and I found it helpful for building better mental stamina. Thankfully, I still benefitted even while walking in a weight vest.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="article-body__section" id="section-one-week-later-is-it-good-to-wear-a-weighted-vest-while-walking"&gt;&lt;span&gt;One week later — Is it good to wear a weighted vest while walking?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;What did weighted walking workouts do for me?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It takes much longer than a week to build noticeable differences in strength and fitness metrics, but I could feel my legs and trunk working much harder with the added weight, and I had to focus on core engagement to prevent my back from taking too much of the load. That said, a rucksack would have been even more challenging.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I usually use my morning&lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.tomsguide.com/wellness/i-took-a-mindful-walk-every-day-for-a-week-here-s-how-it-changed-my-mind-and-body" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.tomsguide.com/wellness/i-took-a-mindful-walk-every-day-for-a-week-here-s-how-it-changed-my-mind-and-body"&gt; 5K walks for mindfulness &lt;/a&gt;(and to exercise my four-year-old pooch), but a week of walking with a weighted vest felt more like a low-impact conditioning workout before starting my day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Walking has plenty of benefits, aside from increasing your step count and getting you into nature, it can also improve various &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.tomsguide.com/features/the-5-components-of-physical-fitness-you-need-to-know" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.tomsguide.com/features/the-5-components-of-physical-fitness-you-need-to-know"&gt;components of fitness&lt;/a&gt; like cardiovascular health, which can decrease the risk of chronic conditions like high blood pressure while strengthening your muscles, bones, and joints.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To make bodyweight strength workouts harder or add more intense cardio conditioning to your routine without going high-impact — a weight vest may help.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We know that walking with weights can also contribute toward bone loading — loading the bones with resistance to help build them up. One&lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://go.redirectingat.com/?id=92X1584493&amp;amp;xcust=tomsguide_us_6638888917789054658&amp;amp;xs=1&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Flink.springer.com%2Farticle%2F10.1007%2FBF00435733&amp;amp;sref=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.tomsguide.com%2Fwellness%2Ffitness%2Five-been-walking-with-a-weight-vest-for-5k-every-day-heres-what-happened-to-my-body" target="_blank" data-url="https://link.springer.com/article/10.1007/BF00435733" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" rel="sponsored noopener" data-hl-processed="skimlinks" data-placeholder-url="https://go.redirectingat.com/?id=92X1584493&amp;amp;xcust=hawk-custom-tracking&amp;amp;xs=1&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Flink.springer.com%2Farticle%2F10.1007%2FBF00435733&amp;amp;sref=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.tomsguide.com%2Fwellness%2Ffitness%2Five-been-walking-with-a-weight-vest-for-5k-every-day-heres-what-happened-to-my-body" data-google-interstitial="false" data-merchant-name="SkimLinks - springer.com" data-merchant-network="SkimLinks"&gt; study&lt;/a&gt; even found bone density increased by 1% when exercising in a weighted vest compared with a control group who didn't.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I'd need to continue testing this out daily for a few weeks to a few months to really notice the physical impacts. However, because wearing a weight vest during walks is low-impact, you can tick the boxes for consistency and frequency without overstraining your muscles and joints.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you plan to start walking with weights, increase by a few kgs or lbs every few weeks as you get stronger and fitter, and try to keep your strides even without leaning too far forward as you walk. Think proud chest and strong core.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;My final verdict? A weighted vest for walks could help you slightly increase overall calorie burn, build strength and endurance, and increase the intensity of workouts, including walks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s simple and affordable, too, but sometimes, I like to walk for pure enjoyment, so I’m not sure this is a challenge I’ll (quite literally) carry into my daily wellness routine going forward.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="article-body__section" id="section-more-from-tom-s-guide"&gt;&lt;span&gt;More from Tom’s Guide&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Tom's Guide</author><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 09:15:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMixAFBVV95cUxONjJCamJTYnVvRTlBRjNPZnVhOVlPQ1pQdl81ZTFxdXhqOXdHazFibllSQml1UGNzWFo4TmU2b2NZYTNOVlZFelZjYzNNWmwteUpXSE5aenNONzBzbDhaeXVHeEpLSWNtQmNTd213ZkxfTUFtRzhpaGNfRl82YmMxOEQ1Z1FiRVpxZlU4RVBfWVJlNzVKaEc1Uk04NG5jczNUZFVZRHlkQ3FMWFAyZHZaSU9MTnF4b1A4c2RXWVR1VWFqR2NG</guid></item><item><title>This nutrition expert avoids a so-called health food at all costs: he says you’re better going full fat instead - Fortune</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiekFVX3lxTE5MNmRoZmsycDFzUkxTZFpIbkkwcUhUemIteHNYMl8yWHV4ZEhnMGNhTzZsT2JSSG0xMWM4UWpybGlUMVh5dFhBdG9BdG9zOGRKNVRCRWIxblluTVQxLS1KYzRNUk9WSnNac09tcm1oYkZkcGZDQTFIMHBR?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Fortune</author><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 09:09:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiekFVX3lxTE5MNmRoZmsycDFzUkxTZFpIbkkwcUhUemIteHNYMl8yWHV4ZEhnMGNhTzZsT2JSSG0xMWM4UWpybGlUMVh5dFhBdG9BdG9zOGRKNVRCRWIxblluTVQxLS1KYzRNUk9WSnNac09tcm1oYkZkcGZDQTFIMHBR</guid></item><item><title>Dementia May Not Always Be the Threat It Is Now. Here’s Why. - The New York Times</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMieEFVX3lxTE9mVWJSOEdkVVRjS1FsREc1a3dZakRKLWdMaWhZMERlMTVvaGlfVVRGOHFQNlM2NzktYXp5NnBaMldtRVlRbVFvWjF5NTJPSmxGcnV6bWZZbWEwa3hhQUR0MGQ3Vl9BSGpydnNFYWo3YW5HZFd1RHF5YQ?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="css-s99gbd StoryBodyCompanionColumn" data-testid="companionColumn-0"&gt;&lt;div class="css-53u6y8"&gt;&lt;p class="css-at9mc1 evys1bk0"&gt;Joan Presky worries about dementia. Her mother lived with Alzheimer’s disease for 14 years, the last seven in a memory-care residence, and her maternal grandfather developed dementia, too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="css-at9mc1 evys1bk0"&gt;“I’m 100 percent convinced that this is in my future,” said Ms. Presky, 70, a retired attorney in Thornton, Colo.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="css-at9mc1 evys1bk0"&gt;Last year, she spent almost a full day with a neuropsychologist, undergoing an extensive evaluation. The results indicated that her short-term memory was fine — which she found “shocking and comforting” — and that she tested average or above in every cognitive category but one.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="css-at9mc1 evys1bk0"&gt;She’s not reassured. “I saw what Alzheimer’s was like,” she said of her mother’s long decline. “The memory of what she went through is profound for me.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="css-s99gbd StoryBodyCompanionColumn" data-testid="companionColumn-1"&gt;&lt;div class="css-53u6y8"&gt;&lt;p class="css-at9mc1 evys1bk0"&gt;The prospect of dementia, which encompasses Alzheimer’s disease and a number of other cognitive disorders, so &lt;a class="css-yywogo" href="https://journals.sagepub.com/doi/full/10.1177/1533317514568889" title="" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;frightens Americans&lt;/a&gt; that a &lt;a class="css-yywogo" href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41591-024-03340-9" title="" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;recent study projecting steep increases&lt;/a&gt; in cases over the next three decades drew enormous public attention. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="css-at9mc1 evys1bk0"&gt;The researchers’ findings, published in January in Nature Medicine, even showed up as a joke on the Weekend Update segment of “Saturday Night Live.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="css-1336jj"&gt;&lt;div class="css-121kum4"&gt;&lt;p class="css-171quhb"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="css-asuuk5"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;div class="css-7axq9l" data-testid="optimistic-truncator-noscript"&gt;&lt;svg viewbox="0 0 24 24" aria-hidden="true" class="css-1b5b8u1"&gt;&lt;path fill="currentColor" fill-rule="evenodd" d="M2.5 12a9.5 9.5 0 1 1 19 0 9.5 9.5 0 0 1-19 0Zm8.5 1.75v-7.5h2v7.5h-2Zm0 2v2h2v-2h-2Z" clip-rule="evenodd"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;div data-testid="optimistic-truncator-noscript-message" class="css-6yo1no"&gt;&lt;p class="css-3kpklk"&gt;We are having trouble retrieving the article content.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="css-3kpklk"&gt;Please enable JavaScript in your browser settings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;div class="css-1dv1kvn" id="optimistic-truncator-a11y" tabindex="-1"&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thank you for your patience while we verify access. If you are in Reader mode please exit and &lt;a href="https://myaccount.nytimes.com/auth/login?response_type=cookie&amp;amp;client_id=vi&amp;amp;redirect_uri=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.nytimes.com%2F2025%2F03%2F22%2Fhealth%2Fdementia-rates-elderly.html&amp;amp;asset=opttrunc"&gt;log into&lt;/a&gt; your Times account, or &lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/subscription?campaignId=89WYR&amp;amp;redirect_uri=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.nytimes.com%2F2025%2F03%2F22%2Fhealth%2Fdementia-rates-elderly.html"&gt;subscribe&lt;/a&gt; for all of The Times.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="css-1g71tqy"&gt;&lt;svg viewbox="0 0 24 24" aria-hidden="true" class="css-63woee" data-testid="optimistic-truncator-spinner"&gt;&lt;g fill="currentColor"&gt;&lt;path d="M11.28 22.8a.72.72 0 1 0 1.44 0v-6.72a.72.72 0 1 0-1.44 0v6.72Z" opacity=".37"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="M17.766 21.16a.72.72 0 1 0 1.165-.846l-3.95-5.436a.72.72 0 1 0-1.165.846l3.95 5.437Z" opacity=".26"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="M1.506 14.653a.72.72 0 0 0 .445 1.37l6.391-2.078a.72.72 0 1 0-.445-1.369l-6.39 2.077Z" opacity=".61"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="M5.07 20.314a.72.72 0 0 0 1.164.847l3.95-5.437a.72.72 0 1 0-1.165-.846l-3.95 5.436Z" opacity=".48"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="M22.049 16.022a.72.72 0 0 0 .445-1.37l-6.391-2.076a.72.72 0 1 0-.445 1.37l6.39 2.076Z" opacity=".17"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="M22.494 9.347a.72.72 0 1 0-.445-1.37l-6.391 2.078a.72.72 0 1 0 .445 1.369l6.39-2.077Z" opacity=".09"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="M6.234 2.84a.72.72 0 0 0-1.165.846l3.95 5.436a.72.72 0 0 0 1.165-.846l-3.95-5.437Z" opacity=".87"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="M1.951 7.978a.72.72 0 1 0-.445 1.37l6.391 2.076a.72.72 0 1 0 .445-1.37l-6.39-2.076Z" opacity=".74"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="M18.93 3.686a.72.72 0 0 0-1.164-.847l-3.95 5.437a.72.72 0 0 0 1.165.846l3.95-5.436Z" opacity=".02"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="M12.72 1.2a.72.72 0 1 0-1.44 0v6.72a.72.72 0 0 0 1.44 0V1.2Z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/g&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;div data-testid="optimistic-truncator-message" class="css-6yo1no"&gt;&lt;p class="css-3kpklk"&gt;Thank you for your patience while we verify access.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="css-3kpklk"&gt;Already a subscriber? &lt;a data-testid="log-in-link" class="css-z5ryv4" href="https://myaccount.nytimes.com/auth/login?response_type=cookie&amp;amp;client_id=vi&amp;amp;redirect_uri=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.nytimes.com%2F2025%2F03%2F22%2Fhealth%2Fdementia-rates-elderly.html&amp;amp;asset=opttrunc"&gt;Log in&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="css-3kpklk"&gt;Want all of The Times? &lt;a data-testid="subscribe-link" class="css-z5ryv4" href="https://www.nytimes.com/subscription?campaignId=89WYR&amp;amp;redirect_uri=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.nytimes.com%2F2025%2F03%2F22%2Fhealth%2Fdementia-rates-elderly.html"&gt;Subscribe&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The New York Times</author><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 09:02:24 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMieEFVX3lxTE9mVWJSOEdkVVRjS1FsREc1a3dZakRKLWdMaWhZMERlMTVvaGlfVVRGOHFQNlM2NzktYXp5NnBaMldtRVlRbVFvWjF5NTJPSmxGcnV6bWZZbWEwa3hhQUR0MGQ3Vl9BSGpydnNFYWo3YW5HZFd1RHF5YQ</guid></item><item><title>The People Who Never Get Hangovers - The New York Times</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMihgFBVV95cUxQZjc0X1lHQ0dNQXcyYzZaZHQzQm5teGxOVzZhZXFBeTVjVXdtbUt3UWI3cEJ2eWI5UjdJdThSRXg2N1drRXlha19xclBLaElYdmcwWjhjTktZOWVCTlg4T3pJU25TV1NzS1pMdTYtSkc3cnIxbU9nNk52b3p3YXBTbEI3aXpzZw?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="css-s99gbd StoryBodyCompanionColumn" data-testid="companionColumn-0"&gt;&lt;div class="css-53u6y8"&gt;&lt;p class="css-at9mc1 evys1bk0"&gt;Just once, Matthew Slater would like to experience a hangover. But even if Mr. Slater, 34, finishes a bottle of vodka, he still wakes up feeling fine the next day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="css-at9mc1 evys1bk0"&gt;“Unless they know me, people don’t really believe me,” Mr. Slater said. “It’s just kind of assumed that when you drink a bunch of poison, your body is going to react.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="css-at9mc1 evys1bk0"&gt;Daniel Adams, 23, has also never felt queasy or shaky the morning after a night out. One night earlier this month, he drank a six-pack of Budweiser, then a six-pack of Coors Light, then a few shots (he doesn’t remember how many).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="css-at9mc1 evys1bk0"&gt;The next morning, while his friends groaned, he woke up at 6:30 a.m. and ran four miles.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="css-at9mc1 evys1bk0"&gt;Scientists have a term for people like Mr. Slater and Mr. Adams: “hangover resistant.” And over the last decade and a half, researchers have tried to understand why some people feel weary and wrung-out the day after drinking — and others feel nothing at all.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="css-s99gbd StoryBodyCompanionColumn" data-testid="companionColumn-1"&gt;&lt;div class="css-53u6y8"&gt;&lt;p class="css-at9mc1 evys1bk0"&gt;It’s tricky to determine just how many people are truly hangover resistant. Much of the research relies on trial participants to describe the agony of their own hangovers, a subjective measure. After all, a headache that feels excruciating to one person might not seem worth mentioning to another.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="css-at9mc1 evys1bk0"&gt;One of the first studies to show the prevalence of hangover resistance was published in 2008. The researchers happened upon the phenomenon by accident, said Jonathan Howland, a professor emeritus at Boston University School of Medicine and one of the paper’s authors. They had been trying to understand how heavy drinking affected people’s performance at work the next day, only to discover nearly a quarter did not get hungover at all.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="css-1336jj"&gt;&lt;div class="css-121kum4"&gt;&lt;p class="css-171quhb"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="css-asuuk5"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;div class="css-7axq9l" data-testid="optimistic-truncator-noscript"&gt;&lt;svg viewbox="0 0 24 24" aria-hidden="true" class="css-1b5b8u1"&gt;&lt;path fill="currentColor" fill-rule="evenodd" d="M2.5 12a9.5 9.5 0 1 1 19 0 9.5 9.5 0 0 1-19 0Zm8.5 1.75v-7.5h2v7.5h-2Zm0 2v2h2v-2h-2Z" clip-rule="evenodd"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;div data-testid="optimistic-truncator-noscript-message" class="css-6yo1no"&gt;&lt;p class="css-3kpklk"&gt;We are having trouble retrieving the article content.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="css-3kpklk"&gt;Please enable JavaScript in your browser settings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;div class="css-1dv1kvn" id="optimistic-truncator-a11y" tabindex="-1"&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thank you for your patience while we verify access. If you are in Reader mode please exit and &lt;a href="https://myaccount.nytimes.com/auth/login?response_type=cookie&amp;amp;client_id=vi&amp;amp;redirect_uri=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.nytimes.com%2F2025%2F03%2F22%2Fwell%2Fthe-people-who-never-get-hangovers.html&amp;amp;asset=opttrunc"&gt;log into&lt;/a&gt; your Times account, or &lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/subscription?campaignId=89WYR&amp;amp;redirect_uri=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.nytimes.com%2F2025%2F03%2F22%2Fwell%2Fthe-people-who-never-get-hangovers.html"&gt;subscribe&lt;/a&gt; for all of The Times.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="css-1g71tqy"&gt;&lt;svg viewbox="0 0 24 24" aria-hidden="true" class="css-63woee" data-testid="optimistic-truncator-spinner"&gt;&lt;g fill="currentColor"&gt;&lt;path d="M11.28 22.8a.72.72 0 1 0 1.44 0v-6.72a.72.72 0 1 0-1.44 0v6.72Z" opacity=".37"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="M17.766 21.16a.72.72 0 1 0 1.165-.846l-3.95-5.436a.72.72 0 1 0-1.165.846l3.95 5.437Z" opacity=".26"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="M1.506 14.653a.72.72 0 0 0 .445 1.37l6.391-2.078a.72.72 0 1 0-.445-1.369l-6.39 2.077Z" opacity=".61"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="M5.07 20.314a.72.72 0 0 0 1.164.847l3.95-5.437a.72.72 0 1 0-1.165-.846l-3.95 5.436Z" opacity=".48"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="M22.049 16.022a.72.72 0 0 0 .445-1.37l-6.391-2.076a.72.72 0 1 0-.445 1.37l6.39 2.076Z" opacity=".17"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="M22.494 9.347a.72.72 0 1 0-.445-1.37l-6.391 2.078a.72.72 0 1 0 .445 1.369l6.39-2.077Z" opacity=".09"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="M6.234 2.84a.72.72 0 0 0-1.165.846l3.95 5.436a.72.72 0 0 0 1.165-.846l-3.95-5.437Z" opacity=".87"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="M1.951 7.978a.72.72 0 1 0-.445 1.37l6.391 2.076a.72.72 0 1 0 .445-1.37l-6.39-2.076Z" opacity=".74"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="M18.93 3.686a.72.72 0 0 0-1.164-.847l-3.95 5.437a.72.72 0 0 0 1.165.846l3.95-5.436Z" opacity=".02"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="M12.72 1.2a.72.72 0 1 0-1.44 0v6.72a.72.72 0 0 0 1.44 0V1.2Z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/g&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;div data-testid="optimistic-truncator-message" class="css-6yo1no"&gt;&lt;p class="css-3kpklk"&gt;Thank you for your patience while we verify access.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="css-3kpklk"&gt;Already a subscriber? &lt;a data-testid="log-in-link" class="css-z5ryv4" href="https://myaccount.nytimes.com/auth/login?response_type=cookie&amp;amp;client_id=vi&amp;amp;redirect_uri=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.nytimes.com%2F2025%2F03%2F22%2Fwell%2Fthe-people-who-never-get-hangovers.html&amp;amp;asset=opttrunc"&gt;Log in&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="css-3kpklk"&gt;Want all of The Times? &lt;a data-testid="subscribe-link" class="css-z5ryv4" href="https://www.nytimes.com/subscription?campaignId=89WYR&amp;amp;redirect_uri=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.nytimes.com%2F2025%2F03%2F22%2Fwell%2Fthe-people-who-never-get-hangovers.html"&gt;Subscribe&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The New York Times</author><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 09:00:03 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihgFBVV95cUxQZjc0X1lHQ0dNQXcyYzZaZHQzQm5teGxOVzZhZXFBeTVjVXdtbUt3UWI3cEJ2eWI5UjdJdThSRXg2N1drRXlha19xclBLaElYdmcwWjhjTktZOWVCTlg4T3pJU25TV1NzS1pMdTYtSkc3cnIxbU9nNk52b3p3YXBTbEI3aXpzZw</guid></item><item><title>Revolutionary Cancer Vaccine Targets Any Solid Tumors - SciTechDaily</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMihgFBVV95cUxOOTFYWkVWQVF3eTh2anE1UGtha3FkUmVLOUZuSTN2MFpoSmtPWWRwQVVsS19ycTFnMjIyZWprVnZkVmhJejdXU1NSUDFXVWF2czYtenpHaWJnbEQ4TkgyclJfb3doUjlDaUJhR2lTcjJDTkw3N0pqLVRDSE1GVTV1VThQRHZQdw?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>SciTechDaily</author><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 08:25:28 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihgFBVV95cUxOOTFYWkVWQVF3eTh2anE1UGtha3FkUmVLOUZuSTN2MFpoSmtPWWRwQVVsS19ycTFnMjIyZWprVnZkVmhJejdXU1NSUDFXVWF2czYtenpHaWJnbEQ4TkgyclJfb3doUjlDaUJhR2lTcjJDTkw3N0pqLVRDSE1GVTV1VThQRHZQdw</guid></item><item><title>Updated migraine treatment guidelines ‘a long time coming’ - Pittsburgh Post-Gazette</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMinAFBVV95cUxPTy1kTy1vcG5JYmRINTV0R2dtZmVmU0hCMEowWXVQQk4tLWU0enJiQWRCVjBkX3VPakV1SWZ2NWlUakUtdFdDX3lySER2djgzUDhSWlJCVkxyQXhtNHFRSmdqTzNXS05QcnZLMXFheWZlUDBpWk1aWXNQa3lleHpzTnNlc2stV05YWlo5U0g0OGFDMDhVb1pPZG9XZUw?oc=5</link><description>&lt;body class="pgevoke bs-grid pg-hasicomoon pg-site-pg pg-user-checkingstatus pg-requesttype-story pgevoke-pageparentsection-news pg-piano" id="readabilityBody"&gt;

		
	&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;
	
	

	
	
	
	

	

	
	
	
	
	&lt;p id="dfp-peelback" class="hidden-xs hidden-sm"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
	

	&lt;p class="pgevoke-header-placeholder"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
	
	
	&lt;div class="pgevoke-pagewrapper clearfix"&gt;
			&lt;div class="pgevoke-slidemenu"&gt;
	&lt;div class="pgevoke-slidemenu-inner"&gt;
		&lt;p class="pgevoke-slidemenu-topborder"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;p class="pgevoke-slidemenu-header pgevoke-slidemenu-header-account"&gt;ACCOUNT&lt;/p&gt;
					
			
				&lt;p class="pgevoke-slidemenu-header"&gt;SECTIONS&lt;/p&gt;
		
		&lt;p class="pgevoke-slidemenu-header"&gt;OTHER&lt;/p&gt;
		
		&lt;p class="pgevoke-slidemenu-header"&gt;CLASSIFIEDS&lt;/p&gt;
		
				&lt;p class="pgevoke-slidemenu-header"&gt;CONTACT US / FAQ&lt;/p&gt;
		
	&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;		


&lt;p class="dfp-wallpaper"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  
		
		 

					
		
	&lt;/div&gt; 

	


&lt;p id="pgevoke-apwidgetloader"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;p id="pgtarget"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;


























	




			
		
		









  
  
  








  
























	











  







&lt;p id="dfpinterstitial-content" class="mfp-hide"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="dfpinterstitialmobile-content" class="mfp-hide"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



  
      
    
  
&lt;/body&gt;
</description><author>Pittsburgh Post-Gazette</author><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMinAFBVV95cUxPTy1kTy1vcG5JYmRINTV0R2dtZmVmU0hCMEowWXVQQk4tLWU0enJiQWRCVjBkX3VPakV1SWZ2NWlUakUtdFdDX3lySER2djgzUDhSWlJCVkxyQXhtNHFRSmdqTzNXS05QcnZLMXFheWZlUDBpWk1aWXNQa3lleHpzTnNlc2stV05YWlo5U0g0OGFDMDhVb1pPZG9XZUw</guid></item><item><title>Red wine or white? Which one is worse for cancer risk? - Medical News Today</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMixwFBVV95cUxNNGtSVDRxdTF2Z0duWGJIZGxWWUFhTUtsUlVUT3dVVjhXMkh5ZU1mSnlQNHZMX0NtWi1NOXZuY1VxeHJ6QlBQLVAyTTl3RXZMX2RKS1oxOXZmMW9vQkNHUEs4UUlOOFVHSUJKZzJWaUhNTFhRZmFyWkU5elZpbTFSM19EdlZ6Ul9pV1MyVVVCaVI0bDc5cGRWNFZYdXdmN2xaeEFDLU1oRGNWbExfSTNkZVFnQi1MVHhxSklMQ0d0aHQxd2tUdVow?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div data-testid="tabbed-article-section" class="css-12va8w7"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;figure class="css-yhe8zq"&gt;&lt;span class="css-rwmw5v"&gt;&lt;span class="css-mjp0j9"&gt;&lt;picture class="css-16pk1is"&gt;&lt;source srcset="https://media.post.rvohealth.io/wp-content/uploads/sites/3/2025/03/red-wine-glass-shadow-1296x728-header-1024x575.jpg 750w" media="(min-width: 1190px)"&gt;&lt;/source&gt;&lt;source srcset="https://media.post.rvohealth.io/wp-content/uploads/sites/3/2025/03/red-wine-glass-shadow-1296x728-header-1024x575.jpg 750w" media="(min-width: 990px)"&gt;&lt;/source&gt;&lt;source srcset="https://media.post.rvohealth.io/wp-content/uploads/sites/3/2025/03/red-wine-glass-shadow-1296x728-header-1024x575.jpg 879w" media="(min-width: 768px)"&gt;&lt;/source&gt;&lt;img src="https://media.post.rvohealth.io/wp-content/uploads/sites/3/2025/03/red-wine-glass-shadow-1296x728-header-1024x575.jpg" alt="photo of glass of red wine with long shadow" class="css-1jytyml"&gt;&lt;/picture&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;hl-share-overlay class="css-1mqo1cs"&gt;&lt;a class="icon-hl-pinterest css-11oz8gb" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer nofollow" data-event="Any Page|Image Pinterest Click|Icon Clicked" data-element-event="OPEN|CONTENTBLOCK|Any Page|Article Body|BUTTON|Image Widget Pinterest Click|" href="https://www.pinterest.com/pin/create/button/?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.medicalnewstoday.com%2Farticles%2Fis-red-wine-a-healthier-choice-than-white-wine-epidemiologists-uncork-the-cancer-risks&amp;amp;media=https%3A%2F%2Fmedia.post.rvohealth.io%2Fwp-content%2Fuploads%2Fsites%2F3%2F2025%2F03%2Fred-wine-glass-shadow-1296x728-header-1024x575.jpg&amp;amp;description=Red%20wine%20vs%20white%20wine%3A%20Is%20one%20type%20worse%20for%20cancer%20risk%3F" title="Share on Pinterest" data-pin-custom="true" data-share-url="https://media.post.rvohealth.io/wp-content/uploads/sites/3/2025/03/red-wine-glass-shadow-1296x728-header-1024x575.jpg"&gt;&lt;span class="css-z1zfa"&gt;Share on Pinterest&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/hl-share-overlay&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;figcaption class="css-13b3g0x"&gt;Recent evidence pits red wine against white wine, asking which one might be worse for cancer risk. Image credit: seksanwangjaisuk/Getty Images.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Research is ongoing about how consuming wine may affect the risk of cancer.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A recent meta-analysis did not find an association between consuming wine and overall cancer risk, regardless of wine type. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;White wine appeared to increase the risk for cancer when only cohort studies were considered, and to increase the risk for skin cancer and cancer, in general, in women.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alcohol consumption may increase the risk for some &lt;hl-trusted-source source="National Cancer Institute " rationale="Governmental authority"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cancer.gov/about-cancer/causes-prevention/risk/alcohol/alcohol-fact-sheet" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;types of cancer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/hl-trusted-source&gt;, with the amount and frequency affecting risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, there is ongoing research about red wine, with &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC9955827/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;some evidence&lt;/a&gt; supporting that red wine might decrease some cancer risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;A meta-analysis of observational studies published in &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.mdpi.com/2072-6643/17/3/534" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;Nutrients&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; sought to compare the potential effects of white and red wine on cancer risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;In their analysis of 42 studies, researchers did not find red or white wine to be associated with overall cancer risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;However, when they looked at only cohort studies, they found white wine consumption was associated with an increased risk for cancer.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;White wine consumption was also associated with an increased risk for cancer in women and an increased risk for &lt;a href="https://www.medicalnewstoday.com/articles/154322" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;skin cancer&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-testid="tabbed-article-section" class="css-1avyp1d"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;The authors of this meta-analysis note the research regarding wine consumption and cancer risk has been mixed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;For the current meta-analysis, researchers from the Brown University School of Public Health, the Brown University Warren Alpert Medical School, and Harvard Medical School sought to compare red and white wine consumption and how each beverage affects overall and site-specific cancer risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;First, they conducted a comprehensive search of the Embase and Pubmed digital archives to find relevant studies. They excluded studies that did not specify the type of wine and articles like literature reviews and experimental studies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;They included 22 case-control studies and 20 cohort studies in the final meta-analysis. Researchers did subgroup analyses looking at wine type and cancer type when there were more than three studies regarding the cancer type.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;They also conducted analsyses only including the cohort studies since these have less bias risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thirty-seven of the studies looked at site-specific cancer and consumption of red and white wine, while five only looked at red wine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;When researchers compared the greatest to the lowest wine intake, they did not find an association between wine intake and cancer risk. They also did not observe a difference in how red wine or white wine affected cancer risk.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Study author &lt;a href="https://vivo.brown.edu/display/ec78" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;Eunyoung Cho&lt;/a&gt;, ScD, associate professor of epidemiology and dermatology at Brown School of Public Health, explained the following to &lt;em&gt;Medical News Today&lt;/em&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;blockquote class="is-layout-flow wp-block-quote-is-layout-flow css-34gtoi"&gt;&lt;p&gt;“While it’s well-known that alcohol (including wine) consumption increases the risk of cancer, many people consider red wine to be a healthier option due to its higher levels of antioxidants compared to white wine. However, there have been few large-scale studies directly comparing red wine to white wine in terms of cancer risk, which was why we decided to conduct this meta-analysis. Our findings revealed no significant difference in cancer risk between red and white wine overall. The main message is that there are no safe alcoholic beverages in terms of cancer prevention.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="css-zya54r"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-testid="tabbed-article-section" class="css-1avyp1d"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;When looking only at cohort studies, researchers observed that white wine was associated with an increased risk for cancer, while red wine still lacked association.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;There did not appear to be a difference in cancer risk for red versus white wine in men. However, in women, white wine was associated with an increased risk for cancer.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Next, researchers examined the dose-response relationship, including three cohort and 12 case-control studies. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Researchers observed that each additional 10 grams of estimated ethanol from red wine, or about one glass, consumed in a day “was associated with a 5% increase in overall cancer risk.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, when only looking at the cohort studies, this association did not persist. Researchers did not observe a significant dose-response relationship for white wine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;When looking at specific cancers, researchers observed that white wine was associated with an increase in the risk of skin cancer by 22%. Researchers did not observe an association between skin cancer and red wine.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Skin cancer was the only site-specific cancer that showed a significant difference in associated cancer risk when comparing red wine to white wine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Red and white wine were associated with an increased risk for female breast cancer, but there was no significant difference in the associated risk. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Additionally, when researchers estimated “what the summary effect size would be if there was no publication bias,” they found a small increase in overall cancer risk for red and white wine, with a possibly higher risk from white wine. However, researchers noted later in the paper that the summary estimates were similar.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-testid="tabbed-article-section" class="css-1avyp1d"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;This meta-analysis has some limitations. The studies were observational, so the findings cannot show a causal relationship. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;The studies used self-reported food frequency questionnaires, and not all the studies used validated food frequency questionnaires. This could have led to misclassification and a minimization of the findings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Researchers acknowledge recall bias may be more likely to occur in case-control studies than in cohort studies but they also looked at the results examining only the cohort studies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;The authors only used two databases to conduct their literature search. They also faced potential limitations from their inclusion and exclusion criteria, the information they chose to extract from each of the included studies, and the methods they chose to use, as well as possible publication bias.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers acknowledge that the observed increase in skin cancer risk in white wine drinkers might be related to different demographic and lifestyle factors between white and red wine drinkers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, the included studies did account for other skin cancer risk factors, so the researchers suggest that the results likely reflect the true effect of white wine on skin cancer risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;For some cancer sites, they only had a limited number of studies to examine. This meta-analysis also had the biggest sample size related to skin cancer risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Researchers acknowledge that this could have given them enough statistical power to see a difference between red and white wine consumption. This needed amount may have been lacking for the other cancer types.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;They also could only include a certain number of studies in the dose-response analyses, primarily case-control studies. Finally, the authors note, “[p]otential regression dilution bias in the included cohort studies might have also played a role in underestimating summary risk estimates.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hendricks.org/physicians/details.aspx?sid=1&amp;amp;physician=615" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;Brian Black&lt;/a&gt;, DO, an osteopathic physician specializing in family medicine, who was not involved in this work, noted to &lt;em&gt;MNT&lt;/em&gt; that:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;blockquote class="is-layout-flow wp-block-quote-is-layout-flow css-34gtoi"&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Looking at the study as I observe with nonsubstantial overall difference in risk of cancer between the two, it does challenge the stated popular perception that red wine is healthier. I found the limitations of the analysis include its observational design and wine-specific focus, rather than total alcohol intake. That constrains its ability to address broader alcohol-related cancer or health risks.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="css-zya54r"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-testid="tabbed-article-section" class="css-1avyp1d"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;There is room for further exploration in this area of study. More research into site-specific cancers and wine consumption will likely be helpful and more follow-up into the risk of skin cancer from white wine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cho noted that it is not entirely clear why they observed this result.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;“One possibility is that heavy alcohol consumption might be linked to high-risk behaviors, such as sunburn, indoor tanning, or insufficient sunscreen use,” she explained. “But it’s still unclear why white wine appears to be the key factor. Our study suggests that more research is needed to better understand the potential mechanisms behind this.”&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;The authors note that a component of red wine is resveratrol and that some evidence supports its anticancer properties. Additionally, red wine has higher levels of resveratrol than white wine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, this meta-analysis did not show that red wine decreased cancer risk. Researchers acknowledge that this may be due to the rapid metabolism of &lt;a href="https://www.medicalnewstoday.com/articles/resveratrol-benefits" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;resveratrol&lt;/a&gt;, leading to low levels of resveratrol in the body after consuming red wine, which might not yield beneficial concentrations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Overall, the findings suggest that red wine might not be a better choice compared to white wine when it comes to cancer risk. Cho noted that this “study, which is one of the first of its kind, challenges the belief that red wine is inherently healthier than white wine.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Medical News Today</author><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 06:17:56 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMixwFBVV95cUxNNGtSVDRxdTF2Z0duWGJIZGxWWUFhTUtsUlVUT3dVVjhXMkh5ZU1mSnlQNHZMX0NtWi1NOXZuY1VxeHJ6QlBQLVAyTTl3RXZMX2RKS1oxOXZmMW9vQkNHUEs4UUlOOFVHSUJKZzJWaUhNTFhRZmFyWkU5elZpbTFSM19EdlZ6Ul9pV1MyVVVCaVI0bDc5cGRWNFZYdXdmN2xaeEFDLU1oRGNWbExfSTNkZVFnQi1MVHhxSklMQ0d0aHQxd2tUdVow</guid></item><item><title>A longevity scientist who says he's reversed his age by 15 years shares the diet he follows — and 3 foods he avoids - Business Insider</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMirgFBVV95cUxPaW0xX0xCSTZRcnhudnZQSUpYR21wUkJuWkRtbWM0cUhUSHktWUw2bnpxMGJ2eDlfQ2haX1RVSVlvc214aGdXTVpza2FLQ0tTZ0hqVEpwTkdmVUMzcEhDaVp3cHhJcHlOLXZBU0pVVE5VRDBMclJJSUFka0F4LXBibUZWMmJxaFlFakVZcjdra1czU1lKcnJhSHNfMkRiUDNPZU9vSW1meEVhemhaVmc?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;section class="post-content typography
                      
                            " data-track-content="" data-post-type="post" data-user-status="anonymous"&gt;
                      
                          &lt;ul class="summary-list"&gt;&lt;li&gt;Dr. Eric Verdin, 63, studies the biology of aging and how to get and stay healthy.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;He believes lifestyle factors such as diet play the biggest role in how long we live.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;He follows a Mediterranean-style diet and rarely drinks alcohol.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;A &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.businessinsider.com/doctor-researches-healthy-aging-takes-supplements-daily-vitamin-d-creatine-2025-1" data-analytics-product-module="body_link" rel=""&gt;healthy aging doctor and researcher&lt;/a&gt; who claims to have reversed his biological age by up to 15 years said he follows a Mediterranean-style diet — but avoids things like alcohol.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr. Eric Verdin, the CEO and president of the&lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.businessinsider.com/keto-drink-for-longevity-and-aging-being-tested-across-us-2024-10" data-analytics-product-module="body_link" rel=""&gt; Buck Institute for Research on Aging&lt;/a&gt;, studies how we can extend our "healthspan," or &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.businessinsider.com/101-year-old-live-longer-than-husband-longevity-tips-2025-1" data-analytics-product-module="body_link" rel=""&gt;quality of life&lt;/a&gt;, by maintaining faculties that tend to decline with age, such as cognition, and preventing chronic diseases like cancer and type 2 diabetes. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For the last decade, Verdin has used &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.businessinsider.com/guides/tech/fitness-wearables-trackers-pros-cons-wellness-experts-2024-1" data-analytics-product-module="body_link" rel=""&gt;wearable devices&lt;/a&gt;, such as smartwatches, as well as quarterly blood tests, to track his own health and makes tweaks according to the results. Currently, he's working on eating an earlier dinner to extend his &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.businessinsider.com/intermittent-fasting-benefits-and-risks-for-longevity-weight-loss-cancer-2024-4" data-analytics-product-module="body_link" rel=""&gt;intermittent fasting&lt;/a&gt; window.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to tests that measure biomarkers such as inflammation, blood pressure, and cholesterol, while his chronological age is 68, Verdin's biological age is between 48 and 53. There is no consensus on the &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.businessinsider.com/what-is-the-maximum-age-of-humans-115-or-older-2023-3" data-analytics-product-module="body_link" rel=""&gt;definition of biological age&lt;/a&gt; or how to measure it, so it differs according to the tests he refers to.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In general, Verdin believes lifestyle factors, including diet, exercise, sleep, stress management, and social connections, play a larger role in determining &lt;a target="_blank" class="" href="https://www.businessinsider.com/longevity-lifestyle-changes-live-longer-healthy-habits-genes-study-2024-5" data-analytics-product-module="body_link" rel=""&gt;how long we will live in good health&lt;/a&gt; than genes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Verdin shared the&lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.businessinsider.com/longevity-diet-food-list-cheap-easy-2023-11" data-analytics-product-module="body_link" rel=""&gt; diet he swears by for longevity&lt;/a&gt;, and the three foods he limits as much as possible.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="df33d72a-30d2-43d9-aa42-469f511db45c" data-toc-id="df33d72a-30d2-43d9-aa42-469f511db45c"&gt;Swears by: eating a Mediterranean-style diet &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Verdin said that there's strong evidence to suggest eating a good balance of complex carbohydrates — such as sweet potatoes — fats, and proteins is essential for health.&lt;/p&gt;
                      
                        
                      &lt;p&gt;He follows the principles of &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.businessinsider.com/chef-grew-up-mediterranean-diet-tricks-add-fiber-meals-2025-2" data-analytics-product-module="body_link" rel=""&gt;the Mediterranean diet&lt;/a&gt;, which is based on the traditional eating habits of people in countries such as Greece, Italy, and Turkey, and has been ranked the &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.businessinsider.com/mediterranean-diet-best-healthy-eating-longevity-rankings-2025-1" data-analytics-product-module="body_link" rel=""&gt;healthiest way to eat&lt;/a&gt; by the US News &amp;amp; World Report for eight years running.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"When you look at populations that are on this type of diet, they really are the healthy ones," Verdin said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The eating plan emphasizes fruits and vegetables, whole grains, legumes, nuts and seeds, and lean sources of protein such as fish.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="ff345d87-6451-4f6c-8143-210f59f54bb3" data-toc-id="ff345d87-6451-4f6c-8143-210f59f54bb3"&gt;Avoids: ultra-processed foods&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Verdin follows the&lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.businessinsider.com/michael-pollan-diet-to-avoid-ultra-processed-foods-2024-4" data-analytics-product-module="body_link" rel=""&gt; food writer Michael Pollan&lt;/a&gt;'s advice of never eating anything you could order from a window or your grandmother wouldn't recognize as food — or what would be considered ultra-professed foods.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There isn't an agreed definition of &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.businessinsider.com/how-ultra-processed-foods-impact-your-body-calories-weight-gain-2025-1" data-analytics-product-module="body_link" rel=""&gt;ultra-processed foods&lt;/a&gt;, but they're typically considered to be made using ingredients and processes that you wouldn't have in a home kitchen. They tend to be highly marketed, low in fiber, and contain large amounts of fat, sugar, and salt: a combination which makes them "&lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.businessinsider.com/new-research-explains-why-cant-stop-eating-chips-ice-cream-2023-2" data-analytics-product-module="body_link" rel=""&gt;hyper-palatable&lt;/a&gt;," which studies suggest leads to overeating.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Scientists are still trying to understand how they affect our health, but eating a diet high in &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.businessinsider.com/ultra-processed-foods-health-problems-study-2024-2" data-analytics-product-module="body_link" rel=""&gt;UPFs was linked to 32 health &lt;/a&gt;problems, including obesity, cancer, and depression in a recent study.&lt;/p&gt;
                        &lt;figure class="figure image-figure-image   " data-type="img" data-e2e-name="image-figure-image" data-media-container="image" itemscope="" itemtype="https://schema.org/ImageObject"&gt;
                        
                        
                        
                          
                        
                        &lt;span class="image-source-caption "&gt;
                              &lt;figcaption class="image-caption headline-semibold" data-e2e-name="image-caption"&gt;
                                Burgers made of reconsituted meat can be classed as ultra-processed.
                                
                        &lt;span class="image-source headline-regular" data-e2e-name="image-source" itemprop="creditText"&gt;
                        
                        Aleksandr Zubkov/Getty Images
                        
                        &lt;/span&gt;
                              &lt;/figcaption&gt;
                            &lt;/span&gt;
                        &lt;/figure&gt;
                      &lt;h2 id="2c3755ae-1d35-462d-b7f8-70174faa6f6e" data-toc-id="2c3755ae-1d35-462d-b7f8-70174faa6f6e"&gt;Avoids: fruit juice&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;While Verdin advocates eating plenty of fruit, he doesn't recommend drinking it, as juice tends to be high in sugar.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Juicing removes the &lt;a target="_blank" class="" href="https://www.businessinsider.com/high-protein-fiber-recipes-gut-health-avoid-ultra-processed-food-2025-3" data-analytics-product-module="body_link" rel=""&gt;fiber&lt;/a&gt; from fruit. So you can drink several pieces of fruit in seconds, which you wouldn't be able to do if you ate them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When we consume sugary foods or beverages, our blood sugar spikes and the pancreas needs to release more insulin to balance it. With repeated spikes, after a period of time the pancreas may not be able to keep up with production needed, which can lead to insulin resistance, prediabetes, and type 2 diabetes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fiber, which is great for &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.businessinsider.com/gut-health-boost-overall-digestion-better-moods-2024-7" data-analytics-product-module="body_link" rel=""&gt;gut health&lt;/a&gt;, also delays the absorption of the sugar therefore &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.businessinsider.com/how-to-eat-carbs-without-blood-sugar-spikes-2024-9" data-analytics-product-module="body_link" rel=""&gt;preventing blood sugar spikes&lt;/a&gt;, he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"When you eat an orange, the sugar comes in at a much slower rate. So your body is actually able to cope with it," Verdin said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="a6d835a4-6e3c-4e9f-80fa-7239d650259a" data-toc-id="a6d835a4-6e3c-4e9f-80fa-7239d650259a"&gt;Avoids: alcohol&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Verdin used to have a glass of wine with his wife most evenings, but after trying &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.businessinsider.com/dry-january-tips-first-timers-2022-12" data-analytics-product-module="body_link" rel=""&gt;Dry January &lt;/a&gt;during the COVID pandemic, he realized that he had more energy and slept better without it. "So I never went back," he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He'll still have the odd glass of wine on a special occasion but he rarely drinks these days.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In January 2023, the World Health Organization said that "no level of alcohol consumption is safe when it comes to human health," and the US Surgeon General Dr. Vivek Murthy published an advisory bringing awareness to&lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.businessinsider.com/alcohol-cancer-risk-surgeon-general-report-smoking-cigarettes-obesity-2025-1" data-analytics-product-module="body_link" rel=""&gt; alcohol's links to cancer&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;in January.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The advisory said alcohol consumption was the third leading &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.businessinsider.com/colon-cancer-risks-young-people-reduce-diet-alcohol-2024-2" data-analytics-product-module="body_link" rel=""&gt;preventable cause of cancer&lt;/a&gt; in the US, after tobacco and obesity and recommended advocated for warning labels on alcoholic drinks.&lt;/p&gt;
                      
                        &lt;/section&gt;
                      
                      
                      &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Business Insider</author><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 05:52:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMirgFBVV95cUxPaW0xX0xCSTZRcnhudnZQSUpYR21wUkJuWkRtbWM0cUhUSHktWUw2bnpxMGJ2eDlfQ2haX1RVSVlvc214aGdXTVpza2FLQ0tTZ0hqVEpwTkdmVUMzcEhDaVp3cHhJcHlOLXZBU0pVVE5VRDBMclJJSUFka0F4LXBibUZWMmJxaFlFakVZcjdra1czU1lKcnJhSHNfMkRiUDNPZU9vSW1meEVhemhaVmc</guid></item><item><title>Forget the treadmill — I boosted my metabolism and walked 2,000 steps with this 15-minute workout - Tom's Guide</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMi1AFBVV95cUxOems1ZVNodWdVekctenRDcE9sczllMVVydUJDX3FaVkg5dFgtMUNmQjNaMXFlUTVPXzlrQTV1eXNkVmdTLTZQQjA0bzREOUpMZjNTSWF3YzNHSGxpMTU2SFhOalAyWmxGN2ZSN2pNMG5oZW9iQi1NampyVkZhd2ZObld4d3YzRWR5V0p0YWRiWFVMWlQ3TzJvNzBrTE83V3B3QkZTeHBRdzZrYWxVR3ljQjhpWXdEdm01TzR1Q3RJWm1WWE9rOV9zVEpuT1kyUno5UDljLQ?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="article-body" class="text-copy bodyCopy auto"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’ll be honest, this is the first walking workout I’ve ever done from my living room.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="ad-unit-1" class="ad-unit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As a fitness editor and a marathon runner, I prioritize getting outside and getting my steps in — I’ve been known to do meetings on the move, with my over-enthusiastic cocker spaniel in tow.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yet with walking workouts on the rise, I decided to walk 2,000 steps without setting foot outdoors, and surprised myself by how much I loved it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you’re a fan of Sabrina Carpenter, but didn’t manage to get tickets to her Short n’ Sweet tour, this is a workout worth bookmarking. The 15-minute, low-impact workout is designed by &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.youtube.com/@rickbhullarfitness" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.youtube.com/@rickbhullarfitness" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;YouTube trainer Get Fit With Rick&lt;/a&gt;. You’ll walk 2,000 steps and burn calories as you move and groove.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="ad-unit-2" class="ad-unit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Read on to find out more.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="article-body__section" id="section-what-is-the-workout"&gt;&lt;span&gt;What is the workout?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;div class="youtube-video youtube-facade" data-nosnippet&gt;
&lt;div class="video-aspect-box"&gt;
&lt;div class="watch-on-iframe-ZQbu896QI-M" data-yt-video-token="ZQbu896QI-M" title="Sabrina Carpenter Walking Workout | 2000 steps in 15 minutes - YouTube"&gt;
&lt;span class="youtube-video-title"&gt;Sabrina Carpenter Walking Workout | 2000 steps in 15 minutes - YouTube&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;img src="https://img.youtube.com/vi/ZQbu896QI-M/maxresdefault.jpg" alt="Sabrina Carpenter Walking Workout | 2000 steps in 15 minutes - YouTube" data-aspect-ratio="16/9" loading="lazy"&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;svg class="play-button" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 234.67 165.33"&gt;&lt;path fill="red" d="M229.763 25.817c-2.699-10.162-10.65-18.165-20.748-20.881C190.716 0 117.333 0 117.333 0S43.951 0 25.651 4.936C15.553 7.652 7.6 15.655 4.903 25.817 0 44.236 0 82.667 0 82.667s0 38.429 4.903 56.85C7.6 149.68 15.553 157.681 25.65 160.4c18.3 4.934 91.682 4.934 91.682 4.934s73.383 0 91.682-4.934c10.098-2.718 18.049-10.72 20.748-20.882 4.904-18.421 4.904-56.85 4.904-56.85s0-38.431-4.904-56.85"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path fill="#fff" d="m93.333 117.559 61.333-34.89-61.333-34.894z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;
&lt;a class="watch-on-youtube-ZQbu896QI-M" href="https://youtu.be/ZQbu896QI-M" target="_blank" data-url="https://youtu.be/ZQbu896QI-M" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;Watch On &lt;svg class="youtube-logo" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 507.9 113.39"&gt;&lt;g fill="#fff"&gt;&lt;path d="M64.792 80.99V32.396l42.082 24.297zm93.803-63.285a20.285 20.285 0 0 0-14.32-14.32C131.642 0 80.99 0 80.99 0S30.337 0 17.705 3.385a20.286 20.286 0 0 0-14.32 14.32C0 30.338 0 56.693 0 56.693S0 83.049 3.385 95.68A20.285 20.285 0 0 0 17.705 110c12.632 3.386 63.285 3.386 63.285 3.386s50.652 0 63.285-3.386a20.284 20.284 0 0 0 14.32-14.32c3.385-12.632 3.385-38.988 3.385-38.988s0-26.355-3.385-38.988m94.473 74.326c.887-2.314 1.332-6.098 1.332-11.35V58.556c0-5.097-.445-8.822-1.332-11.178-.888-2.355-2.452-3.533-4.69-3.533-2.163 0-3.69 1.178-4.577 3.533-.888 2.356-1.332 6.081-1.332 11.178V80.68c0 5.25.424 9.035 1.275 11.35.848 2.318 2.392 3.475 4.633 3.475 2.239 0 3.803-1.157 4.691-3.475zm-17.953 11.122c-3.207-2.16-5.486-5.52-6.835-10.079-1.352-4.554-2.027-10.617-2.027-18.185v-10.31c0-7.644.771-13.784 2.316-18.417 1.544-4.633 3.956-8.011 7.24-10.135 3.282-2.123 7.587-3.186 12.916-3.186 5.251 0 9.459 1.082 12.626 3.243 3.165 2.162 5.482 5.542 6.95 10.136 1.466 4.595 2.2 10.715 2.2 18.36v10.31c0 7.567-.714 13.65-2.142 18.243-1.43 4.595-3.747 7.955-6.951 10.077-3.205 2.124-7.548 3.186-13.03 3.186-5.64 0-10.06-1.082-13.263-3.243m248.053-57.981c-.81 1.005-1.352 2.646-1.621 4.923-.272 2.278-.404 5.734-.404 10.367v5.097h11.697V60.46c0-4.555-.155-8.011-.463-10.367-.309-2.355-.868-4.014-1.678-4.98-.812-.966-2.067-1.449-3.766-1.449-1.7 0-2.954.503-3.765 1.506zm-2.025 29.886v3.591c0 4.557.132 7.974.404 10.251.269 2.279.828 3.94 1.68 4.982.849 1.041 2.16 1.564 3.938 1.564 2.392 0 4.035-.927 4.923-2.781.887-1.853 1.37-4.942 1.447-9.268l13.785.812c.077.62.116 1.469.116 2.548 0 6.565-1.795 11.47-5.387 14.712-3.589 3.242-8.669 4.865-15.232 4.865-7.876 0-13.398-2.47-16.564-7.414-3.168-4.94-4.75-12.586-4.75-22.935V63.589c0-10.657 1.641-18.436 4.924-23.342 3.281-4.903 8.9-7.355 16.854-7.355 5.482 0 9.691 1.004 12.626 3.012 2.933 2.01 5 5.137 6.197 9.383 1.197 4.247 1.796 10.117 1.796 17.607v12.163h-26.757m-284.953-1.33-18.187-65.68h15.869l6.37 29.77c1.623 7.339 2.82 13.594 3.591 18.766h.464c.54-3.706 1.738-9.922 3.591-18.65l6.603-29.886h15.869l-18.417 65.68v31.51h-15.754v-31.51M322.115 34.23v71.007h-12.511l-1.39-8.688h-.347c-3.399 6.564-8.496 9.845-15.291 9.845-4.71 0-8.185-1.543-10.425-4.633-2.24-3.087-3.359-7.915-3.359-14.48V34.23h15.985v52.126c0 3.168.348 5.426 1.043 6.776.695 1.353 1.853 2.027 3.475 2.027 1.39 0 2.722-.423 3.996-1.275 1.274-.849 2.22-1.928 2.838-3.241V34.229h15.986m81.995.001v71.007h-12.511l-1.391-8.688h-.345c-3.402 6.564-8.498 9.845-15.292 9.845-4.711 0-8.186-1.543-10.426-4.633-2.24-3.087-3.358-7.915-3.358-14.48V34.23h15.985v52.126c0 3.168.347 5.426 1.041 6.776.696 1.353 1.855 2.027 3.476 2.027 1.391 0 2.723-.423 3.996-1.275 1.275-.849 2.22-1.928 2.839-3.241V34.229h15.985"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="M365.552 20.908h-15.87v84.329h-15.637v-84.33h-15.869V8.05h47.376v12.858m76.811 53.636c0 5.174-.215 9.229-.639 12.162-.424 2.937-1.139 5.021-2.143 6.255-1.004 1.236-2.357 1.854-4.053 1.854a7.404 7.404 0 0 1-3.65-.927c-1.12-.618-2.026-1.544-2.722-2.78V50.796c.54-1.93 1.467-3.513 2.78-4.749 1.313-1.234 2.74-1.853 4.285-1.853 1.623 0 2.876.637 3.766 1.91.886 1.275 1.505 3.418 1.853 6.43.348 3.011.523 7.297.523 12.857zm14.652-28.964c-.967-4.478-2.531-7.721-4.692-9.73-2.163-2.007-5.136-3.011-8.919-3.011-2.935 0-5.676.83-8.224 2.49a16.926 16.926 0 0 0-5.908 6.545h-.117l.001-37.416h-15.405v100.777h13.204l1.622-6.717h.347c1.235 2.393 3.088 4.285 5.56 5.675 2.47 1.39 5.213 2.085 8.225 2.085 5.404 0 9.382-2.491 11.931-7.471 2.548-4.982 3.823-12.76 3.823-23.341V64.23c0-7.953-.484-14.17-1.448-18.65"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/g&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Taking me back to my step aerobics days, this workout is more than just walking on the spot. There’s a number of different steps and sequences that Rick takes you through with an infectious enthusiasm, all to the beat of some of Sabrina Carpenter’s most popular songs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You’ll walk for 15-minutes in total, and can follow along with Rick in real-time. Unlike other workouts, you can set your &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.tomsguide.com/best-picks/best-adjustable-dumbbells" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.tomsguide.com/best-picks/best-adjustable-dumbbells"&gt;best adjustable dumbbells &lt;/a&gt;and &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.tomsguide.com/best-picks/best-kettlebells" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.tomsguide.com/best-picks/best-kettlebells"&gt;best kettlebells &lt;/a&gt;to one side, as you won’t need any equipment to complete this one. That said, you might want to wear one of the &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.tomsguide.com/us/best-fitness-trackers,review-2066.html" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.tomsguide.com/us/best-fitness-trackers,review-2066.html"&gt;best fitness trackers&lt;/a&gt; to keep an eye on your step count and calorie burn — I wore my &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.tomsguide.com/wellness/smartwatches/apple-watch-series-10-review" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.tomsguide.com/wellness/smartwatches/apple-watch-series-10-review"&gt;Apple Watch Series 10&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div id="slice-container-newsletterForm-articleInbodyContent-DgBgSKS8HjboKLfchpvmmR" class="slice-container newsletter-inbodyContent-slice newsletterForm-articleInbodyContent-DgBgSKS8HjboKLfchpvmmR slice-container-newsletterForm"&gt;&lt;div data-hydrate="true" class="newsletter-form__wrapper newsletter-form__wrapper--inbodyContent"&gt;&lt;div class="newsletter-form__container"&gt;&lt;section class="newsletter-form__main-section"&gt;&lt;p class="newsletter-form__strapline"&gt;Get instant access to breaking news, the hottest reviews, great deals and helpful tips.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;As Rick mentions in the video, most fitness trackers measure steps by your arm swing, so be sure to move your arms as well as your legs as you step if you are wearing one.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alternatively, you could always strap your &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.tomsguide.com/tag/apple-watch" data-auto-tag-linker="true" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.tomsguide.com/tag/apple-watch"&gt;Apple Watch&lt;/a&gt; around your ankle — but I haven’t had much success with this in the past (here’s why &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.tomsguide.com/wellness/fitness/i-tried-the-red-hot-apple-watch-ankle-trend-heres-what-happened" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.tomsguide.com/wellness/fitness/i-tried-the-red-hot-apple-watch-ankle-trend-heres-what-happened"&gt;I’d never follow the Apple Watch ankle trend again&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ready to get started? Here’s the workout:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="i-tried-this-15-minute-sabrina-carpenter-walking-workout-here-s-what-happened-3"&gt;I tried this 15-minute Sabrina Carpenter walking workout — here’s what happened &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;h3 class="article-body__section" id="section-i-loved-it-from-minute-one"&gt;&lt;span&gt;I loved it from minute one &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;As mentioned, I wasn’t expecting to love this workout. When I opt for home workouts it’s normally Pilates or HIIT sessions, not walking, but I pressed play anyway and was immediately marching on the spot. I love the focus during Rick’s workout videos, and found his enthusiasm really uplifting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The different step routines reminded me how uncoordinated I am, but unlike those step aerobics classes I took in my local gym, missing steps didn’t matter in the comfort of my own living room.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I also found the different step patterns made the time fly. At the end of the 15-minutes, I wished the workout was longer — it really boosted my mood and left me with a smile on my face.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="article-body__section" id="section-it-was-low-impact-enough-that-i-didn-t-need-shoes"&gt;&lt;span&gt;It was low-impact enough that I didn’t need shoes &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;While I wouldn’t normally recommend doing any form of cardio workout in socks, this workout was low-impact enough for me to leave my running shoes by the front door.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There’s no jumping whatsoever, making this suitable for all levels of fitness. As always, if you’re new to exercise or you’re returning to exercise following an injury or pregnancy, it’s always a good idea to check with a doctor or personal trainer before taking on a new workout routine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="article-body__section" id="section-i-walked-further-than-i-thought"&gt;&lt;span&gt;I walked further than I thought &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;While it’s tricky to say how accurate the step counting was on my Apple Watch, after 15-minutes my watch told me I’d walked 0.84 miles in my living room. My walking pace was a little slower than my normal gait, however I’m not normally side-stepping and ladder-walking along the street.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;My heart rate stayed in the ‘easy’ zone, but if you’re a beginner, this is a great workout to start adding some movement to your day, plus you can increase the intensity by making this more of a cardio dance workout, should you wish.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;See you on the dancefloor (I’ll be the one doing the grapevine).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="article-body__section" id="section-more-from-tom-s-guide"&gt;&lt;span&gt;More from Tom's Guide &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Tom's Guide</author><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 04:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi1AFBVV95cUxOems1ZVNodWdVekctenRDcE9sczllMVVydUJDX3FaVkg5dFgtMUNmQjNaMXFlUTVPXzlrQTV1eXNkVmdTLTZQQjA0bzREOUpMZjNTSWF3YzNHSGxpMTU2SFhOalAyWmxGN2ZSN2pNMG5oZW9iQi1NampyVkZhd2ZObld4d3YzRWR5V0p0YWRiWFVMWlQ3TzJvNzBrTE83V3B3QkZTeHBRdzZrYWxVR3ljQjhpWXdEdm01TzR1Q3RJWm1WWE9rOV9zVEpuT1kyUno5UDljLQ</guid></item><item><title>Doctors say ‘mini epidemic’ is possible after measles case confirmed in Middle Tennessee - WSMV 4</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMitwFBVV95cUxQM2YyN01VMGdIVDJ4TU5FaExuY0k4SkdZUXgza29UVXlWcGlweEJFY29XbU1ocVZUQXFIeWVteXdEZHhhS19BOF9ZTVVsZVJOSlNGaDhIdUZvU2xJMVluLThxNTZiYjVvQ3BXS1JVX1FVMk55ZnR0UEI3QkZkM0FrV2QyTW93S1h4ZWVBSUNHR1AyRVhKRmlNWUFRZ2xVVWRVX3l4RS1ISkN4OU9iYnNRQ09FRmFqWmPSAcsBQVVfeXFMTk80TVZzQUlMODl5TlQtckZnTW4zSjVTZ3gwYmpXM2p3QTkzbWFTMG5iZnVLYnZyOU1fbUdWREVrV0IxS2c2cmlwdFJ3TmFVc2FndnhaTlhYSzh4VjM1ZTNVNVhCSlNJYTRYSFVuNU5YSTAxa2JGc0dxWENSRE5DcUFZcEtVNkQ2SFlhWm1KRi14YTdCbnZWRjdRNElUcGl5YmlWdXNzV2t5REszcnlnVTZEQTVmSEozdFBWZnNMNjBLVURmdlhybUw0Vjg?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body | article w-100"&gt;&lt;p class="text | article-text"&gt;NASHVILLE, Tenn. (WSMV) - The first measles case of 2025 has been confirmed in the state, and it’s in Middle Tennessee, according to the Tennessee Department of Health. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text | article-text"&gt;Health officials said the infected person is recovering in their home, while doctors and people worry about the viral infection spreading. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text | article-text"&gt;The measles is an infection some people said they weren’t too surprise was spreading, Breanna Thomas said she almost expected it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text | article-text"&gt;“I’m going to be honest I wasn’t too shocked because a lot of mothers and fathers are very hesitant to vaccinate their children,” Thomas said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="w-100"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text | article-text"&gt;Doctor Joseph Gigante with the Monroe Carole Junior Children’s Hospital at Vanderbilt said the spread of measles seemed to be moving fast. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text | article-text"&gt;“Unfortunately, the most recent outbreak that started in west Texas has now spread,” Dr. Gigante said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text | article-text"&gt;The Tennessee Department of Health announced a measles case was found in Middle Tennessee in March on Friday. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text | article-text"&gt;“This is where you get really worried and really concerned,” Dr. Gigante said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="w-100"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text | article-text"&gt;Tennessee health officials said measles is highly infectious. The virus spreads through the air when an infected person speaks, coughs or sneezes. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text | article-text"&gt;Officials said the person in Middle Tennessee was infected in early March, but they’re investigating to find out where or how they got the virus.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text | article-text"&gt;“It’s a tragedy, but it’s so easy to prevent measles. The best thing parents could do is to vaccinate your child,” Dr. Gigante said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text | article-text"&gt;Doctors said watch out for symptoms of small bumps, high fever, cough and a runny noise. Measles can also be fatal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="w-100"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text | article-text"&gt;“There could definitely be a mini epidemic here in Tennessee for sure,” Thomas said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text | article-text"&gt;The department reports that there’s an active national measles outbreak with over 300 cases in 11 states, including two deaths.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text | article-text"&gt;“I would hope that the cases are quarantined very well and even put in isolation rooms if they do have to go unfortunately to the hospital,” Thomas said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text | article-text"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="copyright |"&gt;&lt;i&gt;Copyright 2025 WSMV. All rights reserved.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>WSMV 4</author><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 02:50:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMitwFBVV95cUxQM2YyN01VMGdIVDJ4TU5FaExuY0k4SkdZUXgza29UVXlWcGlweEJFY29XbU1ocVZUQXFIeWVteXdEZHhhS19BOF9ZTVVsZVJOSlNGaDhIdUZvU2xJMVluLThxNTZiYjVvQ3BXS1JVX1FVMk55ZnR0UEI3QkZkM0FrV2QyTW93S1h4ZWVBSUNHR1AyRVhKRmlNWUFRZ2xVVWRVX3l4RS1ISkN4OU9iYnNRQ09FRmFqWmPSAcsBQVVfeXFMTk80TVZzQUlMODl5TlQtckZnTW4zSjVTZ3gwYmpXM2p3QTkzbWFTMG5iZnVLYnZyOU1fbUdWREVrV0IxS2c2cmlwdFJ3TmFVc2FndnhaTlhYSzh4VjM1ZTNVNVhCSlNJYTRYSFVuNU5YSTAxa2JGc0dxWENSRE5DcUFZcEtVNkQ2SFlhWm1KRi14YTdCbnZWRjdRNElUcGl5YmlWdXNzV2t5REszcnlnVTZEQTVmSEozdFBWZnNMNjBLVURmdlhybUw0Vjg</guid></item><item><title>Parents of girl who died from measles urge others to not vaccinate - NewsNation Now</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMihwFBVV95cUxNTnQyNGdUQXIyX0o3aUF0X0VHdHAwcXdHa3FmZGstRi1ZbHBnb3U0cUtqRWQxVHh3M3d3T2VKdElhV1FMendTVWpLQ0U2Zl9ha1NwR1JycU96QTd0ODNkWUcxRUJ4MUo4WldrNEptUXRQaFl0NlZ2MDdIU3QxVV9GUUt3VGlFU2vSAYwBQVVfeXFMTkRhbncybVp5NU5HU0tuVkRDU296WXZxelF3QkRqdHo5cWg2eXh6R1pvOGZNVDlQS1BzWTlDLXN4RWRQUE5NTHdDeldDbE52dkN4bXRNaWM4ZjBiQTFwNTlDQkI3akxLUEFRTjE0QjhzbVJDYW1wdDlka0w2TnpJUEtBWC1adF9uWUVlVEM?oc=5</link><description>&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;
    
    
    &lt;noscript&gt;
      
    &lt;/noscript&gt;
  &lt;/body&gt;
</description><author>NewsNation Now</author><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 02:26:26 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihwFBVV95cUxNTnQyNGdUQXIyX0o3aUF0X0VHdHAwcXdHa3FmZGstRi1ZbHBnb3U0cUtqRWQxVHh3M3d3T2VKdElhV1FMendTVWpLQ0U2Zl9ha1NwR1JycU96QTd0ODNkWUcxRUJ4MUo4WldrNEptUXRQaFl0NlZ2MDdIU3QxVV9GUUt3VGlFU2vSAYwBQVVfeXFMTkRhbncybVp5NU5HU0tuVkRDU296WXZxelF3QkRqdHo5cWg2eXh6R1pvOGZNVDlQS1BzWTlDLXN4RWRQUE5NTHdDeldDbE52dkN4bXRNaWM4ZjBiQTFwNTlDQkI3akxLUEFRTjE0QjhzbVJDYW1wdDlka0w2TnpJUEtBWC1adF9uWUVlVEM</guid></item><item><title>EXPLAINER: All you need to know about hypertension and why it is killing many young people - GhanaWeb</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMi4gFBVV95cUxPbFhiM2NMSEVTbUYwaFdDVnZrbmJTNHN5NzFzVW8zNmdQTDFRV3FxQUgyZUJxXzJLblZSdW1vZjNRLWZ5R0FOb2VKWnhMZGN1Qk9feXl4Q1NEbF9fMUtwZTB2enFhVzUzNVlTMVFzTTVfUW1pQ3lZWnp3SmsxdmIxZlhjVjl5NWNjbURkQTNmZ3RhY2lKX3prbnZDSktLVk5KSzd1TTRHVk1HM1NsRkdIdUVtMFVyVzJaUlF0ZUt0VmJrTXRZTFAwbEhSeGozdTlabmthdU85bkxmMTBvSkYwTC1R?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-left"&gt;
&lt;p class="article-image"&gt;&lt;a href="EXPLAINER-All-you-need-to-know-about-hypertension-and-why-it-is-killing-many-young-people-1976681?gallery=1"&gt;&lt;img src="https://cdn.ghanaweb.com/imagelib/pics/671/67164401.295.jpg" alt="File photo of a blood pressure monitor" title="File photo of a blood pressure monitor"&gt; &lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class="image_caption"&gt;&lt;span&gt;File photo of a blood pressure monitor&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="article-content-area"&gt;&lt;p id="article-123"&gt;Hypertension, also known as high blood pressure, has become quite common lately, claiming lots of lives in the country.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
The effects of the disease have been such that even many young people have been forced to drop out of school because they lost their bread winners through hypertension.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
But a bigger question is, what is hypertension, and what exactly causes it?&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
This article provides some insights on hypertension, its causes, and the dangers it poses.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Overview&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Hypertension has become rampant among young people in the country, many of whom are unaware of their status. This has become a major health concern due to the alarming rate at which this group is developing hypertension.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;b&gt;What is hypertension&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Hypertension, also known as high blood pressure, is a medical condition in which the blood pressure in the arteries is consistently too high. Blood pressure is measured in millimetres of mercury (mmHg) and is expressed as two numbers: systolic pressure (the top number) and diastolic pressure (the bottom number).&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Blood pressure ranges&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Normal blood pressure: Less than 120/80mmHg&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Elevated blood pressure: 120-129/80mmHg&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Stage 1 hypertension: 130-139/80-89mmHg&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Stage 2 hypertension: 140 or higher/90 or higher mmHg&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Causes of hypertension and risk factors&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Family history: Having a family history of hypertension increases the risk.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Age: The risk of developing hypertension increases with age.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Obesity: Being overweight or obese is a significant risk factor.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Lifestyle: Lack of physical exercise, smoking, and consuming a diet high in salt, sugar, and saturated fats contribute to hypertension.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Stress: Chronic stress can raise blood pressure.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Kidney diseases: Certain kidney diseases can cause hypertension.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Symptoms&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Hypertension often has no particular symptoms, but some people may experience:&lt;br&gt;
 &lt;br&gt;
Headaches&lt;br&gt;
Dizziness&lt;br&gt;
Nosebleeds&lt;br&gt;
Shortness of breath&lt;br&gt;
Chest pain&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Complications&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Untreated hypertension can lead to serious health complications, which include:&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Heart attack&lt;br&gt;
Stroke&lt;br&gt;
Vision loss&lt;br&gt;
Kidney disease&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Diagnosis&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Hypertension is diagnosed using a sphygmomanometer, which measures the pressure in the arteries.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Treatment&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Treatment of hypertension usually involves a combination of medication and lifestyle changes.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;b&gt;What can be done?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Education and awareness: Raising awareness about hypertension and the dangers it poses can help to regulate it.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Regular checkup: Having checked regularly can help to reduce the dangers.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Medication and positive lifestyle: Always take your medication, which helps to remove excess fluid from the body.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Lifestyle Changes: Engage in moderate-intensity physical activity.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Eat a balanced diet focused on whole unprocessed foods.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Stay hydrated by drinking lots of water.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Reduce salt intake.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Manage stress by engaging in stress-reducing activities like yoga.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Conclusion&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Regular blood pressure checks and maintaining a healthy lifestyle can help identify and manage hypertension regardless of age.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
MRA/AE&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;b&gt;You can also watch a compilation of the latest Twi news on GhanaWeb TV below:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;iframe class="gh-jwplayer" loading="lazy" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/rAjqY1HplQc" title="EXPLAINER: 'Forced retirement' of senior officers as Mahama appoints Brigadier General as CDS" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen&gt;VIDEO&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>GhanaWeb</author><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 02:25:54 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi4gFBVV95cUxPbFhiM2NMSEVTbUYwaFdDVnZrbmJTNHN5NzFzVW8zNmdQTDFRV3FxQUgyZUJxXzJLblZSdW1vZjNRLWZ5R0FOb2VKWnhMZGN1Qk9feXl4Q1NEbF9fMUtwZTB2enFhVzUzNVlTMVFzTTVfUW1pQ3lZWnp3SmsxdmIxZlhjVjl5NWNjbURkQTNmZ3RhY2lKX3prbnZDSktLVk5KSzd1TTRHVk1HM1NsRkdIdUVtMFVyVzJaUlF0ZUt0VmJrTXRZTFAwbEhSeGozdTlabmthdU85bkxmMTBvSkYwTC1R</guid></item><item><title>Colon cancer in young adults: Utahn shares experience being diagnosed at 21 - KSL.com</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMisAFBVV95cUxPZHB6UlJQLXZwS1hNb0l3V1NTWVNFZXNlaTJ2dW8yTDBBWmQwMHp5OE5VVWNaYTN5c2hiUzMxNS1uOVdESm9qQjc4aXVzTzJTcWpNaDNLaEZyUTZoZzRyZ0ZiYk9raDVEeDlIakJtaE80WXdBdG56aGZsbUlGbldPVmdINThCbl9lekt4WVI2SmdWRlIxRmNJTnZqd3dJTE0wM0xOTXZQWHhlQ1QwVFFOOA?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;
                                        Estimated read time: 3-4
                                        minutes&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div id="articleContainer"&gt;&lt;p&gt;HEBER CITY — Brinlee Luster and her twin sister, Mariela Luster, are inseparable. They went to college together, studied the same major, met their husbands on the same day and got married two months apart.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You just have this bond unlike any other," Mariela Luster said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But something they didn't share — a cancer diagnosis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Having her go through something that I couldn't go through, and I couldn't experience was just so hard," Mariela Luster said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;Brinlee Luster and her twin sister, Mariela Luster. (Photo: Brinlee Luster)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Two years ago, at age 21, Brinlee Luster started experiencing puzzling symptoms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I was having severe abdominal cramping," she said. "I remember going on a hike and I was just out of breath. I was so fatigued, so tired."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Doctors initially attributed her symptoms to irritable bowel syndrome, anxiety or her birth control.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I just thought, you know, I'm stressed, I'm planning my wedding, I'm about to graduate college, there's a lot of changes," Brinlee Luster said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But when her symptoms worsened, she went in for a colonoscopy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Her results turned her life upside down.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I don't think anything can prepare you for that moment when you're told you have cancer," she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Brinlee Luster was diagnosed with stage IV colon cancer and underwent 30 rounds of chemotherapy and several surgeries.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"As a young adult, like right at the brink of where my life was accelerating, I had to slow down and watch everyone else go forward, and that was really hard," she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;Brinlee Luster receives treatment for her cancer. (Photo: Brinlee Luster)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to the American Cancer Society, since 2020, there has been a 9% increase in colon cancer diagnoses in people under 50.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"There really is unfortunately no such thing as too young for colon cancer. About 1 in 7 of the patients in my practice with colon cancer are under the age of 45," said Dr. Mark Lewis, a cancer survivor and director of gastrointestinal oncology at Intermountain Health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lewis said this could be due to lifestyle factors, genetics or certain medications.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Antibiotics in childhood and in adulthood can affect the bacteria that line the colon," he said. "We're being very, very careful about prescribing antibiotics to young people because we do know there is at least a slight increased risk for colon cancer decades later."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Symptoms of colorectal cancer include abdominal pain, unintentional weight loss, changes in bowel movements like diarrhea, or blood in the stool.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Though it may be uncomfortable, Lewis said bringing up concerns to a provider can make all the difference.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"If you are willing to talk to your doctor about your gut health, I promise you we are going to be better at finding colon cancer sooner," he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;Brinlee Luster is accompanied in the hospital by her sister Mariela Luster. (Photo: Brinlee Luster)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Brinlee Luster finished her last round of chemo in December and is in remission.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mariela Luster has since had a colonoscopy, where they removed polyps.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I like to think that she really did save my life in a way because I was headed down that route," Mariela Luster said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The twins created "&lt;a href="https://theportstudio.com/" rel="nofollow" target="_blank"&gt;The Port Studio&lt;/a&gt;," a line of comfortable sweatshirts with IV access for people going through chemo. They also started a podcast called "&lt;a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/hu/podcast/live-today/id1757263555" rel="nofollow" target="_blank"&gt;Live Today&lt;/a&gt;."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It's been so healing for us to work on together," Mariela Luster said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I don't want to hide that I had cancer," Brinlee Luster said. "Sharing your story is uncomfortable, but I want to be able to share it so that people can be inspired. There's always room for hope."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;National guidelines recommend people begin colorectal screening at age 45. If you are younger than 45 and are experiencing any abnormal symptoms, talk to your doctor. Intermountain Health also offers &lt;a href="https://intermountainhealthcare.org/services/virtual-care/fit-test" rel="nofollow" target="_blank"&gt;home-based tests for colon cancer screening&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>KSL.com</author><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 01:41:51 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMisAFBVV95cUxPZHB6UlJQLXZwS1hNb0l3V1NTWVNFZXNlaTJ2dW8yTDBBWmQwMHp5OE5VVWNaYTN5c2hiUzMxNS1uOVdESm9qQjc4aXVzTzJTcWpNaDNLaEZyUTZoZzRyZ0ZiYk9raDVEeDlIakJtaE80WXdBdG56aGZsbUlGbldPVmdINThCbl9lekt4WVI2SmdWRlIxRmNJTnZqd3dJTE0wM0xOTXZQWHhlQ1QwVFFOOA</guid></item><item><title>Expert Reveals 8 'Essential' Ways to Reduce Your Risk of Stroke - ScienceAlert</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMilAFBVV95cUxPNnRibTZBbWxsV0VUTFY5MmNoanNYM0RzMjJ6ZHItZUVGYXRsV3hXQno3Tm9PSnU2d2hYMUNDTU1mZ0VDMllEbGlTSGdDVEtDdUQweTdTQ2VoVV9sREdYaUhwajgxMXNPV3EyTFRNd2YtamE2Y05GZnktN3AyRHdsRzJvbV9ZSjEtTktmWTc5WTluWjlH?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;As a nurse working in a neurocritical care, I witnessed the sudden and devastating effects of stroke on &lt;a href="https://researchportal.lsbu.ac.uk/en/publications/an-overview-of-traumatic-brain-injury-in-adults-3"&gt;survivors and their carers&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Following my nursing career, I became a researcher specializing in stroke. Knowledge of &lt;a href="https://groups.stroke.org.uk/what-is-stroke/what-can-i-do-to-reduce-my-risk"&gt;stroke risk factors&lt;/a&gt; in the general public is poor, so stroke prevention is a priority for public health.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Stroke is &lt;a href="https://cks.nice.org.uk/topics/stroke-tia/background-information/prevalence/"&gt;a leading cause&lt;/a&gt; of death and disability in England – yet it is &lt;a href="https://linkinghub.elsevier.com/retrieve/pii/S0140673616306791"&gt;largely preventable&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It's often considered an older person's illness but, although stroke risk does increase with age, it can happen at any time of life. In fact, stroke incidence is &lt;a href="https://www.medicalnewstoday.com/articles/stroke-in-young-adults-causes"&gt;increasing among adults&lt;/a&gt; below the age of 55 years.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Stroke risk factors that tend to be more common among older people – such as high blood pressure (hypertension), high cholesterol, obesity,  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/diabetes" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73018" data-postid="155781" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;diabetes&lt;/a&gt;, smoking, physical inactivity and poor diet – are increasingly found in younger people.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Other lifestyle risks include heavy alcohol consumption or binge drinking and recreational drugs such as amphetamines, &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/cocaine-and-alcohol-heres-why-theyre-such-a-deadly-combination-125278"&gt;cocaine&lt;/a&gt; and heroin.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some risk factors are not modifiable such as age, sex, ethnicity, family history of stroke, genetics and certain inherited conditions. Women, for example, are &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC9911842/"&gt;particularly susceptible to strokes&lt;/a&gt; – and women of all ages are more likely than men to die from a stroke.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.ahajournals.org/doi/10.1161/STROKEAHA.117.018415"&gt;Stroke risks unique to women&lt;/a&gt; include pregnancy and some contraceptive pills (especially for smokers), as well as  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/endometriosis" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73093" data-postid="155781" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;endometriosis&lt;/a&gt;, premature ovarian failure (before 40 years of age), early-onset menopause (before 45 years of age) and estrogen for transgender women.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="aspect-w-16 aspect-h-9 youtube-iframe relative"&gt;&lt;iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/cJBsV93T1Sg?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen&gt;VIDEO&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Also, inherited vascular abnormalities such as &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/around-3-of-us-will-develop-a-brain-aneurysm-in-our-lives-so-what-is-it-and-how-do-you-treat-it-248882"&gt;cerebral aneurysms&lt;/a&gt; – a weakness in the artery wall – can increase the risk of &lt;a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/books/NBK559173/"&gt;hemorrhagic stroke&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some risk factors are social rather than biological, however. &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1186/s12889-020-09580-x"&gt;Studies have found&lt;/a&gt; that people with a lower income and education level are at a higher risk of having a stroke. This is due to a combination of factors.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Unhealthy lifestyle habits, such as smoking, heavier drinking and lower physical activity levels &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41598-020-75822-y"&gt;are more common&lt;/a&gt; in people with lower incomes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;However, &lt;a href="https://www.thelancet.com/journals/laneur/article/PIIS1474-4422(15)00200-8/abstract"&gt;research also shows&lt;/a&gt; that people with lower socioeconomic status are less likely to receive good quality healthcare than people with higher incomes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But, regardless of biological or social risk factors, there are things you can do – right now – to reduce your risk of having a stroke.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Essential eight&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. Stop smoking&lt;/strong&gt; Smokers are &lt;a href="https://www.hopkinsmedicine.org/health/conditions-and-diseases/smoking-and-cardiovascular-disease"&gt;more than twice as likely&lt;/a&gt; to have a stroke than non-smokers. Smoking causes damage to blood vessel walls, increases blood pressure and heart rate but reduces oxygen levels.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Smoking also causes &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/tobacco/campaign/tips/diseases/heart-disease-stroke.html"&gt;blood to become sticky&lt;/a&gt;, further increasing the risk of blood clots that can block blood vessels and cause a stroke.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2. Keep blood pressure in check&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC9441708/"&gt;High blood pressure&lt;/a&gt; damages the walls of blood vessels, making them weaker and more prone to rupture or blockage. It can also cause blood clots to form, which can then travel to the brain and block blood flow, leading to a stroke.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you're over 18 years of age, get your blood pressure checked regularly so, if you do show signs of developing high blood pressure, you can nip it in the bud and make appropriate changes to your lifestyle to help reduce your risk of stroke.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3. Keep an eye on your cholesterol&lt;/strong&gt; According to the &lt;a href="https://www.stroke.org.uk/stroke/managing-risk/high-cholesterol"&gt;UK Stroke Association&lt;/a&gt; your risk of a stroke is nearly three and a half times higher if you have both high cholesterol and high blood pressure.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To lower cholesterol, aim to keep saturated fat – found in fatty meats, butter, cheese, and full-fat dairy – below 7 percent of your daily calories, stay active and maintain a healthy weight.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;4. Watch your blood sugar&lt;/strong&gt; High blood glucose levels &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S0261561420306002"&gt;are linked&lt;/a&gt; to an increased risk of stroke. This is because &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/sugar-its-not-just-the-calories-that-are-bad-for-you-56459"&gt;high blood sugar&lt;/a&gt; damages blood vessels, which can lead to blood clots that travel to the brain.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To reduce blood glucose levels, try to take regular exercise, eat a balanced diet rich in fiber, drink enough water, maintain a healthy weight, and try &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/how-to-remain-youthful-and-resilient-despite-stress-173173"&gt;to manage stress&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;5. Maintain a healthy weight&lt;/strong&gt; Being overweight is one of the &lt;a href="https://www.nhlbi.nih.gov/health/stroke/causes"&gt;main risk factors&lt;/a&gt; for stroke. It is associated with almost one in five strokes, and &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/20299666/"&gt;increases your stroke risk by 22 percent&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Being obese raises that risk by 64 percent. &lt;a href="https://www.niddk.nih.gov/health-information/weight-management/adult-overweight-obesity/health-risks#stroke"&gt;Carrying too much weight&lt;/a&gt; increases your risk of high blood pressure, heart disease, high cholesterol and type 2 diabetes, which all contribute to higher stroke risk.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;6. Follow a Mediterranean diet&lt;/strong&gt; One way to eat a fiber-rich balanced diet and maintain a healthy weight is to follow a &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/both-statins-and-a-mediterranean-style-diet-can-help-ward-off-heart-disease-and-stroke-64609"&gt;Mediterranean diet&lt;/a&gt;. This has been shown to &lt;a href="https://link.springer.com/article/10.1007/s10654-019-00504-7"&gt;reduce the risk of stroke&lt;/a&gt;, especially when supplemented with nuts and olive oil.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="aspect-w-16 aspect-h-9 youtube-iframe relative"&gt;&lt;iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/xjPl7K5vh_M?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen&gt;VIDEO&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;7. Sleep well&lt;/strong&gt; Try to to get seven to nine hours of sleep daily. Too little sleep &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/health-check-three-reasons-why-sleep-is-important-for-your-health-41176"&gt;can lead to high blood pressure&lt;/a&gt;, one of the most important modifiable risk factors for stroke.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Too much sleep, however, is also &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S1389945721005505?via%3Dihub"&gt;associated with increased stroke risk&lt;/a&gt;, so try to stay as active as possible so you can sleep as well as possible.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;8. Stay active&lt;/strong&gt; The &lt;a href="https://www.nhs.uk/live-well/exercise/"&gt;NHS recommends &lt;/a&gt; that people should avoid prolonged sedentary behavior and aim for at least 150 minutes of moderate intensity activity or 75 minutes of vigorous intensity activity a week.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Exercise should be spread evenly over four to five days a week, or every day. Do strengthening activities, usually more than two days per week.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The good news is that while the effects of stroke can be devastating and life-changing, it is largely preventable. Adopting these eight simple lifestyle changes can help to reduce stroke risk and optimize both heart and brain health.&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://counter.theconversation.com/content/251524/count.gif?distributor=republish-lightbox-basic" alt="The Conversation" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" loading="lazy"&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/profiles/siobhan-mclernon-2339489"&gt;Siobhan Mclernon&lt;/a&gt;, Senior Lecturer, Adult Nursing and co-lead, Ageing, Acute and Long Term Conditions. Member of Health and Well Being Research Center, &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/institutions/london-south-bank-university-909"&gt;London South Bank University&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This article is republished from &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com"&gt;The Conversation&lt;/a&gt; under a Creative Commons license. Read the &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/eight-ways-to-reduce-your-stroke-risk-no-matter-what-age-you-are-251524"&gt;original article&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 01:01:13 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilAFBVV95cUxPNnRibTZBbWxsV0VUTFY5MmNoanNYM0RzMjJ6ZHItZUVGYXRsV3hXQno3Tm9PSnU2d2hYMUNDTU1mZ0VDMllEbGlTSGdDVEtDdUQweTdTQ2VoVV9sREdYaUhwajgxMXNPV3EyTFRNd2YtamE2Y05GZnktN3AyRHdsRzJvbV9ZSjEtTktmWTc5WTluWjlH</guid></item><item><title>Tennessee reports first measles case of 2025 amid national outbreak involving 11 states - WTVC</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiwAFBVV95cUxPWnJBUGRyUW11V3FFdzEtdWhnM2Z2QU5PZEhVRTgyUWxGRWNyMHNGS2t5Si1VRlNYRTAxOUQ2SnI0eTJwYWVQdkgzdERhSDRnQ21nTUFaZkxLd3czWmJVSEtVNk5iOWJvM2lESGhTaldrUGRHX2tvdUE2RURBS05nZ1FSMXBra2EyVGhieDNuR2g4WXlERXFZZU1MdVpMcHJmeXNPSkt5UzlRRTVoU2x3YmVNMmVpWThWa2ZIdGsySlk?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="index-module_storyColumn__EZ7G" id="js-Story-Content-0"&gt;&lt;p class="StoryTags-module_tagWrapperLine__Jfav"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="StoryText-module_storyText__FWhP"&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Tennessee Department of Health confirmed the state’s first &lt;a href="https://www.tn.gov/health/cedep/reportable-diseases/measles-rubeola.html" target="_blank" title="https://www.tn.gov/health/cedep/reportable-diseases/measles-rubeola.html" class="themeColorForLinks"&gt;measles &lt;/a&gt;case in 2025 in a middle Tennessee resident Friday.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The department says the source of the infection is being investigated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;TDH says the person became infected with measles in early March and is recovering at home. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Public health officials are working to identity other locations and persons potentially exposed to the virus.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There is currently an ongoing, national measles outbreak,&lt;a href="https://newschannel9.com/news/nation-world/health-official-warns-katherine-wells-director-of-public-health-for-lubbock-of-prolonged-measles-outbreak-as-cases-rise-in-texas-new-mexico-oklahoma" target="_blank" title="https://newschannel9.com/news/nation-world/health-official-warns-katherine-wells-director-of-public-health-for-lubbock-of-prolonged-measles-outbreak-as-cases-rise-in-texas-new-mexico-oklahoma" class="themeColorForLinks"&gt; involving over 300 cases in 11 states, including two deaths.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Measles typically has a classic red, spotty rash that begins on the face and spreads over the body. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Additional symptoms can include fever, headache, and generally not feeling well, followed by rash, cough, red eyes, or congestion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Measles is a highly infectious and potentially fatal disease which spreads very easily through the air when an infected person speaks, coughs or sneezes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;TDH encourages consultation with your medical provider about measles prevention. Two doses of the MMR vaccine are highly effective at preventing measles.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It is important for medical providers to consider measles and report suspected cases immediately to TDH at (615) 741-7247.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>WTVC</author><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 00:14:19 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiwAFBVV95cUxPWnJBUGRyUW11V3FFdzEtdWhnM2Z2QU5PZEhVRTgyUWxGRWNyMHNGS2t5Si1VRlNYRTAxOUQ2SnI0eTJwYWVQdkgzdERhSDRnQ21nTUFaZkxLd3czWmJVSEtVNk5iOWJvM2lESGhTaldrUGRHX2tvdUE2RURBS05nZ1FSMXBra2EyVGhieDNuR2g4WXlERXFZZU1MdVpMcHJmeXNPSkt5UzlRRTVoU2x3YmVNMmVpWThWa2ZIdGsySlk</guid></item><item><title>Man with STD infected multiple coworkers after urinating into water cooler - WKRC TV Cincinnati</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMi-gJBVV95cUxNRTJvcDIxX1FCMXJ3dGNPQ09zd0ROay1WU3RNVERJMkIwM001QTFweFFjVlZRZ3ZrR3FBbkRqTTNqUVNzM3Bra09YM2F5eVdOSlo0WEpXOEJOMmtpd0lFVmREb0gza0xPY2Q5S2Vya0E4OGFPTHVTLVNHX2dIemJQdVlXM3pKaGg5X0QzdDZza3ZibElsZkQzRWZjcnZRdW5YQ1FGZ2NXTzJHT01pZGpRQjRfS3MyaUdqLTJScGdOZE9icXBVODJQWjIxX2pGTFd5QXM4QVhXWFhFS0MtTHdTLUdXbEZScHItWlBaM2xsYS1DckVPSmRmWDhIc1VGd3hmSTZ1RlBSaFZPOFNkTkxRekpHdVBCd2NSUmZxWlpzZ0pEUVFWdkdBS1FxVzY4MjNXMTBPT0VHaW8zVEQ2XzRWS1ZkelB1NUtUTVliYmxKU3puRUZYbFFmcXdUVzU5SHdaQUltN0ZjLS1aRm9HRXBHRXBSYlJlWk1ldXc?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="index-module_storyColumn__EZ7G" id="js-Story-Content-0"&gt;&lt;p class="StoryTags-module_tagWrapperLine__Jfav"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="StoryText-module_storyText__FWhP"&gt;&lt;p&gt;HOUSTON (WKRC) - A man pled guilty to assault with a deadly weapon after he intentionally infected multiple coworkers with an incurable STD by urinating into a shared water cooler at his office.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;50-year-old Lucio Diaz pled guilty on Wednesday to one of his multiple alleged assaults from 2022 in which he intentionally infected his coworkers with his contaminated urine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to local outlet &lt;em&gt;KPRC&lt;/em&gt;, Diaz's crimes came to light when a 54-year-old woman contracted Herpes Simplex 1 Virus from a shared office cooler and from tainted water bottles at the office building that Diaz worked as a janitor at.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The police connected the crime to Diaz through urinalysis and because the victim caught Diaz in the act with a hidden camera.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Previous coverage:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The woman reported that the camera caught Diaz as he "pulls out his penis and puts his penis in my bottle, basically rinses his penis in the water."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"He gave me an STD I will have for the rest of my life," she told local outlet &lt;em&gt;KTRK&lt;/em&gt;. "Nothing is going to change it. Nothing will make it better for me."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At least 13 other women accused Diaz of infecting them with STDs since 2022, ranging between two different office buildings. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Diaz was sentenced to six years in prison on Wednesday after pleading guilty to indecent assault and aggravated assault with a deadly weapon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>WKRC TV Cincinnati</author><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 23:43:55 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi-gJBVV95cUxNRTJvcDIxX1FCMXJ3dGNPQ09zd0ROay1WU3RNVERJMkIwM001QTFweFFjVlZRZ3ZrR3FBbkRqTTNqUVNzM3Bra09YM2F5eVdOSlo0WEpXOEJOMmtpd0lFVmREb0gza0xPY2Q5S2Vya0E4OGFPTHVTLVNHX2dIemJQdVlXM3pKaGg5X0QzdDZza3ZibElsZkQzRWZjcnZRdW5YQ1FGZ2NXTzJHT01pZGpRQjRfS3MyaUdqLTJScGdOZE9icXBVODJQWjIxX2pGTFd5QXM4QVhXWFhFS0MtTHdTLUdXbEZScHItWlBaM2xsYS1DckVPSmRmWDhIc1VGd3hmSTZ1RlBSaFZPOFNkTkxRekpHdVBCd2NSUmZxWlpzZ0pEUVFWdkdBS1FxVzY4MjNXMTBPT0VHaW8zVEQ2XzRWS1ZkelB1NUtUTVliYmxKU3puRUZYbFFmcXdUVzU5SHdaQUltN0ZjLS1aRm9HRXBHRXBSYlJlWk1ldXc</guid></item><item><title>Parents of girl who died from measles urge others to not vaccinate - NewsNation Now</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMihwFBVV95cUxNTnQyNGdUQXIyX0o3aUF0X0VHdHAwcXdHa3FmZGstRi1ZbHBnb3U0cUtqRWQxVHh3M3d3T2VKdElhV1FMendTVWpLQ0U2Zl9ha1NwR1JycU96QTd0ODNkWUcxRUJ4MUo4WldrNEptUXRQaFl0NlZ2MDdIU3QxVV9GUUt3VGlFU2s?oc=5</link><description>&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;
    
    
    &lt;noscript&gt;
      
    &lt;/noscript&gt;
  &lt;/body&gt;
</description><author>NewsNation Now</author><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 23:27:15 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihwFBVV95cUxNTnQyNGdUQXIyX0o3aUF0X0VHdHAwcXdHa3FmZGstRi1ZbHBnb3U0cUtqRWQxVHh3M3d3T2VKdElhV1FMendTVWpLQ0U2Zl9ha1NwR1JycU96QTd0ODNkWUcxRUJ4MUo4WldrNEptUXRQaFl0NlZ2MDdIU3QxVV9GUUt3VGlFU2s</guid></item><item><title>The #1 Thing People Get Wrong About the High-Protein Diet, According to a New Survey - EatingWell</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiekFVX3lxTE43ZVZWRUhsOW9wZU5UZFIta1ZjUmIyR2dyX01BYllzLXlJRWllX0YtVW5EOWo2RG9YMVN3cFpBbzV5andqUnJKaEZOTEUwVzlwMEVGcHUwUFY4WlZJbFVOSXRtUXpHMkY1TUIzT2lzLThMckIydnJLbWdn?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-page_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-page mntl-block structured-content" data-sc-sticky-offset="90" data-sc-ad-label-height="24" data-sc-ad-track-spacing="100" data-sc-min-track-height="250" data-sc-max-track-height="600" data-sc-breakpoint="50em" data-sc-load-immediate="4" data-sc-content-positions="[1, 1250, 1550, 1950, 2350, 2750, 3150, 3550, 3950]" data-bind-scroll-on-start="true"&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-block_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-callout mntl-sc-block-universal-callout theme-generic" data-tracking-id="mntl-sc-block-callout" data-tracking-container="true"&gt; &lt;h3 class="mntl-sc-block-universal-callout__heading"&gt;Key Takeaways&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;div class="mntl-sc-block-universal-callout__body"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;A survey found that 87% of U.S. adults believe it’s important to eat animal products to get enough protein.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Studies show that plant-based protein can help you build muscle and support your heart health and longevity.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Plant-based foods like beans, whole grains, nuts and some vegetables can be great sources of protein.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_2-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Protein is &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/8022629/counting-macros/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;one of the macronutrients&lt;/a&gt;—along with carbohydrates and fats—vital for our bodies to function properly and for overall good health. You’ll find some type of protein in every cell of your body, highlighting its importance. &lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_3-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_5-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_6-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; When most of us think of protein, our minds automatically go to meat, eggs and dairy. In fact, a new survey from Morning Consult and the Physicians Committee for Responsible Medicine found that nearly 9 out of every 10 U.S. adults believe it’s important to eat meat, dairy products, eggs or other animal products to get adequate protein.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="1"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_7-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_8-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; One of the questions in the survey, which polled 2,203 U.S. adults, asked if it’s possible to build muscle on a plant-based diet. Over half responded yes, but 22% disagreed and 21% said they didn’t know. These responses, says &lt;a href="https://www.pcrm.org/about-us/staff/roxanne-becker" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Roxanne Becker&lt;/a&gt;, medical editor and educator for the Physicians Committee for Responsible Medicine, suggest that consumers are still unclear on the benefits of a plant-based diet. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_9-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_10-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; “Plant protein has been shown in randomized controlled trials to be as effective as animal protein for building muscle when the amounts of protein are equal,” says Becker in a &lt;a href="https://www.eurekalert.org/news-releases/1075695" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;press release&lt;/a&gt; about the survey. “And it is full of nutrients and fiber, unlike animal-based protein sources.” &lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_11-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_13-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_14-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; This makes sense when you consider that many animals we eat—like cows and deer—are herbivores and seem to have no problem building plenty of muscle mass. Plus, there is evidence from research that humans can also build muscle and get the amino acids they need for optimal bodily functions from plants. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_15-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_16-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; For example, a meta-analysis of 13 clinical trials involving older adults suggests that plant protein can be equally as effective as animal protein for maintaining and building strength and lean muscle mass.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="2"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; And a study of men who ate either a vegan diet or an omnivorous diet found no differences in strength or muscle mass gains over 12 weeks when coupled with a strength-training program.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="3"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_17-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_18-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; And there are other benefits of eating more plants. An original Harvard study suggests that women who ate more plant protein in midlife increased their odds of healthy aging.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="4"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; And an umbrella review examining cardiovascular disease, cancer and plant-based diets found that plant-based diets were associated with a lower risk of these diseases.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="5"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_19-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_21-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-how-does-this-apply-to-real-life"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_22-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; How Does This Apply to Real Life? &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_23-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Let’s be real, though. If you love your meat, the chances of completely shunning it altogether are probably low. After all, what would a summer cookout be without barbeque chicken or smoked brisket? 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_24-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_25-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; But you could start taking advantage of the benefits of plant-based protein by increasing your plant intake and reducing your animal protein intake—there’s evidence that this flexitarian-type eating pattern also has benefits, including for your heart.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="6"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;There’s also a good chance you’re already eating plant proteins. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_26-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_27-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; “Most people already enjoy a variety of plant protein without even realizing it,” says &lt;a href="https://www.pcrm.org/about-us/staff/xavier-toledo" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Xavier Toledo, M.S., RD, LDN&lt;/a&gt;, a registered dietitian with the Physicians Committee for Responsible Medicine. “Whole-wheat bread, nut butters, beans, seeds, nuts and vegetables such as broccoli, spinach, and potatoes are all great examples. In fact, all plants contain protein—just to varying degrees. Start by incorporating more of the familiar plant-based foods you already enjoy.”&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_28-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_30-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_31-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; While a flexitarian eating pattern doesn’t completely cut out meat—including beef, pork and chicken—it does reduce it. Flexitarianism focuses more on plant-based proteins but also includes dairy and eggs fairly regularly. Seafood? Yes. This eating style also limits or cuts out ultra-processed foods and refined grains, in part, because you’ll get more plant protein from whole grains.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_32-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_33-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Eggs are a great protein source. But did you know some plants and &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/plant-based-foods-with-more-protein-than-an-egg-8424134" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;plant-based foods have more protein&lt;/a&gt; than an egg? One of our &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/protein-you-should-be-eating-more-of-on-the-mediterranean-diet-8789966" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;favorite plant proteins is legumes&lt;/a&gt;. Besides being loaded with protein, they’re also rich in antioxidants and fiber, both of which support a healthy heart and gut. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_34-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_35-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; It’s easy to add legumes or other plant-based proteins to recipes that call for meat. And you don’t have to be all-or-nothing about it—and for many, it’s easier to ease into the change. For example, you could totally swap the meat in tacos out for tofu like we do in our &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/recipe/272203/beefless-vegan-tacos/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Beefless Vegan Tacos&lt;/a&gt;. Or you could use half the amount of ground beef you normally use and make up the other half with tofu or black beans. That’s a tasty strategy we use in recipes like our &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/cheesy-beef-black-bean-skillet-casserole-8414702" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;Cheesy Beef &amp;amp; Black Bean Skillet Casserole&lt;/a&gt;.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_36-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_37-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Some plant proteins mimic meat in texture and can be grilled or sauteed just like you would meat. “If meat is your go-to protein, try marinated tofu, &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/8050521/what-is-seitan-and-is-it-healthy/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;seitan&lt;/a&gt; or tempeh,” says Toledo. “They’re versatile, blank canvases that soak up flavor just like meat. While these foods may be unfamiliar at first, simple techniques, like &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/how-to-cook-tofu-8671953" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;pressing and marinating tofu&lt;/a&gt; can make all the difference in achieving a texture and depth of flavor that feels just right.”&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_38-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_40-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-the-bottom-line"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_41-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; The Bottom Line &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_42-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Now that you know that you can, indeed, get your necessary protein—including those essential amino acids—from plants, the power is in your hands to start incorporating more plants into your diet. If finances &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/gallery/7960483/budget-friendly-vegetarian-dinner-recipes/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;are a potential obstacle&lt;/a&gt; to eating more plants, go for &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/8034364/best-budget-friendly-fruits-vegetables-spring/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;produce that’s in season&lt;/a&gt; since it’s typically more economical. Plus, frozen produce is a great budget-saver and just as nutritious as fresh.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_43-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_44-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; And remember, &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/7775696/plant-based-diet-for-beginners-your-guide-to-getting-started/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;eating more plants&lt;/a&gt; doesn’t have to be an all-or-nothing proposition. “Eating more plant proteins is about rethinking your plate, leaning into plant-forward familiar favorites and discovering new foods that fit well into your routine,” says Toledo. “Instead of making meat the star of every meal, consider recasting it in a supporting role. Try cutting your usual portion [of meat] in half and filling the rest of your plate with beans, lentils or extra veggies. Over time, you might find that the meal is just as satisfying—if not better—without meat in the spotlight or on your plate at all.”
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_45-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>EatingWell</author><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 22:08:45 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiekFVX3lxTE43ZVZWRUhsOW9wZU5UZFIta1ZjUmIyR2dyX01BYllzLXlJRWllX0YtVW5EOWo2RG9YMVN3cFpBbzV5andqUnJKaEZOTEUwVzlwMEVGcHUwUFY4WlZJbFVOSXRtUXpHMkY1TUIzT2lzLThMckIydnJLbWdn</guid></item><item><title>Toxicology report shows ketamine in Wyoming mom's system before murder-suicide - Q2 News</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMizAFBVV95cUxOYmZnSW1VWnAyWTU3RzJZWW9JZVlNOGhneUtDMUlxOEQwcGFEdFl3VHB6RWhObmxCOU81dEhWSmNzTnQ3YXdWTkNHLUs3WU9QbllPZEM2WXlIYVgxSklVSFZMamlmekxGRlhxdTlZUXpfWTd6dUZfVW12YkszU2NIR2VsX1djTUpTUHd2TjlVTlhDYUNaUjNNc2tNUVVfNUg2b2FWSnRsXzdscVhpRHRVQW5naDRJWGJmV250SnVScERFM1JOdkdGOFVkNms?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="RichTextArticleBody-body"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Toxicology reports show the Wyoming mother who shot and killed her four daughters had large amounts of ketamine in her system when she died by suicide in February, according to the Big Horn County Coroner's Office.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Watch the video below:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="VideoEnhancement" data-video-disable-history&gt;
    
        &lt;p class="VideoEnhancement-title"&gt;Toxicology report shows ketamine in Wyoming mom's system before murder-suicide&lt;/p&gt;
    
    
    
        
    
    
&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Chief Deputy Coroner Bill Brenner told MTN News that 32-year-old Tranyelle Harshman also had a regular amount of clonazepam, an anti-anxiety drug, in her system. Family and friends have said she was suffering from post-partum depression when she killed her children at their home in Byron.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ketamine was developed in the 1960s as an anesthetic used by soldiers injured on the battlefield. It's used today as treatment for severe depression, but health experts note it can come with serious and sometimes hallucinogenic side effects. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Toxicology reports also indicated Harshman's four children all had high amounts of propranolol and diphenhydramine, both of which cause drowsiness, in their systems, according to Brenner. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The cause of death was gunshot wounds to the head for all four girls. The two youngest, Jordan Basil Harshman and Brooke Seline Harshman, and a 9-year-old, Braylee Shae Blackmer, died at the scene. The fourth daughter, 7-year-old Olivia Harshman, died days later at a Salt Lake City hospital.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Police said T&lt;a class="Link" href="https://www.ktvq.com/news/crime-watch/wyoming-mom-shoots-4-daughters-and-calls-911-before-shooting-herself" target="_blank" data-cms-ai="0"&gt;ranyelle Harshman called 911 to report she had shot the four girls before turning the gun on herself&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Q2 News</author><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 22:02:32 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMizAFBVV95cUxOYmZnSW1VWnAyWTU3RzJZWW9JZVlNOGhneUtDMUlxOEQwcGFEdFl3VHB6RWhObmxCOU81dEhWSmNzTnQ3YXdWTkNHLUs3WU9QbllPZEM2WXlIYVgxSklVSFZMamlmekxGRlhxdTlZUXpfWTd6dUZfVW12YkszU2NIR2VsX1djTUpTUHd2TjlVTlhDYUNaUjNNc2tNUVVfNUg2b2FWSnRsXzdscVhpRHRVQW5naDRJWGJmV250SnVScERFM1JOdkdGOFVkNms</guid></item><item><title>'I'm worried it's getting worse': Texas measles outbreak grows as families resist vaccination - NBC News</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiwgFBVV95cUxOdjVtdFN0bW1pdm9MTUJYczB2c0E2TEFMeC0xZ2lsbmd1RWduLW5VR2FpYXBHanlMRTZDNUtpWXZlTE5Vb3U0MUxDOEprM0E1NWxqUWlDT0dvWTk3X253cTVlMm1kUE9YcE5fWmdGaGYwMkwtVnRNeEtXSXVHVkJJSk9ES2wtR1NTeWlBYndYZGlPM25iX0R6YS1vSWNsS2gyU3hPcTV6TTZEekVUWHRuLWhMOTBPbl9rZWVpZFlhc0dOQdIBVkFVX3lxTE1SdzgyT3pXa242SHlZM25zeFgxNHJxVGd6aVRoLVN1NnhULVRXdklOQ3c1NXpsTFk3b0Z3RXQzeEZ6STdNd01OZzZvaUtENk9aU1NIVUZB?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body__content"&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;The &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/measles-outbreak-west-texas-grows-unvaccinated-rcna192163" target="_blank"&gt;measles outbreak that began in Texas&lt;/a&gt; before spreading to at least two other states swelled to 355 confirmed cases on Friday — and officials say there is no sign it’s slowing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;“I’m worried it’s getting worse,” Katherine Wells, director of public health for Lubbock, told NBC News.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="taboolaReadMoreBelow"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;Many people aren’t getting tested for measles, and efforts to increase vaccination in the affected areas have gotten a lukewarm response, Wells said during a media briefing by the Big Cities Health Coalition on Tuesday.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;Wells said she thought it could be a year until the outbreak is controlled. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;The &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/anti-vaccine-influencers-weaponized-measles-death-texas-rcna196900" target="_blank"&gt;outbreak that started in West Texas&lt;/a&gt; in late January has now infected 309 people in 14 Texas counties. “All of the cases in these counties are related to each other,” Wells said, adding: “We are going to see mini outbreaks” as the virus spreads unchecked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;Measles is doing what measles does: It seeks out anyone and everyone who isn’t vaccinated against the virus and infects them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;Nearly all of the people who have gotten sick have been &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/texas-measles-outbreak-hospital-newborn-babies-exposed-rcna196519" target="_blank"&gt;children &lt;/a&gt;and teenagers never vaccinated against the virus. At least 40 patients have been hospitalized.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;Neighboring &lt;a href="https://www.nmhealth.org/about/erd/ideb/mog/" target="_blank"&gt;New Mexico reported 42 cases&lt;/a&gt; on Friday. Twenty of the people in New Mexico were ages 18 or older, eight were 4 or younger. And as of Tuesday, &lt;a href="https://oklahoma.gov/health/health-education/acute-disease-service/rash-illness/measles.html" target="_blank"&gt;Oklahoma had confirmed four cases&lt;/a&gt; related to the outbreak. All were either unvaccinated or it was unclear if they had gotten the shots.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;Two people, a &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/anti-vaccine-influencers-weaponized-measles-death-texas-rcna196900" target="_blank"&gt;6-year-old girl in Texas&lt;/a&gt; and an adult in New Mexico, have died. The epicenter of the outbreak, Gaines County, Texas, has one of the state’s highest vaccine exemption rates, at nearly 18%, according to&lt;a href="https://www.dshs.texas.gov/immunizations/data/school/conscientious-exemptions" target="_blank"&gt; health department data.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;Vaccine clinics have been set up in the county, but uptake hasn’t been robust, Wells said. Many families in the area remain steadfast in long debunked fears that vaccines cause autism, she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;Now is the time, Wells said during Tuesday’s briefing, for health departments across the country to boost their vaccination rates.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;“Measles is going to find those pockets of unvaccinated individuals, and with the number of cases and ability for people to travel, there is that risk of it entering other unvaccinated pockets anywhere in the United States right now,” she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;&lt;a href="https://kshealthdata.kdhe.ks.gov/t/KDHE/views/InfectiousDiseaseCaseDashboard/DataTable?%3Aembed=y&amp;amp;%3AisGuestRedirectFromVizportal=y" target="_blank"&gt;Kansas has reported 10 measles cases&lt;/a&gt; in three counties that border Oklahoma. Those cases haven’t been officially linked to the ongoing outbreak.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/measles/data-research/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Cases linked not to the outbreak&lt;/a&gt; but to international travel have been reported in Alaska, California, Florida, Georgia, Kentucky, Maryland, Michigan, New Jersey, Ohio, Pennsylvania, Rhode Island, Texas, Vermont and Washington.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;“Measles will find a way to continue transmitting until it runs out of a susceptible population,” said Dr. Brian Borah, medical director for vaccine-preventable diseases surveillance at the Chicago Department of Public Health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;The only thing that’s going to stop a national outbreak is a massive effort to find people who aren’t vaccinated and &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/texas-measles-outbreak-grows-parents-vaccinate-rcna193637" target="_blank"&gt;get them the shots as soon as possible&lt;/a&gt;, Dr. Simbo Ige, commissioner of the Chicago Department of Public Health, said during Tuesday’s briefing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;“The duration of the outbreak is dependent on your ability to identify everyone who is vulnerable, determine if they have been exposed, and then how quickly vaccination starts,” Ige said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="recommended-intersection-ref" data-activity-map="recommended-article-body-recommended" data-testid="recommended-wrapper"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;Last year, Ige’s team faced a &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/chicago-measles-cases-migrant-shelter-rcna142801" target="_blank"&gt;measles outbreak&lt;/a&gt; that ultimately infected 64 people, mostly associated with a housing shelter in Chicago.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;The health department enlisted community health workers and other trusted members in the area, such as politicians and faith leaders, to encourage vaccination, Borah said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;“We put people in the shelter who we knew were trusted messengers,” he said. Nearly everyone who hadn’t been vaccinated got the shots.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;Within two months, &lt;a href="https://www.chicago.gov/city/en/depts/cdph/provdrs/health_protection_and_response/news/2024/may/cdph-press-release-05-30-2024.html" target="_blank"&gt;the outbreak was over.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="body-heading"&gt;How the virus develops and causes symptoms&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;Measles is one of the most contagious viruses in the world. When an infected person coughs, sneezes or even breathes, tiny viral particles are hurled through the air — and stay there, floating around for hours.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;“If I’m just sitting in my office and talking, I’m spewing virus around,” said Dr. Ronald Cook, chief health officer at the Texas Tech University Health Sciences Center in Lubbock and the city’s top health official, explaining how easily measles spreads. “If my door is open, that virus can leave my office and go out into the hallway. Somebody walking up and down the hallway can get infected.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;Once a person is infected, the virus quietly multiplies in the body for about seven to 14 days without causing symptoms. This is called the incubation period.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;Around day 10 or 11, the body’s immune system becomes overwhelmed and symptoms develop, including a cough, runny nose, high fevers up to 103 and 104 degrees and inflamed, red eyes. “Think of pink eye, but worse,” Cook said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="recommended-intersection-ref" data-activity-map="recommended-article-body-recommended" data-testid="recommended-wrapper"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;Then, small, white dots called Koplik spots show up in the mouth and spread into the lungs, causing inflammation. That’s why babies and small children in particular are at risk for trouble breathing. Their tiny airways can’t handle so much inflammation. At this point, the virus can cause bacterial pneumonia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;It’s not until several days later that the characteristic measles rash begins — angry, red splotches that start at the top of the head and work their way down the body.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;By that time, the patient has already infected vulnerable people. An infected person spreads the virus four days before the rash ever shows up, as well as four days after. That’s why it’s a mistake, Cook said, to think of measles as “just a rash.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="body-heading"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Measles vaccination guidelines&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;Two doses of the measles, mumps and rubella (&lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/have-you-had-your-measles-shot-learn-if-you-need-n996096" target="_blank"&gt;MMR) vaccine&lt;/a&gt; are 97% effective in preventing infection, according to the &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/measles/hcp/vaccine-considerations/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Centers for Disease Control and Prevention&lt;/a&gt;. The first dose is given at around age 1, offering 93% protection, but the second isn’t given until around age 5, when a child enters kindergarten. That leaves kids slightly vulnerable for the several years they are in between doses.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;The general rules change, however, during an outbreak.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="endmark body-graf"&gt;Doctors have the option of giving the second dose early if a child has been exposed to the virus. Pediatricians can give the vaccine to babies at least 6 months old, doctors say, but they will still need the two standard doses when they’re old enough.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>NBC News</author><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 21:59:48 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiwgFBVV95cUxOdjVtdFN0bW1pdm9MTUJYczB2c0E2TEFMeC0xZ2lsbmd1RWduLW5VR2FpYXBHanlMRTZDNUtpWXZlTE5Vb3U0MUxDOEprM0E1NWxqUWlDT0dvWTk3X253cTVlMm1kUE9YcE5fWmdGaGYwMkwtVnRNeEtXSXVHVkJJSk9ES2wtR1NTeWlBYndYZGlPM25iX0R6YS1vSWNsS2gyU3hPcTV6TTZEekVUWHRuLWhMOTBPbl9rZWVpZFlhc0dOQdIBVkFVX3lxTE1SdzgyT3pXa242SHlZM25zeFgxNHJxVGd6aVRoLVN1NnhULVRXdklOQ3c1NXpsTFk3b0Z3RXQzeEZ6STdNd01OZzZvaUtENk9aU1NIVUZB</guid></item><item><title>Measles arrives in Kansas, spreads quickly in undervaccinated counties - Ars Technica</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMitgFBVV95cUxOM1lPTjh1TzBvTjFkWDM3VVBGYmJWS2tlSVBHVXJWVTAycUY4Q0F6X1h4Ym9FODZCV0hRY0ZhdFBPeXhPenl2dXRZZVdNaVhmSDEyTVhZZzB0ZTItVmlUb1hiS0ZTam9NNm1YV2FZRUJfNWRDanlvOEh1Wi11WlhxaXFESHdldVZvQ2FMQ3BBTW9JeUZLaXVCLWtSX09hdFN4RDlORGFjaE9Cekh6cXhHbWFuTEpaZw?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content post-content-double"&gt;
          
          
&lt;p&gt;On Thursday, the county on the northern border of Stevens, Grant County, &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/permalink.php?story_fbid=pfbid0uJqqfNbQYF3UD23EAQ7Q9P6Wc6GkviiwrfakYuVguwSTy34HzPUmNbLdH4dCMB6Jl&amp;amp;id=100068906386981"&gt;also reported three confirmed cases&lt;/a&gt;, which were also linked to the first case in Stevens. Grant County is in a much better position to handle the outbreak than its neighbors; its one school district, Ulysses, reported 100 percent vaccination coverage for kindergartners in the 2023–2024 school year.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Outbreak risk&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So far, details about the fast-rising cases are scant. The Kansas Department of Health and Environment (KDHE) has not published another press release about the cases since March 13. Ars Technica reached out to KDHE for more information but did not hear back before this story's publication.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The outlet &lt;a href="https://www.kwch.com/2025/03/20/6-measles-cases-reported-kansas-according-kdhe/"&gt;KWCH 12 News out of Wichita published a story Thursday&lt;/a&gt;, when there were just six cases reported in just Grant and Stevens Counties, saying that all six were in unvaccinated people and that no one had been hospitalized. On Friday, KWCH updated the story to note that the case count had increased to 10 and that the health department now considers the situation an outbreak.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/measles/about/index.html"&gt;Measles is an extremely infectious virus&lt;/a&gt; that can linger &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/measles/causes/index.html"&gt;in airspace and on surfaces for up to two hours&lt;/a&gt; after an infected person has been in an area. Among unvaccinated people exposed to the virus, 90 percent will become infected.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Vaccination rates have slipped nationwide, creating pockets that have lost herd immunity and are vulnerable to fast-spreading, difficult-to-stop outbreaks. In the past, strong vaccination rates prevented such spread, and in 2000, &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/measles/about/history.html"&gt;the virus was declared eliminated&lt;/a&gt;, meaning there was no continuous spread of the virus over a 12-month period. Experts now fear that the US will lose its elimination status, meaning measles will once again be considered endemic to the country.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So far this year, the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention has documented 378 measles cases as of Thursday, March 20. That figure is already out of date.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On Friday, the Texas health department &lt;a href="https://www.dshs.texas.gov/news-alerts/measles-outbreak-2025"&gt;reported 309 cases in its ongoing outbreak&lt;/a&gt;. Forty people have been hospitalized, and one unvaccinated child with no underlying medical conditions has died. The outbreak has spilled over to New Mexico and Oklahoma. In New Mexico, officials reported Friday that the case count has risen to &lt;a href="https://www.nmhealth.org/about/erd/ideb/mog/"&gt;42 cases&lt;/a&gt;, with two hospitalizations and one death in an unvaccinated adult. In Oklahoma, &lt;a href="https://oklahoma.gov/health/health-education/acute-disease-service/rash-illness/measles.html"&gt;the case count stands at four&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;


          
                  &lt;/div&gt;

                  
          &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Ars Technica</author><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 21:53:29 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMitgFBVV95cUxOM1lPTjh1TzBvTjFkWDM3VVBGYmJWS2tlSVBHVXJWVTAycUY4Q0F6X1h4Ym9FODZCV0hRY0ZhdFBPeXhPenl2dXRZZVdNaVhmSDEyTVhZZzB0ZTItVmlUb1hiS0ZTam9NNm1YV2FZRUJfNWRDanlvOEh1Wi11WlhxaXFESHdldVZvQ2FMQ3BBTW9JeUZLaXVCLWtSX09hdFN4RDlORGFjaE9Cekh6cXhHbWFuTEpaZw</guid></item><item><title>Tuberculosis cases in the US rose to their highest levels in more than a dozen years - The Associated Press</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMikwFBVV95cUxORVVUaTdZRVd3TDVtRXBXZ2VaRVI3STNTZTRhQlZsdzIxbnJydlN4REs5Mk9pWWFBcHFXalRoQ0s2Z1ZLMzFzYkM0VzZfd3p5UmxPeVdGeXZickhLTFVZVWNuQkNBbjAzV1FEYmc3RXRpTGh0Z0xrV0N3THdoWHFlVGJ3Y2RzMlZON01nMGVCbUc2aDg?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="LeaderBoardAd-Mobile "&gt;
                                    
                                        
                                            
                                        
                                    
                                &lt;/p&gt;
                            
                            
                                
                                
                                    &lt;div class="RichTextStoryBody RichTextBody"&gt;
                                        &lt;p&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://apnews.com/article/tb-who-tuberculosis-covid-c0fd5cc6542e7f9135833366b71546d2"&gt;Tuberculosis continued to rise&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; again in the U.S. last year, reaching its highest levels in more than a dozen years. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;More than 10,300 cases were reported last year, an 8% increase from 2023 and the highest since 2011, according to preliminary &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://www.cdc.gov/tb-data/2024-provisional/index.html#cdc_report_pub_study_section_2-provisional-data" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;data&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; posted this month by the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Both the number of cases and the rate of infections rose. Rates were up among all age groups, and 34 states reported an increase. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;CDC officials say the rise is the mainly due to international travel and migration. The vast majority of U.S. TB cases are diagnosed in people born in other countries. Other illnesses that weaken the immune system and allow latent TB infections to emerge may also be at play.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Outbreaks in several states have contributed to recent TB trends, including a recent &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://apnews.com/article/tuberculosis-tb-outbreak-kansas-largest-b6b58f4f5461abb430745e3a8e7dc758"&gt;one in the Kansas City, Kansas area&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;. The Kansas TB rate jumped 148% last year, according to the new CDC data. Alaska and Hawaii continue to have the highest case rates.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p class="SovrnAd Advertisement " data-module data-class="sovrn-story-feed" data-delayadinsertion&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tuberculosis is caused by bacteria that usually attack the lungs, and is spread through the air when an infectious person coughs or sneezes. If not treated properly, it can be fatal. In the late 1800s, TB killed one out of every seven people living in the United States and Europe. But the development of antibiotics and public health efforts succeeded in treating infections and tracking down those they infected, leading to cases falling for decades.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The new CDC statistics are not a count of how many people were newly infected, but rather of how many people developed a cough or other symptoms and were diagnosed.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h2&gt;___&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="optimizelyHubpeekId" class="optimizelyHubpeekClass"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Associated Press Health and Science Department receives support from the Howard Hughes Medical Institute’s Science and Educational Media Group and the Robert Wood Johnson Foundation. The AP is solely responsible for all content.&lt;/p&gt;
                                    &lt;/div&gt;
                                
                            

                            
                    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Associated Press</author><pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 21:53:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikwFBVV95cUxORVVUaTdZRVd3TDVtRXBXZ2VaRVI3STNTZTRhQlZsdzIxbnJydlN4REs5Mk9pWWFBcHFXalRoQ0s2Z1ZLMzFzYkM0VzZfd3p5UmxPeVdGeXZickhLTFVZVWNuQkNBbjAzV1FEYmc3RXRpTGh0Z0xrV0N3THdoWHFlVGJ3Y2RzMlZON01nMGVCbUc2aDg</guid></item></channel></rss>