<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>GNews Health</title><link>https://news.google.com/</link><description></description><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>健康编辑与年轻人疾病激增的癌症斗争-每日邮报</title><link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-15310871/health-editor-cancer-surge-young-people-signs.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div itemprop="articleBody"&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The panic hit first. Then came the embarrassment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;After all, I had spent years giving health advice to colleagues, friends and family, convinced I was an expert in so many areas of medicine. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Yet there I was, at my desk as Health Editor at the Daily Mail in &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/new_york/index.html" id="mol-454e28a0-c942-11f0-9d74-9506a24b12fb"&gt;New York City&lt;/a&gt;, being told that I had &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/cancer/index.html" id="mol-4546d5a0-c942-11f0-9d74-9506a24b12fb"&gt;cancer&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;It was especially hard to take because being healthy had become so much a part of my identity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;I trained in martial arts, worked out religiously, tracked everything I ate and, if I'm honest, bragged constantly about it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Friends came to me for health advice: &lt;span class="mol-style-italic"&gt;Should I eat this? Will that give me cancer? What supplements do you take? How do I get abs?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In fact, my unusual eating habits were a running office joke: six boiled eggs for lunch, yoghurt parfaits mixed in giant baking bowls, and my infamous popcorn that would stink out the newsroom every afternoon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;So getting diagnosed with cancer at 29, when I was seemingly in perfect health, felt not only deeply unfair, but a little like some kind of cosmic payback for being so confident in my own good health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;To my utter shock, I was diagnosed with testicular cancer at 29 (author pictured)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;A forced smile barely hides my nerves as I prepare for my first CT scans, which will reveal if the cancer has spread &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;That said, however, the diagnosis didn't come entirely out of nowhere. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The day before, after putting it off for months, I'd finally had an ultrasound on an almond-sized lump in my left testicle.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The scan was meant to take 30 minutes, but dragged on for an hour and a half. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The technician muttered about 'poor visibility' and 'protocol' requiring clear images of every region.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Now I realize what was really happening: she was taking as many images as possible, knowing - or strongly suspecting - it was cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;I didn't get out until 3pm, and assumed I'd hear back in a few days.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But the next morning, at 9.03am exactly, my phone lit up. Most offices open at 9am, I thought, so clearly this was urgent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;I shot out of my chair and raced across the newsroom floor as the person on the phone told me to find a private room and turn my camera on. The doctor needed to speak to me urgently.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;I propped my phone up in front of me and sat awkwardly as the doctor connected and said, 'I'm so sorry - we're fairly confident you've got cancer.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;I trained in martial arts (pictured in my uniform) and worked out multiple times a week - being fit and healthy had become part of my identity &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Pictured: I wear a sheepish look as I wait to hear what stage the cancer has reached&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;As she delivered the hammer blow, I felt utterly numb. I was listening to every word, but they weren't registering. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;It was as if she was describing someone else, maybe one of the hundreds of patients I'd written about, but not me.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Then she added, 'There's good news… and bad news.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The bad news: they were confident it was cancer. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But the doctor told me that if you had to pick a cancer, this is one of the most treatable forms (which didn't feel very reassuring at the time).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But she was right. Testicular cancer has a five-year survival rate above 95 percent - and it doesn't take a health journalist to know how good that is.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The overall five-year survival rate for all cancers is roughly 69 percent, but many types which are increasingly common in young people are far deadlier, such as pancreatic (12 percent) and liver (21 percent).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Testicular cancer is uniquely treatable for a few reasons. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;First, the tumors are extraordinarily sensitive to chemotherapy, which can melt away cancer cells even if the disease has spread to other parts of the body. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;And it usually strikes men in their 20s or 30s, whose bodies handle aggressive treatment well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;In my mind I had prepared to do chemotherapy - after all, the doctor told me there was a 40 percent chance of the disease returning&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Pictured: The joy on my face after learning the cancer was contained to the testicle and I didn't need to have chemo&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Removing the testicle is also fairly straightforward - you're in and out of hospital in hours. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;And because lumps appear early, surgeons often remove the entirety of the cancer, reducing the risk of spread.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Still, I was told I needed surgery immediately.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;After hanging up with my doctor, I was struck by a blizzard of emotions. Looking back, I now recognize it as 10 minutes of sheer panic.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;My eyes filled with tears as visions flashed through my mind of the worst-case scenario: bald, weak, dying young, not fulfilling my ambitions or dreams.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;I tried calling my mom, who was at work, and Googled survival statistics, which calmed me a little.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Then, strangely, something switched in my mind.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;I became intensely practical, with absolute focus on the next appointment, scan or blood test. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;That focus lasted throughout my fight and I haven't been emotional about my cancer since then.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;A lot of that is down to how efficient my treatment plan was. From diagnosis to surgery was less than two weeks - startlingly fast.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;As a Briton whose grandfather had to wait six months to start treatment for stage 3 prostate cancer on the National Health Service, the speed of American healthcare, despite its flaws, felt surreal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;The timing of the cancer was terrible - I'd been due to move apartments. Pictured: I was fresh out of surgery and unable to lift heavy items, so I recruited the help of friends to move a sofa into my new home&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;When I visited my oncologist at Memorial Sloan Kettering - a surreal experience, given I'd spent years writing about the hospital&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Of course, it was reassuring to be treated so quickly. But the worst part of a cancer diagnosis is one that nobody talks about: when the doctor says 'you have cancer,' you still don't know your chance of survival.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Not until they figure out how big the tumor is, whether it has spread to nearby lymph nodes or organs and exactly what type of cancer it is. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Only then can doctors give an accurate picture of your outlook and the treatment you'll need.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;My blood tests came back the next day: no tumor markers. A feeling of shattering relief.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;CT scans followed a few days later - chest, abdomen, pelvis - to see if it had spread.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;It was a testament to the speed of the US health system that, later that day, I received the results: negative again. Another hurdle cleared.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Only after surgery could they confirm whether it was stage 1 - easily treatable, no chemotherapy required. It was looking good.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Based on the negative blood tests, scans and size of the tumor, my doctors had been confident I had a single 'seminoma,' a slow-growing tumor that develops over years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Instead, they found two tumors: one seminoma and one embryonal carcinoma - a far more aggressive type that can spread in weeks or months. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Pictured: A post-surgery thumbs up. The moment I woke from the operation, my years-long back pain was gone. It never returned&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;When I go out, I now try to stick to a two-drink max rule. The 'alcohol guilt' after cancer has been one of many surprises post-diagnosis &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;There were also early signs cancer cells had started migrating toward the bloodstream. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Tiny cells may have leaked into the blood which can, over time, raise the risk of growing new tumors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;When I visited my oncologist at Memorial Sloan Kettering - a surreal experience, given I'd spent years writing about the hospital - he told me plainly that with this combination, I had about a 40 percent chance of the cancer returning.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;To my surprise, despite the risk, my doctors advised against chemotherapy, even though it would reduce the risk to just one to three percent. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;As they told me, doctors are now rethinking the old blanket-chemo approach because the treatment is brutal - hospitalizations, infections, sepsis, even a small risk of secondary cancers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;For young, otherwise healthy patients, they said it was sometimes worth playing the odds. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;I was skeptical. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;It was tempting to just get it over with, to never have to worry about the cancer again, and I'd mentally prepared myself for chemo. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;I sought a second opinion at Mount Sinai. To my surprise, the oncologist there also recommended surveillance only. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;With two of the world's top cancer doctors in agreement, I felt I needed to be humble and listen. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;And as vain as it sounds, what unsettled me most was the thought of losing my hair.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The chemotherapy used for testicular cancer almost guarantees hair loss - even eyebrows. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;It's a brutal prospect, though many would feel it's a price worth paying for survival.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;&lt;p class="clear"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;I am now closely monitored with blood tests, scans and X-rays every few months. If the cancer returns, I'll need chemo. Pictured: Me at my latest checkup in November 2025 (left) and returning to work in September 2025 (right)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;My mindset is: If it can happen to me, it can happen to anyone. I now urge all my male friends to check for lumps regularly and stay vigilant&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;So what's the next step?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;I am now closely monitored with blood tests, scans and X-rays every few months. If it returns, I'll need chemo.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The cancer also affected my hormones.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;My testosterone crashed to the level of a 70-year-old, causing overwhelming fatigue.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;I now inject medication three times a week and feel stronger all the time. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;After two months off training, I'm back to working out five times per week, including three martial arts sessions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;While I'm eating the same, something curious has happened with my weight.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;I've shot up more than 10lbs in three months without gaining much, if any, new fat - almost certainly the result of my testosterone bouncing back.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;I now drink far less alcohol, and when I do, I stick to a two-drink maximum.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;One of the more surprising psychological changes is the guilt I feel after drinking.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Knowing alcohol is a class 1 carcinogen - and that I'm in a critical period where my cancer could return - it just feels reckless.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;By reading this, you know I haven't kept my cancer a secret. I decided long ago I wanted to be an advocate. My mindset is: If it can happen to me, it can happen to anyone.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;I now urge all my male friends to check their testicles regularly and stay vigilant.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Curiously, my weight has shot up 10lbs since returning to work and exercise - almost certainly a result of my testosterone bouncing back &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Pictured: On vacation in October 2025, trying to reclaim what I can of the summer I missed&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;I mentioned embarrassment I felt when I received the diagnosis. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Well, the second wave of it hit when I realized my symptoms had been there all along.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Two major health issues I'd battled for years - excruciating back pain and chronic fatigue - were almost certainly caused by the tumor.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;For two years, I'd suffered pain I attributed to slipped discs and jiu-jitsu. On surgery morning, I could barely walk, yet the moment I woke from surgery, the pain was gone. It never returned.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Doctors now think the tumor caused inflammation that radiated through my pelvis, irritating the nerves around my discs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;I also spent years chronically exhausted, no matter how much I slept. I blamed the move to America, stress and long hours, despite fatigue being one of the most common symptoms of cancer that shows itself before a diagnosis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Yet I, the person leading the Daily Mail's coverage of cancers in young people, had somehow missed my own. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;I initially thought my body had failed me, but perhaps it was my mind that had failed to listen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Testicular cancer appears to be one of those genetic lottery diseases - I was probably born with a defect in the cells that form the testicles, called germ cells.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;These are the cells that eventually develop into sperm, but if they go awry during development, they can later turn cancerous.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;We still don't fully understand what sparks the cancerous change, but we know testicular cancer is rising among young men.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Studies show its incidence has nearly doubled in the past 40 years in American men aged 20 to 34. It is now the most common form of cancer for men under 35.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;So, I urge anyone who notices anything unusual, no matter how small, to get it checked. It could save your life - I'm hoping it's saved mine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
            

            
            
            
            
            &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Daily Mail</author><pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 22:10:40 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipAFBVV95cUxQS2xoMDdRajFaMk0wVm5MWENZR0dycWdCN1VYQ2tPeXZreDBOeW10TjZzSThEWjdiTk1aSVhxaFJEbG1KSzM4M0FMWE5aR0cwZDFJTzVLRHMyQlBRbnh3TnNJQWNjMnQxQ184NGoxQlI3TFNEQnJrTEFrNHZzdGdDSXJLMmg0Y21OSWQwbTZHWXBzYXVxWkJYOFZpdVZ4NHhxNk1NOA</guid></item><item><title>皮肤科医生对新的头皮狂热给予侧视-新闻</title><link>https://www.newser.com/story/379332/were-spending-hundreds-to-take-care-of-our-scalps.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="divStoryBodyAbove"&gt;
                                
                                    &lt;span id="StoryTextTop"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
                                
                                
                                
                                    &lt;p class="storyParagraph"&gt;
                                        A rising beauty trend has Americans massaging their scalps and flocking to high-end head spas—sometimes for hundreds of dollars a session—all in pursuit of healthier hair, even if dermatologists aren't convinced most people need the help, per the &lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2025/11/20/style/scalp-care-beauty-trends-2025.html"&gt;&lt;em&gt;New York Times&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. The scalp has emerged as the latest focus of the beauty world, and the trend, fueled by TikTok and other social media, has seen a significant spike in interest: According to market insights company Spate, online searches and posts about "scalp serum" jumped 77% over the past year, while "scalp massagers" and "scalp treatment" also saw notable increases.
                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                    
                                
                                
                            &lt;/div&gt;

                            
                            
                            
                            
                            

                            &lt;div id="divStoryBodyBelow"&gt;
                                
                                    &lt;p class="storyParagraph"&gt;
                                        Influencers are documenting their intensive scalp routines—sometimes involving hours of massage or the use of expensive serums—and sharing with hundreds of thousands of followers, helping to drive the trend. Many major hair-care brands, from drugstore staples to high-end labels, have launched scalp-focused products. Beyonce's Cecred brand famously sells out of its Restoring Hair &amp;amp; Edge Drops serum; it reportedly moved one bottle every 16 seconds from last November through July.
                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                

                                
                                    &lt;p class="storyParagraph"&gt;
                                        While some dermatologists acknowledge that scalp care can improve hair health, they caution that elaborate routines aren't necessary for most people. "If you're not having a problem, there shouldn't be this huge drive to have to get all this stuff to put on your scalp," says Maryanne Senna, director of the Hair Loss Center of Excellence at Lahey Hospital &amp;amp; Medical Center.
                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                

                                
                                
                                
                                

                                
                                    &lt;p class="storyParagraph"&gt;
                                        Still, the allure of scalp care persists, with head spas—especially those offering microscopic analysis of hair follicles and customized treatments—drawing crowds in cities like New York and Los Angeles. Prices for these treatments range widely, with some sessions costing upward of $300. Even if they're not terribly helpful for most people, it's not likely you'll hurt yourself in any way by getting a scalp massage or similar treatment. "The only real danger is to a person's wallet," Senna tells the &lt;em&gt;Times&lt;/em&gt;. Meanwhile, &lt;a href="https://www.womenshealthmag.com/beauty/a69073403/scalp-steaming-benefits/"&gt;some dermatologists recommend&lt;/a&gt; "scalp steaming," while &lt;a href="https://www.today.com/shop/scalp-care-guide-t289360"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Today&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; notes the two most important things you can do for your scalp: Keep it clean and protected from the sun.
                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                

                                



                            &lt;/div&gt;
                        &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Newser</author><pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 18:10:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilAFBVV95cUxOWU5JZmVxOGpOQlYxbE9PNG1vQmlqRFBNZ0pyMW1mbV81d01lX2RrNloyNU05ZHV5V0xpUU8xd3BaVjFfV1kwbzBjdDRDZ0s5NUtBMUVRT2VvOGRNN1Y2UU82TWxZbTBXMFlzN3p1dTU0WGQ3cDRRSTF3VzNqTXp5U2FfR0F1cDZCTDNHeWZDcFhuV2gz</guid></item><item><title>为什么美国人在20世纪80年代突然变胖？ - Daily Kos</title><link>https://www.dailykos.com/stories/2025/11/30/2356160/-Why-Did-Americans-Suddenly-Get-Fat-in-the-1980s</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="story__text"&gt;
          &lt;h2&gt;The Obesity Epidemic: What Really Happened in the 1980s&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You've seen the arguments. Seed oils are poison. Sugar is the devil. Fast food destroyed America. The government ruined everything. Or maybe it's all Big Pharma's fault.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Everyone's got a villain. Everyone's wrong.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The truth? Multiple things broke at once. Around 1980, several massive changes hit simultaneously, and we're still living with the consequences.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;The Data Doesn't Lie&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;figure class="image-captioned align-right"&gt;&lt;img alt="obesity_trends_by_age_sex.png" src="https://cdn.prod.dailykos.com/images/1503733/large/obesity_trends_by_age_sex.png?1764524981" title="obesity_trends_by_age_sex.png"&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/nchs/nhanes/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;NHANES surveys&lt;/a&gt; show something remarkable: obesity rates were relatively flat for decades, then suddenly bent upward between 1976–1980. Not a gradual drift—a sharp inflection point. Adult obesity jumped from roughly 15% to over 30% in just two decades.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That's not normal. That's not genetics. That's environmental.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;What Actually Changed&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;The Government Picked the Wrong Enemy&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In 1977, the &lt;a href="https://www.dietaryguidelines.gov/about-dietary-guidelines/history-dietary-guidelines" target="_blank"&gt;McGovern Committee&lt;/a&gt; told Americans to slash fat intake to 30% of calories and replace it with carbohydrates. Three years later, the first official Dietary Guidelines made it policy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The food industry listened. Boy, did they listen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Suddenly, everything was "low-fat." Cookies, yogurt, salad dressing, frozen dinners. But fat makes food taste good, so manufacturers replaced it with something else: sugar. Lots of sugar. And refined starches.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The result? Hyper-processed, hyper-palatable foods that were technically "low-fat" but absolutely terrible for metabolic health.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;High-Fructose Corn Syrup Went Supernova&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://ajcn.nutrition.org/article/S0002-9165(22)03883-7/fulltext" target="_blank"&gt;HFCS consumption increased roughly 1,000% between 1970 and 1990&lt;/a&gt;. It was cheap, stable, and sweeter than regular sugar. Food manufacturers dumped it into everything—soda, bread, ketchup, crackers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Total added sugar intake skyrocketed. We didn't peak until around 2000, but the damage was already done by the mid-1980s.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Portions Exploded&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.ers.usda.gov/data-products/food-availability-per-capita-data-system/" target="_blank"&gt;USDA data show&lt;/a&gt; average calorie intake rose 200–300 calories per day from the late 1970s to early 2000s. That's an extra meal's worth of energy, every single day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;McDonald's didn't introduce Super Size until the 1990s, but portions were already growing throughout the 1980s. Bigger sodas. Bigger burgers. Bigger everything.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Grain-based desserts, soft drinks, and fast food drove most of the increase.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;We Stopped Moving&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The shift from manual labor to desk jobs accelerated through the 1960s–1980s. More people drove everywhere. Fewer people walked or biked.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then came home computers and video games. Television watching was already high, but the 1980s added new reasons to sit still.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kids especially. Recess got shorter. PE programs got cut. Screen time went up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Smoking Declined (Yes, This Matters)&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Adult smoking rates &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/nchs/hus/topics/tobacco-use.htm" target="_blank" title=""&gt;dropped from 42% in 1965 to 25% by the early 1990s&lt;/a&gt;. That's overwhelmingly good news—smoking kills.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But quitting typically adds 4–5 kg. At the population level, that contributed roughly 1–2 percentage points to obesity prevalence. Not the main driver, but not nothing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Everything Else&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Restaurant eating increased. Ultra-processed foods were engineered to maximize consumption. Sleep patterns changed. Stress increased.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some researchers point to endocrine disruptors, though evidence for the 1980s timeframe remains speculative.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;The Bottom Line&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.aeaweb.org/articles?id=10.1257/089533003769204371" target="_blank"&gt;Peer-reviewed analyses&lt;/a&gt; attribute roughly 50–70% of the calorie increase to greater intake of refined grains, added sugars, and added fats (mostly seed oils used in processed and restaurant food). The rest comes from reduced physical activity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It wasn't &lt;em&gt;just&lt;/em&gt; seed oils. It wasn't &lt;em&gt;just&lt;/em&gt; sugar. It wasn't &lt;em&gt;just&lt;/em&gt; the government or &lt;em&gt;just&lt;/em&gt; fast food.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was all of it. At once.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The 1980s created a perfect storm: official dietary policy that backfired spectacularly, cheap hyper-palatable processed foods, massive portion increases, and a simultaneous collapse in physical activity. The effect was rapid and population-wide.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Why This Matters Now&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Understanding what actually happened matters because the simplistic answers—ban seed oils, ban sugar, ban carbs—miss the point.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The food environment changed fundamentally. We made calories cheaper, more available, more rewarding, and easier to overconsume. We built cities around cars instead of walking. We replaced recess with standardized tests.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fixing this requires addressing multiple systems simultaneously. Better food policy. Better urban design. Better food labeling. Better education about ultra-processed foods.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One villain makes for better social media engagement. But multiple causes make for better solutions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The 1980s broke something. We can't fix it by picking just one scapegoat.&lt;/p&gt;





&lt;p class="is-empty-p"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



        &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Daily Kos</author><pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 17:55:57 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiogFBVV95cUxOMGlKX0NYUFBuVUl3ZkVMUE56eG1tU1FXSUd4eFJlbUs0RUpseVJkdFBmYmw2Q211V1FzcklLeHNMeEhjQ1BhYXdHQVZXVmlfbDJNLWpKbDJmUFhVNXpTdnVjT3V2TXBLUU5MUlExTWlwUGRGZDhNdGFUVURicU9qbWZvRHdua0duQTJVWjNYcFpYN3dpV05oZFFQNjBwZzRjbnc</guid></item><item><title>自然降低胆固醇：每天吃黑小茴香种子，获得惊人的好处-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/lower-your-cholesterol-naturally-eat-black-cumin-seed-daily-for-surprising-benefits/articleshow/125676409.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;p&gt;For generations, black cumin seed has been sprinkled into breads, curries and traditional remedies, a quiet staple with an ancient reputation. Now emerging scientific evidence is shedding new light on its potential health benefits. A Japanese study published in &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/fsn3.70888" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;Food Science and Nutrition&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; suggests that eating black cumin seed daily could meaningfully lower cholesterol and even support weight loss, offering a natural route to better heart health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="5"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="6"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;br&gt;Black cumin seed: An age-old spice to lower cholesterol&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="7"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Black cumin seed, also known as Nigella sativa or kalonji, has long been valued in Middle Eastern and South Asian households for its warm, peppery bite. But the new research gives its traditional reputation a solid scientific foundation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="11"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="lOvcW vdo_embedd"&gt;&lt;div class="k7lcu"&gt;&lt;p class="efT4r"&gt;What Your Cholesterol Report Is Hiding — The Truth That Could Save Your Heart | Dr Vinayak Agarwal&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="13"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the study, adults who took a small daily dose of black cumin seed powder for eight weeks saw notable improvements in several key markers: LDL, or bad cholesterol, dropped, HDL, or good cholesterol, rose and overall lipid profiles shifted in a healthier direction.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="15"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Meanwhile, those in the control group, who made no changes to their diets, saw no improvement at all.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="17"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Perhaps the most intriguing part of the findings is that some participants lost weight during the trial. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Laboratory tests in the same study showed that black cumin seed extract slowed the formation of fat cells, hinting at an underlying anti-adipogenic effect.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="21"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; This dual benefit, supporting heart health while helping regulate body fat, is rare for such a simple dietary addition. It is one reason researchers believe black cumin could serve as a functional food in preventing lifestyle-related diseases, including obesity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="24"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="25"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;How to use black cumin seed daily&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="26"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to the study, even a teaspoon of black cumin seed powder a day was enough to produce measurable health benefits. For everyday use, the spice can be taken in several easy forms: mixed into warm water in the morning, stirred into yoghurt or smoothies, added to dal and vegetable dishes or sprinkled over salads.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="28"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; The simplest and often recommended option is to take a teaspoon of black cumin seed powder in warm water first thing in the morning. But you can just as easily mix it into yoghurt, smoothies or your daily meals. The key is taking it consistently.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="30"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="31"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="32"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="em" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Note: The information provided in this article is for educational purposes only and is not intended as medical advice. Always consult with a qualified healthcare professional before starting any new medication or treatment and before changing your diet or supplement regimen.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 17:11:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikAJBVV95cUxOWlI0T3pJTWs0WE4xdjlPcHNzMFl3bEYtak1pcTJzbXREZkFZMUFib1JZdGk4X2EyUnFLU09zVGx3eElySjBkLVQ0cXdnNHFPb0hhNmFockROSzdaNkpJZHBGV1JRVXBxQXc0Qk5lNG05VDZ1LTJ4STZFY1k3TExxd1BtNG00dUhfWDF6Vm13eFhocno4Z2ZzaTgtTXAyNF9iV1BWM28xUjdXeHVRYk83Q2RkeGdRSWh1UW9uZjlHZDdMQzgzUm02bGkybDlyZGZ3dFBrT1Z6THlLYzZLSzNER0FlTGNkaUhpVDBGNW1LSTNvZ1ViNXNWMHo2X2pvdi13TFEyS1U1cDZwajFoZm5xWQ</guid></item><item><title>Shelli经常头晕。医生发现她的大脑“脱落” -每日邮报</title><link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-15329481/doctors-dismissed-symptoms-brain-health-chiari-malformation.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div itemprop="articleBody"&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;A teacher whose symptoms were repeatedly dismissed by doctors actually had a serious neurological disorder: one she describes as feeling like her brain was 'falling out' of her head.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Shelli Gunnoe, 26, from South Carolina, was diagnosed with a Chiari malformation this year after more than a decade of confusing symptoms. Early on, doctors told her that issues like laughter-triggered headaches were nothing to worry about. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But Chiari malformation, which is a rare condition impacting around 300,000 Americans, or one in 1,000, causes the lower part of the brain to push down into the spinal canal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;This pressure, which disrupts nerves and the normal flow of cerebrospinal fluid, can cause a wide variety of symptoms, including headaches that worsen with straining, neck pain, balance issues and, in severe cases, coordination or vision problems.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;For Gunnoe, uncovering the cause of her symptoms took more than 14 years. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;As years went on, she began to experience tingling in her arms and fingers, bouts of nausea, heat intolerance and episodes in which her vision would dim. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;She recalled one incident at work when she became so dizzy and overwhelmed by heat that she collapsed in a restroom, saying she was 'unable to get up' until her fiancé arrived to take her home. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;That crisis finally led to a neurology referral and the MRI that revealed a 4mm Chiari malformation. Even then, &lt;a class="" rel="nofollow noreferrer noopener" target="_blank" href="https://www.instagram.com/onbrandbyshelli/"&gt;doctors initially said &lt;/a&gt;surgery wasn't needed. But Gunnoe's symptoms kept worsening, as simple movements like bending or standing provoked dizziness or instability. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Shelli Gunnoe, 26, from South Carolina, was diagnosed with a Chiari malformation after more than a decade of confusing symptoms&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    
    
    &lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;A follow-up MRI complicated matters further, as a neurologist suggested her symptoms more closely resembled pseudotumor cerebri, a condition where pressure inside the skull rises abnormally. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;This, along with enlarged brain ventricles (a network of fluid-filled cavities within the brain that produce, contain and circulate cerebrospinal fluid) and her earlier diagnosis of hydrocephalus, (a condition when there is too much fluid in the brain, causing swelling and pressure) hinted at a deeper issue. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Deep down, I knew something wasn't adding up,' she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Doctors now believe some of her symptoms may trace all the way back to birth. Chiari malformation is usually present at birth (congenital), although symptoms may not appear until childhood or adulthood.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Gunnoe was delivered by emergency C-section because she was breech, 'upright with my head positioned in my mother's rib cage,' she explained. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;She inhaled a large amount of amniotic fluid and initially needed NICU care. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Although her parents hoped for a routine infancy afterward, she soon required a hip brace for developmental support. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;She was also 'extremely irritable and only soothed by being held,' and her parents worried her head looked unusually large. Despite their concerns, a neurologist dismissed the issue at the time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Years later, in 2009, Gunnoe was taken to hospital for chronic migraines. CT and MRI scans revealed mild hydrocephalus, and she was treated with medication. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Early on, doctors told Gunnoe that issues like laughter-triggered headaches were nothing to worry about&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;That crisis finally led to a neurology referral and the MRI that revealed a 4mm Chiari malformation, pictured here&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Chiari malformation, which is a rare condition impacting around 300,000 Americans, causes the lower part of the brain to push down into the spinal canal&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Throughout childhood and her teen years she fainted often and lived with intense fatigue and headaches. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Doctors kept telling me it was my weight,' she said. But after losing 50lbs, the symptoms persisted. In January 2022, immediately after standing up from a bike in a cycling class, she fainted again.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Her symptoms escalated in the years that followed: blurry vision, vertigo, crushing fatigue, and mornings when she felt 'frozen and unable to wake.' &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;She described episodes that 'didn't feel normal for someone my age.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;When she finally received a clear diagnosis of Chiari malformation in November 2024, she felt both 'relieved, but frustrated.' &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;A neurologist used a skull model to show how her cerebellar tonsils were being pulled downward into the opening at the base of her skull. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'He explained that mine are pushed down further than they should be, slipping through the opening where the spinal cord runs,' she said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Because they're squeezed into a space that's too tight, they press on my spinal cord and disrupt the flow of cerebrospinal fluid.' &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;When that flow is slowed or blocked, she added, 'it irritates the nerves and causes many of the symptoms I've been dealing with.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Gunnoe was delivered by emergency C-section because she was breech, 'upright with my head positioned in my mother's rib cage,' she explained&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Throughout childhood and her teen years, Gunnoe fainted often and lived with intense fatigue and headaches&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;For now, Gunnoe is being closely monitored while her neurologist determines the best course of action. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Because of my combination of Chiari, hydrocephalus history, enlarged ventricles, and possible pseudotumor, my case is still being evaluated,' she said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;While waiting, she manages her symptoms through pacing, careful activity choices and prioritizing rest and hydration. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'I'm still very much in the 'watch and wait' stage,' she added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Despite the uncertainty, she tries to live fully. She still experiences dizziness when standing, visual disturbances, sensory overload and difficulty tolerating certain movements. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Simple tasks, looking upward, bending down or standing too quickly, can trigger symptoms instantly. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Even so, she continues teaching full-time, creates online content and models, and is training, with thoughtful modifications, in hopes of participating in the Hyrox race, a global, indoor fitness competition that combines eight 0.62m runs with eight different functional fitness workout stations. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'It's a strange balance,' she said, 'acknowledging the reality of a neurological condition while refusing to let it shrink my goals or identity.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Her symptoms escalated in the years that followed: blurry vision, vertigo, crushing fatigue, and mornings when she felt 'frozen and unable to wake'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Despite the uncertainty, Gunnoe tries to live fully. She is hopeful of participating in the Hyrox race: a global, indoor fitness competition that combines eight 1km runs with eight different functional fitness workout stations&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Gunnoe hopes her story encourages others not to ignore their symptoms or allow them to be dismissed. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Invisible illnesses don't always look dramatic,' she said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'People see me lifting weights, teaching, modelling, smiling online, and they don't see the hours I spend navigating dizziness, pressure or exhaustion behind the scenes.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;She wants to speak especially to women who feel overlooked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;She said: 'You can advocate for yourself. You can ask for second opinions. And you can still chase big dreams while living with something hard.' &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Her life, she insists, remains 'full, meaningful and ambitious, not because my neurological issues disappeared, but because I've learned to move with them while still moving forward.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
            

            
            
            
            
            &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Daily Mail</author><pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 16:41:08 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMitwFBVV95cUxNNGJwcjhLYTh0RXp3ejF2RzhlbTBXVElFM01pZDlwNy1uNGFiaG40bE1WMXdNU2VkdUlTZDRIOEZwQzc4aVVpaGtkOHl6ZWRwb3Q5Vk5DYkxUQkNSQ2FjWGVBTl8xNE81VjNaVWtKR3Z4Sm4zQ0ZIOThZNWV1VWVYRWxOV3J3ZzB3d3UzZkt1UmJhT2EtWmJKbkxndUJqT0NxQ1h3YXJWcWVPWTJmV2hvc3V6S2xGVGc</guid></item><item><title>医生揭示了您可能体内有寄生虫的5个警告信号-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/doctor-reveals-5-warning-signs-you-may-have-parasites-in-your-body/articleshow/125675180.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Parasites are far more common than most people realize, yet their symptoms are often subtle and easily misinterpreted as ordinary digestive issues, stress-related changes, or nutritional problems. When we talk about “parasites” in this context, we are mainly referring to intestinal parasites; organisms that live inside the digestive tract. Some parasites feed on nutrients, others irritate the intestinal lining, and some feed on blood and can cause anemia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="3"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="5"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Because these infections vary widely in severity, the symptoms they cause can be equally diverse and often nonspecific. Still, certain patterns have stronger scientific backing. In a recent &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/shorts/8AjFD2mM9mc" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;video&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, popular health educator Dr. Eric Berg, shared 5 symptoms that may signal the presence of parasites in the body, and two natural remedies that can help get rid of them. Below we explore. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="12"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="lOvcW vdo_embedd"&gt;&lt;div class="k7lcu"&gt;&lt;p class="efT4r"&gt;How Lifestyle Choices Can Increase Your Risk of Stomach Cancer&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="14"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;How dangerous are parasites&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="16"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="17"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://medlineplus.gov/ency/article/000629.htm" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;Parasite infections &lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;occur when parasites enter the body and begin living, reproducing, or feeding inside you. This usually happens through contaminated food, water, soil, insect bites, poor hygiene, or contact with infected animals/humans. Parasitic infections are not trivial; they can translate into serious health burdens, especially if recurrent or untreated. Parasites can cause damage in multiple ways:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="20"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some physically attach to the intestinal wall (or other organs), feed on blood or nutrients, and thereby deprive the host of essential nutrients. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="23"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some disturb the&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/books/NBK8191/" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt; intestinal lining&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; and interfere with absorption of nutrients, resulting in malnutrition even if diet is adequate. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="27"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chronic infections can trigger inflammation (in gut, liver, bladder, or other organs), cause tissue damage (e.g., scarring, fibrosis, cyst formation), or even lead parasites to migrate to and damage distant organs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="29"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;In heavy or uncontrolled infestations, especially in people with weak immunity, parasites can cause life‑threatening complications.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="32"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Five warning signs you may have parasites&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="34"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="35"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="37"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;1. Unexplained sugar cravings&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="39"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to Dr. Berg, unexplained sugar cravings, especially for dairy, is a sign of parasites. Dr. Berg adds, “Parasites love sugar, especially milk sugar. If you crave that, you could have parasites.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="41"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;2. Grinding teeth at night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="43"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Night-time teeth grinding may also be connected to parasitic stress on the nervous system.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="45"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Parasites can release toxins that irritate the gut–brain axis, triggering restlessness, tension, and involuntary muscle activity during sleep.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="48"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;3. Itchy skin at night (especially in private parts) &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="50"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Night-time itching around the anal or genital area is one of the classic signs of parasites such as pinworms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="52"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Parasites tend to be more active at night, which is why symptoms often intensify when you lie down to sleep.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="54"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;4. Extreme bloating after eating- despite what you eat&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="56"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you experience constant bloating or gas regardless of the meal, parasites may be interfering with digestion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="58"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many of them reside in the small intestine, just below the stomach, where they:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="60"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;- ferment food, producing gas&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="62"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;- cause inflammation&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="64"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;- steal essential nutrients&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="66"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;This can leave you feeling overfull, heavy, or distended after even small meals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="69"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;5. Iron deficient anemia&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="71"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Certain parasites feed directly on blood or damage the intestinal lining, reducing iron absorption.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="73"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Over time, this can lead to:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="75"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;- chronic fatigue&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="77"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;- pale skin&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="79"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;- weakness&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="81"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;- low stamina&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="83"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr. Berg emphasizes that parasites can literally “steal your iron,” causing anemia in otherwise healthy individuals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="85"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;How parasites are actually diagnosed&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="87"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Parasitic infections are best confirmed through laboratory testing, since symptoms alone can be misleading and often overlap with other digestive or nutritional problems. The most common method is a stool examination, where a lab looks for parasite eggs, larvae, or cysts under a microscope. In many modern labs, more advanced stool antigen tests and PCR panels are used to detect parasites with higher accuracy. These diagnostic methods allow doctors to pinpoint the exact parasite and offer appropriate treatment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="89"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="em" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Disclaimer: This article is for informational purposes only and does not substitute for professional medical advice. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="91"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 16:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi-gFBVV95cUxPdVBxZ3NVZkhlS0U2M193UVMyZm95NVhCVk5NSzMwYTgzSndYbHJkdVBFWFJOU0tyd1hSN0Zpa3dYRjFTMDRFbnhIRXlpLWYzTkJ4OWEwRWZTX3VwUlo3YzUwYzc3c25DS015QUI0WW8zMEtVSWNHLTNnaDdEQklmVmJXdXozc2NPNndUSEhFb3g3T1ZYWEQ1YjdTMWpKcVBhTllmalhadk1aaWs4T0RFMFN3R2dDWUJ2aWVKQlYwWUYyM3VPckVzb2ltS2JlSk9UaDFFdkI5MnYzZmVwc1pmZ24tcVhyVGJhcF9XMUNBQTliMkhMOFV6Q2pR</guid></item><item><title>这种常见的零食在16周的试验中增强了记忆力和脑血管功能- PsyPost</title><link>https://www.psypost.org/this-common-snack-enhanced-memory-and-brain-vascular-function-in-a-16-week-trial/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="content-inner "&gt;&lt;p&gt;A new study in &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.clnu.2025.10.020" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Clinical Nutrition&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; provides evidence that the regular consumption of unsalted, skin-roasted peanuts may enhance brain vascular function and memory in older adults. The research indicates that eating a moderate daily amount of peanuts improves blood flow to specific regions of the brain and aids in the retention of verbal information.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As individuals age, the vascular system in the brain often undergoes changes that can reduce the efficiency of blood flow. This reduction in cerebral blood flow is a known physiological marker associated with cognitive decline and neurodegenerative conditions such as dementia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Because the delivery of oxygen and nutrients is vital for maintaining neuronal health, researchers have focused on identifying modifiable lifestyle factors that can support vascular function. Diet is considered a significant factor in this regard.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While peanuts are botanically classified as legumes rather than tree nuts, they share a comparable nutritional profile. They are dense in protein, unsaturated fatty acids, and fiber. The researchers, led by Peter J. Joris and Lucia Kerkhof, initiated this study to investigate whether peanuts specifically could offer neuroprotective benefits similar to those observed with tree nuts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A primary motivation for the trial was the high content of L-arginine found in peanuts. L-arginine is an amino acid that serves as a precursor for the synthesis of nitric oxide, a molecule essential for relaxing blood vessels and regulating blood flow.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Additionally, the study focused on skin-roasted peanuts because the peanut skin is rich in bioactive compounds, including polyphenols like resveratrol, which have antioxidant properties that may further support vascular health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The number of people who suffer from age-related cognitive decline or are diagnosed with dementia is increasing rapidly. Currently, dementia is ranked as the 7th leading cause of death worldwide according to the World Health Organization,” said Joris, an associate professor at the Institute of Nutrition and Translational Research in Metabolism (NUTRIM) at Maastricht University.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“As researchers studying nutrition and brain health, we are very interested in how the food we consume can support healthy aging. Peanuts are widely consumed, affordable, and nutrient-dense, yet relatively little was known about their specific effects on the brain.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Earlier work from our group showed that mixed nuts can improve memory and blood flow in the brain in older adults. Adequate blood flow in the brain is important for the delivery of oxygen and nutrients to the brain cells. Without enough oxygen and nutrients, the highly metabolically active brain cannot function properly, and key functions like memory can be affected.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“In this study, we sought to determine whether peanuts, which are botanically classified as legumes rather than nuts, also exert beneficial effects on brain health,” Joris explained.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To test the effects of peanut consumption, the investigators designed a randomized, single-blind, controlled crossover trial. This study design allowed each participant to serve as their own control, reducing variability caused by individual differences.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The research team recruited 31 healthy older adults ranging in age from 60 to 75 years. The participants included both men and women with body mass indexes between 20 and 35 kg/m ². Individuals were excluded if they had a history of cardiovascular disease, diabetes, peanut allergies, or if they were current smokers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study consisted of two 16-week periods separated by an eight-week washout phase. During the intervention period, participants consumed 60 grams of unsalted, skin-roasted peanuts daily. This portion size is approximately equivalent to two servings or two handfuls.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The peanuts were of the runner variety and were eaten with the skins intact. Participants were instructed to incorporate the peanuts into their regular diet but were not permitted to heat or crush them, as this might alter their nutritional properties. During the control period, participants refrained from eating peanuts and avoided other nut-based products to ensure a clear comparison.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The primary measure for the study was cerebral blood flow, assessed using a non-invasive imaging technique called pseudo-continuous arterial spin labeling magnetic resonance imaging. This advanced method allows researchers to quantify the amount of blood reaching brain tissue without the use of radiation or contrast dyes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Secondary outcomes included cognitive performance, which was evaluated using the Cambridge Neuropsychological Test Automated Battery, a series of computerized tests designed to measure memory, psychomotor speed, and executive function. The researchers also monitored blood pressure and gathered data on dietary intake through food frequency questionnaires.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The imaging results revealed a statistically significant improvement in brain vascular responsiveness following the peanut intervention. Global cerebral blood flow increased by 3.6 percent compared to the control period.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When the analysis focused specifically on gray matter, which contains the cell bodies of the brain’s neurons, the increase in blood flow was 4.5 percent. The researchers observed regional improvements as well. Blood flow increased by 6.6 percent in the frontal lobes and 4.9 percent in the temporal lobes. These areas of the brain are intimately involved in processing memories, language, and executive control.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“We were intrigued to see improvements not only in specific brain regions, but also at the whole-brain level,” Joris told PsyPost. “That indicates a more widespread effect on brain vascular function than what we observed in earlier studies.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In parallel with the physiological changes, the researchers identified improvements in cognitive function. Participants demonstrated a 5.8 percent increase in verbal memory performance. This was measured by a delayed recall task where participants were asked to identify words they had seen on a list twenty minutes earlier. Those who had consumed the peanuts were able to correctly recognize more words than they did during the control period.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Our results suggest that eating unsalted, skin-roasted peanuts every day can support brain health as we age,” Joris said. “After 16 weeks, participants showed better brain blood flow and improved memory.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While memory improved, the study did not find significant changes in executive function or psychomotor speed. There was a slight increase in reaction latency during one of the multitasking tests, which the authors suggest might reflect a trade-off where participants prioritized accuracy over speed, although this particular finding requires further verification.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Beyond brain health, the intervention appeared to benefit cardiovascular metrics. Systolic blood pressure, the top number in a blood pressure reading, decreased by an average of 5 mmHg during the peanut consumption phase. Pulse pressure, which represents the difference between systolic and diastolic blood pressure, decreased by 4 mmHg. These reductions are relevant for older adults, as elevated blood pressure is a risk factor for both cardiovascular disease and cognitive impairment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dietary analysis confirmed that during the peanut intervention, participants had higher intakes of total fat, monounsaturated fatty acids, and fiber, while their carbohydrate intake was lower.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Despite the addition of approximately 340 calories per day from the peanuts, body weight remained generally stable across the study population, though there was a minor interaction effect depending on the order in which the participants completed the intervention and control phases. This suggests that participants may have naturally adjusted their intake of other foods to compensate for the added peanuts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study has several limitations that provide context for the findings. Due to the nature of the dietary intervention, it was not possible to blind the participants to the fact that they were eating peanuts. This awareness could potentially influence their behavior or self-reported data, although the researchers analyzing the MRI and cognitive data remained blinded to the treatment conditions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Additionally, while the results show a clear association between peanut consumption and improved vascular function, the specific biological mechanism remains to be fully elucidated. It is not yet known if the effects are driven primarily by L-arginine, the phenolic compounds in the skins, the fatty acid profile, or a synergistic combination of these nutrients.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The research was funded by The Peanut Institute Foundation. The authors state that the funding body had no role in the design of the study, the collection and analysis of data, or the decision to publish the results. The authors declared no conflicts of interest.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Future research directions include investigating whether different forms of peanut products offer similar benefits. The investigators also aim to explore the dose-response relationship to determine if smaller amounts of peanuts could yield comparable results.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“We would like to examine whether different peanut preparations, such as peanut butter, produce similar effects,” Joris said. “In addition, we seek to clarify which peanut components may underlie the observed benefits. To this end, we are now conducting a study assessing the effects of protein on the same outcomes, given that peanuts are rich in protein.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“One important point is that the peanuts were unsalted and skin-roasted,” the researcher added. “The skin contains many antioxidants and fibre that may contribute to the beneficial effects.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study, “&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.clnu.2025.10.020" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Longer-term skin-roasted peanut consumption improves brain vascular function and memory: A randomized, single-blind, controlled crossover trial in healthy older adults&lt;/a&gt;,” was authored by Lucia Kerkhof, Ronald P. Mensink, Jogchum Plat, Kevin M. R. Nijssen, and Peter J. Joris.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>PsyPost</author><pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 15:43:56 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiqAFBVV95cUxOUHFUSlVYMFEycUk0dlBrb0VFYmNFd2RPTXBWZlc3Z2pVSzVPUWwwLUdrYVJ3REUtV19Nc21hQ0l3X2NTaS1PR0k2cHR6MnZYNUlqa01XOFl6WXFRQjJqNmJiaTVRS2tpSDZaTXF4OU1OQlVaN0JpZEY0dVR1cGl3OWVIcHRaYXdPX2RNMnZMNzN2YkRMY0RxaG01ZFhaS0hGYWdrZnNWOFA</guid></item><item><title>疾病预防控制中心的破坏-黑客新闻</title><link>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=46097102</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Hacker News</author><pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 15:33:20 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiWEFVX3lxTFAxWmNxRGRLeGN0bFVrME5GQmtSVmE1cmhzWW1ZMW1KTi1hZExrU0trY0FoUmVXUzFUOFpTNHR6XzJUUDlhQV9XS0d2QklLTDhqWDZoZ0RUaks</guid></item><item><title>可以默默增加心力衰竭风险的5种常见假日习惯-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/5-common-holiday-habits-that-can-silently-increase-your-risk-of-heart-failure/articleshow/125668291.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;p&gt;The holiday season is a time for family, festivities, and indulgent meals, but for people with heart conditions, it can also bring hidden risks that often go unnoticed. Cardiologist &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/reel/DRj-49lALbj/?utm_source=ig_web_copy_link&amp;amp;igsh=NTc4MTIwNjQ2YQ==" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;Dr Dmitry Yaranov recently shared on Instagram&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; that small changes in daily routines during holidays, such as altered sleep patterns, heavier meals, alcohol consumption, travel stress, and emotional excitement, can quietly trigger heart failure flare-ups. Many patients experience preventable complications during festive periods simply because they overlook subtle warning signs or dismiss early symptoms. Dr Yaranov emphasises that being mindful of your body, recognising early changes, and taking prompt action can help prevent serious issues. With the right awareness and precautions, it is possible to enjoy celebrations safely without compromising heart health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="8"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="9"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;5 ways typical &lt;keyword id="22125639" type="General" weightage="20" keywordseo="holiday-habits" source="keywords"&gt;holiday habits&lt;/keyword&gt; may put your heart at risk&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="10"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="11"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Hidden sodium in festive meals&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="12"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;High sodium intake is one of the most common holiday triggers for heart issues. Traditional holiday dishes such as stuffing, gravy, ham, canned broths, and many restaurant-prepared foods contain large amounts of salt. Sodium causes the body to retain fluid, which increases blood volume and places extra stress on the heart. Even one particularly salty meal can lead to overnight fluid accumulation, resulting in swelling, breathlessness, or sudden weight gain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; For individuals with heart failure, carefully monitoring salt intake and reading labels for hidden sodium is essential. Moderation doesn’t mean missing out entirely; it means making smarter choices like limiting processed foods or choosing lower-salt alternatives.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="16"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="18"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="19"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Breathing changes after meals&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="20"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another important early warning sign is a change in breathing patterns following large meals. When the stomach is full, the increased venous return sends more blood to the heart, forcing it to work harder. Dr Yaranov notes that new shortness of breath, difficulty lying flat, or waking up feeling breathless after a meal can indicate fluid retention. These symptoms should not be ignored as they can precede more serious heart complications. Paying attention to breathing changes, eating smaller portions, and allowing the body time to digest before lying down can help reduce unnecessary stress on the heart.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="25"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="26"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Alcohol can worsen heart health&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="27"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alcohol consumption is often part of holiday celebrations, but even small amounts can be risky for people with heart failure. Alcohol can lower blood pressure, trigger arrhythmias, and interact with medications such as diuretics, blood pressure drugs, and heart rhythm medications. Dr Yaranov warns that even modest alcohol intake can cause sudden complications in patients taking these medications. For those with heart failure, the safest approach is to avoid alcohol altogether during holiday festivities. Choosing non-alcoholic alternatives or enjoying festive drinks in moderation while monitoring for any symptoms can make a meaningful difference in heart safety.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="33"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="34"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Fatigue shouldn’t be ignored&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="35"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The holidays often involve late nights, high activity levels, and emotional excitement, all of which can contribute to fatigue. While it is normal to feel tired occasionally, unusual or excessive tiredness may be an early sign that the heart is struggling to cope with additional stress. Dr Yaranov emphasises that persistent fatigue should never be dismissed, especially if it is accompanied by other symptoms like swelling or shortness of breath. Prioritising rest, pacing activities, and maintaining a consistent sleep routine are important strategies to help the heart handle holiday pressures without being overworked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="39"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="40"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Swelling and rapid weight gain&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="41"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sudden swelling or rapid weight gain is a clear indicator that fluid is building up in the body, a common problem in heart failure. Dr Yaranov explains that a 2–3 pound increase in weight overnight or new swelling in the ankles, hands, or abdomen is usually a red flag. These changes rarely occur from a single heavy meal; they often reflect underlying heart stress or fluid retention. Monitoring weight daily and checking for swelling can help catch early signs of decompensation. Acting promptly by contacting a doctor or adjusting medications under medical guidance can prevent serious complications.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="46"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Despite the risks, Dr Yaranov reassures patients that it is possible to enjoy the holidays safely. The key is awareness, moderation, and timely action. He advises taking medications as prescribed, monitoring for subtle warning signs, and seeking medical attention immediately if unusual symptoms appear. “You can absolutely enjoy Thanksgiving with your family. Just stay aware of how you feel, know your limits, and take symptoms seriously,” he says. By staying mindful of hidden sodium, changes in breathing, alcohol intake, fatigue, and sudden swelling, those with heart concerns can celebrate the season without compromising their health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="49"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="em" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Disclaimer: This content is intended purely for informational use and is not a substitute for professional medical, nutritional or scientific advice. Always seek support from certified professionals for personalised recommendations.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="51"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="52"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="53"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Also Read: &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/greasy-hair-even-after-washing-causes-prevention-tips-and-home-remedies-for-oily-scalp/articleshow/125637706.cms" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;Greasy hair even after washing: Causes, prevention tips, and home remedies for oily scalp&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 14:40:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiAJBVV95cUxOb2FqanpaLVkxZWNsakcwaldPLWVTSDY1d0dHT2x2LWZZTnhnd3o2M0R2aktQTDFKZXJSN3dGMGRzVFBraGhITUxLTXEtSThHa2JJd1VUYjNiZGxUSW5KTG5DOXpoazJJd3UzdWl3aXdWeWlhZmVKVTFZV1lvVFlKZmtDRGdIVElqYWtELWFkd3p4QWpzSXA2Z3BaVFBoMVMtdVI1Y1VMSVFoRjNuYVVNY1Q1dHNyR0wtdDdXb2tQTmRGWDJrWndYRXR5RFZ5VmtBM2dvNTZZSzhOU0VQdWcyWHJITlhqZjY1OU1feC01UUhjQVliYTE0WUJOZmZQVXdDOUUtLUtMS1PSAY4CQVVfeXFMTW1QZXk5QU1kTjUtOElCVjZDd3d5MS1mOGNMVjd0X0ZqN0cxeDN1eTM1QzZwVTV4aS1sM1gzOEJPNm9neENFZXFMWDdSckFMUnVJYV9vM0t3bHF1M0JmLTVtRUhTaTJIT1JJMy1YN1V3THFONHlQc3EyY01jTm4teHBtWmZ6N2wyZkFEUDJNcGZMMHRNT25CdV9OdUVnRjM3czhsYk9sQUg3U255b3VoTzFiUkZJdU5qdkxXMzlqZnNiV1hlWHliaHdQMTFXTEpwczIwWnhIYnpMdGdRclJVdDhxaFZfdTB3a0lxdi1Vc0JNYi1RYmlXWWxPcENrRm1Mc1lwa1BBWHhybHhKZmxR</guid></item><item><title>大麻诱导的“Scromiting”正在上升，研究结果- Gizmodo</title><link>https://gizmodo.com/cannabis-induced-scromiting-is-on-the-rise-study-finds-2000691530</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content prose dark:prose-invert lg:prose-xl prose-science dark:prose-science"&gt;
                &lt;p&gt;As much fun and &lt;a href="https://gizmodo.com/cannabis-can-help-relieve-chronic-low-back-pain-major-trial-finds-2000665517"&gt;helpful&lt;/a&gt; as cannabis can be, every drug has its potential tradeoffs. Case in point, a study out this week finds that more Americans are coming down with a stomach-churning side effect of long-term use.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Researchers at the University of Illinois Chicago examined emergency department visits from across the country. They found evidence that ER visits for cannabinoid hyperemesis syndrome (CHS)—a condition characterized by constant, painful bouts of vomiting—have noticeably risen in the last several years, especially among younger adults. The researchers say that more doctors need to be aware of this debilitating, but ultimately treatable, health problem.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="not-prose my-8 -mx-5 xs:max-w-xs xs:mx-auto"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;“Cannabinoid hyperemesis syndrome is real, and it’s becoming a more routine part of emergency medicine in the U.S.,” lead author James Swartz, a professor at UIC’s Jane Addams College of Social Work, told Gizmodo.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;The scromiting syndrome&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;People with &lt;a href="https://my.clevelandclinic.org/health/diseases/21665-cannabis-hyperemesis-syndrome"&gt;CHS&lt;/a&gt; will experience cyclical periods of intense cramps, nausea, and vomiting. An acute episode can last one to two days, and the experience is often so intolerable that people will scream out in pain as they’re vomiting—a phenomenon that’s been given the charming nickname “&lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC6690288/#:~:text=Young%20people%2C%20typically%20between%20the,to%20the%20term%20%E2%80%9Cscromiting%E2%80%9D."&gt;scromiting&lt;/a&gt;.”&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;p&gt;CHS typically happens in people who have been using cannabis chronically for at least several years. Scientists aren’t sure why it develops, but it might be caused by the overstimulation of native cannabinoid receptors in the gastrointestinal tract. It’s thought to be a rare complication, but recent research has &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S0376871624013437"&gt;suggested&lt;/a&gt; that cases of CHS have been increasing in the U.S. and other places where cannabis legalization has expanded.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="not-prose"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;In this latest study, the researchers analyzed data from a nationwide sample of ER visits in the U.S. between 2016 and 2022. Until recently, doctors couldn’t diagnose CHS as a distinct medical condition for record-keeping and insurance purposes. So the researchers instead looked for diagnoses related to cyclical vomiting syndrome (severe, sudden vomiting that can’t be explained by other known causes) and cannabis use; cases where both diagnoses were present were used as a proxy for CHS.&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;p&gt;During the study period, roughly 100,000 cases of suspected CHS were documented. Prior to the covid-19 pandemic, they found, annual rates of CHS were steady. Starting in 2020, however, suspected cases of CHS seen in the ER surged. And though cases did decline in 2022, they were still above the pre-pandemic baseline. Importantly, cases of cannabis-related health problems in general also rose during that same period, while cases of cyclical vomiting syndrome without any cannabis link did not, further suggesting a real rise in CHS.&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;p&gt;The team’s findings were &lt;a href="https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jamanetworkopen/fullarticle/2841769"&gt;published&lt;/a&gt; Monday in JAMA Network Open.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;figure id="attachment_2000691635" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-2000691635" class="wp-caption alignleft"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-2000691635" src="https://gizmodo.com/app/uploads/2025/11/CHS-chart.jpg" alt="Chs Chart" srcset="https://gizmodo.com/app/uploads/2025/11/CHS-chart.jpg 1325w, https://gizmodo.com/app/uploads/2025/11/CHS-chart-336x161.jpg 336w, https://gizmodo.com/app/uploads/2025/11/CHS-chart-1280x613.jpg 1280w, https://gizmodo.com/app/uploads/2025/11/CHS-chart-768x368.jpg 768w, https://gizmodo.com/app/uploads/2025/11/CHS-chart-672x322.jpg 672w, https://gizmodo.com/app/uploads/2025/11/CHS-chart-960x460.jpg 960w" sizes="(max-width: 639px) 100vw, (max-width: 1023px) calc(100vw - 2rem), (max-width: 1258px) calc((100vw - 3.68rem) * 2 / 3), 800px"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-2000691635" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;The chart shows that the likelihood of CHS among people diagnosed with cannabis-related health problems at the ER rose over time. © Swartz et al./JAMA Network Open&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt; &lt;p&gt;Though this study can’t directly answer why CHS is becoming more common, the timing of this surge indicates that covid-19 probably played a role. At the same time, ongoing factors like the growing legalization of cannabis in the U.S. and perhaps the increased amounts of THC in today’s cannabis strains are also likely important, the researchers say.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;“The COVID-19 pandemic likely catalyzed the rise in CHS through stress, isolation, and increased cannabis use,” the authors wrote. “After peaking in 2021, CHS incidence declined but plateaued above prepandemic levels, suggesting sustained structural or clinical drivers.”&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;h2&gt;How to stay safe from CHS&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;CHS is a horrific experience, but it’s one that we know how to effectively manage and treat.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;For some reason, hot baths and showers can temporarily relieve an acute episode. The only way to truly keep it from happening, though, is to stop using cannabis altogether. It might take weeks, but the symptoms will eventually stop.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;And while the rate of CHS may be climbing, it’s still a relatively rare side effect, the authors say.&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;p&gt;“Our findings shouldn’t be interpreted as a reason to panic, but they do reinforce that cannabis is not risk-free, especially at higher doses and with long-term, heavy use,” Swartz said.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p class="not-prose"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Earlier this year, CHS was &lt;a href="https://adai.uw.edu/icd-10-code-chs/"&gt;officially added&lt;/a&gt; to the latest edition of the International Classification of Diseases (ICD), the codebook that’s used worldwide for diagnostic and billing purposes. So it’s now much easier for doctors to diagnose the condition and for researchers to track its prevalence. That said, doctors and hospitals will still need to know that CHS exists in order to make a timely diagnosis, the study authors say.&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;p&gt;“Given frequent misdiagnosis and costly, unnecessary testing, greater clinical awareness is needed,” the authors wrote. They also argue that more research is needed to figure out the exact causes of CHS and why only some long-term users develop it.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Days like these, I’m glad that I only occasionally indulge in the &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Sticky_icky"&gt;sticky icky.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;      &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Gizmodo</author><pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 14:00:55 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijgFBVV95cUxOWU1GbHFURmJzNDlreV9OZDBDdVJxTDJQb1JoQklZSGpJcHdudER3LW9YdWJicm5SUTZERnRweVB1RVFnMzlvSE1VVjZwM0YwRUFJbFVzbGRPNEl0ak1sUmRzVVFDTTJUSEJDVXdPUnRpMHRSRUxQMmtfNmgtTC0yTS1BbFdkeWpuY184NjZR</guid></item><item><title>科学家发现流行的糖尿病药物在令人惊讶的研究中影响大脑-预防</title><link>https://www.prevention.com/health/health-conditions/a69545377/metformin-brain-impact-study/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div data-journey-body="standard-article" class="article-body-content article-body standard-body-content css-n3hm4j et2g3wt7"&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="0" class="css-6wxqfj emevuu60"&gt;With buzzy medications like &lt;a href="https://www.prevention.com/food-nutrition/a64501989/ozempic-reshapes-the-food-people-eat-study/" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.prevention.com/food-nutrition/a64501989/ozempic-reshapes-the-food-people-eat-study/" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="Ozempic" data-node-id="0.1" class="body-link css-inlxvj emevuu60"&gt;Ozempic&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.prevention.com/health/health-conditions/a45250651/mounjaro-vs-ozempic/" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.prevention.com/health/health-conditions/a45250651/mounjaro-vs-ozempic/" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="Mounjaro" data-node-id="0.3" class="body-link css-inlxvj emevuu60"&gt;Mounjaro&lt;/a&gt; making headlines for blood sugar management, it’s easy to forget that some medications have been helping patients with &lt;a href="https://www.prevention.com/diabetes/" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.prevention.com/diabetes/" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="type 2 diabetes" data-node-id="0.5" class="body-link css-inlxvj emevuu60"&gt;type 2 diabetes&lt;/a&gt; for decades. Metformin is a popular one. But while this medication has been around for more than 60 years, scientists are uncovering what it does to the brain. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="1" class="css-6wxqfj emevuu60"&gt;New research published in the journal &lt;em data-node-id="1.1"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.science.org/doi/10.1126/sciadv.adu3700" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.science.org/doi/10.1126/sciadv.adu3700" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="Science Advances" data-node-id="1.1.0" class="body-link css-inlxvj emevuu60"&gt;Science Advances&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/em&gt;identifies a brain pathway that metformin seems to work through (along with the impact it has on other areas of the body). It’s been generally accepted that metformin lowers blood sugar by reducing how much glucose the liver puts out, but this study found that a lot of that glucose regulation seems to happen in the brain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="2" class="body-tip css-19jy3s emevuu60"&gt;&lt;strong data-node-id="2.0"&gt;Meet the experts&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;a href="https://rwjmg.rwjms.rutgers.edu/doctor_page.php?phys_id=115212" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://rwjmg.rwjms.rutgers.edu/doctor_page.php?phys_id=115212" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="Christoph Buettner, M.D., Ph.D." data-node-id="2.2" class="body-link css-inlxvj emevuu60"&gt;Christoph Buettner, M.D., Ph.D.&lt;/a&gt;, chief of the division of endocrinology at Rutgers Robert Wood Johnson Medical School; &lt;a href="https://www.medstarhealth.org/doctors/kelly-krisna-johnson-arbor-md" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.medstarhealth.org/doctors/kelly-krisna-johnson-arbor-md" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="Kelly Johnson-Arbor, M.D." data-node-id="2.4" class="body-link css-inlxvj emevuu60"&gt;Kelly Johnson-Arbor, M.D.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.medstarhealth.org/doctors/kelly-krisna-johnson-arbor-md" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.medstarhealth.org/doctors/kelly-krisna-johnson-arbor-md" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="," data-node-id="2.5" class="body-link css-inlxvj emevuu60"&gt;,&lt;/a&gt; a toxicologist at MedStar Health; &lt;a href="https://phmtox.msu.edu/people/alanjami" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://phmtox.msu.edu/people/alanjami" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="Jamie K. Alan, Ph.D.," data-node-id="2.7" class="body-link css-inlxvj emevuu60"&gt;Jamie K. Alan, Ph.D.,&lt;/a&gt; an associate professor of pharmacology and toxicology at Michigan State University&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="4" class="css-6wxqfj emevuu60"&gt;In a previous mouse study, the same research team found a protein in the brain called Rap1, which impacted how glucose is broken down in the body. During that study, the researchers found that metformin traveled to an area of the brain called the ventromedial hypothalamus, where it essentially turned off Rap1. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="5" class="css-6wxqfj emevuu60"&gt;The researchers then bred mice that didn’t have Rap1 and found that metformin had no impact on their blood sugar management, even though other medications did. Overall, the findings suggest that metformin has a big impact on the brain. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="6" class="css-6wxqfj emevuu60"&gt;But why does this matter? Here’s what doctors want you to know.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="what-is-metformin" data-node-id="7" class="body-h2 css-ne8qws emevuu60"&gt;&lt;strong data-node-id="7.0"&gt;What is metformin?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="8" class="css-6wxqfj emevuu60"&gt;Metformin is an oral medication in a class of drugs called biguanides that is commonly used to treat type 2 diabetes, according to the &lt;a href="https://medlineplus.gov/druginfo/meds/a696005.html" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://medlineplus.gov/druginfo/meds/a696005.html" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="U.S. National Library of Medicine" data-node-id="8.1" class="body-link css-inlxvj emevuu60"&gt;U.S. National Library of Medicine&lt;/a&gt;. The medication is designed to help control the amount of glucose (or sugar) in the blood. “Metformin has been used for decades to treat diabetes, although there has been extensive research on its use in other conditions like cancer and PCOS,” says &lt;a href="https://phmtox.msu.edu/people/alanjami" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://phmtox.msu.edu/people/alanjami" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="Jamie K. Alan, Ph.D.," data-node-id="8.3" class="body-link css-inlxvj emevuu60"&gt;Jamie K. Alan, Ph.D.,&lt;/a&gt; an associate professor of pharmacology and toxicology at Michigan State University.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="9" class="css-6wxqfj emevuu60"&gt;Metformin specifically decreases the amount of glucose you absorb from food, as well as the amount of glucose made by the liver, per Alan. At the same time, the drug increases the body’s response to insulin, a hormone that controls the amount of glucose in the blood. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="10" class="css-6wxqfj emevuu60"&gt;“There are likely more complex mechanisms also at play,” Alan says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="11" class="css-6wxqfj emevuu60"&gt;Metformin is being explored for other health conditions, too. “Because metformin can pass through the bloodstream and into the brain, scientists have also studied whether it may be an effective treatment for depression and neurological disorders,” says &lt;a href="https://www.medstarhealth.org/doctors/kelly-krisna-johnson-arbor-md" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.medstarhealth.org/doctors/kelly-krisna-johnson-arbor-md" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="Kelly Johnson-Arbor, M.D." data-node-id="11.1" class="body-link css-inlxvj emevuu60"&gt;Kelly Johnson-Arbor, M.D.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.medstarhealth.org/doctors/kelly-krisna-johnson-arbor-md" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.medstarhealth.org/doctors/kelly-krisna-johnson-arbor-md" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="," data-node-id="11.2" class="body-link css-inlxvj emevuu60"&gt;,&lt;/a&gt; a toxicologist at MedStar Health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="why-does-this-matter" data-node-id="12" class="body-h2 css-ne8qws emevuu60"&gt;&lt;strong data-node-id="12.0"&gt;Why does this matter?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="13" class="css-6wxqfj emevuu60"&gt;Even though metformin has been widely used for decades, the details about how it works haven’t been totally figured out. “Amazingly, even though metformin is a drug that has been used for more than six decades in the U.S., we still do not fully understand how it works,” says &lt;a href="https://rwjmg.rwjms.rutgers.edu/doctor_page.php?phys_id=115212" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://rwjmg.rwjms.rutgers.edu/doctor_page.php?phys_id=115212" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="Christoph Buettner, M.D., Ph.D." data-node-id="13.1" class="body-link css-inlxvj emevuu60"&gt;Christoph Buettner, M.D., Ph.D.&lt;/a&gt;, chief of the division of endocrinology at Rutgers Robert Wood Johnson Medical School. “It’s the most prescribed diabetes drug in the world.”&lt;br data-node-id="13.3"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="14" class="css-6wxqfj emevuu60"&gt;These findings suggest it could impact the brain, liver, and gut. “It is valuable to learn how this works in the brain,” Alan says. “There is so much we don’t know about satiety and central mechanisms behind appetite and blood sugar control.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="15" class="css-6wxqfj emevuu60"&gt;The findings “change the way we think about metformin,” Dr. Buettner says. “It supports the important role the brain plays in glucose metabolism,” he continues. “It also may explain why metformin causes modest weight loss, changes in appetite and hunger, and possible effects on brain aging or cognition, as these are brain effects.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="16" class="css-6wxqfj emevuu60"&gt;Metformin is also “extremely affordable,” Alan says. “It’s oral, so no injections are needed,” she adds. (By comparison, Ozempic and Mounjaro are injectable medications.) As a result, finding new ways to use it or similar treatments would be a big win for the diabetes community and beyond, she says. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="17" class="css-6wxqfj emevuu60"&gt;These findings could potentially lead to new and better treatments for a range of diseases, according to Dr. Johnson-Arbor. “By studying the effects of metformin outside of the liver, scientists may be able to find new applications of this decades-old drug, such as novel treatments for diabetes, neurological disorders, and heart disease,” she says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="what-happens-now" data-node-id="18" class="body-h2 css-ne8qws emevuu60"&gt;&lt;strong data-node-id="18.0"&gt;What happens now?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="19" class="css-6wxqfj emevuu60"&gt;These are new findings, so more research is needed. However, the study’s research team also shared in a &lt;a href="https://www.bcm.edu/news/how-does-metformin-lower-blood-sugar" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.bcm.edu/news/how-does-metformin-lower-blood-sugar" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="press release" data-node-id="19.1" class="body-link css-inlxvj emevuu60"&gt;press release&lt;/a&gt; that they plan to dive deeper into how metformin impacts the brain, including looking at humans.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="20" class="css-6wxqfj emevuu60"&gt;Still, experts say this is just the start. “The research is a long way from the clinic, but it is important,” Alan says. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-ad-exclude="true" id="journey-inline" class="css-ciejky e1ye6jr30"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Prevention</author><pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 13:32:12 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilgFBVV95cUxNQkxVc2dzaHM1c2hVbzZQYXRQelhNc0NQdmZDV0xPYkljMjR5SVNHb2wxSXZXLVptQ19VUTFEZFU4aEJtaWZKaW13dXVBN0RwWTlsNHZFM3Fla21XdHhYRWpmc2xTcllQc0t6MVpDM1Q4Q2lScldwcFpMRXluU2Nld3dOUVdNVWtGOWYxZTBud2R0TjJGSHc</guid></item><item><title>寻找更浓密、更饱满的头发？专家权衡生物素补充剂-今日美国</title><link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/life/health-wellness/2025/11/30/biotin-hair-growth-benefits/87468315007/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="gnt_ar_b"&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;People looking to grow out thicker, fuller hair or stronger, healthier nails are presented with plenty of commercials and product recommendations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;Could &lt;a href="/story/life/health-wellness/2024/11/20/what-does-biotin-do/75900383007/" data-t-l=":b|e|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;biotin supplements&lt;/a&gt; offer you a solution to those &lt;a href="/story/life/health-wellness/2023/10/18/why-is-my-hair-falling-out/71180805007/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" data-t-l=":b|e|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;common beauty concerns&lt;/a&gt;?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;Proponents tout biotin's potential benefits for hair, nails and more. But do they offer benefits for some people more than others? And how necessary are the &lt;a href="/story/life/health-wellness/2024/08/15/what-is-vitamin-b6-good-for/74550359007/" data-t-l=":b|e|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;supplements&lt;/a&gt;? &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;Biotin deficiency is a relatively uncommon condition. Eating a well-rounded, &lt;a href="/story/life/health-wellness/2024/10/18/cauliflower-good-for-you/75478336007/#:~:text=Moreover%2C%20as%20a%20filling%20and,per%20cup%2C%22%20says%20Weintraub." target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" data-t-l=":b|e|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;balanced diet&lt;/a&gt; is how the &lt;a href="https://www.healthline.com/health/the-benefits-of-biotin" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" data-t-l=":b|z|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;vast majority of people&lt;/a&gt; can get enough biotin (also known as vitamin B7), per Healthline.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;We asked the experts to break down what you need to know about biotin. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="gnt_ar_b_h2"&gt;What does biotin do?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;Biotin supports several functions in the body, including the &lt;a href="/story/news/health/2021/09/13/fewer-calories-more-exercise-weight-loss-its-more-complicated/8274034002/?gnt-cfr=1&amp;amp;gca-cat=p" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" data-t-l=":b|e|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;metabolism&lt;/a&gt; of carbs, fats and proteins, said &lt;a href="https://www.uwmedicine.org/bios/misbah-keen" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" data-t-l=":b|z|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;Dr. Misbah K. Keen&lt;/a&gt;, MD, MBI, MPH, a professor of family medicine at the University of Washington School of Medicine. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;Biotin also plays an important role in supporting &lt;a href="https://reviewed.usatoday.com/beauty/features/its-a-10-miracle-leave-in-plus-keratin-review" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" data-t-l=":b|e|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;the structure of keratin&lt;/a&gt;, a protein that’s essential to the maintenance of healthy hair, skin and nails, Keen previously told USA TODAY. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;During pregnancy, biotin is an essential nutrient that supports the &lt;a href="https://www.mountsinai.org/health-library/supplement/vitamin-h-biotin" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" data-t-l=":b|z|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;growth of the embryo&lt;/a&gt;, per Mount Sinai.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="gnt_ar_b_h2"&gt;Who is at risk for biotin deficiency?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;It’s important to understand that most people can satisfy their need for biotin just from eating a variety of biotin-rich foods − think eggs, seeds, &lt;a href="/story/life/health-wellness/2024/07/26/are-walnuts-good-for-you/74323707007/#:~:text=No%20matter%20which%20variety%20you,the%20U.S.%20Department%20of%20Agriculture." target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" data-t-l=":b|e|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;nuts&lt;/a&gt;, meat and fish, said &lt;a href="https://wexnermedical.osu.edu/find-a-doctor/barbara-bawer-md-79613" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" data-t-l=":b|z|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;Dr. Barbara Bawer&lt;/a&gt;, a family medicine physician at The Ohio State University Wexner Medical Center. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;Biotin deficiency is very uncommon, but experiencing it can cause an array of side effects, including: &lt;a href="/story/life/health-wellness/2024/08/10/what-vitamins-are-good-for-hair-growth/74551135007/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" data-t-l=":b|e|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;hair thinning or loss&lt;/a&gt;, brittle nails, a red scaly rash (around the eyes, nose, and mouth), a swollen, painful tongue, neurological changes (such as numbness and tingling), and mental health changes (including depression and lethargy), Keen said.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;A very small group of people are born without the enzyme biotinidase. This is an inherited condition that impacts an individual’s biotin metabolism, said &lt;a href="https://www.stamfordhealth.org/find-a-doctor/lidya-bal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" data-t-l=":b|z|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;Dr. Lidya Bal&lt;/a&gt;, MD, a physician with Stamford Health. Global estimates approximate that biotinidase deficiency ranges anywhere from one in 40,000 people to &lt;a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/books/NBK560607/#:~:text=Biotinidase%20deficiency%20is%20a%20rare,the%20Kingdom%20of%20Saudi%20Arabia." target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" data-t-l=":b|z|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;one in 60,000 people&lt;/a&gt;, per NCBI. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;Though rare, there is an elevated risk for &lt;a href="/story/life/health-wellness/2024/10/26/can-pregnant-women-eat-deli-meat/75594937007/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" data-t-l=":b|e|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;people who are pregnant&lt;/a&gt; or breastfeeding to experience biotin deficiency. As for why this may occur, during pregnancy, your body metabolizes biotin faster, Bawer explained. When breastfeeding, “you tend to excrete more biotin and therefore are at higher risk of being low,” she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;Individuals with chronic alcoholism, and people taking long-term antiseizure medications, are also at risk for biotin deficiency, Keen added. “These can interfere with biotin metabolism or absorption,” he said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="gnt_ar_b_h2"&gt;Who benefits from biotin supplements?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;“Biotin supplements are used to prevent or treat biotin deficiency,” and individuals with a biotin deficiency may benefit from taking them, said Bal. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;Biotin supplements should always be taken under medical supervision, underscores &lt;a href="https://utswmed.org/doctors/sarah-hemeida/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" data-t-l=":b|z|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;Dr. Sarah Hemeida&lt;/a&gt;, MD, MPH, an assistant professor and family physician at UT Southwestern Family Medicine Department and the co-director of Empowher Health, a women's health education program focused on dispelling cultural misinformation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;The adequate intake (AI) for biotin is 30 micrograms a day for adults and eight to 12 micrograms a day for children, Bal said. However, depending on the patient and the severity of their biotin deficiency, dosages will vary. For example, in certain cases, treatment could require taking a dosage of biotin supplements as high as 10mg per day, Bal noted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;Biotin supplements may offer benefits during pregnancy and times of lactation, when it’s especially important to maintain healthy biotin levels, Hemeida said. There are risks to taking biotin supplements during pregnancy, so always consult your doctor first, she recommended.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="gnt_ar_b_h2"&gt;Does biotin increase hair growth?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;Unfortunately, for most people, taking biotin supplements will probably not make much of an impact on hair growth. “Although biotin is widely marketed for hair loss, the evidence supporting its effectiveness is mixed,” Keen said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;&lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC5582478/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" data-t-l=":b|z|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;According to a 2017 review&lt;/a&gt;, some studies have shown biotin supplementation had positive outcomes for hair growth in individuals who had an acquired or inherited deficiency in biotin. However, these cases are still relatively uncommon. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;In healthy individuals who aren’t deficient in biotin, biotin supplementation will likely have no effect on hair growth, the same review concluded.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="gnt_ar_b_h2"&gt;Does biotin support nail health?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;Some &lt;a href="https://www.tandfonline.com/doi/full/10.1080/09546634.2017.1395799" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" data-t-l=":b|z|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;small clinical trials&lt;/a&gt; have shown biotin supplements may help strengthen brittle nails by improving their firmness, thickness and hardness. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;However, biotin supplements will likely have no strengthening effect on your nails if you aren’t deficient in biotin, said &lt;a href="https://school.wakehealth.edu/faculty/m/amy-mcmichael" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" data-t-l=":b|z|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;Dr. Amy McMichael&lt;/a&gt;, MD, FAAD, a board-certified dermatologist and professor of dermatology at Wake Forest University School of Medicine. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;If you’re facing brittle, &lt;a href="/story/life/health-wellness/2023/08/11/why-do-people-bite-their-nails/70429437007/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" data-t-l=":b|e|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;easily broken nails&lt;/a&gt;, biotin supplements may be used as a short-term treatment, McMichael said. But, if you are considering taking any kind of supplement for nail health, always have a conversation with your board-certified dermatologist first, McMichael underscored.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="gnt_ar_b_h2"&gt;What is the downside of taking biotin?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;Biotin is a &lt;a href="https://www.mountsinai.org/health-library/supplement/vitamin-h-biotin" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" data-t-l=":b|z|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;water soluble vitamin&lt;/a&gt;, meaning “when there's an excess supply, it's excreted through the urine,” said Hemeida. Overall, biotin is considered to be “a very safe vitamin."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;However, “there is too much of a good thing when it comes to biotin, because it can prevent you from accurately diagnosing other important issues,” and it may interfere with the results of certain laboratory tests, Hemeida warned. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;“For that reason, we now recommend to patients to really not take biotin unless they are biotin-deficient, and that is proven by their physician,” McMichael said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;&lt;em&gt;This article contains affiliate links. If you click on a link and make a purchase, we may earn a commission at no extra cost to you.&lt;/em&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="gnt_ar_b_h2"&gt;Shop top-rated related products: &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_s gnt_ar_s0"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_s gnt_ar_s25"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_s gnt_ar_s50"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_s gnt_ar_s75"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_s gnt_ar_s100"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>USA Today</author><pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 12:40:11 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipgFBVV95cUxPM0hFM0Vaek9VbUtPQVBxeHA5UGNsYmExQ180MGFoWE9LcmxaZllQUU5neXJJZTVBaWNqbG1aVlprRjE4S1pDdFBGUDVtWWplLXBBbURyd0w2cm1LQkU2Q2ZYQUtNUGxVbUhwRUlHdERNa0FDU3gzaE5NWWladjg5M2NXN1ZKRFNHek1ONThGUzU0Q0Zjd05YSnRVTlkwUHhaNXlaOFd3</guid></item><item><title>研究人员发现了两种新的痴呆症风险因素。这就是它们的本质。- HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffpost.com/entry/dementia-research-new-risk-factors-goog_l_69209634e4b06c13afa4a363</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;section class="entry__content-list js-entry-content js-cet-subunit"&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Strides have been made in the world of dementia research compared with even just a few years ago. There’s now a blood test that can diagnose &lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2024/07/28/health/alzheimers-blood-test.html" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Alzheimer’s accurately 90% of the time" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="69209634e4b06c13afa4a363" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.nytimes.com/2024/07/28/health/alzheimers-blood-test.html" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="0"&gt;Alzheimer’s accurately 90% of the time&lt;/a&gt;, and more is understood about the factors (many of which are lifestyle habits) that can put you at higher risk for the condition.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a new &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/life/topic/dementia" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-internal-link" data-vars-item-name="dementia" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="69209634e4b06c13afa4a363" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="/life/topic/dementia" data-vars-target-content-type="feed" data-vars-type="web_internal_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="1"&gt;dementia&lt;/a&gt; report published in &lt;a href="https://www.thelancet.com/journals/lancet/article/PIIS0140-6736(24)01296-0/abstract" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="The Lancet journal" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="69209634e4b06c13afa4a363" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.thelancet.com/journals/lancet/article/PIIS0140-6736(24)01296-0/abstract" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="2"&gt;The Lancet journal&lt;/a&gt; by researchers who are part of The Lancet Commission, two new modifiable risk factors have been identified: high cholesterol after 40 and untreated vision loss.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;In 2020, these same researchers determined 12 modifiable risk factors that are known to put folks at higher risk of developing dementia. These are:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;Physical inactivity&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Smoking&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Excessive alcohol consumption&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Air pollution&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Head injury&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Infrequent social contact&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Less education&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Obesity&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Hypertension&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Diabetes&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Depression&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Hearing impairment&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to the report, these 12 factors, along with the two new ones, account for 49% of dementia cases across the world. Researchers determined these two new risk factors by looking at recent meta-analyses and studies on the topics; they looked at 14 papers on vision loss and 27 on high cholesterol. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“It makes a lot of mechanistic sense,” said &lt;a href="https://www.yalemedicine.org/specialists/arman-fesharaki" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Dr. Arman Fesharaki-Zadeh" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="69209634e4b06c13afa4a363" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.yalemedicine.org/specialists/arman-fesharaki" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="3"&gt;Dr. Arman Fesharaki-Zadeh&lt;/a&gt;, a behavioral neurologist and neuropsychiatrist at Yale Medicine in Connecticut. “A lot of these factors are very much interrelated.” (Fesharaki-Zadeh is not affiliated with the report.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“There are many sources of vision loss, of course, but it tends to be a lot more common in folks who have metabolic risk factors such as high blood pressure, such as poorly controlled diabetes, such as high cholesterol, which is the other risk factor [identified in the report],” he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Moreover, vision is our primary sensory organ — it’s how we process the world around us — and when you can’t see clearly, you’re less likely to spend time doing brain-boosting activities like puzzles, reading or even spending time with other people, said Fesharaki-Zadeh. And these activities are known to help prevent dementia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;When it comes to high LDL cholesterol (the so-called bad cholesterol), it can lead to the hardening of the blood vessels in the heart and brain, Fesharaki-Zadeh said, adding that high blood pressure and uncontrolled diabetes also affect the blood vessels.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;This can &lt;a href="https://www.hopkinsmedicine.org/health/conditions-and-diseases/atherosclerosis" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="make it more difficult for oxygen" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="69209634e4b06c13afa4a363" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.hopkinsmedicine.org/health/conditions-and-diseases/atherosclerosis" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="4"&gt;make it more difficult for oxygen&lt;/a&gt; to get to the brain, which over time can lead to neuron damage — “and dementia is essentially an end product of the neurons dying out, so it’s a neurodegenerative process,” Fesharaki-Zadeh explained.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I can’t tell you how often I see in our patient populations, especially folks above the age of 60, there are certain parts of the brain that are more vulnerable to damage ... and these are the areas that are especially vulnerable to hardening of blood vessels. Someone who has ... high cholesterol, the correlation between that and hardening of blood vessels is quite high, and we see it in our clinical setting very frequently as well.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The saying that I like to use with patients quite often is what affects your heart will affect your brain, and we see that time and time again,” the doctor said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure class="cli cli-image js-no-inject"&gt;&lt;p class="cli-image__spacer"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="cli-image__source-wrapper"&gt;&lt;div class="cli-image__credit" aria-label="Image Credit: Olena Ruban via Getty Images"&gt;&lt;p class="credit-container"&gt;&lt;span class="credit"&gt;Olena Ruban via Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption class="cli-image__caption caption-cli"&gt;If you suffer from vision loss, it's important to manage it for the sake of your future health.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You can lower your risk. First, have a good medical team and primary care doctor.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I cannot highlight the importance of a collaborative model between primary care physicians and specialties,” said Fesharaki-Zadeh. Having a primary care doctor who understands your health and is willing to share pertinent information with specialists, like cardiologists and neurologists, will help you stay on top of any issues putting your well-being at stake.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Your primary care doctor should also be proactively working to help you control the risk factors — like high cholesterol and high blood pressure — whether that’s through medication, diet or exercise.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fesharaki-Zadeh said you and your doctor should focus on these lifestyle changes as early as possible, at least in midlife, not when you’re at the point when dementia starts to show up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The front line of medical care are primary care physicians. These are the folks that, by having early discussions ... can go a long distance to prevent the onset of dementia,” he explained.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;There are also tests that can detect early signs of neurodegeneration and genetic markers of the disease. A primary care doctor can help you learn about these options.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Up to 40% of dementias are potentially preventable,” he added, but it’s worth noting that dementia can also be genetic, which makes prevention trickier. But someone who is diagnosed with dementia or mild cognitive impairment can benefit from managing these risk factors, too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The research is also showing that if you have two groups of individuals, someone who has comorbid metabolic diseases such as hypertension, high cholesterol, diabetes, versus somebody who doesn’t, and both of these individuals have dementia, the rates of progression of dementia in somebody who doesn’t have metabolic risk factors tend to be slower,” explained Fesharaki-Zadeh.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s never too late to make changes and corrections, he noted, whether you’re a young, seemingly healthy person, in your 80s or 90s, or someone who has already been diagnosed with dementia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Our brains are highly malleable, Fesharaki-Zadeh said. So if you decide to make healthy lifestyle changes at any point, your brain will respond and be healthier for it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>HuffPost</author><pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 12:00:17 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMingFBVV95cUxPR01raHVvZGdGai1LY0hsaVVuajRRYkN2Sm9lOFNFdW1IanVUWlRwRnVrN3dEaFFWQnNRTE5zRjJxbTVkOVFwQlktX1J6ZlF2MkdseGdYUzh5RjJsTmtWeVYydEliTll4TXA5RFF1R2hIX3cyb2s4WHpGMVVzY2hjU1pmOHJaUFNjVC00cnh0MW5BSWlJYUZBT2dPM2laUdIBowFBVV95cUxPN3BLM1ltSGtRVFJzVG1GZDA2RDFwYkNwdmVYSzlXRXpud1ZGT0l3NVp6ZmlrMEFHcVpydTUxajktU1pta1pYSkxLendmWG9LZlFFZFlUakFic3BnUDdxRVp3XzFBb1g1bjNWMkgwVEplTFZpQTdISlVXMThodmxWYTZORHlJd1d0MnZ5ODNOTXlSQnFFSXVCT1RwQjZHTWl2S3I0</guid></item><item><title>研究人员发现了两种新的痴呆症风险因素。以下是它们的内容。- Yahoo News Canada</title><link>https://ca.news.yahoo.com/researchers-discovered-2-dementia-risk-120017476.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="" data-article-body="true"&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Strides have been made in the world of dementia research compared with even just a few years ago. There’s now a blood test that can diagnose &lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2024/07/28/health/alzheimers-blood-test.html" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Alzheimer’s accurately 90% of the time;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Alzheimer’s accurately 90% of the time&lt;/a&gt;, and more is understood about the factors (many of which are lifestyle habits) that can put you at higher risk for the condition.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;In a new &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/life/topic/dementia" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:dementia;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;dementia&lt;/a&gt; report published in &lt;a href="https://www.thelancet.com/journals/lancet/article/PIIS0140-6736(24)01296-0/abstract" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:The Lancet journal;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;The Lancet journal&lt;/a&gt; by researchers who are part of The Lancet Commission, two new modifiable risk factors have been identified: high cholesterol after 40 and untreated vision loss.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Health: &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/entry/dissociation-protect-mental-health_l_69270610e4b0ee43600b68e5?utm_campaign=yahoo-recirc" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:This Coping Behavior Is Super Common Right Now — And It Says So Much About Where We Are As A Country;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;This Coping Behavior Is Super Common Right Now — And It Says So Much About Where We Are As A Country&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;In 2020, these same researchers determined 12 modifiable risk factors that are known to put folks at higher risk of developing dementia. These are:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ol class="mb-4"&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-decimal"&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-decimal"&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-decimal"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Excessive alcohol consumption&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-decimal"&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-decimal"&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-decimal"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Infrequent social contact&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-decimal"&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-decimal"&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-decimal"&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-decimal"&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-decimal"&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-decimal"&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;According to the report, these 12 factors, along with the two new ones, account for 49% of dementia cases across the world. Researchers determined these two new risk factors by looking at recent meta-analyses and studies on the topics; they looked at 14 papers on vision loss and 27 on high cholesterol.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“It makes a lot of mechanistic sense,” said &lt;a href="https://www.yalemedicine.org/specialists/arman-fesharaki" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Dr. Arman Fesharaki-Zadeh;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Dr. Arman Fesharaki-Zadeh&lt;/a&gt;, a behavioral neurologist and neuropsychiatrist at Yale Medicine in Connecticut. “A lot of these factors are very much interrelated.” (Fesharaki-Zadeh is not affiliated with the report.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“There are many sources of vision loss, of course, but it tends to be a lot more common in folks who have metabolic risk factors such as high blood pressure, such as poorly controlled diabetes, such as high cholesterol, which is the other risk factor [identified in the report],” he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Health: &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/entry/dementia-research-new-risk-factors-goog_l_68f10a1ae4b0ab08d3191f7d?utm_campaign=yahoo-recirc" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Researchers Have Discovered 2 New Dementia Risk Factors. Here's What They Are.;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Researchers Have Discovered 2 New Dementia Risk Factors. Here's What They Are.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Moreover, vision is our primary sensory organ — it’s how we process the world around us — and when you can’t see clearly, you’re less likely to spend time doing brain-boosting activities like puzzles, reading or even spending time with other people, said Fesharaki-Zadeh. And these activities are known to help prevent dementia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;When it comes to high LDL cholesterol (the so-called bad cholesterol), it can lead to the hardening of the blood vessels in the heart and brain, Fesharaki-Zadeh said, adding that high blood pressure and uncontrolled diabetes also affect the blood vessels.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;This can &lt;a href="https://www.hopkinsmedicine.org/health/conditions-and-diseases/atherosclerosis" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:make it more difficult for oxygen;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;make it more difficult for oxygen&lt;/a&gt; to get to the brain, which over time can lead to neuron damage — “and dementia is essentially an end product of the neurons dying out, so it’s a neurodegenerative process,” Fesharaki-Zadeh explained.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“I can’t tell you how often I see in our patient populations, especially folks above the age of 60, there are certain parts of the brain that are more vulnerable to damage ... and these are the areas that are especially vulnerable to hardening of blood vessels. Someone who has ... high cholesterol, the correlation between that and hardening of blood vessels is quite high, and we see it in our clinical setting very frequently as well.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“The saying that I like to use with patients quite often is what affects your heart will affect your brain, and we see that time and time again,” the doctor said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="relative mb-4"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="relative text-sm mt-1 pr-2.5"&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you suffer from vision loss, it's important to manage it for the sake of your future health. &lt;span class="copyright"&gt;Olena Ruban via Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;h2 class="mb-4 text-xl font-bold md:text-2xl"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You can lower your risk. First, have a good medical team and primary care doctor.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“I cannot highlight the importance of a collaborative model between primary care physicians and specialties,” said Fesharaki-Zadeh. Having a primary care doctor who understands your health and is willing to share pertinent information with specialists, like cardiologists and neurologists, will help you stay on top of any issues putting your well-being at stake.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Your primary care doctor should also be proactively working to help you control the risk factors — like high cholesterol and high blood pressure — whether that’s through medication, diet or exercise.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Health: &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/entry/hip-flexor-stretch-aging-goog_l_6920a1b1e4b0536e01acda27?utm_campaign=yahoo-recirc" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:This Is 1 Stretch You Should Be Doing More Of As You Age;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;This Is 1 Stretch You Should Be Doing More Of As You Age&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Fesharaki-Zadeh said you and your doctor should focus on these lifestyle changes as early as possible, at least in midlife, not when you’re at the point when dementia starts to show up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“The front line of medical care are primary care physicians. These are the folks that, by having early discussions ... can go a long distance to prevent the onset of dementia,” he explained.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;There are also tests that can detect early signs of neurodegeneration and genetic markers of the disease. A primary care doctor can help you learn about these options.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“Up to 40% of dementias are potentially preventable,” he added, but it’s worth noting that dementia can also be genetic, which makes prevention trickier. But someone who is diagnosed with dementia or mild cognitive impairment can benefit from managing these risk factors, too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Health: &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/entry/study-reveals-the-biggest-risk-factors-for-getting-early-dementia-goog_l_689e1d2fe4b048e97f076d0f?utm_campaign=yahoo-recirc" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Study Reveals The Biggest Risk Factors For Getting Early Dementia;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Study Reveals The Biggest Risk Factors For Getting Early Dementia&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“The research is also showing that if you have two groups of individuals, someone who has comorbid metabolic diseases such as hypertension, high cholesterol, diabetes, versus somebody who doesn’t, and both of these individuals have dementia, the rates of progression of dementia in somebody who doesn’t have metabolic risk factors tend to be slower,” explained Fesharaki-Zadeh.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;It’s never too late to make changes and corrections, he noted, whether you’re a young, seemingly healthy person, in your 80s or 90s, or someone who has already been diagnosed with dementia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Our brains are highly malleable, Fesharaki-Zadeh said. So if you decide to make healthy lifestyle changes at any point, your brain will respond and be healthier for it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="mb-4 text-lg font-bold"&gt;Related...&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/entry/dementia-research-new-risk-factors-goog_l_69209634e4b06c13afa4a363?utm_campaign=yahoo-recirc" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Read the original on HuffPost;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Read the original on HuffPost&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Yahoo News Canada</author><pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 12:00:17 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihgFBVV95cUxQZ1N4WFF6aTJHa1pHQW1URVM2cUl0TVlJX2Q5dDUxeUFjcTJfVkZOdlhDU0dWMVo5UlRNNmFCZjFmYllJNGdDUTlOYmF4NzRqNV81RVdSWklqbnQwVTBxS3lZRlU1VGZ6SkRKM3o4dTZzcWdWY1V3LWR2NFNVd1d4UWJCRnUxZw</guid></item><item><title>根据顶级营养学家的说法，冬季可以吃5种超级食物来增强免疫力-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/5-superfoods-to-eat-during-winter-foods-to-boost-immunity-according-to-top-nutritionist/articleshow/125670007.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;div class="MwN2O"&gt;&lt;div class="vdo_embedd"&gt; &lt;div class="T22zO"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is the season of festivities, flu, and everything in between. As the temperature drops and the holiday season begins, the germs lurking in the dark also grow stronger. Most people may experience sniffles, colds, and that constant feeling of being one step away from falling sick. How do you keep illnesses at bay during this winter? By eating the right foods. In an Instagram video, Suman Agarwal, an Oxford-trained nutritionist and qualified fitness expert, has shared a list of foods that can help to boost immunity and protect you from diseases. “These are the foods that strengthen your immunity, keep your energy stable, and protect you from common winter infections, so make sure they’re on your plate every single day,” she said. Let’s take a look.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="6"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="7"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Mustard greens&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; Eat your greens, especially mustard greens. These tiny greens are at the top of Agarwal’s winter food list. “They are rich in antioxidants like A, C, and K. Very good for immunity and heart health because they are naturally high in fibre, support digestion, and prevent constipation,” she said. Mustard greens belong to the Brassicaceae family. A recent study by researchers at Nanjing Agricultural University found that Brassica vegetables, including broccoli, kale, cabbage, and mustard greens, contain numerous phytonutrients.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; The study, published in the journal &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="em" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Horticulture Research&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;, found that the glucosinolates, vitamins, carotenoids, phenolics, and essential minerals can &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://academic.oup.com/hr/article/12/2/uhae302/7849786" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;reduce the risk of cancer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, cardiovascular disease, and other chronic conditions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="15"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="lOvcW vdo_embedd"&gt;&lt;div class="k7lcu"&gt;&lt;p class="efT4r"&gt;7 Foods that boost immunity before winter sets in&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="17"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="18"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Gond (edible gum)&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; The second on the nutritionist’s list is Gond, or edible gum. A personal favourite winter food, Agarwal swears by gond ladoos. This edible gum is a natural resin obtained from the sap of acacia trees. “It helps you to maintain your body heat and provides energy. The presence of magnesium and zinc improves your immune system. Rich in calcium, it supports your bone health, and the presence of zinc and magnesium makes your immune system robust,” she said. The nutritionist also added that the gum acts as a galactagogue and naturally improves milk production.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="23"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="24"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Indian gooseberries&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; Indian gooseberry, or amla, is known for its numerous health benefits. An excellent source of vitamin C, this fruit also has potential antioxidant and heart-health benefits. A 2015 study published in the journal &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="em" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Oxidative Medicine and Cellular Longevity&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; found that gooseberry has potential &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1155/2015/950890" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;anticancer properties&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;. “It is very rich in vitamin C. But did you know that vitamin C in all fruits and vegetables starts getting oxidised after you cut it? But in amla, oxidation of vitamin C is very slow,” the nutritionist said. Consuming this fruit during winter boosts immunity and also improves hair and skin health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="32"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="33"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Sesame&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; Another kitchen staple, sesame, used in both sweet and savoury dishes, is a superfood. “Sesame seeds are thermogenic, meaning they naturally generate heat in your body. They have the highest calcium content among all seeds — 975 mg in just 100 grams,” she said. A 2012 American Heart Association meeting report also found that sesame oil is linked to a significant &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://newsroom.heart.org/news/sesame-and-rice-bran-oil-lowers-238424" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;drop in blood pressure and improved cholesterol levels&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="38"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="39"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Fresh turmeric&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; According to the nutritionist, turmeric, a popular spice used in Asian cuisines, is also a winter superfood. She noted that this yellow-coloured spice “is rich in antioxidants, has anti-inflammatory properties, and boosts your immunity.” A 2023 review of several studies has shown that turmeric contains several bioactive compounds that &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S2667142523000088" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;improve gut health&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; and the immune system. Agarwal revealed that she likes to add turmeric to her tea. “My winter tea is made from grated ginger and turmeric, maybe half and half a teaspoon, and by adding a little bit of honey and lime to it. This winter tea reduces gas and bloating, and is one of the best anti-inflammatory drinks you can have in the winter,” she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="43"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="44"&gt;&lt;i&gt;Note: The information provided in this article is for educational purposes only and is not intended as medical advice. Always consult a qualified healthcare professional before starting any new medication or treatment, or before changing your diet or supplement regimen.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="45"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 11:55:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilgJBVV95cUxNMS1CS0xRY3FwRUZCQzNyUWgzc1ZhVjczZjZKd0RrWjJBZVNYVk5pY3U4LXRSUzU5U3dXM0JoV0Zmb1FNWUtMcVlQS0FDZ01rZUxZNDhIQy1NSGJRNnI3TmpOMTMxSFdqbjZzVk5SazNJTG1xd04tYWdDcUJlc25xcWwxa1RCVE9DaXBQdlZjd2JUNHFOMTZJN3U4TlBWUFUxM1JVYll0OWVkRTRYUk5Xa1JIZ08xTi1LV0hiMEFOblRIT253ZkozZUM1RFhmdU9OSGtOUEEwVENBWHhjLUx3RHNxc3BGb3RsTXJLUHU4WVY3bEdOdHZDaXBPRDA1V1hBeExoN3N5UWZuQVZUQ251WDBNNFYyUQ</guid></item><item><title>微塑料和Forever Chemicals无处不在，包括您的水-这款水壶有助于过滤它们- EatingWell</title><link>https://www.eatingwell.com/lifestraw-water-filter-pitcher-amazon-11857656</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-page_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-page mntl-block structured-content" data-sc-sticky-offset="90" data-sc-ad-label-height="24" data-sc-ad-track-spacing="100" data-sc-min-track-height="250" data-sc-max-track-height="600" data-sc-breakpoint="50em" data-sc-load-immediate="4" data-sc-content-positions="[1, 1250, 1550, 1950, 2350, 2750, 3150, 3550, 3950]" data-bind-scroll-on-start="true"&gt;&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Water is something we all need. There are quite a few side effects &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/292133/10-dangerous-side-effects-of-not-drinking-enough-water/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;if you don’t drink enough every day&lt;/a&gt;. Not only can you experience brain fog, low energy, mood swings and weakness, but it can also lead to headaches, weight gain, an increased risk of stroke, a slower metabolism, overeating and skin damage. While &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/how-much-water-you-should-drink-daily-11739359" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;optimal hydration&lt;/a&gt; can vary from person to person, we generally recommend that women drink 11.5 cups of water per day, while men should aim for 15.5 cups. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_2-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_3-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; The only issue? Water doesn’t always taste good, &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/8072180/why-does-some-water-taste-better-than-others/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;nor does it taste the same&lt;/a&gt; everywhere. There can be unwanted minerals and even &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/why-is-the-california-prop-65-warning-label-on-my-food-containers-8420160" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;forever chemicals&lt;/a&gt; that make it far less motivating to pour a glass. The easiest solution is to invest in a &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/dp/B09R6211QP?tag=eatingwell-onsite-backup-20" data-component="amazon" data-source="affiliate" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="3" rel="sponsored nofollow noskim"&gt;water filter pitcher&lt;/a&gt;, and we found what might be the perfect one. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_4-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-lifestraw-home-water-pitcher"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_5-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; LifeStraw Home Water Pitcher &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure id="mntl-sc-block_6-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image--no-theme no-theme figure-landscape figure-high-res"&gt; 
&lt;figcaption id="mntl-figure-caption_1-0" class="comp mntl-figure-caption text-utility-100 figure-article-caption"&gt; &lt;span class="figure-article-caption-owner"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Amazon&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_8-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_9-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; The LifeStraw is a sleek, double-filtered water pitcher that claims to remove all unwanted impurities from your water. It’s made from glass, meaning your risk of adding &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/scientist-recommended-plastic-kitchen-tools-to-replace-amazon-11720768" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;additional microplastics&lt;/a&gt; from the container itself is mitigated. It does have a plastic BPA-free filter system, although it’s challenging to find a water filter pitcher without one, unfortunately. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_10-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_11-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; So, how does it work, exactly? The top section of the white insert includes a tall, slim membrane filter that removes microplastics, and potentially bacteria, according to the brand. Once the water passes through this filter, it makes its way through a carbon and ion exchange filter that can eliminate chemicals like PFAs (aka forever chemicals), lead, mercury and other heavy metals. LifeStraw claims that between the two filters, you’ll be weeding out over 30 contaminants while still maintaining the presence of minerals like magnesium and potassium. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_12-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_13-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; The membrane filter needs replacing once a year, and the carbon and ion filter every two months. Thankfully, the initial purchase of the pitcher includes filters, plus the brand sells a year's worth of filters in a &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/LifeStraw-Complete-Replacement-Membrane-Microfilter/dp/B092DN3W2B?tag=eatingwell-onsite-backup-20" data-component="amazon" data-source="affiliate" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1" rel="sponsored nofollow noskim"&gt;convenient kit&lt;/a&gt; for repurchase. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_14-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_15-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; This particular bottle holds up to 7 cups of water. It has a nifty spout on top and a flip-top lid to refill it easily. And, to make sure it doesn’t move around, the base is fitted with a removable silicone sleeve. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_16-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_17-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Amazon shoppers rave about this pitcher’s “&lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/gp/customer-reviews/RUSCBYPKJDST3?tag=eatingwell-onsite-backup-20" data-component="amazon" data-source="affiliate" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1" rel="sponsored nofollow noskim"&gt;perfect&lt;/a&gt;” design. “I have used numerous water filter pitchers over the years from numerous brands. This is by far the best-designed one as well as the one that produces the best-tasting filtered water,” &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/gp/customer-reviews/RSZ6EPDW7X08E?tag=eatingwell-onsite-backup-20" data-component="amazon" data-source="affiliate" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="2" rel="sponsored nofollow noskim"&gt;one reviewer wrote&lt;/a&gt;. “You can actually fill this one with water and use it immediately after without unfiltered water being poured out.” 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_18-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_19-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; “I notice a stark difference between water before the filter and after the filter,” a &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/gp/customer-reviews/R22YF1L1CT9XV4?tag=eatingwell-onsite-backup-20" data-component="amazon" data-source="affiliate" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1" rel="sponsored nofollow noskim"&gt;third person&lt;/a&gt; added, speaking to the filters’ effectiveness. “We like the design, how easy it is to clean and how easy it is to replace the filters,” a &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/gp/customer-reviews/R1M5AFUBJ6537M?tag=eatingwell-onsite-backup-20" data-component="amazon" data-source="affiliate" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="2" rel="sponsored nofollow noskim"&gt;fourth shopper&lt;/a&gt; noted. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_20-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_21-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; For cleaner water that’ll help you hit those necessary hydration goals, opt for the smart &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/LifeStraw-Home-Protection-parasites-microplastics/dp/B09R6211QP?tag=eatingwell-onsite-backup-20" data-component="amazon" data-source="affiliate" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1" rel="sponsored nofollow noskim"&gt;LifeStraw water pitcher&lt;/a&gt;. While it runs for $49, it’s undoubtedly “&lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/gp/customer-reviews/R1RA3788I14XH6?tag=eatingwell-onsite-backup-20" data-component="amazon" data-source="affiliate" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="2" rel="sponsored nofollow noskim"&gt;worth the money&lt;/a&gt;." 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_22-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-shop-more-glass-water-pitchers-on-amazon"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_23-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Shop More Glass Water Pitchers on Amazon &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-waterdrop-7-cup-glass-water-filter-pitcher"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_24-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Waterdrop 7-Cup Glass Water Filter Pitcher &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure id="mntl-sc-block_25-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image--no-theme no-theme figure-landscape figure-high-res"&gt; 
&lt;figcaption id="mntl-figure-caption_2-0" class="comp mntl-figure-caption text-utility-100 figure-article-caption"&gt; &lt;span class="figure-article-caption-owner"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Amazon&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_27-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-waterdrop-glass-large-22-cup-rechargeable-water-filter-dispenser"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_28-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Waterdrop Glass Large 22-Cup Rechargeable Water Filter Dispenser &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure id="mntl-sc-block_29-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image--no-theme no-theme figure-landscape figure-high-res"&gt; 
&lt;figcaption id="mntl-figure-caption_3-0" class="comp mntl-figure-caption text-utility-100 figure-article-caption"&gt; &lt;span class="figure-article-caption-owner"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Amazon&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_31-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-zerowater-40-cup-ready-pour-glass-water-filter-dispenser"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_32-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; ZeroWater 40-Cup Ready-Pour Glass Water Filter Dispenser &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure id="mntl-sc-block_33-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image--no-theme no-theme figure-landscape figure-high-res"&gt; 
&lt;figcaption id="mntl-figure-caption_4-0" class="comp mntl-figure-caption text-utility-100 figure-article-caption"&gt; &lt;span class="figure-article-caption-owner"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Amazon&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_35-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-aarke-purifier-5-cup-glass-water-pitcher"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_36-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Aarke Purifier 5-Cup Glass Water Pitcher &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure id="mntl-sc-block_37-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image--no-theme no-theme figure-landscape figure-high-res"&gt; 
&lt;figcaption id="mntl-figure-caption_5-0" class="comp mntl-figure-caption text-utility-100 figure-article-caption"&gt; &lt;span class="figure-article-caption-owner"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Amazon&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_39-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_40-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;em&gt;At the time of publishing, the price was $49.&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>EatingWell</author><pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 11:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMifkFVX3lxTE1Sb1dFQXlOX1pKRW5rNVp4NnY2cmV0bE5rRXZhMGhHM1ZwSUx0QS0zWXNCTEpSa2VXQVBTYk5WaDI0cllXemZ4bEZoMlpZQVJ1UzFHdF90UVprdDJjdnlYdndRblJ1cmtKSnJJQXhsQzkzRXNIenhIRnB2Mld1Zw</guid></item><item><title>如何在寒冷的冬季增加卡路里消耗的棕色脂肪- BBC</title><link>https://www.bbc.com/future/article/20251128-how-to-boost-your-calorie-crunching-brown-fat-in-the-cold-winter-months</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="sc-85f9acf9-0 kfxpiP"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;However, it's possible that, while brown fat might not help you shed the pounds, it could still boost your health in other ways. For instance, instead of burning calories, brown fat could help &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.pnas.org/doi/10.1073/pnas.2216435119" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;to improve metabolic health&lt;/a&gt; – the body’s ability to process and use energy from food effectively. People who have poor metabolic health are unable to clear glucose from their blood quickly, raising their risk of type 2 diabetes. Brown fat could act simply by taking up glucose from the bloodstream, or by secreting hormones that act on other tissues to regulate insulin sensitivity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"In terms of whole-body energy expenditure, it [brown fat] probably does not play as large of a role in humans as it does in mice," says Cohen. "So my personal feeling, based on the data, is that brown fat activation is not going to be a good means to treat obesity or to lose significant amounts of weight." &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"However, the data is much stronger to suggest that activating brown fat might lower glucose levels and improve metabolic health. So, I think if there is going to be a therapeutic side to this, it's much more likely going to be in treating the complications of obesity and ageing than in treating obesity per se."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="sc-2b8ea91d-0 faEbjU"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-2b8ea91d-2 ejktow"&gt;The shock of cold-water immersion causes the body to think it's in danger&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;But how can we activate brown fat, and harness the superpowers it may – or may not – contain? One way is to expose yourself to cold, as uncomfortable as it may be. Think ice baths, cold water swimming, or cryotherapy chambers – a specialised device that exposes the body to extremely low temperatures for one to three minutes to promote healing and wellness. The shock of cold-water immersion causes the body to think it's in danger, activating the fight-or-flight response. This releases the neurotransmitter noradrenalin, which binds to and "activates" brown fat cells.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BBC</author><pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMitgFBVV95cUxOajZuN2h4MjBvaUFJZ25lNmNKU2steGpQS2M0Qk50OGZaVEdta0duTEJwWWJ1a056X2FFbGZ1My1MMURHNVN1UWtSQnAzWGYtNzM0bWdYR3R3QUk3M0ZlTlRwSUVaRkVwUUN6aXF4ZDljSV9vQk9Ta1NZRkl5akFKVXlrMHVLUDJoQTNzSlBQanluRGlKWC1SbUs5NUs2c3FYbHpVVTYyS0MtS2dlUTdmYW5NRTVDQQ</guid></item><item><title>学校的疫苗接种率引起了家长、医疗专业人员的关注- TribLIVE.com</title><link>https://triblive.com/local/valley-news-dispatch/vaccination-rates-in-schools-cause-concern-for-parents-medical-professionals/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="storyContent"&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lucas James relies on others to be vaccinated because, for now, he can’t be.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="neFMT neFMT_body-editorial"&gt;A leukemia patient and stem cell transplant recipient, Lucas, 16, of Hempfield receives intravenous antibody treatments to help him rebuild his immune system.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="neFMT neFMT_body-editorial"&gt;“(Doctors) said he may never be able to be vaccinated again if his body doesn’t stop needing these transfusions,” said his mother, Megan James.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="neFMT neFMT_body-editorial"&gt;Lucas is among the growing number of school-age children who, for one reason or another, are not being vaccinated against preventable diseases. Some, like Lucas, may be unvaccinated for medical reasons. Others might be because of religious beliefs.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="neFMT neFMT_body-editorial"&gt;The trend is causing concern among medical professionals — and affecting the population’s herd immunity.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In Pennsylvania, students in kindergarten are required to have four doses of the vaccine against diphtheria, tetanus and pertussis; four doses of the polio vaccine; two doses of measles, mumps, rubella (MMR); three doses of hepatitis B; and two doses of the varicella (chickenpox) vaccine.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Students also can provide evidence of immunity, such as proof they’ve already had and recovered from a disease such as chickenpox.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Without the vaccinations, students must apply for an exemption. Increasingly, more parents or guardians are doing just that. Students in Pennsylvania also can be declared exempt from vaccines for religious or philosophical reasons.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Almost 1,800 students in Allegheny County submitted medical, religious or philosophical vaccination exemptions in 2024, compared with about 1,300 in 2020, a 38% increase, according to figures from the state health department.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Westmoreland County saw an even bigger jump — about 130% — with 926 students filing for exemptions in 2024, compared with just under 400 in 2020.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are numerous reasons a child is unable to be vaccinated, including that they have weakened immune systems, are on chemotherapy or had an allergic reaction to a vaccine, said Dr. Joseph Aracri, system chair of pediatrics with Allegheny Health Network Pediatric Institute.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Someone like Lucas relies on herd immunity to remain illness-free. Herd immunity is when a disease has little chance of spreading within a population because people are resistant to it, either from having the disease and recovering or, more commonly, because they have been vaccinated against it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once a nonissue for many diseases, herd immunity is coming back into question for some diseases, according to the state Department of Health.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Data shows school-age children in several Western Pennsylvania counties below herd immunity levels for some diseases, including measles, mumps and rubella. Allegheny, Westmoreland, Butler, Fayette, Greene, Indiana and Beaver counties report vaccination rates for kindergarten-age children for the MMR vaccine are below the 95% threshold for herd immunity, according to 2024 data from the &lt;a href="https://www.pa.gov/agencies/health/programs/immunizations/rates" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Pennsylvania Department of Health&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That can be concerning for someone like Lucas.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“He’d be very vulnerable if he were exposed to someone with a virus,” his mother said. “It would be very likely that he would catch something.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Things like the measles are really scary for us.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A sophomore at Hempfield Area Senior High School, Lucas was diagnosed with leukemia in January 2022. After two years of treatments, doctors thought the cancer had gone into remission, but it returned in January 2024, just days after he had finished a course of chemotherapy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In June 2024, Lucas underwent a blood-making bone marrow stem cell transplant. The procedure left his immune system vulnerable.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While Lucas attends school in-person, he wears a mask to protect himself. Megan James said that if Hempfield’s vaccination rates drop, Lucas would need to be pulled out of school again.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It’s very frustrating,” James said. “He’s been through enough. We shouldn’t have to isolate him because of misinformation.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Neither federal nor state health agencies track how many students are fully up to schedule for all vaccines; they instead track the student population by individual vaccines.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lucas’ doctors are keeping an eye on outbreaks and will notify her if it becomes dangerous, James said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Things that most kids can fight off, his body wouldn’t be able to fight back,” she said. “It’s scary times.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="neFMT neFMT_body-subhead"&gt;Growing hesitancy&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Vaccine hesitancy has become a growing trend thanks, in part, to the covid-19 pandemic and skepticism surrounding the covid vaccine, Aracri said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;People can easily fall victim to misinformation about vaccines on social media, said Barbara Nightingale, deputy director for clinical services with the Allegheny County Health Department.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“We are not surprised by the decline (in vaccination rates), since vaccine hesitancy has been growing across the U.S. and globally for the past decade,” Nightingale said. “Because vaccine misinformation feeds off fear, it can spread easily, particularly as more residents receive health information from social media.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She recommends residents speak with their health care provider if they have any concerns about the effects or safety of vaccinations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Aracri said this is the second time in his career he has seen a trending decrease in vaccination rates. The first time was in the late 1990s when a paper by an English anti-vaccine activist and former surgeon falsely claimed a link between the MMR vaccine and bowel disease and autism, he said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now Aracri is seeing what he calls hesitancy from parents rather than resistance in regard to vaccinating their children.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I think that this time around what we’re seeing is just more questions and more of an understanding,” Aracri said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The covid pandemic was a major culprit and particularly damaging from a vaccine acceptance standpoint, he said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“(People were) being forced to get a covid shot, and the covid shot was supposed to bring an end to the pandemic,” Aracri said. “And we found out that, while it really didn’t — it protected those of our most vulnerable — but it didn’t necessarily prevent the spread or end the covid pandemic anytime sooner. So whenever you give a child a shot and they still end up getting covid, that makes you doubt the other things.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This, combined with political unrest, has created uncertainty, he said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“People have access to all kinds of unedited information that’s out there,” Aracri said. “Our job is to be able to, first, be aware of all misinformation, disinformation or whatever you want to call it, and be able to have that conversation and discuss with the patient the benefits of being vaccinated as opposed to the risks.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Part of the problem: No vaccine is 100% effective for 100% of the population.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Different vaccines have different levels of effectiveness, Aracri said. The MMR vaccine is about 98% effective, he said, while other vaccines such as the flu shot — a seasonal vaccine — can be anywhere from 40% to 75% effective each year because the flu virus constantly mutates. He emphasized the importance for providers to counsel patients and parents when they have questions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="neFMT neFMT_body-subhead"&gt;In-school concerns&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Darcy Lutz has been a nurse at Shaler Area High School for the past six years. She said her job involves two main responsibilities regarding student vaccinations: making sure the school, parents and students are in compliance with Pennsylvania school health laws and providing accurate information about vaccines.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lutz called the dropping vaccination rates concerning. Although, she said, the district’s percentages haven’t dropped from last school year, education about vaccines is more important than ever.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“We’re not here to fight with people about their strongly held beliefs,” Lutz said. “If people have questions, we’re always here to talk and educate.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Shaler Area has a 97% MMR vaccination rate, but because the disease is so contagious, an outbreak could occur if that were to fall as little as 2%, Lutz said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“The most vulnerable populations really rely on herd immunity,” she said. “When we see those rates dip, it really is dangerous.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In her nine years as a school nurse, Lutz said, she has encountered various reasons children go unvaccinated. The biggest factor is access to health care, she said. Some families have no insurance or don’t have reliable transportation to get to a doctor. There’s also a rising immigrant and refugee population in the district, and some of those families are still working to catch up with the required vaccine schedule, she said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The district has brought Allegheny County’s mobile health clinic to its schools to give families direct access to health care.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She also cited two other reasons for parents deciding not to vaccinate their children: misinformation and feeling as though their freedoms are being threatened when they’re told it’s required by law to get vaccinated.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="neFMT neFMT_body-subhead"&gt;Disease resurgence &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Aracri pointed to a recent outbreak of the measles in Texas as an example of how a disease can reemerge.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He said a large population was unvaccinated, falling below herd immunity levels, and it caused an outbreak. It grew to be the largest measles outbreak in the U.S. in more than 30 years, with about 760 confirmed cases in Texas by August. The outbreak resulted in 99 hospitalizations and the deaths of two unvaccinated school-age children.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nightingale said residents should know that many people are vaccinated against diseases that once were common and caused serious illness or death. For example, the polio vaccine, developed by Jonas Salk at the University of Pittsburgh and widely distributed during the 1950s, has brought down cases of polio worldwide by more than 99%, she said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“All vaccines play an important role in saving lives, reducing disease and creating a healthy community,” Nightingale said. “This role is increasingly important when school-age children are involved, as their immune system is not completely developed.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nightingale said that if rates continue to drop, communities are at a higher risk of a resurgence of diseases.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It is especially important for residents to remember that, like any medical intervention, vaccines carry some risks,” she said, “but for most people the risk of the disease is far greater.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p class="credits"&gt;Haley Daugherty is a TribLive reporter covering local politics, feature stories and Allegheny County news. A native of Pittsburgh, she lived in Alabama for six years. She joined the Trib in 2022 after graduating from Chatham University. She can be reached at &lt;a href="mailto:hdaugherty@triblive.com"&gt;hdaugherty@triblive.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>TribLIVE.com</author><pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 09:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiwwFBVV95cUxOaUJEN0JhbXlkM2g1N3RMR2gtc1hUWmFqaTZLanZ2NDQzdkZGeVo3MUR5b29RaldyZmZkSUYzSWdqMXR4TEVJSGo1WFdkMjhELUdZei1hYXp5Y2JjRlhUYmN6ZTFEVU5lbEFreXFndHIzOXBjZFRocWJyZjFxVklVLWYwblR6dHlmUlJicmNlZm1rQVRQWmR2QXR2Wlp6bERUNjVWZV9vYTdXd2ZfRVM1U1JxQTZNQWNUb3pQdVFVX3k3d1U</guid></item><item><title>不仅仅是低密度脂蛋白胆固醇：这里有6种可以预测寿命的生物标志物-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/fitness/not-just-ldl-cholesterol-here-are-6-biomarkers-that-can-predict-longevity/photostory/125669525.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="COQxt" data-ua-type="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Since these biomarkers tap distinct, and partly overlapping, pathways , combined assessment yields a richer picture of biological age and mortality risk than any single measure. Many cohort studies use multi-marker models and find improved prediction when functional (fitness/strength), anthropometric and biochemical markers are combined.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;Relying on a single biomarker, whether LDL cholesterol, BMI or resting heart rate, captures only one dimension of health, which can miss early physiological changes occurring elsewhere in the body. In contrast, using a panel of diverse biomarkers provides a far more accurate and holistic picture of biological aging and long-term risk. This integrated approach helps identify risk earlier, guide more personalized interventions and track meaningful improvements across multiple physiological domains, ultimately improving both lifespan and healthspan.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 07:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi_AFBVV95cUxNcmtXWmNjaVB1UDVKUEFyTjc4akNnLUpaT01UN1dvblphckpsTHZGQjFJc2ZubDFMUVlvcWhYa1BkSTVaNFFVSkYzT2x1R0tYU1BUVDMyRXFFeFgzU24yTjhmMXdqQ0xrMUtDYm95b1k4R3NXWG92WDFDOG11bDJMQVhZNVRZQVQxS0JjS1ozb2Y4NnM1UzNrdFVaTWNyaFVDbzhkV2ROY0oxZTJScXdKb1NzeE9TNU9lNWVsWE1EZFJYbWhrSk9CalY5NVUzNGYtTmoydFpPQXZSS0VlVk81aWlETXNTMG11STVpaGNzWmlCM2hiTkNVWDlDN1XSAYQCQVVfeXFMT1EzSmltY095ampESDdRZXJNX01fQkIyVXpoZzZ4X3p6UEE0RC1MY1VZQzl1Y0pfZEZwM0tRaUhtYmhNeU52OERXaGhJZ0ROMWFzeW8zbDY3WG9LbmhMNGtCUjd6WUdlbDRDbUVZWlBYY2JxU1VGbU90UmU5QnFpTkE0THd4QWJXYnN2TDdBS3F1ZVBQbHRJQTUzb1RITmZJZUpmaDIwSUo3cHdHVGJoaEt3ZDVSY0hva3NoYmthZzRKcnRYUS03RHFLYk85RzdYelNOaTUtdUVIS1ZBYkJiclJ5U2ZfLWhtdW8zckh2VEhKbFAtRXoxdkdKNkNyV1FuLUFHN1M</guid></item><item><title>“时时刻刻” ：迪比克人学习如何驾驭患有罕见疾病的生活- TelegraphHerald.com</title><link>https://www.telegraphherald.com/news/tri-state/article_b3f969d4-8a01-4468-a284-154ff34d4c42.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="article-body" itemprop="articleBody" class="asset-content  subscriber-premium" false&gt;
                                &lt;meta itemprop="isAccessibleForFree" content="false"&gt;
                                
                                
                                &lt;div class="subscriber-preview"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Evan Erickson was a thriving young college graduate with a bright future, having studied clarinet and music composition at the University of Memphis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="subscriber-preview"&gt;&lt;p&gt;A Dubuque native and Hempstead High School alum, the accomplished 22-year-old already had realized his instrumental music being performed by ensembles throughout the country.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="subscriber-only"&gt;&lt;p&gt;He had just finished his engagement as a community coordinator for a summer music festival in August 2024 when suddenly Erickson came down with what he described as a panic attack, followed by a severe and prolonged migraine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="subscriber-only"&gt;&lt;p&gt;“It came out of nowhere,” he said. “Nothing like that had ever happened to me before.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="subscriber-only"&gt;&lt;p&gt;A month later, the illness seemingly progressed, with Erickson suffering debilitating migraines almost daily.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="subscriber-only"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Then, Erickson came down with what he described as “the worst flu” he had ever experienced, resulting in a series of doctor’s appointments, X-rays and seven courses of antibiotics that treated symptoms but never got to the root of the cause.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="subscriber-only"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Erickson was hospitalized in October 2024, with his liver and spleen in serious decline. He was diagnosed with mononucleosis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="subscriber-only"&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, more than one year later, Erickson said he has never recovered from the feeling he was experiencing upon entering the hospital.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="subscriber-only"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Having returned to Dubuque to be cared for by his mother, Erickson began traveling to Iowa City for further testing and to receive treatment at University of Iowa Health Care, where mounting evidence pointed him toward the possibility of a rare and complex neuro-immune disease known as myalgic encephalomyelitis/chronic fatigue syndrome, or ME/CFS.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="subscriber-only"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Although Erickson finally can name what has been ailing him, the diagnosis yields more questions than answers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="subscriber-only"&gt;&lt;p&gt;“There is no direct pinpoint to say what caused it,” Erickson said. “There is no cure. From day to day, I can never know how I’ll be feeling, what will trigger the next spiral or how long it will take me to recover from it.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="subscriber-only"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;‘A nightmare’&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="subscriber-only"&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention, 1% of mononucleosis cases have been known to trigger ME/CFS.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="subscriber-only"&gt;&lt;p&gt;The various symptoms are problematic, as they can mirror the common cold and flu, including muscle and joint pain, problems with standing, headaches, sore throat, tender lymph nodes, digestive issues and increased sensitivity to food and chemicals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="subscriber-only"&gt;&lt;p&gt;A hallmark of the disease is post-exertional malaise, in which physical or mental activity can cause a significant worsening of symptoms, as well as severe fatigue, cognitive difficulties and trouble sleeping.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="subscriber-only"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Symptoms also can come and go, with limited predictability of their severity over time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="subscriber-only"&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The anxiety of it is such a scary thing from the possibility of the symptoms that can occur, even from sitting, standing or trying to go for a short walk,” Erickson said. “It feels like I’m at death’s door. There are some days I’m stuck in my room or can’t leave my bed. I don’t interact with people very much. I’m only able to watch videos or play games because I never know what’s going to trigger it.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="subscriber-only"&gt;&lt;p&gt;There are no known causes or cures. And treatment usually equates to catering to symptoms that most impact an individual’s ability to perform normal daily activities.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="subscriber-only"&gt;&lt;p&gt;“It has been a terrible discovery to realize that the disease I am dealing with, there are very little answers for,” Erickson said. “The whole process has been ruling out every other possible thing that could be causing it. It has taken me from literally graduating as one of the top students in my class, earning awards in outstanding achievement and with a promising career in music ahead of me — all that work to being struck with so much pain I can barely move some days. It has been a nightmare.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p id="tncms-region-article_instory_middle" class="tncms-region hidden-print"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="subscriber-only"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Still bedridden most days, Erickson was able to tap into his creativity, recording a timelapse video, “Spend a Week with M.E.,” a weeklong documentation of his experience with the disease to raise awareness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="subscriber-only"&gt;&lt;p&gt;The video captures Erickson alone in his room — sometimes sleeping, sometimes reading, sometimes scrolling on a digital tablet or playing a game. It shows the true crux of the disease: the isolation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="subscriber-only"&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I spend a lot of time by myself,” Erickson said. “Sometimes, I’ll feel well enough to have a visit from a friend.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="subscriber-only"&gt;&lt;p&gt;After a year of being too ill to write music or tolerate sounds in the same way, Erickson recently mustered enough energy to put together an album, titled “A Gesture Makes a World,” to accompany the video.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="subscriber-only"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Both projects led him to launch Gifts for M.E., a nonprofit to provide items to ME/CFS patients and their caregivers throughout the U.S.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="subscriber-only"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Because symptoms also can include dizziness and increased sensitivity to light and sound, items include black-out sleep masks, noise-canceling headphones, shower chairs, heart-rate monitors, low-light and low-stimulation gaming consoles and grocery delivery subscriptions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="subscriber-only"&gt;&lt;p&gt;“It has been a very calm and very simple thing I can do that enables me to feel as though I am still productive in some way in the world,” Erickson said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="subscriber-only"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;A misunderstood disease&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="subscriber-only"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Despite an estimated 3.3 million people suffering from it in the U.S., according to the CDC, ME/CFS remains a highly misunderstood disease. More than nine out of 10 individuals with it have yet to be diagnosed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="subscriber-only"&gt;&lt;p&gt;“One reason it’s difficult to diagnose is because there is no targeted test for ME/CFS, as it has the ability to affect all parts of the body,” said Ruby Tam, of ME/CFS Clinic Minnesota. “Another reason is that some individuals suffering from the disease have limited access to health care or resources to connect them to health care providers who know enough about ME/CFS to be able to treat it or understand it.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="subscriber-only"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tam, who also treats Erickson, is a family medicine doctor who practiced at Northwest Family Clinics in Minnesota from 2012 to 2022. She encountered her first ME/CFS patient in 2015. After retiring from family practice in 2023, Tam launched ME/CFS Clinic Minnesota, volunteering her time to study and treat individuals with ME/CFS.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="subscriber-only"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Erickson’s charity is partnered with the organization.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="subscriber-only"&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Most people who come and see me have exhausted their resources and don’t know who else to talk to,” Tam said. “They don’t know what they’re dealing with, but they know how they’re feeling, and they want answers as to what they’re dealing with. In many cases of ME/CFS, unfortunately, what we’re finding is many patients aren’t being believed by practitioners. But there also has been limited research and no path to learning more about this disease. So, there are limitations in treating only the symptoms, rather than understanding the underlying cause.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="subscriber-only"&gt;&lt;p&gt;ME/CFS Clinic Minnesota advocates for patients and works with providers to promote additional research, “providing resources toward knowing how to work with this disease and how to treat symptoms to make them more manageable for patients,” Tam said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="subscriber-only"&gt;&lt;p&gt;In working with patients, Tam said she has seen some go into periods of remission, where — with ongoing care and not overly exerting themselves — they can experience reasonable sleep and a normalized way of life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="subscriber-only"&gt;&lt;p&gt;“That, of course, is the main goal — allowing people to have some chance at a normal life,” Tam said. “It’s different for everyone dealing with the illness. For Evan, we’re still working. But he’s a remarkable person, and the work he is doing to raise funds and bring more eyes and awareness to the disease is encouraging.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="subscriber-only"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tam’s work for the cause also has provided a spark of optimism for Erickson, who described most days now as witnessing “a slow melting away” of his life prior to the disease and everything he had been working toward.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="subscriber-only"&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Sometimes, it’s not even taking it day by day, but hour by hour, and realizing that I might not ever get back to my old life, but be building something new,” he said. “Still, there is some hope and fulfillment that has come from knowing I’m trying to do something in my experience with ME/CFS to help others as well, and to educate people that this is real. That’s what’s driving me right now.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
                                &lt;p id="tncms-region-article_bottom_content" class="tncms-region hidden-print"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
                                
                            &lt;/div&gt;

                            

                            
    


                            
    


                            
                                &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>TelegraphHerald.com</author><pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMinAFBVV95cUxNd1ZaM3dnbUZ2eENxVUs2bGJ3R212SDl1N3V1SVk1OWZlS1VORkRtZFZCdFdsWGxERXptcUF0MTluUFRwWk91bldScFJ2NHpSVmNVdGtzUXg4WDRxb2s5bWE5d1ZhNm5ycXduNGRhSVllb1JtcWtjWjRvMWdyZlZLcWpIUUxONTBXb2NBY2hVNnVob054YmtNVmJYcXk</guid></item><item><title>为什么可以改变您的健康和福祉–方法如下-《独立报》</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/health-and-fitness/forest-bathing-mindful-hiking-nature-wellness-b2857783.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="sc-jbiisr-0 bxpovR sc-jbiisr-1 sc-1wfc891-0 fooWDH" id="main"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="big-letter"&gt;F&lt;/span&gt;orest bathing, that is, taking a mindful walk or hike through the woods, is nothing new. It’s something I’ve done since I could walk and people were mindfully spending time among trees for centuries before we coined the term “forest bathing” in the eighties. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Multiple medical experts on my &lt;a href="/topic/well-enough"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Well Enough&lt;/em&gt; podcast &lt;/a&gt;have told me that a walk in nature, a hand on a tree trunk or time spent thinking about trees can improve mood. And the NHS is now directly recommending time in nature, with new “green social prescribing” initiatives urging those with poor mental health to spend more time outdoors (something they have been doing in &lt;a href="/travel/europe/sweden/sweden-prescribed-digital-detox-b2862011.html" title="Doctors are now ‘prescribing’ Sweden – this is what happened when I ditched my phone for the Scandi wilderness"&gt;Sweden &lt;/a&gt;for a while). &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Still, recent data from a &lt;a rel="nofollow" data-affiliate="true" target="_blank" href="http://redirect.viglink.com?u=https%3A%2F%2Flink.springer.com%2Farticle%2F10.1007%2Fs13280-025-02275-w&amp;amp;articleId=b2857783&amp;amp;key=5b1a6400a3c0d931ed2037885e1a27a3"&gt;global study&lt;/a&gt; shows that the UK is one of the places where people feel the least connected to nature. So to mark National Tree Week, I spoke with experts to learn more about the benefits of forest bathing and why a mindful walk in the woods can make all the difference to your health. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-kk992l-0 dDVXDN"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What is forest bathing?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Shinrin-yoku” translates as “bathing in the forest atmosphere”, or “taking in the forest through our senses”. It was conceived of as an intentional practice as a response to high stress levels in Japanese city workers by government minister Tomohide Akiyama in the eighties.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The&lt;a href="/health-and-fitness/walking-step-count-heart-health-b2854590.html" title="The big mistake people make when walking 10,000 steps per day"&gt; walking part is obviously good for you. &lt;/a&gt;But forest bathing is considered more of a workout for the mind than the body. The key part is simply being in nature, connecting with it through all of our senses: sight, hearing, taste, smell and touch, dropping out of the mind and into the body. It sounds simple but this is something we rarely do, surrounded as we are by the distractions of modern life. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“We are often told that distress is ‘all in the mind’, says clinical psychologist &lt;a rel="nofollow" target="_blank" href="https://www.operationcentaur.com/team"&gt;Puffin O’Hanlon. &lt;/a&gt;“Actually, distress lives in our bodies, and in our relationships. And more specifically, distress radiates from points of disconnection – from the natural world, from each other, and between parts of ourselves.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“In much of the Western world we have come to separate body from mind and to privilege mind,” says O’Hanlon, who recently led me on a forest bathing tour through Richmond Park, where she runs Project Centaur – an organisation offering nature and equine therapy. “We are taught to experience and navigate the world through language, and the problem-solving, impulse-controlling functions of the prefrontal cortex – our so-called rational brains.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“But the more we rely on the human rational brain to lead the way, the more difficult it becomes to direct attention or energy to the myriad other ways of being, problem solving and communicating.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Read more: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="/health-and-fitness/essentialism-changed-my-life-b2731188.html" title="Essentialism: how the disciplined pursuit of less changed my life"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Essentialism: how the disciplined pursuit of less changed my life&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Indeed, some of us need help to do this, which is why all manner of wellness studios, hotels and organisations now offer to guide visitors through forest bathing and mindful hiking experiences, showing us how to focus on the senses and connect with the natural world. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;During a stay at Mallorca’s clifftop &lt;a href="/travel/hotels/jumeirah-mallorca-hotel-and-spa-review-b2816041.html" title="Jumeirah Mallorca, hotel review"&gt;Jumeirah hotel&lt;/a&gt;, I was able to book a brilliant guided mindfulness hike up into the mountains. I’ve been lucky to forest bathe in Japan too, in the forests surrounding Kinosaki and Kyoto, where I traversed glades, climbed mossy staircases and paused at temples to reflect. And I’ve also experienced many forest bathing in programmes closer to home, in the New Forest, Hertfordshire and Sussex.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But obviously, you don’t need to be led by anyone or pay a fee to walk mindfully and focus on your senses. A guide might help, but for the most part, this practice is about embracing simplicity, stillness and awareness. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="sc-awdjp1-2 cbpRGD sc-awdjp1-3 image align-center"&gt;&lt;figure class="sc-1cbdeug-0 cXcwgU"&gt;&lt;div data-gallery-length="2" class="sc-awdjp1-0 cztisH"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.independent.co.uk/2025/11/25/17/50/iStock-2226638823.jpg" srcset="https://static.independent.co.uk/2025/11/25/17/50/iStock-2226638823.jpg?quality=75&amp;amp;width=320&amp;amp;auto=webp 320w, https://static.independent.co.uk/2025/11/25/17/50/iStock-2226638823.jpg?quality=75&amp;amp;width=640&amp;amp;auto=webp 640w" loading="lazy" alt="Forest bathing has been shown to reduce stress hormones and blood pressure" class="sc-1mc30lb-0 ggpMaE inline-gallery-btn"&gt;&lt;p class="hydrate-root sc-10wlkbs-0 sc-awdjp1-1 bMDiiD" data-component="AutoGalleryButton" data-theme-name="base"&gt;&lt;button class="sc-1uf4o3q-0 dkRtZs inline-gallery-btn" id="trigger-autogallery-90421"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-1uf4o3q-1 hwVecx"&gt;open image in gallery&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-1cbdeug-1 sc-1cbdeug-3 gtVitN hgzWpY"&gt;Forest bathing has been shown to reduce stress hormones and blood pressure&lt;span class="sc-1cbdeug-7 exGSyR"&gt; (Getty/iStock)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="sc-kk992l-0 dDVXDN"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Science-backed benefits of being in nature&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you still need convincing, there are various studies that show that forest bathing makes us feel better. Olga Terebenina and Gary Evans, the founders of &lt;a rel="nofollow" target="_blank" href="https://tfb.institute/"&gt;The Forest Bathing Institute&lt;/a&gt; and authors of &lt;em&gt;The Healing Power of Trees&lt;/em&gt;, write in the book’s preface: “Groundbreaking research has shown that forests are able to boost our immune system and even affect our physiology after only a couple of hours spent mindfully among the trees.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A &lt;a rel="nofollow" target="_blank" href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC9665958/"&gt;2022&lt;/a&gt; study indicated that forest bathing has the power to reduce blood pressure, heart rate and stress hormone levels. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study’s author, Qing Li, says, “My research team has established a new medical science called Forest Medicine; a new interdisciplinary science that studies the effects of forest environments on human health.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“In the profile of mood states (POMS) test, shinrin-yoku reduces the scores for anxiety, depression, anger, fatigue and confusion, and increases the score for vigour, showing preventive effects on depression.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A more recent &lt;a rel="nofollow" target="_blank" href="https://www.frontiersin.org/journals/public-health/articles/10.3389/fpubh.2025.1454992/full"&gt;2025 study &lt;/a&gt;corroborated these findings, showing that “forest bathing interventions might improve mental and physical health, reduce blood pressure, improve sleep quality and boost immunity, as well as alleviate depression, anxiety, and stress”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Read more: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="/health-and-fitness/gemma-ogston-functional-mushrooms-b2836844.html" title="Chef and entrepreneur Gemma Ogston on shrooms, social media and why adaptogens aren’t a trend"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Chef and entrepreneur Gemma Ogston on shrooms, social media and why adaptogens aren’t a trend&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;O’Hanlon explains that our brains and bodies are naturally in tune with the scents, shapes and vibrations of green spaces, which is why spending more time in nature can help improve wellbeing. “We are wired for this stuff. We are highly sensitive to the smell of petrichor – the compounds released by bacteria in the soil when it rains after a dry spell. We are fluent in fractals – the repeating patterns of nature found in petals and waves. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“But without attention, there is limited awareness, and as awareness decreases, so does connection. It is really rather difficult for many of us to feel connected to nature, to each other, or to what is happening in and around us in the present moment.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Earth has a natural frequency, known as the Schumann resonance, which is a set of electromagnetic waves around the planet, with the fundamental frequency being approximately 7.83Hz. This fundamental frequency is often called the “earth's heartbeat”, and there are ongoing scientific studies into its effects on human behaviour and wellbeing. What forest bathing seeks to achieve is a quieting of outside noise and an opportunity to tap back into this frequency. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some studies show that our brain activity seems to align with Earth’s natural electromagnetic rhythms. This could explain why changes in these fields can affect our mood, sleep or concentration and why spending time in nature away from cities, noise, technology and other distractions can allow us to reconnect with natural rhythms. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="taboola-mid-article-thumbnails-us-premium-ii" class="sc-looa6c-0 cPCVUJ"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There is another benefit to interacting with nature, which is that it encourages our desire to protect it. By reminding ourselves of the importance of green spaces and natural ecosystems, we seek to preserve them and integrate into them, where previously we had separated ourselves. And that can only be a good thing. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt; Read more: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="/health-and-fitness/mens-mental-health-depression-loneliness-owen-o-kane-b2859419.html" title="Men are still faking it until they break: Inside the crisis of hidden depression"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Men are still faking it until they break: Inside the crisis of hidden depression&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Independent</author><pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMirAFBVV95cUxNOHJIRndSb01CNlJoLUZHV1h2MFNvazFlV1B4Wnp6UnhpV0I4YXNnc0JIUHhoX0p1VnZUX25GOTV6VnpFaXN2Z0NjZ01EY09nOVoySVE1TnF5NHNuWkVHejBTN0NkblBRbGxPOFM2QktrR3RmZ2ZWXzlIeXlCeVlub3l3cTJzUmhpT05TOXJ5RkVmbDhpZFplTjlLaEdQZXJIQmRQQWgxU3lVbjZN</guid></item><item><title>性传播感染病例上升，年轻人发病率最高-牙买加观察家</title><link>https://www.jamaicaobserver.com/2025/11/30/sti-cases-rise-highest-rates-among-young-adults/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="image_caption"&gt;According to data from the Ministry of Health and Wellness, 35,713 cases of sexually transmitted infections were seen in the public health system in 2024, compared to 34,278 the previous year.&lt;/p&gt;				&lt;div class="body content-single-wrap"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;JAMAICA has seen an increase in the number of people being treated for sexually transmitted infections (STIs), such as gonorrhoea, chlamydia, and trichomoniasis, over the past four years, with the highest rate recorded among young adults aged 20 to 24.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;According to data from the Ministry of Health and Wellness, 35,713 cases were seen in the public health system in 2024, compared to 34,278 the previous year, and 31,572 in 2022. In 2021 a total of 33,472 patients were treated.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Women continue to account for the majority of cases, with 28,220 patients compared to 7,493 males in 2024.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“The vast majority of what we see is genital discharge syndrome…well over 99 per cent, and about one per cent in terms of genital ulcer disease,” Dr Nicola Skyers, senior medical officer at the National HIV/STI Programme in the Ministry of Health and Wellness, told the &lt;b&gt;Jamaica Observer&lt;/b&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The data showed that there were 34,411 cases of genital discharge syndrome in 2024, while genital ulcer disease amounted to 86 cases.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Genital ulcers are sores on the genitals commonly caused by herpes, syphilis, and chancroid, while genital discharge syndrome refers to a group of symptoms, including gonorrhoea, chlamydia, trichomoniasis, bacterial vaginosis, and candidiasis when they cannot be uniquely identified.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Meanwhile, syphilis cases rose to 1,216 in 2024, following a low of 865 in 2023.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dr Skyers shared that the Ministry of Health and Wellness is currently conducting a survey to gather more detailed information on each specific sexually transmitted infection, which will become available in 2026.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Meanwhile, the highest STI rates continue to be seen among young adults aged 20 to 24, followed by those aged 15 to 19 and 25 to 29.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“The zero to 14 age group is very low. Then we see the increase in 15 to 19. This is when you’re getting into the adolescent, late adolescent period. Twenty to 24 is the highest; 15 to 19 and 25 to 29 is about the same, as well as 30 to 34. So it’s really your younger age group, your young adults that we’re actually seeing where the burden is primarily,” she explained.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dr Skyers attributed this trend to low condom use and multiple partner relationships.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dr Annisha Skinner, physician at St Ann Medical, an AIDS Healthcare Foundation (AHF) Wellness Centre, told the &lt;b&gt;Sunday Observer&lt;/b&gt; that the most common infections seen at the clinic are genital discharge syndromes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“We’ve been seeing steady testing numbers across the year. The data show that HIV positivity has ranged between zero and 6.7 per cent, while syphilis positivity peaked at about 5.7 per cent in July. Urethral and vaginal discharge syndromes, which would include chlamydia and gonorrhoea, have remained fairly constant in prevalence, and there has been a slight increase in the number of clients with symptomatic mycoplasma genitalium and ureaplasma parvum/urealyticum infections,” Dr Skinner shared.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She said the clinic has been seeing positive trends in the number of people visiting to get tested. However, she warned that STI testing should not be used as a substitute for practising safe sex.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“We encourage prevention of STI transmission among sexually active individuals by promoting condom use, encouraging open and honest conversations with sex partners, and discouraging the engagement in risky sexual behaviours,” she said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dr Skinner also recommended that sexually active people get tested at least twice a year. The physician pointed out all major STIs are treatable and patients diagnosed with HIV are immediately linked to antiretroviral therapy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The rise in STI cases comes as Jamaica also continues to see shifts in HIV trends. According to the latest UNAIDS statistics, an estimated 28,000 Jamaicans were living with HIV in 2024, up from 26,000 in 2023.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;However, there has been a decline in new infections to 1,100 in 2024, compared to 1,200 in 2023, and 1,400 in both 2021 and 2022. Men aged 15 and over accounted for 650 new cases in 2024, compared with 470 women.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some 1,800 Jamaicans aged 15 to 24 were living with HIV in 2024, along with 290 children aged zero to 14.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The national HIV prevalence rate held steady at 1.1 per cent in 2024, lower than the 1.3 per cent recorded in 2021 and 2022.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Data on AIDS-related deaths for 2024 were not available, but 740 deaths were recorded in 2023, down significantly from 1,100 in 2022 and 770 in 2021.&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Jamaica Observer</author><pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 05:13:12 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilgFBVV95cUxNemVKY0Y0bGpiVWN0MmpfWGQ2R1UxRnJfM2lnaW5HYTFFUm9QSXlKMU9PdzJpaGJHMWpQUi1CUXJ3dzN3aHN3VV8zR1F0NWNnUnpQU2tyRG1TS3VObjQ1eVZSWTU4RWxfRmNidWtuVjBNa3dMSDVLVlpOdUJua3N0ZnFfMUIxd0lyU0xNSExaY2Q2NnpMNlE</guid></item><item><title>​外科医生揭示30分钟步行如何改变心脏健康-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/cardiac-surgeon-reveals-how-30-minutes-of-walking-can-transform-heart-health/articleshow/125668505.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;div class="MwN2O"&gt;&lt;div class="vdo_embedd"&gt; &lt;div class="T22zO"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Heart diseases are on the rise. In fact, &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/heart-disease/about/index.html" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;1 out of every 5 deaths&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; in the United States is due to heart disease, according to the CDC. While there are several factors that increase the risk of heart disease, what many tend to ignore is the remarkable power of physical activity in improving heart health. According to experts, the best prescription for good heart health is not pills but physical activity. In an Instagram video, Dr Dmitry Yaranov, a leading heart transplant cardiologist from Memphis, trained at Samara State Medical University, explained the impact of walking on heart health. “I prescribe this more often than pills: just 30–60 minutes of walking a day can literally transform your heart, your mind, and your life,” the doctor, with nearly two decades of clinical experience, said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="7"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="8"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Role of walking in heart health&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; What makes walking a great form of exercise is not just its simplicity but the cascade of physiological changes that happen the moment you start moving. “I’ve seen patients go from exhausted to energised, anxious to peaceful — not because of a new drug, but because they started to move,” Dr Yaranov said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="10"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="lOvcW vdo_embedd"&gt;&lt;div class="k7lcu"&gt;&lt;p class="efT4r"&gt;Winter Heart Care: Doctor-Approved Top Tips For A Healthy Heart This Season&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="12"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; A recent study by the American Heart Association found that getting more daily steps and engaging in moderate-to-vigorous physical activity were both associated with a significantly &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://newsroom.heart.org/news/walking-moving-more-may-lower-risk-of-cardiovascular-death-for-women-with-cancer-history?preview=aaa9&amp;amp;preview_mode=True" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;reduced risk of death from cardiovascular disease&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; in postmenopausal women.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="17"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; Another study, published in the journal &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="em" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Heart&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;, found that a brisk walking pace, and the amount of time spent at this speed, may &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://heart.bmj.com/content/111/16/763" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;lower the risk of heart rhythm abnormalities&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; such as atrial fibrillation, tachycardia (rapid heartbeat), and bradycardia (very slow heartbeat).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="23"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="24"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;How 30 to 60 minutes of walking can improve heart health&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="25"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; Dr Yaranov stated that walking is the most underrated therapy he knows for your body, brain, and soul. The surgeon further explained how every step leads you to a better heart and improved overall health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="28"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; According to him, when you walk for a minute, blood flow surges. By five minutes, something remarkable happens in your brain: your mood begins to lift and anxiety starts to ease. When you reach the 10-minute mark, cortisol, your body's primary stress hormone, starts to drop. This brings a sense of calm.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="30"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="32"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; With every minute, the benefits compound. After 15 minutes of walking, blood sugar levels start to stabilise, the doctor said. By 30 minutes, your body switches into fat-burning mode. Those on a weight-loss journey or wanting to maintain a healthy weight may benefit from just half an hour of walking.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="36"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; Beyond the physical benefits, walking also offers mental wellness. The doctor revealed that mental fog begins to fade 45 minutes into walking. Overthinking starts to die down. You will no longer feel those hundred &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="em" data-ua-type="1"&gt;what ifs&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; popping in your head. And as you complete an hour of walking, your dopamine levels go up and you experience happiness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="41"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; A recent study by researchers at the University of Texas at Arlington, published in the journal &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="em" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Psychology of Sport and Exercise&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;, found that swapping 30 minutes of sitting for light activity such as walking can &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S1469029225001967?via%3Dihub" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;boost energy and mood&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;. Movement will even make you feel happier the next day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="47"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; Remember, you don’t need fancy gym memberships or expensive supplements to improve your heart health. Walking can do just the right job. “Just you, your heart, and a few consistent steps. Start small. Stay consistent. Your heart will remember every step,” the doctor said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="51"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="em" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Note: The information provided in this article is for educational purposes only and is not intended as medical advice. Always consult a qualified healthcare professional before starting any new medication or treatment, or before changing your diet or supplement regimen.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="53"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 04:20:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihwJBVV95cUxQYkE3Y2ZZdHhIenJWSzNuY1FNZklpR09aVk9IbEoyVTFudnNxUHJEUURrakxyVHlnN2RoMnFzeVdueXlSN1Z4T2tMcjRvZW1sakJacXJkWVB3dWIycmVjYmlYdlVFd0VSUGN3Zlo5bmJhX1pWUEl5WlE2cUFqSW5nVnFkcmZVLU1ycElGUVltY05zclZaY2JrVXY3YXNmd0plWHkzX2JWTVl1YmkzbFdXNHFIZ1RMYnRfQTlWMjQ1a3VzMDFWS0tETm5EVzkyWFpwZ2plOFBlUDgtM1ZsV3JnczVvZG1DU1pqcTNrRW9tOHZtb1B2X1NOTjg3TGV2ZkZYUTY4VGNXcw</guid></item><item><title>FDA官方计划改变疫苗审批流程，声称新冠疫苗导致儿童死亡- CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2025/11/29/politics/vaccine-approval-process-fda-official</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article__content" data-editable="content" itemprop="articleBody" data-reorderable="content"&gt;
                
    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmikx2l81009a2cp74hfz6hf8@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            A senior Food and Drug Administration official on Friday said the agency will change its vaccine approval process, alleging that Covid-19 vaccination resulted in the deaths of 10 children.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmikx2n2200003b6noldw3bmg@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            In an internal memo obtained by CNN, Dr. Vinay Prasad — the FDA’s chief medical and scientific officer and the director of the Center for Biologics Evaluation and Research — claimed, “Healthy young children who faced tremendously low risk of death were coerced, at the behest of the Biden administration, via school and work mandates, to receive a vaccine that could result in death.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmikxo0j4000g3b6nutfjg8xc@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Prasad did not provide details about the deaths or how the FDA came to that conclusion, but pointed to “an initial analysis” that examined 96 deaths and linked 10 to the Covid-19 vaccination. He also claimed that Covid-19 “was never highly lethal for children” and that the effects of it “are comparable” to respiratory viruses for which there aren’t annual vaccines.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmiky5zie000q3b6n97g5x3qv@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “I have no doubt that many vaccines have saved millions of lives globally, and many have benefits that far exceed risks, but vaccines are like any other medical product,” Prasad said. “The right drug given to the right patient at the right time is great, but the same drug can be inappropriately given, causing harm.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmikynt8500173b6ngyun33t7@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Prasad said as a result of the FDA analysis, the agency will adopt a new approval process for vaccines that will require more evidence of their safety and value before they can be marketed. Among the changes would be stricter requirements for authorization of vaccines used for pregnant women and trials for pneumonia vaccines that will need to prove the shots reduce disease, instead of showing that the vaccine produces enough antibodies to fight the illness.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmil6rl9o00073b6n0kw2yyh2@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The agency will also “revise the annual flu vaccine framework,” Prasad said, and “will re-appraise safety and be honest in vaccine labels.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmil6rl9o00083b6nvor6u3gc@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Although Prasad’s memo didn’t provide details about how the process would change, it could require larger studies that take longer to complete, slowing the process significantly.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmil6rl9o000a3b6na54yg9ud@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            In the memo, Prasad said he’s open to discussion about the changes but said such debates should be internal to the FDA. “Some staff may not agree with these core principles and operating principles,” he wrote before urging those staffers to submit their resignation letters.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmikzf4lp001f3b6nhxj5ptfg@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            CNN has reached out to the FDA and the Department of Health and Human Services, which oversees the agency, for comment.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmikxfu6m00073b6nlf5epcj5@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Friday’s memo is in line with arguments long made by HHS Secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr., who has repeatedly raised doubts about the effectiveness of vaccines and previously founded the anti-vaccine group Children’s Health Defense.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmikxmx4h000d3b6n7fvskklw@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            As the HHS secretary, Kennedy has &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2025/08/05/health/hhs-slashes-funding-for-mrna-vaccine-development"&gt;slashed funding&lt;/a&gt; for mRNA vaccine development, &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2025/06/09/health/rfk-cdc-vaccine-advisers-removed"&gt;removed all members&lt;/a&gt; of the vaccine advisory committee at the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention, and &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2025/11/21/health/kennedy-cdc-vaccine-guidance"&gt;directed the CDC&lt;/a&gt; to change its website to &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2025/11/20/health/cdc-website-autism-vaccines"&gt;include false claims&lt;/a&gt; that link autism and vaccines.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmikzthfs00003b6nwfisni4b@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The CDC’s Advisory Committee on Immunization Practices, handpicked by Kennedy, is set to meet next week to discuss the childhood vaccine schedule and the timing of the hepatitis B vaccine, according to a &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/acip/downloads/agendas/draft-posted-2025-11-14-508.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;draft agenda&lt;/a&gt; of the meeting.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmil6o3v300003b6nmow3ot93@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            For more than 30 years, the first in the series of hepatitis B shots has been recommended for infants shortly after birth — a strategy that nearly eradicated the potentially fatal disease among children in the US. Although there is no new evidence about the vaccine’s safety or effectiveness, the new advisory panel has been considering whether to delay the first shots by months or years.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmil6uyj1000e3b6nvzq68jow@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            &lt;em&gt;CNN’s Jamie Gumbrecht contributed to this report.&lt;/em&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;

              &lt;/div&gt;
                  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>CNN</author><pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigwFBVV95cUxOQkhFV0pVQzBjZjBhSmdpQ0NNSE1XQkNUVl9MVDlHdmRmbzVyc2hLMFB2V2tvU2NyVmNPcDg5MEUxNW11MGFUNURDdVU3VkdNQlNPRFlDZWtLektmNzJoWjFPWnF5WktGRnBPZWk1ckF3bHZYeWdDNkJtcGtldWFrVUdBQQ</guid></item><item><title>海得拉巴医生揭示了“世界上第一种高纤维食物，其纤维含量是您每日一碗燕麦的10倍” |健康-印度斯坦时报</title><link>https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/hyderabad-doctor-reveals-no-1-high-fibre-food-in-the-world-10-times-more-fibre-than-your-daily-bowl-of-oats-superfood-101764472197426.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="detail " dataid="/lifestyle/health/hyderabad-doctor-reveals-no-1-high-fibre-food-in-the-world-10-times-more-fibre-than-your-daily-bowl-of-oats-superfood-101764472197426.html"&gt; &lt;div class="storyParagraphFigure"&gt; &lt;p&gt;Did you know: beyond fibre, &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/chia-seeds-offer-big-nutrition-benefits-dietitians-reveal-the-smartest-and-healthiest-ways-to-enjoy-them-101763972909868.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="chia seeds"&gt;chia seeds&lt;/a&gt; provide omega-3 for your heart, protein for your muscles, calcium for your bones? &lt;span class="highlight"&gt;Dr Pooja Reddy, a dermatologist from Hyderabad, called chia seeds the number one complete high-fibre food in the world as she explained the significant nutritional value and health benefits of chia seeds, particularly focusing on their role in solving chronic constipation and improving overall gut health.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Also read | &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/hyderabad-doctor-reveals-no-1-most-dangerous-carb-in-the-world-not-maida-white-rice-sugar-101763959160691.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="Hyderabad doctor reveals 'no 1 most dangerous carb in the world': Not maida or white rice"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hyderabad doctor reveals 'no 1 most dangerous carb in the world': Not maida or white rice&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;figure class=""&gt; &lt;span class=""&gt; &lt;picture&gt; &lt;source media="(max-width:767px)" srcset="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/11/30/550x309/2148230545_1764472814084_1764472821938.jpg" alt="Chia seeds are considered one of the highest fibre foods in the world, and are even more fibre-rich than oats. (Freepik)" title="Chia seeds are considered one of the highest fibre foods in the world, and are even more fibre-rich than oats. (Freepik)"&gt;&lt;/source&gt; &lt;img src="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/11/30/550x309/2148230545_1764472814084_1764472821938.jpg" alt="Chia seeds are considered one of the highest fibre foods in the world, and are even more fibre-rich than oats. (Freepik)" title="Chia seeds are considered one of the highest fibre foods in the world, and are even more fibre-rich than oats. (Freepik)"&gt; &lt;/picture&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;figcaption&gt;Chia seeds are considered one of the highest fibre foods in the world, and are even more fibre-rich than oats. (Freepik)&lt;/figcaption&gt; &lt;/figure&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;p id="readMoreFTUser"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;In her November 28 Instagram post, Dr Reddy said they are nutritionally superior to oats and even sabja seeds, offering 10 times the fibre of a standard serving of &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/health/overnight-oats-benefits-for-health-weight-loss-and-recipes/story-Rt9QukbZjEwaCB6UnbqrNN.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="oats"&gt;oats&lt;/a&gt;. A 30-gram daily dose provides 10 grams of fibre, along with significant quantities of omega-3 fatty acids, protein, calcium, and powerful antioxidants, she said.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="mt-10 mb-10 htEchoRecirculationWidget"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="mt10 mb10 htEchoArticlePromo"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="predictorShow mb20" data-vars-predictor="true" data-vars-quiz="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="quizShow mb20" data-vars-minimized="false" data-vars-predictor="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;'Chia seeds have 50% more fibre than sabja seeds'&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the video she posted, Dr Reddy said: “The number one complete&lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/harvard-gastroenterologist-shares-10-tasty-high-fiber-foods-that-are-not-salads-101764057078268.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="high-fibre food"&gt; high-fibre food&lt;/a&gt; in the world is not oats or leafy vegetables. It's something that has 10 times more fibre than your daily bowl of oats. But fibre is just the beginning. This food also gives you omega-3 for your heart, protein for your muscles, calcium for your bones and also keeps you full for hours. What is this superfood? Chia seeds. Not sabja seeds or basil seeds. It's chia seeds. Yes, sabja seeds are good for cooling your body in summer. But chia seeds have 50 percent more fibre, double the omega-3 and protein, making them nutritionally superior for everyday health.”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="highlight"&gt;She added that these seeds effectively address chronic constipation; when soaked in water, they absorb ten times their weight to form a cleansing gel that acts as a natural 'broom' for the intestines.&lt;/span&gt; Dr Reddy said, “They're a complete package. 30 grams of chia seeds will give you 10 grams of fibre, more than what most of us can eat in an entire day. Plus omega-3 fatty acids, 5 grams of protein and powerful antioxidants. And here's the biggest benefit. It solves chronic constipation. 7 out of 10 Indians struggle with chronic constipation because our diet is poor in fibre, and we don't drink enough water. When you soak chia seeds, they absorb 10 times their weight in water and form a gel. This slimy gel acts like a natural broom. It cleans your intestines.”&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;How to have chia seeds?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="highlight"&gt;Dr Reddy recommended consuming the resulting gel and water as the final meal of the day to ensure satiety until the next morning, eliminating late-night cravings.&lt;/span&gt; According to her, this habit can transform your gut health, eliminating the need to spend money on expensive supplements like&lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/gastroenterologist-suggests-top-probiotic-prebiotic-and-fibre-rich-foods-and-drinks-for-happy-gut-health-101748585913446.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="probiotics"&gt; probiotics&lt;/a&gt; or digestive enzymes.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Dr Reddy said, “Here's how I use chia seeds. I take 30 grams of chia seeds, soak them in water for at least four hours. I usually soak them in the afternoon. &lt;span class="highlight"&gt;Then, at 7pm, as my last meal of the day, I drink this gel water directly, or I add it to high-protein lactose-free milk.&lt;/span&gt; Why at night? It keeps me full until the next morning. &lt;span class="highlight"&gt;With this, your late-night cravings will vanish, your gut health will transform, and you won't need to waste thousands on probiotic supplements, digestive enzymes, fibre powders or fancy gut-healthy products.&lt;/span&gt;”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Note to readers: This report is based on user-generated content from social media. HT.com has not independently verified the claims and does not endorse them.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;This article is for informational purposes only and not a substitute for professional medical advice.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Hindustan Times</author><pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 03:23:09 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilAJBVV95cUxNcDJsemUzdGNBOFNNY293NnJ5ZTJvdFkwX28xSzhVZl9TUlJ3elZRTVFuVDl0QXcwTDdyZTk2dmNYMkRmSV9NeWlUbjZYVk01SXNILTdoWmhSZFFaaXZiUGt4d1dNd01ZU1RidjFaZzIwaEEwMmVsLW5nSUlIMC1XQUlFSElyMS1rNlY2WkxPQnNYRW1Vd0dmdlktTHZoMGtoRllRSUsxaTZoZ2JOTHhETEVWb2Vadml5QWdWa3BHX25fR3NRbTRSZWdUdWFNMGhGQzFaOXJjSS1ObkFJbXVfcjNZN3o1RmVUNUJ4aFp2bkstaUVkQnV2YUZPcU41bDVwV3VOOE1wTC1vMkEwb0pXUjFjQnrSAZoCQVVfeXFMUEd5ZzFzVDFkNUNVM3lHY0JwZE9ObXduODRmMzRsdnFmaTNzdUZ3c3BxZGhDeWFCUkFYS3VWOEdSdzV0dGxjaXRzQVd3YlhoQ3VXdkY3MkI0QlVYOWhJTzh5dEgyZjFpZzh2Ri1PN2dveEtkWU1HOWxsZEt6aUpPMXpjUjJDQ2w4Y2ktZ0Zabl9lT3I5eTBDZmp2UmpidTVFTjgyNmF0elhXQzVmS0UxZUFBUVZBREQ4dkRXTE5sY19xcHRscVlma2RuaElBdm1DMVhOcHRWNEtlMlBJQ0ZlQTNLMnhvZVZOajZPVWNSVjg3RmtyVFMwRmpzYXRydUpvTVJYbjNZRmEtTWtFSHY4Q1JTMTNhNjkxcVJR</guid></item><item><title>医务人员正在分享他们的“这个病人怎么还活着？” “故事，哇- BuzzFeed</title><link>https://www.buzzfeed.com/kaylayandoli/medical-incidents-people-survived</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="subbuzz buzz-width--standard__subbuzz buzz-type--list__subbuzz subbuzz-text
  subbuzz-index-2
  
  
  
  
  " data-keywords="fast fashion" data-module="subbuzz-text"&gt;
  
  &lt;p id="139742316" class="subbuzz-anchor"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;h2 class="subbuzz__header subbuzz__header--standard subbuzz__title  "&gt;
    
      &lt;span class="subbuzz__number"&gt;2.&lt;/span&gt;
    

    
      &lt;span class="js-subbuzz__title-text"&gt;"One of my prior patients is a roofer who lived a very full life of alcohol, women, and drugs. He was infected with HIV, Hepatitis B, Hepatitis C, and was cirrhotic, and didn't really care about his health at all. He was thin, weighing 110 pounds on a six-foot frame, which included 20 pounds of ascites in his abdomen. He was angry and didn't listen to anyone, refusing therapy most of the time. I met him first in the ICU, where he had AIDS, end-stage liver disease, hepatorenal syndrome, unexplained lymph nodes all over his body, variceal hemorrhage, Kaposi sarcoma, and spontaneous bacterial peritonitis. The prognosis of in-hospital death was &amp;gt;90% even with therapy."&lt;/span&gt;
    
  &lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;"I was involved in his care for about two weeks, and again, he refused every therapy that his primary physicians suggested. I was surprised he lasted the two weeks. Finally, he was so fed up with the noisiness in the ICU that he requested transfer to palliative care, and was eventually sent to a hospice for patients with advanced HIV to live out his remaining few days.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One year later, I got a call from the hospice requesting a follow-up appointment for him. I was shocked that he was still alive and asked if I could talk to him. He was all better. Turns out he had the hots for his nurse in the hospice and did everything she asked in order to please her, including taking his medications for the first time. She had slowly nursed him back to health, convinced him to restart HIV meds, put him on a low salt diet for his liver disease, and then eventually got him up and mobile.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He spent another six months in a rehabilitation facility, then went back to work. He saw me in follow-up for a while as we treated his Hepatitis C, then his cirrhosis shockingly improved. After a couple of years, he moved to another place to start a construction company and became quite successful financially; he remains abstinent from his former vices.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He's the only person whom I've seen come back from death."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;—&lt;a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/AskReddit/comments/akhsyc/comment/ef5ca7o/" target="_blank"&gt;u/Ralph_Malfredsson&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BuzzFeed</author><pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 02:57:40 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMie0FVX3lxTE1xTjRVS0gxUHRnRFZpaXNkMWtPY1BYeFd3MVJQS1JBdGk2clRwNmhBVWZNYzFsYVEzNnJQZFRGU3JoRlhJY3p3VUZ4WUMxb0ZBdHYwbDZuVEc5TFJLMkh4d2pGd0ktWW1MN2RKVmNPck8wVk8yNU02RV9VTQ</guid></item></channel></rss>