<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>GNews Health</title><link>https://news.google.com/</link><description></description><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>为什么这项临床试验给一些年轻的癌症患者带来了希望-《华盛顿邮报》</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/science/2025/11/01/children-cancer-clinical-trial-solid-tumors/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text subtype-from-the-source grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="JWE7YLHN5FDZTERD72FTOVOQAM" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Years of caring for children with solid tumors and looking into the eyes of parents starved for hope have led Catherine Bollard to what she calls the most important moment of her career.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="2VSXFKHFQRBIVJKFKFQS7DT2RE" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Children’s National Hospital, where Bollard is senior vice president and chief research officer, is poised to start recruiting children with pediatric sarcomas and other solid tumors that have resisted chemotherapy and radiation for a clinical trial that will use an inventive new technique to combat one of the most persistent problems in cancer care.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2025 17:00:26 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimgFBVV95cUxNOEFYb3RIRUZNbEx3Y0RHeGQ0eVJ6OWk5U3FkYkp0S2xibm16TWszazJWVUtUUUlMV2IwQ1Z5RllrODdiWjZmZVoxcTljSXVjZHZMeklUYXZDMVdEc3QtMENuYk9Cemh1ajlNWkx4UFpNMFNrNG5IM2Z4V1Rsd1RwbHNEUW4zcndWZk9LMGtjTUxkUXhTYmhGQVBB</guid></item><item><title>我们与另一对已婚夫妇度过了一个狂野的夜晚。一个丈夫为错误的人参加了狂欢节。-石板</title><link>https://slate.com/advice/2025/11/alcohol-husband-sex-drinking-group-wife-advice.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article__content" itemprop="mainEntityOfPage"&gt;
          &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="18" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmhf99w7b000gbsksr78jaevl@published"&gt;&lt;em&gt;How to Do It is Slate’s sex advice column. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Have a question? &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLSdx34-uOijrCIKqMdw5hnyYahSJBKa4AaSzDCu1nfcpmd3IjA/viewform"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Send it to Stoya and Rich here.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt; It’s anonymous!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="5" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmhf9spfu003h3b78jnozr54x@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dear How to Do It,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="108" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmhf9ftt2001f3b787crws39m@published"&gt;Let’s say you’re in a couple play situation where there is lots of alcohol involved and one husband is feral for the other guy’s wife, to the exclusion of everything else. If his wife is upset by this, and there is almost zero chance the drinking will be less, it seems like continuing the play another time will just lead to more hurt. Is there a way through this? The husband is not interested in moving forward if his wife is hurt by his drunken behavior, but is it worth trying again if his intent is to be more conscious of how his wife is doing during play?&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="2" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmhf9ftw3001g3b78k20ozkzq@published"&gt;—Tunnel Vision&lt;/p&gt;

  

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="3" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmhf9ftze001h3b78c9cv14jp@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dear Tunnel Vision,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="97" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmhf9fu2o001i3b78o1i8xdlh@published"&gt;I think the most prudent thing to do here is to consider what the emotional fallout will be if the same thing were to happen again. You’ve written your letter in a hypothetical voice without identifying yourself, which is uncommon for this column, but I have a hunch that if you’re in this configuration, you’re the wife. If that is true, envision what a scenario will be like if your husband follows the same pattern. Will it be upsetting, devastating, relationship-upending? Something else? What exactly would you be risking if the worst-case scenario were to play out?&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="115" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmhf9fu5j001j3b78b9mcmkky@published"&gt;One positive here is that the husband no longer can claim plausible deniability should he zero in on a single target and others’ feelings catch strays in the process. He knows what happened last time. If alcohol clouded his judgement, he should take it upon himself to drink less—if getting loaded in the presence of available alcohol (and nonmonogamous sex) is an inevitability, that may signal an issue with substances or a general discomfort with this kind of play. Both should be interrogated. I know people love to get drunk and screw, but if they &lt;em&gt;have to&lt;/em&gt; get drunk to screw, they might want to think about why and consider other means of social lubrication.&lt;/p&gt;

  


  


  


  


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="57" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmhf9fu91001k3b78jzdthyr0@published"&gt;Another positive here is that he actively does not want to upset his wife again, which suggests he’s learning. Now is the time for the wife to voice her boundaries and for him to accept them. If these are successfully adhered to, you will both have grown from a negative situation, perhaps rendering it all worth it.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="148" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmhf9fuc7001l3b783575zfk0@published"&gt;So, I say give him another chance unless you (I mean … the wife) are fairly sure that a repetition of the first time will cause irreparable damage. Obviously, he’s extremely into another woman there and part of the point of this kind of play is for people to have their fun. But it truly should not be to the exclusion of everything else, including consideration for one’s partner. If he truly cannot maintain that very meager standard, this kind of play should probably be taken off the table entirely. But you should also consider the fact that his interest for at least one other woman will likely endure whether you go forward and incorporate her into group sex or not. If the very fact of his attraction is bothersome or distracting, it may deserve a sober discussion and your own efforts to come to terms with it.&lt;/p&gt;

  


  &lt;p data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-section-div/instances/cmhf9fyrx001o3b780w11r8as@published" class="section-div"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;div class="prudie-google-form" data-form-response-uri="https://docs.google.com/forms/u/0/d/e/1FAIpQLSdx34-uOijrCIKqMdw5hnyYahSJBKa4AaSzDCu1nfcpmd3IjA/formResponse" data-uri="slate.com/_components/prudie-google-form/instances/cmhf9gecv001w3b78zm9fp7o1@published"&gt;
    
    &lt;p class="prudie-google-form__disclaimer"&gt;
      Please keep questions short (&amp;lt;150 words), and don‘t submit the same question to multiple columns. We are unable to edit or remove questions after publication. Use pseudonyms to maintain anonymity. Your submission may be used in other Slate advice columns and may be edited for publication.
    &lt;/p&gt;
    
    &lt;p class="slate-notification--success js-success-message" hidden&gt;Thanks! Your question has been submitted.&lt;/p&gt;
    
&lt;/div&gt;

  &lt;p data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-section-div/instances/cmhf9gnrj00203b78ong94jhk@published" class="section-div"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="5" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmhf9lw9y002q3b781fn1dvgq@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dear How to Do It,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="80" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmhf9q76t002u3b784984qo2w@published"&gt;I’m a gay man and I don’t get any enjoyment from my penis during sex. I don’t enjoy anal, either. I love closeness and intimacy, including kissing and cuddling, and I am happy to give orally, but getting my dick sucked does nothing for me, nor does penetrating another guy and nor does bottoming. None of it is uncomfortable and I enjoy giving pleasure to others, but none of it is as satisfying as masturbation. Is there something wrong with me?&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="3" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmhf9q76u002v3b78nunm4n95@published"&gt;—(Not) My Pleasure&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="4" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmhf9q76u002w3b78ztshofuu@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dear (Not) My Pleasure,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="158" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmhf9q76u002x3b78smjbc3oi@published"&gt;There’s a good chance there’s nothing “wrong” with you here. Maybe this is just how you are, and all the psychological searching you can muster (alone and/or with a therapist) won’t give you any answers. Maybe you just know what you like and what you don’t. Giving pleasure is a great thing, and there are guys who identify as cocksuckers who know this well. If masturbation is your primary vehicle for pleasure, maybe you’re a bator. Maybe you are somewhere on the asexuality spectrum (some deep thinking on the subject, by reading a book like Angela Chen’s &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/Ace-Asexuality-Reveals-Identity-Meaning-ebook/dp/B07Y7H1WT9/ref=tmm_kin_swatch_0?_encoding=UTF8&amp;amp;dib_tag=se&amp;amp;dib=eyJ2IjoiMSJ9.kUEjXggB_7ggqNfz6k5l9CeMsuUoEMrPtAf932EMoLkRyJt6T1oNSaxDjzaUcPCOq_oYAMscOBxFhdZleUV1LR82ic00Rf3f9R6vBc4xHiqVBPMyR7Bmf7ZiSoYVFfRLif6TptxOirtny5lNPHmXyg.R-bIgGONNmYTuYiVCC65wBJvxqdmM7QGNVgmJnemEHA&amp;amp;qid=1761851333&amp;amp;sr=8-1"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Ace&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; or browsing/participating in the discussion at &lt;a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/asexuality/"&gt;r/asexuality&lt;/a&gt; could be useful). Maybe none of these labels appeal to you. My sense is that you’re navigating your body’s responses to sex very well and still finding activities that are fun. If you can be at peace with where you are sexually, that’s more than can be said for a lot of people.&lt;/p&gt;

  


  


  


  


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="195" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmhf9q76u002y3b78bae8cffj@published"&gt;If, however, this is distressing and something you’d like to work on changing, definitely seek the services of a therapist (preferably a sex therapist, or even a sex coach) who can help you sort out whether these feelings might be a response to something that’s happened in your life or just a regular facet of your particular sexuality. There are no guarantees that you will be changed by the process—nor do I think you need to be—but the more you think about it and the more you attempt to work on it, the more likely such a change will occur. We can’t say for certain what’s going on from here, but if you’ve exhausted all potential reasons and this continues to bother you, you may want to look into whether what you’re experiencing is sexual anhedonia, a condition marked by an inability to feel sexual pleasure. It has many &lt;a href="https://www.menshealth.com/sex-women/a43455963/sexual-anhedonia/"&gt;potential causes&lt;/a&gt;, physical (like low testosterone, neurological issues, or medication) and psychological (depression, performance anxiety), alike. A visit to a doctor, hopefully one with whom you are comfortable discussing sex, may be illuminating. Let them know what’s going on, as they may want to run tests.&lt;/p&gt;

  


  &lt;p data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-section-div/instances/cmhf9sybv003j3b78lwcegfxk@published" class="section-div"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;h3 class="subhead subhead--none" data-uri="slate.com/_components/subhead/instances/cmhf9t23i003l3b786nfh78c3@published"&gt;
&lt;p class="subhead__marker"&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
Send Us Your Questions About the Workplace!

&lt;/h3&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="36" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmhf9ta25003o3b78ui7802ea@published"&gt;The columnists behind our advice column, &lt;a href="https://slate.com/advice/good-job"&gt;Good Job&lt;/a&gt;, want to help you navigate your social dynamics at work. Does your colleague constantly bug you after hours? Has an ill-advised work romance gone awry? &lt;a href="https://forms.gle/DEVPsiDdnLHQVX7h7"&gt;Ask us your question here&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-section-div/instances/cmhf9tdwv003r3b78fqbaomic@published" class="section-div"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="5" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmhf9q76u002z3b78awv61oo9@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dear How to Do It,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="106" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmhf9q76u00303b78ccmagl2y@published"&gt;My boyfriend and I are both very ass-eating curious—especially him! He’s been begging to try this since early on in our relationship. I’ve always hesitated because it took me a while to open up to and get comfortable with being eaten out in the first place. With butt stuff, I’m especially nervous because of cleanliness issues even after a shower. What if it smells or he gets dirty or it’s gross! I don’t want to turn him off entirely! But I also admit I’m curious about it and think I could be into it. How do I get past my fears and give this a shot?&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="2" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmhf9q76v00313b78451oox46@published"&gt;—Backdoor Curious&lt;/p&gt;

  


  


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="3" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmhf9q76v00323b78ydgzfw74@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dear Backdoor Curious,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="192" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmhf9q76v00333b78udurhj85@published"&gt;A shower, in most cases, is sufficient prep for rimming. Things that may complicate this solution include stray hairs that poop can cling to (especially if you are less than thorough with your wash) and fecal incontinence. If you have no reason to suspect you experience the latter (and you’d know), you’re already ahead of the game. To keep things extra tidy, you can trim the hair around your hole (I personally trust the &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/gp/aw/d/B0CLWH333W/?_encoding=UTF8&amp;amp;pd_rd_plhdr=t&amp;amp;aaxitk=28a358c8be016b730e11e90c73409006&amp;amp;hsa_cr_id=0&amp;amp;qid=1761506763&amp;amp;sr=1-1-9e67e56a-6f64-441f-a281-df67fc737124&amp;amp;ref_=sbx_be_s_sparkle_dlcd_asin_0_title&amp;amp;pd_rd_w=VlfpI&amp;amp;content-id=amzn1.sym.9f2b2b9e-47e9-4764-a4dc-2be2f6fca36d:amzn1.sym.9f2b2b9e-47e9-4764-a4dc-2be2f6fca36d&amp;amp;pf_rd_p=9f2b2b9e-47e9-4764-a4dc-2be2f6fca36d&amp;amp;pf_rd_r=3HKJH7ES5X9X4QSPK0QM&amp;amp;pd_rd_wg=JCM99&amp;amp;pd_rd_r=70b7d3bc-1c66-4571-9284-87e350b0597b"&gt;Philips Norelco OneBlade Intimate&lt;/a&gt;, as it’s never nicked me unlike virtually every other shaver I’ve used, even ones marketed for “intimate” areas). I think some would douche in a situation like this, though it’s probably overkill in your case. Still, if you fear there’s any poop lingering around your rectum that may present itself during play, washing out a few times with water (filter it if you’re using tap and the water in your area isn’t suited for drinking) with a small bulb (&lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/Pure-Men-Detachable-Reusable-Capacity/dp/B0C6B2B35B/ref=sr_1_8?dib=eyJ2IjoiMSJ9.c8CU8QHctZ3sGts0WvMHmvu6QH0tc5liZAZiOcWJEsd2So5iHTlt6ZDVvMduKgaAYjDVxOWW9RS-YTDOHHVzg38iNlfH07YWYroNtbvx6Td4vy8vE5a4QqG_aLGvKwcohX_8ROAG3oW3F8vvqXiro1KtF9Vuofmy1HC-edQC8j5Mw3cNzdHKTAIWeIQgQ7nsZgtc6Bvj_-e12VFNmedQ8fUx8zKym5164SI1gNL_xzEACqHIa8bWe6RnSKvDeFHvXW9GaBmGSvACEn1r2l3rr2uk6Os_9MeH_hkRX_payKM.oMYVURE242HER0a2ad8fv2qPX0MAs70fvCf-b5A6GF4&amp;amp;dib_tag=se&amp;amp;keywords=stay+ready+douche&amp;amp;qid=1761506961&amp;amp;sr=8-8"&gt;like this one&lt;/a&gt;) may help you feel hygienically secure. Regular fiber supplementation via psyllium husk could also help quell your fears. It helps bulk stool, often leaving little to none behind after a bowel movement.&lt;/p&gt;

  


  


  


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="166" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmhf9q76v00343b78l271ufas@published"&gt;If he is so excited about eating your ass, he likely realizes what may come with it. A mishap is unlikely to turn him off entirely. Or if it does, then you’d be no worse off than you are now—at least you will have tried this thing that you’re both curious about. So try to put those concerns out of your mind if you’re going to go forward with this. Probably the most effective thing you can do is just go through with it—take necessary steps to clean yourself as much as possible and let him have at it. You may gain a lot of confidence and security when the ass eating goes off without a hitch. It’ll show you that you can do this and make next time even easier to get into. Of course, if you do feel discomfort, unclean or any kind of vague negativity, you have every right to stop the session, but I would follow my curiosity if I were &lt;span class="slate-paragraph--tombstone"&gt;you.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  


  


  &lt;h3 class="subhead subhead--none" data-uri="slate.com/_components/subhead/instances/cmhf9qh8600383b78oul729i1@published"&gt;
&lt;p class="subhead__marker"&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
More Advice From Slate

&lt;/h3&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="100" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmhf9qtb5003b3b78kd0gik8k@published"&gt;This might sound odd, but I’m a 35-year-old woman, and I just found out that the female screaming orgasms you see in movies aren’t actually typical. That’s because I’m lucky enough to orgasm in that way. Occasionally, I’ll have an enjoyable orgasm that’s a little more restrained. But for the most part, I’m full-on Meg Ryan in the restaurant scene in &lt;em&gt;When Harry met Sally&lt;/em&gt;, except mine is real and not at all a performance. I realize this is the opposite of a problem. However, my question is: &lt;a href="https://slate.com/human-interest/2022/10/loud-climax-sex-advice.html"&gt;Have most or even all of my partners assumed I’m probably faking it?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;section class="newsletter-signup   " data-list="Advice" data-uri="slate.com/_components/newsletter-signup/instances/cmhf99w7b000jbskssyf14xoi@published"&gt;


    &lt;p class="newsletter-signup__intro"&gt;
        &lt;svg class="newsletter-signup__arrow"&gt;
          &lt;use xlink:href="/media/components/newsletter-signup/sprite.svg#arrow"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;
        &lt;/svg&gt;
&lt;h1 class="newsletter-signup__headline"&gt;Never miss new Slate Advice columns&lt;/h1&gt;
      &lt;span class="newsletter-signup__description"&gt;Get the latest from Prudie and our columnists in your inbox each weekday, plus special bonus letters on Saturdays.&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;
    



&lt;/section&gt;

  

&lt;/div&gt;

      &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Slate</author><pubDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2025 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijAFBVV95cUxQMVUtSEdPdUlaZGR1T0N6MHRyaGlDbDBJb2tCeFU5QnNlSU8xaUp2eExlWk9JN0RhRFZUUVZhc3VTZnYwOTZ4NXBSRGgxbjM5ZTE3ajZzOVRfTzRpMFpEdFpMaEVjbVRla1pxOTdXS0d4RkkzM3h0ek1UV0k0cmFlSmE2TU5NQVZCdUJMTQ</guid></item><item><title>运动引起的性高潮：科学家们正在深入研究这种不寻常的现象- PsyPost</title><link>https://www.psypost.org/exercise-induced-orgasms-scientists-are-diving-deep-into-the-unusual-phenomenon/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="content-inner "&gt;&lt;p&gt;A new study published in &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://link.springer.com/article/10.1007/s10508-025-03237-9" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Archives of Sexual Behavior&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; provides the most detailed account to date of women’s experiences with orgasms that occur during physical exercise. Through in-depth interviews, researchers found that these experiences often begin in childhood, are felt as a deep, internal sensation, and can be integrated into a person’s sexual life. This work builds on more than a decade of research that challenges the common understanding of orgasm as a strictly sexual event.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The research was conducted by a team at The Center for Sexual Health Promotion at Indiana University, led by Debby Herbenick, a prominent sexuality researcher. The scientific rationale for these studies stems from a desire to understand the full spectrum of human orgasmic response. Before this work began, the phenomenon was mostly a subject of popular curiosity, often called a “coregasm” in magazines and online forums because of its frequent association with abdominal workouts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While orgasm is almost exclusively discussed in sexual contexts, historical medical literature and early sexuality research, like the Kinsey reports, had occasionally noted orgasms occurring during non-sexual activities. However, these observations were limited, and a scientific gap remained between the popular buzz and empirical evidence. By systematically investigating this phenomenon, the researchers hoped to gain a clearer picture of the physiological and psychological processes of orgasm, independent of sexual fantasy or direct genital stimulation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This line of inquiry began with &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1080/14681994.2011.647902" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;a foundational study&lt;/a&gt; in 2011. The researchers conducted an anonymous, internet-based survey of 530 women who had experienced either orgasm or sexual pleasure during exercise. The goal was to systematically describe a phenomenon that had, until then, been confined to popular media articles and scattered case reports. This initial study was exploratory, aiming to identify which exercises were most commonly associated with these experiences and what the experiences felt like for the women involved.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The findings from that first survey established a baseline understanding. Among women who reported exercise-induced orgasms, the most common activities were abdominal exercises, climbing poles or ropes, and lifting weights. A large portion of these women reported feeling self-conscious about their experience, particularly when exercising in public.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The data also showed that sexual thoughts or fantasies were rarely associated with these orgasms, suggesting the experience was primarily physiological rather than psychological in origin. For women who experienced sexual pleasure without orgasm, biking or spinning was frequently identified, along with abdominal exercises and weight lifting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Seeking to understand the prevalence of this phenomenon in the general population, the research team conducted &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1007/s10508-021-01996-9" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;a follow-up study&lt;/a&gt; using data from the 2014 National Survey of Sexual Health and Behavior. This survey involved a nationally representative probability sample of over 2,000 U.S. adolescents and adults, allowing for a much broader and more generalizable analysis. This study was the first to provide population-level estimates for exercise-induced orgasm and included men in its analysis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The 2021 study revealed that approximately 9% of the survey respondents reported having experienced an orgasm during exercise at least once in their lifetime. There was no statistically significant difference in the prevalence between men and women. The researchers did find a gender difference in the age of first experience, with women reporting a mean age of about 23, while men reported a mean age of about 17.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The types of exercises associated with the first experience were consistent with the 2011 findings and included abdominal exercises, climbing, and weight lifting for both genders. The analysis also identified an association between having an exercise-induced orgasm and having an orgasm during sleep, but not with having an orgasm during a recent partnered sexual event.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The most recent study, published in 2025, moved from quantitative surveys to qualitative interviews to capture the rich, lived experiences of women. The research team conducted in-depth, semi-structured interviews with 21 women, ranging in age from 19 to 68, who had a history of exercise-induced orgasms. The interviews took place in a setting equipped with exercise mats and a Roman chair, allowing participants to demonstrate, if they felt comfortable, the specific movements that led to their experiences. This method allowed for a detailed exploration of their personal histories, physical sensations, and emotional responses.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A key finding from these interviews was that the first experience with exercise-induced arousal or orgasm often occurred during childhood or early adolescence. Many women recalled feeling these sensations as young as five or six years old while climbing poles on a playground, doing gymnastics, or performing sit-ups in physical education class.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At the time, they were often confused by the sensations, with several participants describing the initial feeling as a sense that they needed to urinate. They lacked a framework for understanding what was happening to their bodies, but they recognized the feeling was pleasurable and, in some cases, sought to reproduce it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The participants often described an “aha” moment, which typically occurred later in adolescence or adulthood, when they gained more sexual knowledge from peers, media, or their own sexual experiences. It was at this point they connected their childhood sensations with the concept of arousal and orgasm. One woman recounted how making out with someone for the first time made her realize, “This is the same feeling, how strange.” This moment of recognition helped them make sense of a long-standing, and sometimes bewildering, bodily experience.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The interviews provided detailed descriptions of how an exercise-induced orgasm feels physically. Many women characterized it as a deep, internal sensation, originating in the lower abdomen between the belly button and the pelvis. They often contrasted this with orgasms from direct clitoral stimulation, which they described as more external.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some participants noted a progression of sensations, starting with a warmth or tingling in their core that would build and radiate downward. The experience was often predictable, with women learning that orgasm would occur after a certain number of repetitions of an exercise, such as after 50 leg lifts or during the third set of pull-ups.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The emotional responses to these experiences were complex and often evolved over time. Embarrassment and shame were common, especially when the orgasms occurred in public spaces like a gym or during a group fitness class. Participants worried that others might notice their facial expressions or hear them make sounds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some developed strategies to mask the experience, like keeping a serious facial expression, or to avoid it altogether by choosing different exercises. These feelings were sometimes rooted in cultural or familial taboos around sexuality, which made experiencing an orgasm in a non-sexual, public setting feel inappropriate or wrong.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Despite these negative feelings, many women came to accept and even enjoy their ability to have orgasms through exercise. Some viewed it as a motivator to work out, an “added perk at the end of the 100 reps.” Others described it as an empowering experience that gave them a sense of control over their own pleasure, independent of a partner. One woman explained that if she was not getting the attention she needed from her husband, exercise was another way to achieve the stress release of an orgasm.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A significant finding was how some women integrated their knowledge of exercise-induced orgasms into their sexual lives. After learning which muscle contractions produced pleasure during exercise, they were able to apply similar movements during partnered sex. One participant explained that she could tense her core muscles to achieve a stronger or faster orgasm, sometimes allowing her to climax at the same time as her partner. For some, exercise became a form of masturbation or foreplay, and for one woman, it was the only way she had been able to experience orgasm until recently.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These studies have some limitations. The initial survey used a convenience sample, which cannot be used to determine prevalence. The new qualitative study involved a small number of participants who were mostly young, white, and living in the United States, so their experiences may not reflect those of a more diverse population. Future research is needed to explore these experiences among men, gender-diverse individuals, people from different cultural backgrounds, and older adults.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A major direction for future research is to understand the physiological mechanism behind exercise-induced orgasms. It is still not known precisely how muscle contractions during certain exercises trigger an orgasmic response.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Subsequent studies could involve biomechanical analysis, neuro-imaging, or other physiological measures to investigate the roles of muscle tension, nerve pathways, and the sympathetic nervous system. A better understanding of the mechanism could have practical applications for physical therapists, personal trainers, and even military personnel who must pass rigorous fitness tests.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study, “&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1080/14681994.2011.647902" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Exercise-induced orgasm and pleasure among women&lt;/a&gt;,” was authored by Debby Herbenick and J. Dennis Fortenberry.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study, “&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1007/s10508-021-01996-9" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Exercise-Induced Orgasm and Its Association with Sleep Orgasms and Orgasms During Partnered Sex: Findings From a U.S. Probability Survey&lt;/a&gt;,” was authored by Debby Herbenick, Tsung-chieh Fu, Callie Patterson, and J. Dennis Fortenberry.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study, “&lt;a href="https://link.springer.com/article/10.1007/s10508-025-03237-9" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Women’s Experiences with Exercise-Induced Orgasm: Findings from Qualitative Interviews&lt;/a&gt;,” was authored by Debby Herbenick, Callie Patterson Perry, J. Dennis Fortenberry, Ruhun Wasata, Jodi Wilson, Owen Miller, Kayla Willens, Alyssa Williams, and Georgia Frey.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>PsyPost</author><pubDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2025 15:07:29 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipwFBVV95cUxQNUpXZFI3dkt2WnJqeUlybHllSmpBMjdUOTVKMUh0MXU4Y1I3U3E2YURTODI1bEVERURhZ1BJdzBkQktjQnJjQU12NVd5MXNjYmZOOXdGclNyelBpVFI2ZTZMVUVIVF9zcG5WNmp3MDllVjgtUjV3bzBGTHppcVJuZTFURVNqVTZJWE9DaDZJeTNYMjI0T3lITXlSTTBPY2dxZjVCNmNBNA</guid></item><item><title>科学家如何揭示季节性情感障碍背后的生物学-《卫报》</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/society/2025/nov/02/how-to-beat-the-winter-blues-seasonal-affective-disorder</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body-commercial-selector article-body-viewer-selector dcr-hdpgoq"&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-15rw6c2"&gt;F&lt;/span&gt;or some, the darkening days of autumn bring more than the annual ritual of reviving woolly jumpers and turning on the central heating. As the evenings close in and the mornings grow murky, energy ebbs and a heavy sadness settles in.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Although seasonal affective disorder (Sad) was only formally recognised by psychiatrists in the 1980s, the link between the seasons, mood and vitality has long been observed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="sign-in-gate"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The Yellow Emperor’s Classic of Medicine – a Chinese text from roughly 300BC – described how the seasons affect all living things. It advised that in winter, one should “retire early and get up with the sunrise”, keeping “desires and mental activity quiet and subdued, as if keeping a happy secret”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Today, scientists are rediscovering how closely tuned our biology is to the seasons. According to Dr Cathy Wyse, a chancellor’s research fellow at the University of Edinburgh, the biggest advance over the past decade “has been the realisation that seasonal changes in human mood are probably endogenous – that they’re part of our physiology”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Large-scale resources such as &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/science/2025/apr/18/uk-biobank-is-safely-sharing-health-data-to-drive-medical-research" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;the UK Biobank&lt;/a&gt; have transformed this area of research, allowing scientists to track seasonal patterns across hundreds of thousands of people over many years – something that was previously impossible.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;However, where to draw the line between normal winter sluggishness and clinical depression is not straightforward. Sad is recognised as a subtype of major depression or bipolar disorder, defined by its predictable seasonal pattern: symptoms typically begin in autumn or winter and lift in spring. Alongside typical signs of depression, people often sleep longer, feel lethargic and want to eat more, particularly carbohydrates.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The triggers of these changes are still being investigated, but they are almost certainly linked to reduced daylight. Light is the key regulator of our internal body or circadian clock, influencing the timing of hormone release, alertness and mood. Without sufficient daylight – especially when combined with too much artificial light in the evenings – these rhythms can drift out of sync with the external world.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="4bd39955-f577-4324-88ab-06658bf4a4f5" data-spacefinder-role="inline" data-spacefinder-type="model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.ImageBlockElement" class="dcr-173mewl"&gt;&lt;figcaption data-spacefinder-role="inline" class="dcr-fd61eq"&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-1inf02i"&gt;&lt;svg viewbox="0 0 18 13"&gt;&lt;path d="M18 3.5v8l-1.5 1.5h-15l-1.5-1.5v-8l1.5-1.5h3.5l2-2h4l2 2h3.5l1.5 1.5zm-9 7.5c1.9 0 3.5-1.6 3.5-3.5s-1.6-3.5-3.5-3.5-3.5 1.6-3.5 3.5 1.6 3.5 3.5 3.5z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-1qvd3m6"&gt;Amish people in the US, who spend more time outdoors and less time exposed to artificial light at night, have some of the lowest Sad rates among Caucasian populations.&lt;/span&gt; Photograph: Evelyn Hockstein/Reuters&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Some people may be more sensitive to this shift than others. Wyse and her colleagues are studying seasonal effects in &lt;a href="https://www.heliosbd.com/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;bipolar disorder&lt;/a&gt;, where manic episodes often peak in spring and depression tends to be more common in the darker months. “We suspect that people with bipolar disorder may be very sensitive to light and seasonal cues, and that’s triggering their symptoms,” said Wyse.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Even among those without clinical depression, many people experience a milder seasonal dip in mood, known as subsyndromal Sad or “the winter blues”. In the UK, an estimated one in five people are affected, though only about 2% experience full Sad.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Yet, seasonal biology extends far beyond mood. Researchers have found fluctuations in the expression of &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/ncomms8000" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;more than 4,000 protein-coding genes&lt;/a&gt; in white blood cells and fat, along with changes in the cellular composition of blood itself across the year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Wyse and her colleagues recently analysed four years of UK Biobank sleep data from half a million people. “We found that in winter, people tended to sleep longer and had increased sleeplessness – their sleep wasn’t so good as in the summer,” said Wyse, who will present these findings at the British Sleep Society conference in Brighton next week.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;However natural these seasonal changes may be, society still expects people to carry on as normal. Few of us can hibernate, however tempting that may sound. The most effective antidote to the winter slump is light. Bright light therapy remains the gold standard for treating Sad, though timing and dosage are critical (see below). For those unable to manage a daily session in front of a light box, natural sunlight is a powerful substitute.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="aae49198-892e-44fa-813c-7151b7917e50" data-spacefinder-role="showcase" data-spacefinder-type="model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.ImageBlockElement" class="dcr-5h0uf4"&gt;&lt;figcaption data-spacefinder-role="inline" class="dcr-9ktzqp"&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-1inf02i"&gt;&lt;svg viewbox="0 0 18 13"&gt;&lt;path d="M18 3.5v8l-1.5 1.5h-15l-1.5-1.5v-8l1.5-1.5h3.5l2-2h4l2 2h3.5l1.5 1.5zm-9 7.5c1.9 0 3.5-1.6 3.5-3.5s-1.6-3.5-3.5-3.5-3.5 1.6-3.5 3.5 1.6 3.5 3.5 3.5z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-1qvd3m6"&gt;‘Early morning light is especially powerful in resetting the circadian clock.’&lt;/span&gt; Photograph: Rebecca Cole/The Guardian&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Studies of Amish communities in the US – who spend more time outdoors and less time exposed to bright artificial light at night – show some of the lowest Sad rates recorded among Caucasian populations. By contrast, the prevalence in New York is about 4.7%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Exposure to bright, natural light early in the day helps to synchronise the circadian clock and suppress lingering melatonin, a night-time hormone that may make a person feel groggy. Light also has a direct alerting effect: one study found that an hour of blue-enriched light boosted reaction times more than the equivalent of two cups of coffee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;But light isn’t the whole story. Cognitive behavioural therapy tailored for Sad can be &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/25859764/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;as effective as light therapy&lt;/a&gt;, helping people reframe their relationship with winter rather than just manage symptoms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Winter will come regardless. By shifting how we think about it, we can reclaim some joy from the darker months.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="how-to-beat-the-winter-blues" class="dcr-12ibh7f"&gt;How to beat the winter blues&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;footer class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;&lt;ul class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;
 &lt;li class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;
  &lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Seek the morning sun: &lt;/strong&gt;Even on grey days, step outside as early as possible. Daylight resets your circadian clock, improves alertness and suppresses melatonin. Early morning light is especially powerful.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
 &lt;li class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;
  &lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Try a light box: &lt;/strong&gt;Brightness levels are measured in lux. A typical Sad lamp will emit light at about 10,000 lux – 20 to 40 times brighter than typical office lighting, and roughly equivalent to outdoor light on an overcast summer’s day. Sit in front of it for 20–30 minutes soon after waking.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
 &lt;li class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;
  &lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Check your sleep habits: &lt;/strong&gt;Stick to regular sleep and wake times, avoid screens late at night and keep evening lighting warm and dim. This helps prevent your internal rhythms from drifting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
 &lt;li class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;
  &lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Get outside – properly:&lt;/strong&gt; Even on a cloudy day in&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;January, outdoor light is roughly 10 times brighter than indoors. Aim for at least an hour a day, ideally combining it with something enjoyable: a walk, a coffee in the park or a kick-about with friends.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
 &lt;li class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;
  &lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Plan winter pleasures: &lt;/strong&gt;Reframe thoughts such as “I hate winter” into “winter is harder, but I can plan around it”. Embrace cosy rituals, such as candles, hot chocolate or warm baths and schedule social or outdoor activities, such as cold-water dips or winter hikes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
 &lt;li class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;
  &lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Know when to seek help: &lt;/strong&gt;If mood, sleep or motivation problems persist for weeks or interfere with daily life, speak to a GP or mental health professional. Sad is treatable.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span data-dcr-style="bullet"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; In the UK, the charity &lt;a href="https://www.mind.org.uk/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;Mind&lt;/a&gt; is available on 0300 123 3393 and &lt;a href="https://www.childline.org.uk/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;Childline&lt;/a&gt; on 0800 1111. In the US, call or text &lt;a href="https://www.mhanational.org/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;Mental Health America&lt;/a&gt; at 988 or chat 988lifeline.org. In Australia, support is available at &lt;a href="https://www.beyondblue.org.au/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;Beyond Blue&lt;/a&gt; on 1300 22 4636, &lt;a href="https://www.lifeline.org.au/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;Lifeline&lt;/a&gt; on 13 11 14, and at &lt;a href="https://mensline.org.au/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;MensLine&lt;/a&gt; on 1300 789 978&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/footer&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Guardian</author><pubDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2025 13:12:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipwFBVV95cUxOanVwWWVsYk1wSlprWTRKSEVjYi1faWMyNE1LdFFFZjlraElzTFZKN2Q1aFJwSnNFdnotVm0yY0l5SVNINXRrTTRRTWk3eFdPa3YtNjJDTjYySkJTVzBjTzE3d0JTZ1U0T0xyMHFtSmtTNjc4MmhDbmV6a1VnU2dYX1BhaENid2RZU1MyOXBrWWdlaTRYRFhxMzVlMjkwaUZlNVFKU1Fmdw</guid></item><item><title>营养学家实际上是在乞求你吃这些营养素，因为这种情况已经成为一种合法的健康危机- BuzzFeed</title><link>https://www.buzzfeed.com/juliekendrick/shortfall-nutrients-scary-sc</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="subbuzz buzz-width--standard__subbuzz buzz-type--long__subbuzz subbuzz-text
  subbuzz-index-11
  
  
  
  
  " data-keywords="fast fashion" data-module="subbuzz-text"&gt;
  
  &lt;p id="139570610" class="subbuzz-anchor"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;





&lt;p&gt;All this talk of shortfalls might leave you wondering if it’s at all possible to keep yourself well nourished these days. But if you’re reaching for a bottle of multivitamins right to supplement the gaps, you may want to slow your roll, experts said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Registered dietician nutritionist &lt;a href="https://www.mpmnutrition.com/about" target="_blank" data-skimlinks-tracking="7965912" data-affiliate="true"&gt;Marissa Karp&lt;/a&gt; had this advice: “While supplements can help us bridge the gap and serve as an insurance policy, they aren’t a replacement for eating nourishing foods. If you aren’t already eating well, moving your body, drinking water and managing your stress, don’t waste money on supplements. Taking supplements and then eating processed foods is not the same as eating a whole foods diet and using supplements to help ensure you’re getting enough.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She offered this example of the joy of whole foods: “When you eat an avocado, it’s not just about the potassium or dietary fiber, but the synergy of the nutrients working together. It’s how the fat and fiber in the avocado slow down your gastric emptying and help keep you fuller longer. It’s also about how satisfying it tastes.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Staying well-nourished is much simpler than you might think, Walker said. “We don’t need extreme diets or supplements to fill these nutrient gaps, but simple, intentional dietary shifts that can make a significant impact. By increasing whole foods like fruits, vegetables, whole grains, legumes, nuts, seeds, dairy and lean proteins, you can improve your intake of these critical shortfall nutrients, leading to better long-term health and disease prevention.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This article originally appeared on&lt;/em&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/entry/shortfall-nutrients_l_67e43ec0e4b0e572f646b037" target="_blank" data-skimlinks-tracking="7965912"&gt;&lt;em&gt;HuffPost.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BuzzFeed</author><pubDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2025 12:31:02 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMidkFVX3lxTE83Vm93SE4zMEdpWTlSZG5ESm9yeUpMc1ZrbHlJLUI0Sl82ekxTOHB2SU1mYzB2cTktMGZ3SG5qUXhNb09odTlranZjRW1fM3RPMjhlUS1iMWFsdE8wUC1kaWxhbVdySFVCWHBkeVBIcnVXcXlsUUE</guid></item><item><title>叛徒明星Elyn Wyn感谢“异常解剖学” - BBC</title><link>https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/c8dr4y51qd6o</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article&gt;&lt;p data-component="headline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 hNbOGD"&gt;&lt;h1 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 idLnWK"&gt;Traitors star is 'grateful for abnormal anatomy'&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="byline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="byline-new" class="sc-7bfdb3c2-0 fYJjWP"&gt;&lt;span data-testid="byline-new-contributors" class="sc-7bfdb3c2-11 ljQVMv"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="byline-new-contributors-contributor-0" class="sc-7bfdb3c2-5 xGeVU"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="sc-7bfdb3c2-7 djOqvY"&gt;Lena-Zaharah Mohammed&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-testid="byline-new-contributors-contributor-0-role-location" class="sc-7bfdb3c2-8 gvcwmG"&gt;BBC Wales&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 gtLOOD"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="hero-image" class="sc-5340b511-1 cMIbKV"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20251021-134202-667692b2c6-web-2.32.2-1/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 gUePlo hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/d17f/live/a94431b0-b646-11f0-9374-1f3a24e94d38.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/d17f/live/a94431b0-b646-11f0-9374-1f3a24e94d38.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/d17f/live/a94431b0-b646-11f0-9374-1f3a24e94d38.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/d17f/live/a94431b0-b646-11f0-9374-1f3a24e94d38.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/d17f/live/a94431b0-b646-11f0-9374-1f3a24e94d38.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/d17f/live/a94431b0-b646-11f0-9374-1f3a24e94d38.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/d17f/live/a94431b0-b646-11f0-9374-1f3a24e94d38.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/d17f/live/a94431b0-b646-11f0-9374-1f3a24e94d38.jpg.webp" loading="eager" alt="BBC/PA A brown haired woman staring down the barrel of the camera with a slight smirk. She is wearing black clothes with an 'E' shaped necklace. The background is busy with castles and birds." class="sc-5340b511-0 hLdNfA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 jVqbAn"&gt;BBC/PA&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;Elen has previously called on the Welsh government to offer more funding, better information and greater sensitivity to women's health&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The Traitors star and Welsh opera singer Elen Wyn says she is "grateful to have an abnormal anatomy" as it ultimately led to her endometriosis diagnosis. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Appearing on &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://feeds.acast.com/public/shows/its-not-just-a-period" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;the podcast It's Not JUST a Period!&lt;/a&gt;, the 25-year-old from Anglesey said doctors discovered she had only one "abnormally big kidney... two wombs and two cervixes".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The condition, known as uterus didelphys, occurs when the uterus fails to fuse during development in the womb and it affects about &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.toplinemd.com/doral-beach-gynecology/uterus-didelphys-what-are-the-causes-and-right-treatments/" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;0.3% of women&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;This results in a double uterus, which may also have two cervixes and two vaginal canals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Despite living with the condition her whole life, the recent discovery has left Elen with "so many questions" such as "why do [both the wombs] bleed at the same time?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The star of &lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/p0db9b2t/episodes/player" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;The Traitors Series 3&lt;/a&gt;, who was eliminated on episode two, &lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/articles/cgq91e88lepo" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;previously told the BBC&lt;/a&gt; that the pain she suffered was comparable to that of "barbed wire around her stomach".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;When her periods began aged 14, she frequently missed school and sat out of sports because of her discomfort.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;During her 10-year wait for an endometriosis diagnosis, Elen, originally from Llanfair-yng-Nghornwy, was regularly told it was "just a period", that she had a low pain threshold and on one occasion, was &lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/articles/cgq91e88lepo" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;laughed at by a GP&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Elen began suspecting she had endometriosis after watching other people talk about it on TikTok, yet the full extent of her complex condition came to light in a "terrifying" way.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;After her second ultrasound, a doctor assumed she knew she only had one kidney, which she did not. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;She was referred for an internal ultrasound and recalled feeling extremely anxious when a nurse couldn't locate her cervix and more staff were called in for second opinions. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"So many people were just looking at this screen inside of me and they just didn't understand," she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;At first, doctors denied she had &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.nhs.uk/conditions/endometriosis/" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;endometriosis&lt;/a&gt; - a condition where tissue similar to the womb's lining grows elsewhere in the body - but told her that her anatomy looked "very different" and referred her for an urgent MRI scan. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 hNbOGD"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 gXmhTb"&gt;'So many questions'&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;When doctors were trying to make sense of her uterus didelphys, they questioned whether she had two periods a month, which she hadn't.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"They asked me 'do you use tampons or pads?' and I said both.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"They asked me if I insert a tampon, do I continue to bleed, and I said no," she recalled.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"So it's all normal except from my two wombs."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Elen admitted she was still baffled by the discovery, leaving her with "so many questions".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"What I don't understand is if I have two wombs... why do they bleed at the same time?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"Are they just in sync?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"I'm kind of grateful that I do have an abnormal anatomy because otherwise I wouldn't have found out I had stage 4 endometriosis." &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;After years of being made to feel dramatic and "constantly gaslit", Elen said the diagnosis was something she "really needed".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 hNbOGD"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 gXmhTb"&gt;What is uterus didelphys?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Uterus didelphys is a rare congenital condition that develops before birth, when the two tubes that normally form a single uterus fail to fuse properly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Instead, two separate wombs are created - each with its own cervix - and, in some cases, a double vaginal canal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;People with a double uterus are at &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://my.clevelandclinic.org/health/diseases/23301-uterus-didelphys" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;increased risk of miscarriage and preterm birth but can have healthy pregnancies&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Some symptoms include:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class="sc-6f869981-0 diUlgm"&gt;&lt;li class="sc-734a601e-0 cRgahm"&gt;Pain during sex&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="sc-734a601e-0 cRgahm"&gt;Painful cramping before and during your period&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="sc-734a601e-0 cRgahm"&gt;Heavy bleeding during your period&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="sc-734a601e-0 cRgahm"&gt;Leaking blood when using a tampon (tampon is only in one vaginal canal and not the other)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="sc-734a601e-0 cRgahm"&gt;Frequent miscarriages&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="sc-734a601e-0 cRgahm"&gt;Premature labour&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Now that Elen has received her diagnosis, she is waiting for a laparoscopy to surgically remove the endometriosis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;After nine months believing she was on the waiting list, estimated to be six to eight months long, she asked for an update and discovered she was "never referred".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;She has now been added to the list, but feels it means the clock has restarted in her bid to get the answers she needs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BBC</author><pubDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2025 11:51:21 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiWkFVX3lxTE93MUJIenNTWTVqSjRFNU5GMHhWamRXVVlzRnExWHFETDVHdDVIWjZoWklmU210eml2R0Vqa0NNVG15ZmdJX2dOQU1xb3cwM2pOUnk5MjNhSDl3UdIBX0FVX3lxTE5Wem5rLVk5ZWZyVjZWVkMzeDAxVUhsUVBkakZSTHlwbm41ZXJ2Q2s2RnZ0UmpIekVJSlU2Z0trZkczYktPaEQ1OFJmSHpTTXVTWW1MWlRXaGpzU243STUw</guid></item><item><title>这位母亲有三个自闭症孩子。她花了成千上万的钱在虚假的希望上。’-《华盛顿邮报》</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/health/2025/11/02/autism-alternative-treatments-leucovorin/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text subtype-from-the-source grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="AEP5S6AO5RDCHGF3YHNVW6VUDM" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;ROCHESTER HILLS, Mich. — Wrangling three children with autism consumed Dana Paduchowski’s days in a chaotic swirl, her weeks dissolving into a blur of routines and meltdowns. When the house finally quieted at night, the mother would stay awake for hours scouring the internet for a magic treatment that didn’t exist.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2025 11:31:52 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilAFBVV95cUxOWmctelpnbEZZckdpa09zZkwzRVdseHcxM2w3SE1CT01rTWJSeWZqSk9tS2dESTVETnoyY2JOdDNXSEVuOWdSZjN1RTAyUThkbjN3cVp0eV9TbE9vWWpkUmZNTmRXWFhER0tlWms0dmNUS3V6a2FJQ2ZTU3BySHZnWVlkMDlVd3BGcE94eGlQMm1KWTE0</guid></item><item><title>让你闻起来更有吸引力的食物- BBC</title><link>https://www.bbc.com/future/article/20251031-the-foods-that-make-you-smell-more-attractive</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="sc-85f9acf9-0 kfxpiP"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Other vegetables have a very unique effect on our smell. The asparagus plant produces &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S003194221300352X?via=ihub" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;a compound called the asparagusic acid&lt;/a&gt; and, when it's digested by your body, it releases sulphur compounds too. &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://muse.jhu.edu/article/533914" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;It's these chemicals&lt;/a&gt;, such as methanethiol and dimethyl sulphide, that make your sweat and your pee smell a certain way. Sulphur compounds are very volatile, so they easily disperse in the air. That's why they're so easy to smell from the toilet bowl. This smell usually lasts &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://ascpt.onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/psp4.12264" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;more than five hours&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Not everybody produces this smell, although studies about this &lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.bbc.com/future/article/20140818-mystery-of-asparagus-and-urine" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;keep &lt;/a&gt;&lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.bbc.com/future/article/20140818-mystery-of-asparagus-and-urine" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;coming up with different findings&lt;/a&gt;. In the 1950s, research seemed to suggest that fewer than 50% of people produce the tell-tale asparagus pee odour, while in 2010, researchers found more than 90% of test participants did. So it’s not clear cut. And not everybody can perceive the stink: the ability to smell one's pungent &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://academic.oup.com/chemse/article/36/1/9/442551?login=false" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;asparagus-smelling pee seems to be down to genetics&lt;/a&gt; too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;However, when it comes to fruit and vegetables more widely, eating more of them can lead to a more attractive scent. &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S1090513816301933" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;A 2017 study in Australia&lt;/a&gt; found that men who had consumed more fruit and vegetables were significantly associated with smelling better – more fruity, floral and sweet. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The study also notes, interestingly, when people have to rate people's faces, slightly yellower skin rich in carotenoid – a molecule from carrots, pumpkins, tomatoes and papayas and others – is also found to be more attractive. But the same study suggests that people consuming diets with a little bit of fat, meat, egg, and tofu intake were also associated with more pleasant-smelling sweat. Carb-heavy diets produced the least sexy of scents. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 gXmhTb"&gt;&lt;span id="meat-and-fish" class="sc-d16436d-0 gCPVhV"&gt;&lt;b id="meat-and-fish" class="sc-d16436d-0 gnUCoQ"&gt;Meat and fish&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Meat and fish can also produce a distinct body odour as animal proteins are broken down by the body into amino acids and fats, which are then excreted through sweat – where they interact with skin bacteria.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BBC</author><pubDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikwFBVV95cUxNakprX2xSVmdrUVR3Z21GWnRiRnFhS2Q0YW90Q3IzVW03NUk1U3lfQkdFanVSNG5mZTA4SHRLVDlHcm1RMkNVcXhDcEJBbHJsYm9lZi1BRDF6Mk93TDJza0cwU20ycGtmVWQtQnZxYnpBVUdlbFlmZkpXanpBcDRjYTkwa0lDekhYcFZYUHRzazcxSXc</guid></item><item><title>以下是您应该（或不应该）在全身冰浴中浸泡的原因-有线</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/is-cold-plunging-good-for-you/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="body__inner-container"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="lead-in-text-callout"&gt;Cold plunging at&lt;/span&gt; the gym or having a chilly shower at home has become a popular practice in recent years. But is all the self-inflicted freezing really that good for you? With the promise of boosting your mood, providing mental clarity, and reducing muscle soreness post-workout, it may sound enticing, but it’s not for everyone. Aside from making your teeth chatter, there are the notable negatives as well as its positives to consider.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;Tasked with the challenge of testing the &lt;a href="https://www.wired.com/story/best-cold-plunge-tubs/" target="_blank"&gt;latest cold-plunge pools&lt;/a&gt; earlier this year, I reluctantly jumped on the bandwagon. With my adrenaline pumping and my endorphins having a disco post-plunge, I was hooked and have since became an ice bath advocate. But as with every wellness craze, it’s worth keeping up with the ever-changing advice on best practices. Keen to find out more, I asked Gary Brecka, top biohacker and founder of &lt;a data-offer-url="https://www.theultimatehuman.com/" class="external-link" data-event-click='{"element":"ExternalLink","outgoingURL":"https://cna.st/affiliate-link/VDkSwjASRpoWbh7jFFq7H1EGwVjShzD22fmppo1hRHX5MmtKR7XuHmt35Nnxq7CjQFWEQ1TgaXqkBwP5pnW22Ujfa7cjW2ePSJJtykV6HkLSCdCDMaiNujN2urahUWkKvLQ6Bydw1Y9zHp9Wysur87VnuMj4QU6B4ERoc3yKyfv376DtkyyoS4VdqGoHv88TjEiAfhMHjFkTunEgkZCtfRBz5YCiqxv4C9Rtjurt7aZQChpyXWJGT2rFixqBKC7f1c5EGJHq7EuwZksL9C3bk"}' href="https://cna.st/affiliate-link/VDkSwjASRpoWbh7jFFq7H1EGwVjShzD22fmppo1hRHX5MmtKR7XuHmt35Nnxq7CjQFWEQ1TgaXqkBwP5pnW22Ujfa7cjW2ePSJJtykV6HkLSCdCDMaiNujN2urahUWkKvLQ6Bydw1Y9zHp9Wysur87VnuMj4QU6B4ERoc3yKyfv376DtkyyoS4VdqGoHv88TjEiAfhMHjFkTunEgkZCtfRBz5YCiqxv4C9Rtjurt7aZQChpyXWJGT2rFixqBKC7f1c5EGJHq7EuwZksL9C3bk" rel="sponsored" target="_blank"&gt;The Ultimate Human&lt;/a&gt;, for advice on how to cold plunge for maximum benefit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;Whether you’re a seasoned pro or a newbie wondering what all the fuss is about, take a deep, calming breath and jump right in. Find options for your own ice bath in the WIRED guide to the &lt;a href="https://www.wired.com/story/best-cold-plunge-tubs/" target="_blank"&gt;best cold-plunge tubs&lt;/a&gt;, with designs from the likes of &lt;a data-offer-url="https://polarmonkeys.com/products/brainpod?" class="external-link" data-event-click='{"element":"ExternalLink","outgoingURL":"https://cna.st/affiliate-link/7zscoHCrWNbASLQN1h2KUpoPrCLRtaQ4fEKh71zYwvRYxB5GyD6mKp2NZBgXNebLjuYnTL2hWeka8kjLFEkL5MVuAErfuC7C3aR6jZUxdsZtf7QpkYwhZKzgqJ9rJtF3S4MhhaVpoVwcKfZrMA24yMRDvEMkDS2vGLUtrAAjDx352GRWF7sWzfC4k7tgB7m6W9WXUvoyihLZ2KLG7JsFhszh8HfBtXsDedcK2DbmkjpUPHZiq2iNutRdxX5kjt8HP7jfKf2awHyZmrvJN9psgFnP7dZ2H57vHQa"}' href="https://cna.st/affiliate-link/7zscoHCrWNbASLQN1h2KUpoPrCLRtaQ4fEKh71zYwvRYxB5GyD6mKp2NZBgXNebLjuYnTL2hWeka8kjLFEkL5MVuAErfuC7C3aR6jZUxdsZtf7QpkYwhZKzgqJ9rJtF3S4MhhaVpoVwcKfZrMA24yMRDvEMkDS2vGLUtrAAjDx352GRWF7sWzfC4k7tgB7m6W9WXUvoyihLZ2KLG7JsFhszh8HfBtXsDedcK2DbmkjpUPHZiq2iNutRdxX5kjt8HP7jfKf2awHyZmrvJN9psgFnP7dZ2H57vHQa" rel="sponsored" target="_blank"&gt;PolarMonkeys&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a data-offer-url="https://www.amazon.co.uk/CalmMax-Athletes-Portable-Therapy-Outdoor/dp/B0CTK27RS5?" class="external-link" data-event-click='{"element":"ExternalLink","outgoingURL":"https://cna.st/affiliate-link/5a1FMimJbzYezMeMToA4fa2KPpoGk6a3mjMwdfkBSx8vqeN5ZYTnYXCCPjYH6EcN1Byfudtbuz74NZYpgiVk57gSvZfgNc65uYMruFBT5rVMtuYv2U1cHFegNekE4Wp9woqTBv37r6pHdP7EKvnkaMbiUU6rrmm9ohfMjWZwMh2aYYMsjvnxVi14HHedngy4t3ELoSCerfabpaBf2WeuDMeXMsqw2LDeG4r8EKAcbZJQUTVbRmoPK88b8fYDECJ72xZjpKHmazfB9cXgcnp7bsgm1Kitm2W8MD4pAtfaQJhrRxihRQy89kbLfnAk5yAD2A3w6LCqMaGsiJG2QeiN4jQ"}' href="https://cna.st/affiliate-link/5a1FMimJbzYezMeMToA4fa2KPpoGk6a3mjMwdfkBSx8vqeN5ZYTnYXCCPjYH6EcN1Byfudtbuz74NZYpgiVk57gSvZfgNc65uYMruFBT5rVMtuYv2U1cHFegNekE4Wp9woqTBv37r6pHdP7EKvnkaMbiUU6rrmm9ohfMjWZwMh2aYYMsjvnxVi14HHedngy4t3ELoSCerfabpaBf2WeuDMeXMsqw2LDeG4r8EKAcbZJQUTVbRmoPK88b8fYDECJ72xZjpKHmazfB9cXgcnp7bsgm1Kitm2W8MD4pAtfaQJhrRxihRQy89kbLfnAk5yAD2A3w6LCqMaGsiJG2QeiN4jQ" rel="sponsored" target="_blank" data-aps-asin="B0CTK27RS5" data-aps-asc-tag="w050b-20"&gt;CalmMax&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a data-offer-url="https://plunge.com/products/plunge?" class="external-link" data-event-click='{"element":"ExternalLink","outgoingURL":"https://cna.st/affiliate-link/AUmSbTSfyktbrSrBKbpwFxNMcdd1vukjCDSHder9QRM9oqS3iFWcbcCEDv7CodPPhD1MM2aPiCFEAPmnBtDFjkTF2h8JpxygFX6xcVCVmTrhBRdvyyP3GgX4tLhLVXiShJGV55Aa1cDausWBFbRuNVt4N5cQuz1Vn8auFBhUEsFkq7GbRM2uvUePoaSG333428NsDUKEgocnhXYhN1fdwBuN3fAXV28kb9RGrAR1ey2C1gBGmtLou1sdWxwqmbNJTC1WhPcbpNfDUBKUqiUQcBDQ"}' href="https://cna.st/affiliate-link/AUmSbTSfyktbrSrBKbpwFxNMcdd1vukjCDSHder9QRM9oqS3iFWcbcCEDv7CodPPhD1MM2aPiCFEAPmnBtDFjkTF2h8JpxygFX6xcVCVmTrhBRdvyyP3GgX4tLhLVXiShJGV55Aa1cDausWBFbRuNVt4N5cQuz1Vn8auFBhUEsFkq7GbRM2uvUePoaSG333428NsDUKEgocnhXYhN1fdwBuN3fAXV28kb9RGrAR1ey2C1gBGmtLou1sdWxwqmbNJTC1WhPcbpNfDUBKUqiUQcBDQ" rel="sponsored" target="_blank"&gt;Plunge&lt;/a&gt;, and more.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="TableOfContentWrapper-jDOHAN fhKwHR table-of-content"&gt;&lt;div data="[object Object]" class="AccordionWrapper-hsYVHT bgMFty"&gt;&lt;div class="AccordionItemWrapper-eWlGuu eNwKZf"&gt;&lt;div class="AccordionContainer-foSklP iRHdCZ"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="accordion-item-container" class="AccordionItemContainer-ywYcO eQgPvY"&gt;&lt;p class="AccordionItemContainerLabel-ioTxOM diANax"&gt;Jump to Section&lt;/p&gt;&lt;button class="BaseButton-lbLhfD ButtonWrapper-igqDZ gTIqfM hKIiJv button button--utility AccordionItemContainerButton-eSsfaw cSYOvq" data-event-click='{"element":"Button"}' data-testid="Button" role="button" type="button"&gt;&lt;span class="ButtonLabel-cyWivE hvohFn button__label"&gt;AccordionItemContainerButton&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p id="what-is-cold-plunging" tabindex="-1"&gt;&lt;h2 class="paywall"&gt;What Is Cold Plunging?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;Whether it’s in the sea, a lake, or an ice bath at your local gym or at home, cold plunging means immersing your body in water that is 39 to 59 defrees Fahrenheit (4 to 15 Celsius). If you don’t have a gym membership and don’t fancy stripping down to your bathing suit at the local lake, an indoor bathtub filled with icy cold water will do. “You don’t need an expensive set up,” says Brecka. “A bathtub with ice works. A horse trough in the backyard works. Dedicated plunge pools are convenient, but you’ll get benefits no matter how you create cold exposure. It’s consistency that matters more than equipment.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Container-VgtPr ekoLDG"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;So how long do you cold plunge and what temperature should a cold plunge be? Brecka suggests two to six minutes as the ideal time. It’s long enough to activate the nervous system and short enough to stay safe. If you’re new to cold plunging, however, under a minute is plenty.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="is-cold-plunge-good-for-you" tabindex="-1"&gt;&lt;h2 class="paywall"&gt;Is Cold Plunging Good for You?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;“What are the benefits of cold plunging?” is the million dollar question you’re probably asking yourself, right as you're staring into the tub (along with “Why don’t you just have a warm cookie and hot chocolate instead?” which is what I often hear my inner child say.) Brecka suggests persevering for maximum benefit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;“We do a plunge because cold exposure activates your nervous system, improves circulation, and helps your body adapt to stress,” he says. “Cold plunging is not about powering through the shock, it’s about letting that shock drive physiological change.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;Some studies show benefits for cold plunging, including from &lt;a href="https://www.health.harvard.edu/staying-healthy/research-highlights-health-benefits-from-cold-water-immersions?" target="_blank"&gt;Harvard Medical School&lt;/a&gt;. While &lt;a data-offer-url="https://sncs-prod-external.mayo.edu/hometown-health/speaking-of-health/cold-plunge-after-workouts" class="external-link" data-event-click='{"element":"ExternalLink","outgoingURL":"https://sncs-prod-external.mayo.edu/hometown-health/speaking-of-health/cold-plunge-after-workouts"}' href="https://sncs-prod-external.mayo.edu/hometown-health/speaking-of-health/cold-plunge-after-workouts" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;those studies are encouraging&lt;/a&gt;, however, they are not conclusive, and their effects vary considerably across the board.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>WIRED</author><pubDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiakFVX3lxTE5TcUpweTloWm9YTWM3MldlRWY4Q01TN3NPVXVKT2M4UjhmOWk2bnBzSVVRVmZ1OFgwZENlVVpTOVVBQW9JWmJqOUUtSk9JLWVacUZWZXFEbzgwUFdsMm02c0JrUnMya19PTnc</guid></item><item><title>专家对接种宠物疫苗的看法- Lewiston Sun Journal</title><link>https://www.sunjournal.com/2025/11/02/whats-the-reality-of-vaccinating-pets-in-maine/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content"&gt;

		
		&lt;figure class="wp-block-image size-large"&gt;&lt;a href="https://w2pcms.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/10/2025/10/43077767_sj.petshots.1012-1.jpg" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;&lt;img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" src="https://www.sunjournal.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/11/2025/11/43077767_sj.petshots.1012-1.jpg?w=1024" alt="" class="wp-image-11123614" srcset="https://www.sunjournal.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/11/2025/11/43077767_sj.petshots.1012-1.jpg 4000w, https://www.sunjournal.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/11/2025/11/43077767_sj.petshots.1012-1.jpg?resize=300,244 300w, https://www.sunjournal.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/11/2025/11/43077767_sj.petshots.1012-1.jpg?resize=768,625 768w, https://www.sunjournal.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/11/2025/11/43077767_sj.petshots.1012-1.jpg?resize=1024,833 1024w, https://www.sunjournal.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/11/2025/11/43077767_sj.petshots.1012-1.jpg?resize=1536,1250 1536w, https://www.sunjournal.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/11/2025/11/43077767_sj.petshots.1012-1.jpg?resize=2048,1667 2048w, https://www.sunjournal.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/11/2025/11/43077767_sj.petshots.1012-1.jpg?resize=1200,977 1200w, https://www.sunjournal.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/11/2025/11/43077767_sj.petshots.1012-1.jpg?resize=2000,1628 2000w, https://www.sunjournal.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/11/2025/11/43077767_sj.petshots.1012-1.jpg?resize=780,635 780w, https://www.sunjournal.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/11/2025/11/43077767_sj.petshots.1012-1.jpg?resize=400,326 400w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;figcaption class="wp-element-caption"&gt;Greater Androscoggin Humane Society shelter veterinarian Alison Pare fills a syringe with a vaccine for a cat Tuesday at the Lewiston shelter. (Russ Dillingham/Staff Photographer)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;What should I do if I hear about parvovirus cases near me?&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Parvovirus is a highly contagious, often deadly virus that has been reported among dogs in Androscoggin, Penobscot and &lt;a href="https://www.sunjournal.com/2025/10/22/parvo-alert-issued-in-mexico/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Oxford counties&lt;/a&gt;, plus other communities across Maine. If you hear of cases in your area, avoid taking your dog to a dog park or other public places where pets gather. The best protection against parvovirus is to get your dog vaccinated.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Is the rabies vaccine required for Maine’s pets?&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Yes. Dogs and cats that are 3 months or older are required by Maine law to be vaccinated against rabies, but state officials strongly recommend the vaccine for other animals such as ferrets, horses and livestock. Rabies is almost always fatal and is carried by common wildlife animals in Maine, including raccoons, skunks, bats and foxes.&lt;/p&gt;


	
	


&lt;p&gt;“That’s the no-brainer,” David Cloutier, board president of the Maine Veterinary Medical Association, said of the rabies vaccine. “Just do it. They are incredibly effective and we see almost no reaction.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;What vaccines are recommended for dogs?&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Core vaccines are recommended for all dogs, regardless of lifestyle. They include vaccines for rabies, leptospirosis and a combination vaccine for several contagious and potentially deadly viral infections, according to American Animal Hospital Association guidelines.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The combination distemper vaccine, known as a DAPP or DHPP vaccine, is a three-dose shot recommended 6-8 weeks after birth that protects against canine distemper virus, two types of adenovirus, parvovirus and parainfluenza. The vaccine for leptospirosis can be included in the combination distemper or administered separately.  &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;In Maine, tick-related vaccines are considered core by most experts, Cloutier said. “If you live in a place like Maine with a lot of ticks, it makes sense,” he said.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;For cats?&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Cats are recommended to get the rabies vaccine at around 4 months. While vaccine types and schedules differ, cats are recommended to get core vaccines that protect against feline leukemia, panleukopenia, herpes virus and calicivirus.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;How often should my pet get a booster?&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Dogs and cats should both get a rabies booster one year after their first dose, then every three years after that. The canine distemper vaccine follows the same schedule.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Are vaccines bad for my pet?&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;No. Vaccines have been proven to be a safe and effective way to prevent life-threatening diseases in animals. Some pets may experience mild, temporary side effects, but experts say the benefits of vaccinating against dangerous illnesses far outweigh any risks.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Can viruses or diseases be transmitted between humans and pets?&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Yes. Rabies can be transmitted from animals to humans through bites or scratches. Leptospirosis, which can cause kidney damage, liver failure and death in humans, is spread through contact with the urine of infected animals, usually found in contaminated water or soil.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;What if I can’t pay for a vaccine or veterinary care?&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Many shelters and humane societies in Maine hold vaccination clinics at a low cost, including Bangor Humane Shelter, Greater Androscoggin Humane Society in Lewiston and Midcoast Humane in Brunswick. There are also vaccination clinics at several Petco and Tractor Supply Co. stores across Maine.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Clinics are a low-cost, easily accessible way to get vaccines, Cloutier said. You don’t even need a relationship with a veterinarian.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“We’ll vaccinate them right on the bed of the truck, no questions asked, $10 a piece,” he said.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Vaccination is the most cost-effective way to keep veterinary costs low. The canine distemper combination vaccine costs between $20 and $100, while experts say treatment for parvovirus can cost thousands.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Potential pet owners should consider whether they can afford vaccination and veterinary care before adopting a pet.&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;

	

	
			&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Lewiston Sun Journal</author><pubDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2025 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijgFBVV95cUxOM3FLVWI5NHVDcVEtQjZQR2VfdDViR3hxRldjYmtfUkNFakhGc0VWMUFaN0ZmRzNHVFZIQkRSZDhzd3NSOWVfUmp6UzROV0hybk96RHpsYlJidTk3clUxa19zc2ktRWdMYlU4X1I5dlFMcDU1dS1SbS1HTkdpWUsyR0RPMlhZUTBKdkZwREVB</guid></item><item><title>研究表明，运动使女性在心脏健康方面优于男性|健康-印度斯坦时报</title><link>https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/study-says-exercise-gives-women-this-one-edge-over-men-when-it-comes-to-heart-health-101762066922101.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="detail " dataid="/lifestyle/health/study-says-exercise-gives-women-this-one-edge-over-men-when-it-comes-to-heart-health-101762066922101.html"&gt; &lt;div class="storyParagraphFigure"&gt; &lt;p&gt;One of the fundamental pillars of safeguarding &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/cardiac-surgeon-explains-how-to-choose-the-right-cooking-oils-for-heart-health-101761816473497.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="heart health"&gt;heart health&lt;/a&gt; is exercising. It keeps the heart pumping efficiently and keeps the cardiovascular system resilient. From &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/topic/blood-pressure" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="blood pressure"&gt;blood pressure&lt;/a&gt; levels to weight management, there are ample benefits. But did you know the amount of exercise needed for better heart health benefits differs from person to person? One way this distinction appears is sex-based.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;figure class=""&gt; &lt;span class=""&gt; &lt;picture&gt; &lt;source media="(max-width:767px)" srcset="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/11/02/550x309/cyclling_1759048029799_1762067276470.jpg" alt="Men even when they exercise as much as women may not reap the same rewards. (Freepik)" title="Men even when they exercise as much as women may not reap the same rewards. (Freepik)"&gt;&lt;/source&gt; &lt;img src="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/11/02/550x309/cyclling_1759048029799_1762067276470.jpg" alt="Men even when they exercise as much as women may not reap the same rewards. (Freepik)" title="Men even when they exercise as much as women may not reap the same rewards. (Freepik)"&gt; &lt;/picture&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;figcaption&gt;Men even when they exercise as much as women may not reap the same rewards. (Freepik)&lt;/figcaption&gt; &lt;/figure&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;p id="readMoreFTUser"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;ALSO READ: &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/take-the-stairs-over-lift-study-reveals-just-3-minutes-of-daily-movement-can-reduce-heart-attack-and-stroke-risk-101754563066677.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="Take the stairs over lift: Study reveals just 3 minutes of daily movement can reduce heart attack and stroke risk"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Take the stairs over lift: Study reveals just 3 minutes of daily movement can reduce heart attack and stroke risk&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="mt-10 mb-10 htEchoRecirculationWidget"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="predictorShow mb20" data-vars-predictor="true" data-vars-quiz="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="quizShow mb20" data-vars-minimized="false" data-vars-predictor="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;A &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s44161-025-00732-z" target="_blank" class="backlink" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="study"&gt;study&lt;/a&gt; published in the journal of Nature Cardiovascular Research on October 27, 2025, unveiled this difference in how men and women gain heart health benefits from exercise. Turns out, women may gain the same level of heart protection as men with nearly half the amount of activity as men. The study examined wearable device data from around 85,000 adults.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;What did the study find?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Women who exercised for almost 250 minutes a week, which is approximately 35 minutes a day, showed a 30 percent lower risk of developing heart disease. But here's the difference. For men to achieve the same heart protection from exercise of 30 percent lower risk, they need to do exercises for around 530 minutes a week.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;This is not solely for preventing heart diseases, but also the same is applicable for mitigating heart disease complications as well. Women with heart disease who met the recommended activity levels gained the advantage of a whopping 70 percent lower death reduction, compared to those women who stayed inactive. But when men did the same amount and duration of exercise, their risk reduction was only around 19 percent.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;It sheds light on the global recommended activity levels, which are often general and not sex specific. The same 150 minutes of moderate to vigorous activity per week is relevant for everyone, despite gender. But this study serves as an eye-opener, suggesting that exercise's benefits are effective not based on how long one works out but on how the body responds to the activity. This is particularly critical as men and women have greatly different biological responses and systems.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;Why do women's bodies respond differently?&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;figure class="inlineIMG"&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;img data-src="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/10/08/original/1049_1759934877054.jpg" class="lazy" src="https://images.hindustantimes.com/default/550x309.jpg" alt="Muscle type and hormones help women gain better heart health benefits. (Picture credit: Freepik)" title="Muscle type and hormones help women gain better heart health benefits. (Picture credit: Freepik)"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;figcaption&gt;Muscle type and hormones help women gain better heart health benefits. (Picture credit: Freepik)&lt;/figcaption&gt; &lt;/figure&gt; &lt;p&gt;The reason why women have an extra advantage here is due to the hormones and muscle composition. Estrogen, which is a sex hormone, is more common in women, causes fat metabolism when one is exercising. This is essentially an energy process where the body uses fat as fuel during exercise rather than relying on sugar. When fat for energy is used, it puts less pressure on the heart. This is why women have better heart health with less activity. Women also have more endurance-oriented muscle fibres (type I), unlike men, who have more power-oriented muscle fibres (type II).&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;All these biological variations make it possible for women to reap better rewards for cardiovascular health. For women, their hormones and muscles help them gain more benefits.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Note to readers: This article is for informational purposes only and not a substitute for professional medical advice. Always seek the advice of your doctor with any questions about a medical condition.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Hindustan Times</author><pubDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2025 07:47:16 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi6AFBVV95cUxORzlzMDctTWhObkRYUmYwNFBsZDV2VXlnQk5ETklhbVc4Nk5hMElQTFg3WkIzMHpzQzRxU3dIN21fUVlPT3Q2bktNc09URzhiQW1ZUnF0TTdZZ0FCckkxblY2MnpNMlU1aTlndm5DYVFIWVNTQ2hLUjAwTTJ3RGJNemRES2xRcUY3MlNvTlZFNDVmbEhuUERTbGdMUXgzd2pRbktXUWdFSkV2NDMxU3R2M0RKRE5DUHd1V01NQzR4RDdnMnFIVUdLMTlJZHo5dzhfb0ppWHN1b0gyaUVsd3VhVjZER0dUWUhj0gHuAUFVX3lxTE5zMkhSQk5NYnlJN29DZWR2a1lIcW1tX192U2FTbUhRSExCRGlLZ21fdWQyOUxuRUtpOS1iZWRZeTNSVVJualUtNTJ2Z0VPTnhlNnFXX1hXb0o0dHFwdlF1ZWF3Q2g4WHlPeFlYdWxsMkFodGw5RDlDR1RoRk50Yl9pWlRpdC01NllwNnVEemtpVXNQOEJEMTF4OWQzakk3VXhzUDNiV25SUXpFTFE3R2h2dE9EVldPS3B0WDZKM0EzTEgtWVh5VG01Z1I2dDQxcWNFVF9CM0ZUb0o1ZzhDQ3VrX2I4V2ZxZDRDUUtzOHc</guid></item><item><title>营养学家警告说，如果你不想患乳腺癌，请做以下5件事： “如果你没有足够的氧气……” |健康-印度斯坦时报</title><link>https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/nutritionist-warns-if-you-don-t-want-to-suffer-from-breast-cancer-do-5-things-move-daily-increase-protein-intake-101762063859462.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="detail " dataid="/lifestyle/health/nutritionist-warns-if-you-don-t-want-to-suffer-from-breast-cancer-do-5-things-move-daily-increase-protein-intake-101762063859462.html"&gt; &lt;div class="storyParagraphFigure"&gt; &lt;p&gt;Breast cancer is one of the leading causes of cancer death for women in many countries, and the most common cancer found in women globally. In 2022, the &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.who.int/news-room/fact-sheets/detail/breast-cancer" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual"&gt;World Health Organisation (WHO)&lt;/a&gt; estimated that 670,000 women died from breast cancer worldwide.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;figure class=""&gt; &lt;span class=""&gt; &lt;picture&gt; &lt;source media="(max-width:767px)" srcset="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/11/02/550x309/breast_cancer__1762067404309_1762067404447.jpg" alt="If you don't get enough oxygen in ways of exercise, you must move daily. (Freepik)" title="If you don't get enough oxygen in ways of exercise, you must move daily. (Freepik)"&gt;&lt;/source&gt; &lt;img src="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/11/02/550x309/breast_cancer__1762067404309_1762067404447.jpg" alt="If you don't get enough oxygen in ways of exercise, you must move daily. (Freepik)" title="If you don't get enough oxygen in ways of exercise, you must move daily. (Freepik)"&gt; &lt;/picture&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;figcaption&gt;If you don't get enough oxygen in ways of exercise, you must move daily. (Freepik)&lt;/figcaption&gt; &lt;/figure&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;p id="readMoreFTUser"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Also Read |&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/cardiologist-with-20-years-of-experience-shares-secret-to-ageing-better-than-your-parents-know-your-cardiovascular-age-101762049146575.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="Cardiologist with 20 years of experience shares secret to ageing better than your parents: ‘Know your cardiovascular…’"&gt;Cardiologist with 20 years of experience shares secret to ageing better than your parents: ‘Know your cardiovascular…’&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="mt-10 mb-10 htEchoRecirculationWidget"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="predictorShow mb20" data-vars-predictor="true" data-vars-quiz="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="quizShow mb20" data-vars-minimized="false" data-vars-predictor="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Therefore, educating oneself about &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/medanta-hospital-oncologist-explains-which-women-are-most-at-risk-of-breast-cancer-101761893876405.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="breast cancer"&gt;breast cancer&lt;/a&gt; can ensure your loved ones don't suffer. Nutritionist Suman Agarwal, certified from Oxford University, in an Instagram post shared on October 31, listed 5 things people should do immediately to safeguard themselves.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;5 things to safeguard yourself from breast cancer&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listing the 5 precautionary measures, the nutritionist wrote, “If you don't want your wife, your mother, or your sister to suffer from breast cancer, these are the five things you must do immediately.” Here's what she recommends:&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;1. Move daily and get your morning sun&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Calling it the ‘most important step’, the nutritionist recommends daily movement and getting your dose of morning sun. “If you don't get enough oxygen in ways of exercise, you must move daily. Whether it is walking, jogging, paddling, pickleball, cycling, swimming, or any form of exercise is great,” she stressed.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;2. Increase your protein intake&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Next, the nutritionist suggests increasing protein intake in your diet. She stresses that protein deficiency is a very big problem. It is not just for muscle building, it is vital for antibodies and repairing tissues.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;“Your immune system relies on protein to defend against harmful bacteria and invaders, including cancer cells,” she added.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;figure class="inlineIMG"&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;img data-src="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/11/02/original/breast_cancer_prevention_1762066896729.png" class="lazy" src="https://images.hindustantimes.com/default/550x309.jpg" alt="5 breast cancer prevention tips. (Google Gemini)" title="5 breast cancer prevention tips. (Google Gemini)"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;figcaption&gt;5 breast cancer prevention tips. (Google Gemini)&lt;/figcaption&gt; &lt;/figure&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;3. Avoid sugar&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;“As you know, food for cancer is sugar. So what you must avoid is junk food, desserts, ice cream, chocolates, aerated drinks, alcohol, and mithai (sweets). You don't have to completely avoid this food. You can have them, but only on occasions,” she warned.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;4. Manage your stress and your sleep&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Next, the nutritionist highlighted the importance of managing stress and sleep. She stated, “Chronic stress is one of the biggest reasons for disrupting your hormonal balance and suppressing your immune system.”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;This is why long-standing sleep deprivation weakens your immune system and increases the risk of cancer.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;5. Monthly check-ups&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Last, but most important, I recommend everyone to do monthly checks of their breast and visit their gynaecologist on a yearly basis for screening,” the nutritionist stressed. Early detection of cancer can save your loved ones' lives.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Note to readers: This article is for informational purposes only and not a substitute for professional medical advice. Always seek the advice of your doctor with any questions about a medical condition.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;This report is based on user-generated content from social media. HT.com has not independently verified the claims and does not endorse them.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;    &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Hindustan Times</author><pubDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2025 07:16:58 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijgJBVV95cUxNb1RzdDhZdGhHc19qZDhlc05BRzdsTlhlOXRtbmFpVG5GWnVieXV6cXFJNWpZLU9UUHdab3h3RExmNTlaaTFRRjJyQWVJZUFzZ2I5b3RxQkVfZnBnOVpySlF0OGpUdF9NTGt2YUxqTXVxMGVnT0tfZTI1a2RCLWNFbE52REdpUFladnlDM2J0d0ZuOEJNcS1NOEhlRE9QLWt3WjZpUGZ5MEtUMjcwWUR2NEJaZHVaZzByV1F5R1hZSk5CQzRlZzMzREVZVHF1WVpLVHhSV2stcGNTM2J0T1Q1NHlVSTNUVXRTVFV0blQ0VUZvbTluRjZ0ekxCbHlJS1RJUEpzMWVDZ1pyRjhqbVHSAZMCQVVfeXFMTUhSaldjSXVvdEhGcnAtUi04cWJlcW1mSlRScW9RQ2IzQVdFYVJXYWc1YlllZXZmTXJaRGFHbFlpSmg4S1pnLWpkVjR5UWg3aUtKRmllUGE4eHhVdTVRVS1ZU1A0VjVCRUxYTTVhVHE4Q3NtbzdjMVVoNjA3aW5HT3p4T1pnUUtSNkhTNjJkTTFSZEpxRC1mUzZqaUlvSWdGT01na3dnZExKQmZkMzJQdnM2TGFNNk5RemFwbGJrUzFNWEFhLUlvVUNMT0hSLTBQcEt5cTV3cVhTNEhkRkFrcFEtT18yYm82TGhUMHZDZXZEdUtURVYxYkQ1ZDQ1OEFKa0tTMmpMWUZVZ25oZWlZTE1zeFE</guid></item><item><title>自然逆转心脏病：领先心脏病专家的21天生活方式计划-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/reversing-heart-disease-naturally-the-21-day-lifestyle-plan-from-a-leading-cardiologist/articleshow/125028384.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Heart disease is still the leading cause of death worldwide, but what if one of the world's top cardiologists told you it was possible to greatly improve your heart health naturally in just 21 days? Renowned cardiologist Dr. Aseem Malhotra, along with an award-winning health campaigner, developed a science-backed approach based on lifestyle changes that support cardiovascular health without any medication. In the Ultimate Human Podcast with Gary Brecka, Dr. Malhotra shares how heart health can improve drastically within 21 days if a person follows the steps outlined below.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="3"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="4"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;The motivation behind this approach&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr. Malhotra's journey within the NHS began when he faced a concerning paradox: patients admitted with heart attacks were being served unhealthy hospital food, while he performed emergency procedures. This sparked his lifelong commitment to advocating for nutrition and lifestyle as foundational to heart health. In a 2013 BBC article, Dr. Malhotra said, "I mend hearts. Then I see my patients served junk food by our hospitals." This troubling trend persists worldwide, which explains why heart disease is still on the rise.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="9"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="lOvcW vdo_embedd"&gt;&lt;div class="k7lcu"&gt;&lt;p class="efT4r"&gt;Why are women more at risk for heart disease?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="11"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;He emphasizes that modern medicine has often overlooked the simple power of foods, exercise, stress management, and sleep. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While medications such as statins are widely prescribed, Dr. Malhotra notes their benefits are marginal compared to lifestyle changes, which can rapidly improve heart health and overall well-being.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="15"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="16"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;The 21-day heart health reset&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="18"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr. Malhotra's 21-day solution provides actionable, sustainable steps to reset your metabolism, reduce inflammation, and protect your arteries. The core principle is adopting a low-carbohydrate Mediterranean-style diet focused on whole, minimally processed foods: vegetables, nuts, seeds, virgin olive oil, and lean proteins.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="21"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;He advises avoiding sugar, refined carbohydrates, fruit juices, and ultra-processed foods for at least three weeks. This phase helps stabilize blood sugar, lower triglycerides, and improve insulin sensitivity—all key factors in reducing cardiovascular risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="23"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Motion and exercise&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="25"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="26"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Physical activity is another pillar of the reset. Dr. Malhotra recommends a daily brisk walk of 30 minutes. The goal is consistent movement, not extreme gym workouts. Regular walking improves blood flow, aids weight control, and enhances heart and lung function, forming a foundation for cardiovascular longevity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="30"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Meditation for reducing stress&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="32"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="33"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stress is a major contributor to heart disease, and meditation, especially Rajyoga meditation, plays a vital role. Studies suggest it may even reverse artery blockages by reducing inflammation and calming the nervous system. Spending time each day on mindful breathing limits stress hormones that damage blood vessels, helping prevent heart attacks and strokes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="36"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Sleep and quality recovery&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="38"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="39"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sleep is often underestimated but crucial for heart health. Dr. Malhotra recommends 7–8 hours of quality sleep each night. Proper rest regulates blood pressure and inflammation, aiding the repair and maintenance of the cardiovascular system.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="41"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="42"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Beyond diet and exercise: Building a healthy environment and habits&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="44"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;While personal responsibility is important, Dr. Malhotra stresses the need for an environment that supports healthy choices. Junk food marketing and the easy availability of processed meals often work against individuals. He advocates for systemic change alongside individual lifestyle shifts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="48"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;He also notes that approximately 67% of what many people consume daily falls into the highly processed category, which typically contains additives, preservatives, colorings, and flavor enhancers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="50"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thumb rule to check processed foods:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="52"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;If a product has more than five ingredients, it is likely ultra-processed and best avoided. Dr. Malhotra emphasizes that mounting scientific evidence links an ultra-processed diet to increased risk of diseases such as cancer, depression, and overall mortality.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="55"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="56"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Scientific evidence and impact&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr. Malhotra’s approach is grounded in research. Meta-analyses and clinical trials confirm that reducing carbohydrate intake, cutting sugar, and adopting a Mediterranean diet significantly lowers heart disease risk markers within weeks. Stress reduction techniques also have anti-inflammatory and cardiovascular benefits.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="58"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;He further notes that cholesterol alone is an incomplete marker of heart disease risk. Insulin resistance, triglycerides, inflammation, and lifestyle factors are stronger predictors—and all are modifiable through diet and lifestyle changes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="62"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="63"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Tips to get started today&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="65"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Eat real food: Fill your plate with vegetables, healthy fats such as olive oil and nuts, and moderate protein. Avoid sugary drinks, sweets, and processed snacks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="67"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Daily walk: Aim for a brisk 30-minute walk every day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="69"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Meditate: Spend 20–40 minutes a day practicing focused breathing or Rajyoga meditation to calm the mind and heart.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="72"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sleep well: Maintain a pattern that allows 7–8 hours of quality sleep each night.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="74"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr. Aseem Malhotra’s message is one of hope and empowerment: heart health is not about pills or procedures. It’s about embracing a lifestyle that allows your body to heal and function as it was designed to. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="76"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Times of India</author><pubDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2025 03:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihgJBVV95cUxObk9IWnBKbkNVQ05XMHdSQnV3NUN5c1ZoRm1oLWNrUmZ3cXRTTTZNa0tVd1RaX0N1Y3hiNVRFTF82WlZPRWN1dV84Qkw1QVRpb2FlWjM5MEJodHh2TTdIQVUxTW1wY1BXTXZWX2paNnBVM2NkdjB1dDdvUktZMTVVaTJZWW5nTjhGXzZ1cHc3UGctdTNpaU9NdGNYSVNEa1FFUnl2dlJtRDU3NTQ4Z3pGWC0wT3oyY0d4Y2hvSEQzRWtrWXdmaGZxaE9mZVJCakszUnVCcXRsdEtfN2RoZ2dGb0Fqcjh4Y3MwTElkV3E5QWUtSkVoazRhWmZFcTRqZjFKWkdmV1p3</guid></item><item><title>我是一名传染病医生。以下是当我在飞机上坐在怀疑接种疫苗的人旁边时发生的事情。- Yahoo News UK</title><link>https://uk.news.yahoo.com/im-infectious-disease-doctor-heres-023104848.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="" data-article-body="true"&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;It’s hard to believe that infectious diseases have become a political litmus test, but they are now very much part of the “with us or against us” mental sorting more and more people seem to be doing these days. And the topic seems to be everywhere. Do you think the U.S. should continue &lt;a href="https://www.thelancet.com/journals/lancet/article/PIIS0140-6736(25)01186-9/fulltext" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:funding aid programs for diseases such as AIDS, TB and malaria;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;funding aid programs for diseases such as AIDS, TB and malaria&lt;/a&gt;? Are you pleased or horrified about &lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2025/09/03/us/florida-vaccine-mandates.html" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Florida’s plans to undo school vaccine mandates;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Florida’s plans to undo school vaccine mandates&lt;/a&gt;? Do you seek out or steer clear of the annual flu vaccine?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;As someone who recently completed 15 years of post-college training to become an infectious diseases physician-scientist, I can’t avoid these conversations. I just wish I knew the magic words to reach people willing to jettison decades of evidence and research for something they read online.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;I am proud of my work and committed to my profession. Yet in a country polarized by everything from the &lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2025/09/16/us/politics/trump-kirk-free-speech-hate-speech-left.html" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:response to the abhorrent assassination of Charlie Kirk;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;response to the abhorrent assassination of Charlie Kirk&lt;/a&gt; to &lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2025/09/15/health/rfk-jr-hhs-vaccine-committee-members.html" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:RFK Jr.’s abrupt reconfiguration of the nation’s vaccine advisory committee;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;RFK Jr.’s abrupt reconfiguration of the nation’s vaccine advisory committee&lt;/a&gt;, I hesitated to share my occupation with the talkative young man I was recently seated next to on a flight.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;When the inevitable career question came up, he jumped right in. Despite the early hour and lack of sleep, with no viable exit option, I decided to face the challenge, though I braced for the worst.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Lyme disease was first on the list. We were flying out of Connecticut, after all.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“You’ve never heard that Lyme disease was created as a bioterrorism weapon?” I had not (because &lt;a href="https://www.jci.org/articles/view/21681" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:it wasn’t;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;it wasn’t&lt;/a&gt;). Somehow, in between the hours caring for patients, researching disease pathogenesis and staying up to date on the literature in my field, I had missed this infectious disease conspiracy du jour.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“It’s called Lyme because that’s where they released it.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;No. Old Lyme, Connecticut, is where epidemiologists realized that patients’ symptoms coincided with recent tick bites and then confirmed that local ticks carried the disease-causing bacteria.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“You can’t cure it; it was made to weaponize.” Actually, we have very &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/lyme/hcp/clinical-care/index.html" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:effective antibiotics;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;effective antibiotics&lt;/a&gt; to kill the bacteria (though some people can develop a &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/lyme/signs-symptoms/chronic-symptoms-and-lyme-disease.html" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:complex post-treatment Lyme disease syndrome;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;complex post-treatment Lyme disease syndrome&lt;/a&gt;). I’m not a military strategist, but I can’t imagine that indiscriminately infecting outdoor enthusiasts with a non-deadly, treatable disease that requires transmission via a slow-feeding arthropod would be an ideal bioterrorism plan.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“But why is it spreading so fast now?”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Climate change, expanding tick habitats and food sources, and a lack of winters that kill them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;He laughed. “So in your ‘profesh’ opinion, Lyme disease as a bioterrorism weapon is a bunch of horseshit?”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Yes. That I do agree with.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;We moved on to the next obvious infectious disease topic: COVID-19. I gave him space. He wasn’t sparring with a lack of respect, nor was I. We opened up about experiencing the pandemic in completely different ways. He described how hard it was being forced to get vaccinated, feeling coerced to keep his job but fearing the vaccine’s purported harms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;I shared my experience working in the hospital. I told him how I had witnessed numerous people die alone, and how the vaccine was a true savior. He believed it was only old people who had died. I told him I had seen enough young, healthy people become debilitated that I would never make that bet, not in that pandemic or the next one. In fact, by September 2023, &lt;a href="https://data.cdc.gov/National-Center-for-Health-Statistics/Provisional-COVID-19-Deaths-by-Sex-and-Age/9bhg-hcku/data_preview" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:more than 25,000 18-39-year-olds had died from COVID in the U.S.;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;more than 25,000 18-39-year-olds had died from COVID in the U.S.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;I tried to hear his concerns. I admitted that my passion for science and what I had experienced as a physician may have made me unfairly dismissive of people whose primary concerns were being stuck at home unable to pay rent or educate their children. I acknowledged that there’s always a small chance that some people might experience an adverse reaction to any medical intervention, be it a vaccine or over-the-counter drug, and I can understand why that makes some people hesitate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;But I also reiterated the rigor of the scientific process involved in developing treatments, reviewing safety data, and ultimately making clinical recommendations. I told him that mRNA vaccines are neither new — &lt;a href="https://www.niaid.nih.gov/diseases-conditions/decades-making-mrna-covid-19-vaccines" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:they’ve been in development for decades;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;they’ve been in development for decades&lt;/a&gt; — nor a government-led conspiracy to genetically manipulate the population. The reference to “genetic material” may lead to misconceptions, but mRNA does not enter the cell nucleus, where our DNA resides. Our cells do not even possess the molecular machinery capable of turning mRNA into DNA. That’s &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/covid/vaccines/how-they-work.html#:~:text=How%20mRNA%20COVID%2D19%20vaccines%20work" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:fact;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;fact&lt;/a&gt;, not just my “profesh” opinion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;It felt real, the effort to hear and speak to each other. And I learned things from him, too. In response to my insistence that his infection-related conspiracy theories were nothing but that, he admitted, “Yeah, you’re probably right.” Then he added, with a smile on his face, “But conspiracies are a lot more fun.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Conspiracies are a lot more fun&lt;/em&gt;. Maybe vaccine or disease origin conspiracies are fun — if you’re young and healthy, if you’re bored, if you’re motivated to access a community that promises you “inside information.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;But for the population as a whole, they are unbelievably dangerous. Conspiracy theories are why a &lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2025/03/10/health/measles-texas-kennedy-fox.html" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:measles outbreak took hold in the U.S. this year;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;measles outbreak took hold in the U.S. this year&lt;/a&gt;, why &lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2025/08/09/us/gunman-cdc-shooting-vaccines.html" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:CDC employees were targeted in a workplace shooting;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;CDC employees were targeted in a workplace shooting&lt;/a&gt;. They are why &lt;a href="https://www.science.org/content/article/fighting-ebola-hard-congo-fake-news-makes-it-harder" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Ebola outbreaks are hard to contain;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Ebola outbreaks are hard to contain&lt;/a&gt;, why &lt;a href="https://www.pbs.org/newshour/health/the-world-nearly-beat-polio-but-fake-records-misinformation-and-missteps-aided-its-comeback" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:polio vaccine workers are killed;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;polio vaccine workers are killed&lt;/a&gt; abroad.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;By the time our flight was over, our conversation had covered a wide geographic and political space. The experience left me with genuine hope that we could maintain trust in each other and reminded me that scientists and physicians cannot give up on having these conversations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“With COVID, vaccines, Lyme disease, any of it — I’m not your enemy,” I told my seatmate as we were getting ready to disembark. “And I know you’re not the enemy, either.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“True,” he agreed. “But they always want to make someone your enemy.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Exactly&lt;/em&gt;. That is what conspiracy theories require. That is why we have to talk to each other. See me as a person. And I will do the same.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;I am not your enemy. Neither is science.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Morgan Goheen, M.D., Ph.D., works at Yale School of Medicine as a research scientist and board-certified infectious diseases physician, and she is a Public Voices Fellow of The OpEd Project in Partnership with Yale University.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;em&gt;This article originally appeared on &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/entry/infectious-disease-doctor-anti-vaccine-airplane_n_68d2e961e4b03fb4d93463e7" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:HuffPost;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;HuffPost&lt;/a&gt; in October 2025.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Also in Goodful: &lt;a href="https://www.buzzfeed.com/carolinebologna/12-things-millennials-do-that-gen-z-hates?utm_source=yahoo-recirc-links" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk='slk:12 Things Millennials Do That Gen Z Says Give Them The Ultimate "Ick";elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas' class="link "&gt;12 Things Millennials Do That Gen Z Says Give Them The Ultimate "Ick"&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Also in Goodful: &lt;a href="https://www.buzzfeed.com/lizmrichardson/doctors-health-warning-signs-symptoms-shouldnt-ignore?utm_source=yahoo-recirc-links" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Doctors And Nurses Are Revealing The &amp;quot;Small&amp;quot; Health Signs You Should Never Ignore, And It's Shocking;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Doctors And Nurses Are Revealing The "Small" Health Signs You Should Never Ignore, And It's Shocking&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Also in Goodful: &lt;a href="https://www.buzzfeed.com/dannicaramirez/older-adults-are-sharing-the-difficult-truths-about-aging-fs?utm_source=yahoo-recirc-links" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk='slk:"Young People Would Be Surprised By This": 21 "Hard To Swallow" Truths About Getting Older That No One Talks About;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas' class="link "&gt;"Young People Would Be Surprised By This": 21 "Hard To Swallow" Truths About Getting Older That No One Talks About&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.buzzfeed.com/morgangoheen/infectious-disease-doctor-anti-vaccine-airplane?utm_source=yahoo-recirc-links" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Read it on BuzzFeed.com;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Read it on BuzzFeed.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Yahoo News UK</author><pubDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2025 02:31:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigAFBVV95cUxPQm5WdkdzT3k5ZGJXQmlXUmxvUGdfc0VBc1UyTXNWZl9SQzI2ZGRtUXhxUU54YmZsbnFtNTRqNDJKMHYyTWNBcGxvcGMyY3lyV2FRX2ZSVy1qN1lYWEFHbDJqUExBSnEzZ1VpenByaEJjcDNXRDBZSVVFNDNaWF9YNg</guid></item><item><title>我是一名传染病医生。以下是当我在飞机上坐在怀疑接种疫苗的人旁边时发生的事情。- Yahoo News Australia</title><link>https://au.news.yahoo.com/im-infectious-disease-doctor-heres-023104848.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="" data-article-body="true"&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;It’s hard to believe that infectious diseases have become a political litmus test, but they are now very much part of the “with us or against us” mental sorting more and more people seem to be doing these days. And the topic seems to be everywhere. Do you think the U.S. should continue &lt;a href="https://www.thelancet.com/journals/lancet/article/PIIS0140-6736(25)01186-9/fulltext" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:funding aid programs for diseases such as AIDS, TB and malaria;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;funding aid programs for diseases such as AIDS, TB and malaria&lt;/a&gt;? Are you pleased or horrified about &lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2025/09/03/us/florida-vaccine-mandates.html" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Florida’s plans to undo school vaccine mandates;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Florida’s plans to undo school vaccine mandates&lt;/a&gt;? Do you seek out or steer clear of the annual flu vaccine?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;As someone who recently completed 15 years of post-college training to become an infectious diseases physician-scientist, I can’t avoid these conversations. I just wish I knew the magic words to reach people willing to jettison decades of evidence and research for something they read online.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;I am proud of my work and committed to my profession. Yet in a country polarized by everything from the &lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2025/09/16/us/politics/trump-kirk-free-speech-hate-speech-left.html" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:response to the abhorrent assassination of Charlie Kirk;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;response to the abhorrent assassination of Charlie Kirk&lt;/a&gt; to &lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2025/09/15/health/rfk-jr-hhs-vaccine-committee-members.html" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:RFK Jr.’s abrupt reconfiguration of the nation’s vaccine advisory committee;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;RFK Jr.’s abrupt reconfiguration of the nation’s vaccine advisory committee&lt;/a&gt;, I hesitated to share my occupation with the talkative young man I was recently seated next to on a flight.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;When the inevitable career question came up, he jumped right in. Despite the early hour and lack of sleep, with no viable exit option, I decided to face the challenge, though I braced for the worst.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Lyme disease was first on the list. We were flying out of Connecticut, after all.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“You’ve never heard that Lyme disease was created as a bioterrorism weapon?” I had not (because &lt;a href="https://www.jci.org/articles/view/21681" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:it wasn’t;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;it wasn’t&lt;/a&gt;). Somehow, in between the hours caring for patients, researching disease pathogenesis and staying up to date on the literature in my field, I had missed this infectious disease conspiracy du jour.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“It’s called Lyme because that’s where they released it.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;No. Old Lyme, Connecticut, is where epidemiologists realized that patients’ symptoms coincided with recent tick bites and then confirmed that local ticks carried the disease-causing bacteria.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“You can’t cure it; it was made to weaponize.” Actually, we have very &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/lyme/hcp/clinical-care/index.html" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:effective antibiotics;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;effective antibiotics&lt;/a&gt; to kill the bacteria (though some people can develop a &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/lyme/signs-symptoms/chronic-symptoms-and-lyme-disease.html" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:complex post-treatment Lyme disease syndrome;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;complex post-treatment Lyme disease syndrome&lt;/a&gt;). I’m not a military strategist, but I can’t imagine that indiscriminately infecting outdoor enthusiasts with a non-deadly, treatable disease that requires transmission via a slow-feeding arthropod would be an ideal bioterrorism plan.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“But why is it spreading so fast now?”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Climate change, expanding tick habitats and food sources, and a lack of winters that kill them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;He laughed. “So in your ‘profesh’ opinion, Lyme disease as a bioterrorism weapon is a bunch of horseshit?”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Yes. That I do agree with.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;We moved on to the next obvious infectious disease topic: COVID-19. I gave him space. He wasn’t sparring with a lack of respect, nor was I. We opened up about experiencing the pandemic in completely different ways. He described how hard it was being forced to get vaccinated, feeling coerced to keep his job but fearing the vaccine’s purported harms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;I shared my experience working in the hospital. I told him how I had witnessed numerous people die alone, and how the vaccine was a true savior. He believed it was only old people who had died. I told him I had seen enough young, healthy people become debilitated that I would never make that bet, not in that pandemic or the next one. In fact, by September 2023, &lt;a href="https://data.cdc.gov/National-Center-for-Health-Statistics/Provisional-COVID-19-Deaths-by-Sex-and-Age/9bhg-hcku/data_preview" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:more than 25,000 18-39-year-olds had died from COVID in the U.S.;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;more than 25,000 18-39-year-olds had died from COVID in the U.S.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;I tried to hear his concerns. I admitted that my passion for science and what I had experienced as a physician may have made me unfairly dismissive of people whose primary concerns were being stuck at home unable to pay rent or educate their children. I acknowledged that there’s always a small chance that some people might experience an adverse reaction to any medical intervention, be it a vaccine or over-the-counter drug, and I can understand why that makes some people hesitate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;But I also reiterated the rigor of the scientific process involved in developing treatments, reviewing safety data, and ultimately making clinical recommendations. I told him that mRNA vaccines are neither new — &lt;a href="https://www.niaid.nih.gov/diseases-conditions/decades-making-mrna-covid-19-vaccines" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:they’ve been in development for decades;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;they’ve been in development for decades&lt;/a&gt; — nor a government-led conspiracy to genetically manipulate the population. The reference to “genetic material” may lead to misconceptions, but mRNA does not enter the cell nucleus, where our DNA resides. Our cells do not even possess the molecular machinery capable of turning mRNA into DNA. That’s &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/covid/vaccines/how-they-work.html#:~:text=How%20mRNA%20COVID%2D19%20vaccines%20work" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:fact;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;fact&lt;/a&gt;, not just my “profesh” opinion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;It felt real, the effort to hear and speak to each other. And I learned things from him, too. In response to my insistence that his infection-related conspiracy theories were nothing but that, he admitted, “Yeah, you’re probably right.” Then he added, with a smile on his face, “But conspiracies are a lot more fun.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Conspiracies are a lot more fun&lt;/em&gt;. Maybe vaccine or disease origin conspiracies are fun — if you’re young and healthy, if you’re bored, if you’re motivated to access a community that promises you “inside information.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;But for the population as a whole, they are unbelievably dangerous. Conspiracy theories are why a &lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2025/03/10/health/measles-texas-kennedy-fox.html" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:measles outbreak took hold in the U.S. this year;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;measles outbreak took hold in the U.S. this year&lt;/a&gt;, why &lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2025/08/09/us/gunman-cdc-shooting-vaccines.html" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:CDC employees were targeted in a workplace shooting;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;CDC employees were targeted in a workplace shooting&lt;/a&gt;. They are why &lt;a href="https://www.science.org/content/article/fighting-ebola-hard-congo-fake-news-makes-it-harder" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Ebola outbreaks are hard to contain;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Ebola outbreaks are hard to contain&lt;/a&gt;, why &lt;a href="https://www.pbs.org/newshour/health/the-world-nearly-beat-polio-but-fake-records-misinformation-and-missteps-aided-its-comeback" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:polio vaccine workers are killed;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;polio vaccine workers are killed&lt;/a&gt; abroad.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;By the time our flight was over, our conversation had covered a wide geographic and political space. The experience left me with genuine hope that we could maintain trust in each other and reminded me that scientists and physicians cannot give up on having these conversations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“With COVID, vaccines, Lyme disease, any of it — I’m not your enemy,” I told my seatmate as we were getting ready to disembark. “And I know you’re not the enemy, either.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“True,” he agreed. “But they always want to make someone your enemy.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Exactly&lt;/em&gt;. That is what conspiracy theories require. That is why we have to talk to each other. See me as a person. And I will do the same.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;I am not your enemy. Neither is science.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Morgan Goheen, M.D., Ph.D., works at Yale School of Medicine as a research scientist and board-certified infectious diseases physician, and she is a Public Voices Fellow of The OpEd Project in Partnership with Yale University.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;em&gt;This article originally appeared on &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/entry/infectious-disease-doctor-anti-vaccine-airplane_n_68d2e961e4b03fb4d93463e7" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:HuffPost;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;HuffPost&lt;/a&gt; in October 2025.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Also in Goodful: &lt;a href="https://www.buzzfeed.com/abbyzinman/gross-girl-hygiene-trivia-quiz?utm_source=yahoo-recirc-links" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:If You Don't Pass This Extremely Easy Hygiene Test, You're Officially Stinkier Than The Average Human;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;If You Don't Pass This Extremely Easy Hygiene Test, You're Officially Stinkier Than The Average Human&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Also in Goodful: &lt;a href="https://www.buzzfeed.com/lizmrichardson/doctors-bad-health-habits-mistakes?utm_source=yahoo-recirc-links" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:&amp;quot;It's Very Serious&amp;quot;: 15 &amp;quot;Bad&amp;quot; Health Habits You Probably Do Allll The Time (But Really Shouldn't), Straight From Doctors And Nurses;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;"It's Very Serious": 15 "Bad" Health Habits You Probably Do Allll The Time (But Really Shouldn't), Straight From Doctors And Nurses&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Also in Goodful: &lt;a href="https://www.buzzfeed.com/lizmrichardson/doctors-health-warning-signs-symptoms-shouldnt-ignore?utm_source=yahoo-recirc-links" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Doctors And Nurses Are Revealing The &amp;quot;Small&amp;quot; Health Signs You Should Never Ignore, And It's Shocking;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Doctors And Nurses Are Revealing The "Small" Health Signs You Should Never Ignore, And It's Shocking&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.buzzfeed.com/morgangoheen/infectious-disease-doctor-anti-vaccine-airplane?utm_source=yahoo-recirc-links" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Read it on BuzzFeed.com;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Read it on BuzzFeed.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Yahoo News Australia</author><pubDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2025 02:31:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigAFBVV95cUxNMC1xOXg2NmtHX2N2bjNtb3ZsMmI5V3J2WExMYUNpMUJWelBKdWdfenZBNWNpNjV0RXhUWWRVUldULWVkVThxUlN6azdWNkxRQzFKWEYxWHFrUlp3Wnk5aXA0b1NBbVFLQTNHdXctNDAzWk9ZQlhqbWVsam9KRnJGeg</guid></item><item><title>研究人员在发现可能增加ALS风险的被忽视因素后发出警告： “潜在相关” -雅虎</title><link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/articles/researchers-issue-warning-discovering-overlooked-010000764.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="" data-article-body="true"&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Research has revealed a link between the mining and burning of dirty fuels and the development of &lt;a href="https://www.mayoclinic.org/diseases-conditions/amyotrophic-lateral-sclerosis/symptoms-causes/syc-20354022" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:amyotrophic lateral sclerosis;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;amyotrophic lateral sclerosis&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="mb-4 text-lg font-bold"&gt;What's happening?&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;As &lt;a href="https://abcnews.go.com/Health/exposure-mining-fossil-fuel-linked-als-new-research/story?id=126254429&amp;amp;utm_source=instagram&amp;amp;utm_medium=social&amp;amp;utm_campaign=likeshopme&amp;amp;utm_content=www.instagram.com/p/DPtNC0kk0t7" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:ABC News;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;ABC News&lt;/a&gt; observed, the study, published in the journal &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0013935125014835?via%3Dihub" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Environmental Research;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Environmental Research&lt;/a&gt;, found that long-term exposure to sulfur dioxide — a pollutant released during the combustion of oil and gas and during mining activity — increases the risk of developing ALS.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;At an ALS clinic in New Brunswick, Canada, doctors noticed a spike in cases. In response, lead author Daniel Saucier launched a study comparing 304 individuals with the disease to 1,207 healthy individuals, all of the same age and sex. The research used records of environmental pollutants connected to the participants' areas of residence.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Saucier, who holds a master's degree in diagnostic methods for ALS, told ABC that "it looked like air pollution was potentially related to the increased cases of ALS in New Brunswick, with sulfur dioxide appearing to be the one that had a significant association of ALS."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The study found that people exposed to sulfur dioxide over long periods had a 23% higher risk of developing ALS.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;According to Saucier, while burning dirty fuels releases sulfur dioxide, so does "anything that has to do with mining activities."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;All study areas met Canada's &lt;a href="https://ccme.ca/en/air-quality-report" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:clean air guidelines;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;clean air guidelines&lt;/a&gt;, yet the research identified a significant health association between sulfur dioxide exposure and ALS risk. The authors concluded that preventive strategies will be needed to protect public health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="mb-4 text-lg font-bold"&gt;Why is air pollution concerning?&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Harmful pollutants such as sulfur dioxide are released during the extraction and use of coal, oil, and gas. While these fuels remain central to global energy production, their by-products pose serious risks to workers, communities, and the environment, especially in industrial zones.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Beyond sulfur dioxide, many other industrial carbon pollutants contribute to rising global temperatures. A warmer planet intensifies natural disasters, sea-level rise, and other health impacts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="mb-4 text-lg font-bold"&gt;What can be done about air pollution?&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;With new technologies emerging that reduce or eliminate the need to mine and burn dirty fuels, many workplace and public safety concerns can be avoided. For example, &lt;a href="https://guide.thecooldown.com/actions/install-solar-panels/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:solar panels;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;solar panels&lt;/a&gt; generate electricity without releasing harmful pollutants.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Additionally, rising health concerns from exposure to pollution drive a growing demand for cleaner energy. Advocating for solar, wind, hydro, and nuclear energy shows policymakers that the public truly cares about these issues.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Cleaner energy is also becoming increasingly popular and more affordable. A LUT University study concluded that a complete transition is &lt;a href="https://www.lut.fi/en/news/researchers-agree-world-can-reach-100-renewable-energy-system-2050" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:feasible;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;feasible&lt;/a&gt; and could occur before 2050.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;As the world relies more on renewable energy sources, health risks will decrease as heat-trapping pollutants are reduced.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Smaller steps, such as reducing your environmental footprint, are also a great place to start.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Switching from gas-guzzling cars to electric vehicles, turning off lights and appliances when not in use, and eating more plant-based meals are all helpful lifestyle changes that can reduce pollution and the demand for dirty fuels.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Join our &lt;a href="https://www.thecooldown.com/tech-newsletter/?rec0rX1mps1JFgqJm" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:free newsletter;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;free newsletter&lt;/a&gt; for weekly updates on the latest innovations &lt;strong&gt;improving our lives&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;shaping our future&lt;/strong&gt;, and don't miss &lt;a href="https://rb.gy/ivhzmj" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:this cool list;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;this cool list&lt;/a&gt; of easy ways to help yourself while helping the planet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Yahoo</author><pubDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2025 01:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMioAFBVV95cUxOUU54QnE4SC1GcmtIVlotX0lrUUZiUkhoMVZvT1ZWNFZpM0hoc0VYVndkUnFiR3l2Nnk2RHZGaXctUnhHXzNXcDNtUjgwVVQ2LXhGaXBBNkh6U1liX1dVVDdqWVp4OExrNTlBclM2OWgtMjNJRUtOc2NaMFZoT1AyOTBzZFVpN0tvUmhDUDRWNjZpMU9EVF9qYVJiak1lSFNx</guid></item><item><title>分子：在俄罗斯TikTok上疯传的危险减肥药物- BBC</title><link>https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/c201xe61x0lo</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article&gt;&lt;p data-component="headline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 hNbOGD"&gt;&lt;h1 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 idLnWK"&gt;Young Russians are being seduced by a cheap, dangerous weight-loss pill called Molecule&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="byline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="byline-new" class="sc-7bfdb3c2-0 fYJjWP"&gt;&lt;span data-testid="byline-new-contributors" class="sc-7bfdb3c2-11 ljQVMv"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="byline-new-contributors-contributor-0" class="sc-7bfdb3c2-5 xGeVU"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="sc-7bfdb3c2-7 djOqvY"&gt;Sofya Volyanova&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-testid="byline-new-contributors-contributor-0-role-location" class="sc-7bfdb3c2-8 gvcwmG"&gt;BBC News Russian &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 gtLOOD"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="hero-image" class="sc-5340b511-1 cMIbKV"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20251021-134202-667692b2c6-web-2.32.2-1/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 gUePlo hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/20b3/live/a281fad0-b3e7-11f0-a1d0-d5a6c9e4c42e.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/20b3/live/a281fad0-b3e7-11f0-a1d0-d5a6c9e4c42e.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/20b3/live/a281fad0-b3e7-11f0-a1d0-d5a6c9e4c42e.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/20b3/live/a281fad0-b3e7-11f0-a1d0-d5a6c9e4c42e.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/20b3/live/a281fad0-b3e7-11f0-a1d0-d5a6c9e4c42e.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/20b3/live/a281fad0-b3e7-11f0-a1d0-d5a6c9e4c42e.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/20b3/live/a281fad0-b3e7-11f0-a1d0-d5a6c9e4c42e.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/20b3/live/a281fad0-b3e7-11f0-a1d0-d5a6c9e4c42e.jpg.webp" loading="eager" alt="Maria 22-year-old Maria suffered serious side effects after trying the unlicensed weight loss drug promoted on TikTok" class="sc-5340b511-0 hLdNfA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 jVqbAn"&gt;Maria&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;22-year-old Maria suffered serious side effects after trying the unlicensed weight loss drug promoted on TikTok&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Molecule, a pill promising rapid weight loss, went viral on Russian TikTok earlier this year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Young people's feeds started filling up with captions like "Take Molecule and forget food exists", and "Do you want to sit in the back of the class in oversized clothes?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Clips showed fridges lined with blue boxes featuring holograms and "Molecule Plus" labels.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The orders began piling in, as teenagers shared their "weight-loss journeys" on social media.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;But there was a catch.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Maria, 22, had purchased the pill from a popular online retailer. She took two pills per day and, after two weeks, says her mouth dried up and she completely lost her appetite.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"I had absolutely no desire to eat, let alone drink. I was nervous. I was constantly biting my lips and chewing my cheeks."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Maria developed severe anxiety and began having negative thoughts. "These pills were having a profound effect on my psyche," she says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Maria, who lives in St Petersburg, says she wasn't prepared for such severe side effects.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Other TikTok users mentioned dilated pupils, tremors and insomnia. And at least three schoolchildren are reported to have ended up in hospital.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 gXrNRM"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 cMIbKV"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20251021-134202-667692b2c6-web-2.32.2-1/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 gUePlo hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/d2b6/live/989a97f0-b100-11f0-9c44-b9209ab0e9f0.png.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/d2b6/live/989a97f0-b100-11f0-9c44-b9209ab0e9f0.png.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/d2b6/live/989a97f0-b100-11f0-9c44-b9209ab0e9f0.png.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/d2b6/live/989a97f0-b100-11f0-9c44-b9209ab0e9f0.png.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/d2b6/live/989a97f0-b100-11f0-9c44-b9209ab0e9f0.png.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/d2b6/live/989a97f0-b100-11f0-9c44-b9209ab0e9f0.png.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/d2b6/live/989a97f0-b100-11f0-9c44-b9209ab0e9f0.png.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/d2b6/live/989a97f0-b100-11f0-9c44-b9209ab0e9f0.png.webp" loading="lazy" alt="TikTok Clips shared on TikTok show fridges lined with soft drinks and blue boxes of Molecule" class="sc-5340b511-0 hLdNfA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 jVqbAn"&gt;TikTok&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;Clips shared on TikTok show fridges lined with soft drinks and blue boxes of Molecule&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;In April, a schoolgirl in Chita, Siberia, needed hospital care after overdosing on Molecule. According to local reports, she was trying to lose weight quickly, in time for the summer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The mother of another schoolgirl told local media her daughter was admitted to intensive care after taking several pills at once.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;And in May, a 13-year-old boy from St Petersburg needed hospital care after experiencing hallucinations and panic attacks. He had reportedly asked a friend to buy him the pill because he was being teased at school about his weight.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 hNbOGD"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 gXmhTb"&gt;Substance banned in UK, EU and US&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The packaging for Molecule pills often lists "natural ingredients" such as dandelion root and fennel seed extract.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;But earlier this year, journalists at the Russian newspaper Izvestiya submitted pills they had purchased online for testing and found they contained a substance called sibutramine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 gXrNRM"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 cMIbKV"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20251021-134202-667692b2c6-web-2.32.2-1/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 gUePlo hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/6753/live/7fd5a6b0-b100-11f0-9c44-b9209ab0e9f0.png.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/6753/live/7fd5a6b0-b100-11f0-9c44-b9209ab0e9f0.png.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/6753/live/7fd5a6b0-b100-11f0-9c44-b9209ab0e9f0.png.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/6753/live/7fd5a6b0-b100-11f0-9c44-b9209ab0e9f0.png.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/6753/live/7fd5a6b0-b100-11f0-9c44-b9209ab0e9f0.png.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/6753/live/7fd5a6b0-b100-11f0-9c44-b9209ab0e9f0.png.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/6753/live/7fd5a6b0-b100-11f0-9c44-b9209ab0e9f0.png.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/6753/live/7fd5a6b0-b100-11f0-9c44-b9209ab0e9f0.png.webp" loading="lazy" alt="TikTok The pills contain substance called sibutramine, which is banned in many countries" class="sc-5340b511-0 hLdNfA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 jVqbAn"&gt;TikTok&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;The pills contain a substance called sibutramine, which is banned in many countries&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;First used as an antidepressant in the 1980s and later as an appetite suppressant, studies later found sibutramine increased the risk of heart attacks and strokes - while only slightly promoting weight loss.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;It was banned in the US in 2010, and is also &lt;a target="_self" href="http://news.bbc.co.uk/1/hi/health/8473555.stm" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;illegal in the UK&lt;/a&gt;, EU, China and other countries.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;In Russia, it is still used to treat obesity, but available only to adults and by prescription. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Purchasing and selling sibutramine without a prescription is a criminal offence. But that hasn't stopped individuals and small businesses from selling it online - often in higher doses than legal medication - and without requiring prescriptions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The unlicensed pills cost about £6-7 ($8-9) for a 20-day supply - much cheaper than recognised weight-loss injections like Ozempic, which on the Russian market sell for £40-160 ($50-210) per monthly pen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"Self-administration of this drug is very unsafe," says endocrinologist Ksenia Solovieva from St Petersburg, warning of potential overdose risks, "because we do not know how much of the active ingredient such 'dietary supplements' may contain".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 gXrNRM"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 cMIbKV"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20251021-134202-667692b2c6-web-2.32.2-1/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 gUePlo hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/6e9c/live/4ff1bdf0-b0fe-11f0-aa13-0b0479f6f42a.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/6e9c/live/4ff1bdf0-b0fe-11f0-aa13-0b0479f6f42a.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/6e9c/live/4ff1bdf0-b0fe-11f0-aa13-0b0479f6f42a.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/6e9c/live/4ff1bdf0-b0fe-11f0-aa13-0b0479f6f42a.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/6e9c/live/4ff1bdf0-b0fe-11f0-aa13-0b0479f6f42a.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/6e9c/live/4ff1bdf0-b0fe-11f0-aa13-0b0479f6f42a.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/6e9c/live/4ff1bdf0-b0fe-11f0-aa13-0b0479f6f42a.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/6e9c/live/4ff1bdf0-b0fe-11f0-aa13-0b0479f6f42a.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="TikTok Teenagers and young people showing unlicensed weight loss pills sold as dietary supplements from popular marketplaces on their TikTok accounts" class="sc-5340b511-0 hLdNfA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 jVqbAn"&gt;TikTok&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;Teenagers and young people order unlicensed weight loss pills sold as dietary supplements from popular marketplaces&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Russians regularly receive prison sentences for purchasing and reselling Molecule pills. But it's proving difficult for authorities to get a grip on the drug being sold illegally.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;In April, the government-backed Safe Internet League reported the growing trend involving young people to the authorities - prompting several major online marketplaces to remove Molecule from sale. But it soon began appearing online under a new name, Atom, in near-identical packaging.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;A law was recently passed allowing authorities to block websites selling "unregistered dietary supplements" without a court order - but sellers have been getting around this by categorising them as "sports nutrition" instead.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;On TikTok, you can find retailers selling Molecule under listings that look like they are for muesli, biscuits and even lightbulbs. And some retailers aren't even trying to hide it any more.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;A few weeks ago, the BBC found Molecule listings on a popular Russian online marketplace. When approached for comment, the site said it had promptly removed any products containing sibutramine. But it admitted it was difficult to find and remove listings that didn't explicitly mention sibutramine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;If you do manage to get your hands on Molecule, it's hard to know exactly what you're getting - and it's unclear where the pills are being manufactured.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The BBC found some sellers with production certificates from factories in Guangzhou and Henan, in China. Others claim to be sourcing the pills from Germany.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Some packets state they were produced in Remagen in Germany - but the BBC has discovered there is no such company listed at the address given.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Certain Kazakh vendors selling Molecule to Russians told the BBC they bought stock from friends or warehouses in the capital Astana but couldn't name the original supplier.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;ul class="sc-6f869981-0 diUlgm"&gt;&lt;li class="sc-734a601e-0 cRgahm"&gt;&lt;i id="details-of-support-with-eating-disorders-in-the-uk-are-available-at" class="sc-d16436d-0 iVdNuz"&gt;Details of support with eating disorders in the UK are available at &lt;/i&gt;&lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/articles/2DRkg4JC7SLT3B7hlrn6DKN/information-and-support-eating-disorders" class="sc-f9178328-0 kgTYQp"&gt;&lt;i id="bbc-action-line" class="sc-d16436d-0 iVdNuz"&gt;BBC Action Line&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;i id="" class="sc-d16436d-0 iVdNuz"&gt; &lt;/i&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Meanwhile, online eating-disorder communities have become spaces where Molecule is promoted, with users relying on hashtags and coded terms to slip past moderation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Ms Solovieva says Molecule is particularly harmful when taken by young people who already have eating disorders. For those in or near relapse, an easily available appetite suppressant can be seriously dangerous, she says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Anna Enina, a Russian influencer with millions of followers who herself has admitted using unlicensed weight-loss pills in the past, publicly warned her subscribers: "As someone who has struggled with an eating disorder... the consequences will be dire. You'll regret it tenfold."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;Maria from St Petersburg now discourages others from trying Molecule&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Twenty-two-year old Maria suffered bad side effects, and is one of those who regrets it. After taking too many Molecule pills, she was sent to hospital.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Now she discourages other young women and girls from taking the pills in weight-loss forums. She even reached out to one teenage user's parents to alert them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;But Molecule remains popular online.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;And every video that appears on Maria's TikTok feed is a reminder of the pills that made her sick.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BBC</author><pubDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2025 00:07:32 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiWkFVX3lxTE9HTnFadmdrU2NCVXZrTGR6YmFJeXlrYkJMQTEta2RjLXFES0R1UXczWkMzSnNCNmFEUkd0LWsyYm4xY3dGbmRDLXpyVFhsNHQxcGVWbVV5bE91QdIBX0FVX3lxTE1HNjYyYmtHbVFIRXlBSXkzUEFFaGdxaWVqNDRvVzdCRWtkS0p4NmdpX1gyQ21IU1gxcTdIdndhM2ZTRXM1Wm5tSnF5NzhNaklFaTFYbS1La1RDekVhTGVv</guid></item><item><title>牙医警告口干：了解其含义、症状和治疗方法-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/dentists-warn-about-dry-mouth-know-its-meaning-symptoms-and-treatment/articleshow/125023971.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;div class="MwN2O"&gt;&lt;div class="vdo_embedd"&gt; &lt;div class="T22zO"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you have been checking off on your hydration goals daily and yet feel constantly dry in the mouth, then you could likely have dry mouth. Also known as Xerostomia, this is an oral health condition that reduces saliva flow, leading to various symptoms including bad breath, rapid tooth decay and more. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="3"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="4"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;How common is Dry Mouth?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to dentists, the condition is more common than you think. Dry Mouth affects about one in five people, as per the &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://my.clevelandclinic.org/health/diseases/10902-dry-mouth-xerostomia" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="_blank" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;Cleveland Clinic&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;. However, Dr Kourosh Maddahi, a dentist at Dion Health in California shared with NBC Select, that the condition is underdiagnosed as people often mistake it with dehydration. And the longer it remains undiagnosed the more damage it creates for your oral health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="8"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="lOvcW vdo_embedd"&gt;&lt;div class="k7lcu"&gt;&lt;p class="efT4r"&gt;6 Home remedies to get rid of bad breath&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="10"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;A 2023 report by the &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.ada.org/resources/ada-library/oral-health-topics/xerostomia#:~:text=Severity%20of%20dry%20mouth%20symptoms,22%25%20of%20the%20global%20population." rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;American Dental Association&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; stated that dry mouth affects about 10 to 26 per cent of men and 10 to 33 per cent of women. Globally, about 22 per cent of the population is estimated to have xerostomia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="16"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;How would you know if you have dry mouth? Check for these symptoms and follow the treatments mentioned below!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="18"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="19"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Dry Mouth: What are the common symptoms?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="20"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.ada.org/resources/ada-library/oral-health-topics/xerostomia#:~:text=Severity%20of%20dry%20mouth%20symptoms,22%25%20of%20the%20global%20population." rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="_blank" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;American Dental Association&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; states that xerostomia can cause the following symptoms:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="24"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Burning feeling in the mouth&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="26"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Problems in chewing, swallowing, tasting or speaking&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="28"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Altered taste&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="30"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dry or sore throat&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="32"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mouth Sores&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="34"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bad breath&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="36"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cracked or peeling lips&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="38"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;If any of these symptoms persist for long, consulting a professional for diagnosis is advised.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="41"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="42"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Dry Mouth: What are the treatments?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The first step in the treatment is of course consulting with a dentist who can examine the severity of the condition and assess the decay. Most treatments for dry mouth consist of over-the-counter products such as mouthwashes, gels, chewing gums and lozenges. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="44"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, sometimes longer lifestyle changes such as avoiding certain food items and drinks are also required. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="46"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="47"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Understanding dry mouth or xerostomia&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="48"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;In simple words, dry mouth is a condition that makes the mouth feel dry due to an inadequate amount of saliva. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="51"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The most frequent causes of the condition are the use of certain medications. As per a 2018 study published in the &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/29071719/" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="_blank" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;Journal of the American Geriatrics Society&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, urologic medications, antidepressants and psycholeptics were associated with dry mouth in adults. Additionally, chemotherapy or head and neck cancer radiotherapy can also cause the condition as they directly cause toxicity to salivary glands and oral tissues. And, tobacco and cannabis use can also accelerate it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="56"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dry mouth can be damaging to oral health because of the changes it causes to the amount and consistency of saliva in the mouth. Saliva is a natural antibiotic in the mouth and protects it from bacteria, acts as a lubricant, and cleans plaque and other particles from teeth. It also remineralises tooth enamel as it is packed with calcium and phosphate, making the teeth resistant to decay. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="58"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;With a lack of saliva in the mouth, all the symptoms of dry mouth can amp up the progression of the condition and lead to more damage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="60"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Note:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; The information provided in this article is for educational purposes only and is not intended as medical advice. Always consult with a healthcare professional before starting any new medication or treatment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="63"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="65"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Times of India</author><pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 23:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi_gFBVV95cUxQNUN3cGgtSXQ0WDVldG1YQXJGMzNwOEs2eXdQcThWV1NQUmN3V0Z0YzBHaHI0cmpzMzZnYVE1UTJ6UV9zbW45X0g4SUN5aDBXc2toNXVya0tlazFQTjVFSkFHcmJ0RlR4LW8xZnJLTk8wZW1OTzhXbjNLeTRvNGk5T0QtMzNqdXZHM3o4eDNXazJwWVY2Wl96aXhNdGMtSUdXX2dwX2tZNWZJU1dhQnhYb3FoX1Z5T0Q1ZTdfdU1oQmM4RF9mTk9VTFBxTHVGOWhnZWlmS0J3NGtYZm52WXlTZ25xYk5Ja2V3UW96YmJpcThsWENhRTFESmZ4WVluQdIBgwJBVV95cUxNX0xsQVYycGUzYTlUSkY1NjM4Z1gtOEVSWGJSbkhWVk9zbnJWTm9QVzB3ckR2Z3FVWWQwVTVaSG5sSDd4NWU4ekJ6ZnllTmR0M29lbloyQVoySG80VGRLYXhZSU5rMVhRNVlGZWtzZWRRbER3dXh6cm1wS19SS0M0T25TUmNWRTdnVUVPZ1hJaUlYVmdjeFBMdll5R2hLNXk5WFF2Q1RxMjZMWmFqb2hLd1VyTFhkemZaYWNVYjRXa1hlcHV2TkNlM3B2d1lDdm92YV96S1FCbkl0R3piR0NtMnlXNEpqM1F0c0xucC1KQ3BDSVNVUkh5a25Kb2RnWFBaZkNF</guid></item><item><title>科学家发现大麻使用与表观遗传变化有关-雅虎</title><link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/articles/cannabis-linked-epigenetic-changes-scientists-215447890.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="" data-article-body="true"&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Cannabis use may leave lasting fingerprints on the human body, a study of over 1,000 adults published in 2023 suggests – not in our DNA code itself, but in how that code is expressed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;US researchers found it may cause changes in the &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/epigenetic-changes" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:epigenome;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;epigenome&lt;/a&gt;, which acts like a set of switches that activate or deactivate genes involved in how our bodies function; findings that were validated by a systematic literature review &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.drugalcdep.2024.111401" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:published in 2024;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;published in 2024&lt;/a&gt; by researchers in Portugal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;"We observed associations between cumulative marijuana use and multiple epigenetic markers across time," epidemiologist Lifang Hou from Northwestern University &lt;a href="https://news.feinberg.northwestern.edu/2023/07/18/marijuana-use-linked-to-epigenetic-changes/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:explained;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;explained&lt;/a&gt; of his team's findings in 2023.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/cannabis-can-leave-a-distinct-mark-on-your-dna-study-reveals?utm_source=SA_article&amp;amp;utm_campaign=related_link" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Cannabis Can Leave a Distinct Mark on Your DNA, Study Reveals;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Cannabis Can Leave a Distinct Mark on Your DNA, Study Reveals&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cannabis_(drug)" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Cannabis;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Cannabis&lt;/a&gt; is a &lt;a href="https://www.yahoo.com/news/cannabis-rising-across-us-except-025456334.html" data-ylk="slk:commonly used substance in the US;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas;outcm:mb_qualified_link;_E:mb_qualified_link;ct:story;" class="link  yahoo-link"&gt;commonly used substance in the US&lt;/a&gt;, with nearly half of Americans having tried it at least once, Hou and team report in their &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1038/s41380-023-02106-y" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:published paper;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;published paper&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Some US states and &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/australia-s-capital-just-legalised-recreational-marijuana-in-defiance-of-federal-laws" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:other countries;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;other countries&lt;/a&gt; have made cannabis use legal, but we still &lt;a href="https://www.yahoo.com/news/discovery-helps-explain-cannabis-triggers-220057665.html" data-ylk="slk:don't fully understand;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas;outcm:mb_qualified_link;_E:mb_qualified_link;ct:story;" class="link  yahoo-link"&gt;don't fully understand&lt;/a&gt; its &lt;a href="https://www.yahoo.com/news/male-cannabis-users-seem-show-090056205.html" data-ylk="slk:effects on our health;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas;outcm:mb_qualified_link;_E:mb_qualified_link;ct:story;" class="link  yahoo-link"&gt;effects on our health&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;To investigate this, the researchers analyzed data from a long-running health study that had tracked around 1,000 adults over two decades.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Participants, who were between 18 and 30 years old when the study began, were surveyed about their cannabis use over the years and gave blood samples at the 15- and 20-year marks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Using these blood samples from five years apart, Hou and her team looked at the &lt;a class="link " href="https://www.sciencealert.com/epigenetic-changes" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:epigenetic changes;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas"&gt;epigenetic changes&lt;/a&gt;, specifically &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/DNA_methylation" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:DNA methylation;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;DNA methylation&lt;/a&gt; levels, of people who had used cannabis recently or for a long time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The addition or removal of &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Methyl_group" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:methyl groups;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;methyl groups&lt;/a&gt; from DNA is one of the most studied epigenetic modifications.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="relative mb-4"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="relative text-sm mt-1 pr-2.5"&gt;&lt;p&gt;When epigenetic factors, which can come from other genes or the environment inside a cell or beyond, recruit a methyl group, it changes the expression of our genes. (ttsz/iStock/Getty Images)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Without changing the genomic sequence, DNA methylation affects how easily cells 'read' and interpret genes, much like someone covering up key lines in your set of instructions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Environmental and lifestyle factors can trigger these methylation changes, which can be &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/heres-how-events-in-your-grandparents-lives-could-affect-your-genes" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:passed to future generations;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;passed to future generations&lt;/a&gt;, and blood &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Biomarker" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:biomarkers;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;biomarkers&lt;/a&gt; can provide information about both recent and historical exposures.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;"We previously identified associations between marijuana use and the aging process as captured through DNA methylation," Hou &lt;a href="https://news.feinberg.northwestern.edu/2023/07/18/marijuana-use-linked-to-epigenetic-changes/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:said;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;said&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;"We wanted to further explore whether specific epigenetic factors were associated with marijuana and whether these factors are related to health outcomes."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="relative mb-4"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="relative text-sm mt-1 pr-2.5"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Environmental and lifestyle factors can trigger methylation changes, which can be passed to future generations. (&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.canva.com/photos/MADYNemcmnI/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Monkey Business Images/Canva;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Monkey Business Images/Canva&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The comprehensive data on the participants' cannabis use allowed the researchers to estimate cumulative use over time as well as recent use and compare it with DNA methylation markers in their blood for analysis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;They found numerous DNA methylation markers in the 15-year blood samples, 22 that were associated with recent use, and 31 associated with cumulative cannabis use.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;In the samples taken at the 20-year point, they identified 132 markers linked to recent use and 16 linked to cumulative use.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="relative mb-4"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="relative text-sm mt-1 pr-2.5"&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;"Interestingly, we consistently identified one marker that has previously been associated with tobacco use," Hou &lt;a href="https://news.feinberg.northwestern.edu/2023/07/18/marijuana-use-linked-to-epigenetic-changes/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:explained;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;explained&lt;/a&gt;, "suggesting a potential shared epigenetic regulation between tobacco and marijuana use."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Multiple epigenetic changes associated with cannabis use had previously been linked to things like &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cell_proliferation" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:cellular proliferation;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;cellular proliferation&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.mycancergenome.org/content/pathways/hormone-signaling/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:hormone signaling;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;hormone signaling&lt;/a&gt;, infections, neurological disorders like &lt;a class="link " href="https://www.sciencealert.com/schizophrenia" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:schizophrenia;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas"&gt;schizophrenia&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.mayoclinic.org/diseases-conditions/bipolar-disorder/symptoms-causes/syc-20355955" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:bipolar disorder;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;bipolar disorder&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Substance_use_disorder" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:substance use disorders;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;substance use disorders&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;It's important to note that this study doesn't prove that cannabis directly causes these changes or causes health problems.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="relative mb-4"&gt;&lt;a data-ylk="ct:story;elm:img;itc:0;" class="stretched-box" href="https://www.sciencealert.com/spark-into-space-comp" rel="noopener noreferrer nofollow" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;figcaption class="relative text-sm mt-1 pr-2.5"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Win a $10,000 Space Coast Adventure Holiday&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;"This research has provided novel insights into the association between marijuana use and epigenetic factors," &lt;a href="https://news.feinberg.northwestern.edu/2023/07/18/marijuana-use-linked-to-epigenetic-changes/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:said;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;said &lt;/a&gt;epidemiologist Drew Nannini from Northwestern University.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;"Additional studies are needed to determine whether these associations are consistently observed in different populations. Moreover, studies examining the effect of marijuana on age-related health outcomes may provide further insight into the long-term effect of marijuana on health."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The study has been published in &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1038/s41380-023-02106-y" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Molecular Psychiatry;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;&lt;em&gt;Molecular Psychiatry&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;em&gt;An earlier version of this article was published in July 2023.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="mb-4 text-lg font-bold"&gt;Related News&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Yahoo</author><pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 21:54:47 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMinAFBVV95cUxObFJpVTdBbUJidTZEeDhSWG1CNktUT3RMX1JIYmU0dTN6UHRPeVNxckQyX3dEX0pLeHFGWFFGQ0tWMGI3NzMwSnI4M0V6Z2xoWTBqalVONmpCWlltak5XVHI0UWJRSTQtUlRIMnVFRmFrOXRSV3QzZy1SdHBlYU9mcWF2SWZYcWdTLWctOEdVREM5MWU2ODA2ZFhiVzY</guid></item><item><title>与孤独和死亡焦虑相关的社交媒体使用问题- PsyPost</title><link>https://www.psypost.org/problematic-social-media-use-linked-to-loneliness-and-death-anxiety/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="content-inner "&gt;&lt;p&gt;A study of adult social media users in Italy suggested that loneliness and death anxiety might mediate the relationship between attachment anxiety and problematic social media use. The paper was published in &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1080/07481187.2025.2547244"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Death Studies&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Attachment anxiety is a form of insecure attachment characterized by fear of rejection and excessive need for closeness in relationships. People with attachment anxiety constantly worry that their partner does not love them enough or will eventually leave them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This persistent fear can lead to clingy or overly dependent behaviors as they seek reassurance. Even minor signs of distance or withdrawal from a partner can trigger intense distress or jealousy. Such individuals tend to be highly sensitive to changes in tone, attention, or affection. Their self-esteem is often highly dependent on how they are treated by significant others.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Attachment theory proposes that this form of anxiety develops from inconsistent caregiving during childhood, where affection and attention were unpredictable. In adulthood, it can make relationships emotionally exhausting and unstable.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Study author Alessandro Musetti and his colleagues hypothesized that attachment anxiety contributes to problematic social media use through a chain of psychological factors. They proposed that this relationship is mediated first by loneliness and then by death anxiety. Citing Terror Management Theory, they noted that individuals often cope with existential anxiety by seeking “symbolic immortality”—a sense of being part of something larger that will outlast them. The authors suggest that individuals with attachment anxiety may turn to social media to build a lasting digital presence as a way of achieving this symbolic immortality.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study included 799 Italian adults (52% women) with an average age of 32. Regarding education, 54% had finished high school and 16% had a bachelor’s degree. In terms of employment, 31% were employed full-time, while 27% were students.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They completed a survey containing assessments of attachment anxiety (the Relationship Questionnaire), loneliness (the UCLA–Loneliness Scale), death anxiety (the Death Anxiety Scale), and problematic social media use (the Bergen Social Media Addiction Scale). Problematic social media use is a pattern of excessive or compulsive engagement with social media that interferes with daily functioning, relationships, or mental well-being.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Results showed that attachment anxiety was positively correlated with the other measured traits. Individuals with higher attachment anxiety also tended to report greater loneliness, stronger death anxiety, and more symptoms of problematic social media use.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers’ statistical model revealed a nuanced set of relationships. First, it showed that two forms of loneliness—isolation (lacking a social network) and relational disconnectedness (lacking intimate relationships)—each helped explain the link between attachment anxiety and problematic social media use. More specifically, the model supported a sequential pathway: attachment anxiety was linked to higher relational disconnectedness, which in turn was linked to greater death anxiety, which finally was associated with problematic social media use. This specific chain of events was not found for the other types of loneliness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“These findings underscore the significance underlying psychological processes in PSMU [problematic social media use], suggesting potential avenues for targeted interventions that address attachment-related insecurities, relational disconnectedness, and existential concerns,” the study authors concluded.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study contributes to the scientific understanding of the consequences of attachment anxiety. However, it should be noted that the design of the study does not allow any definitive causal inferences to be derived from the results. The statistical model tested and supported by data only shows that the state of relationships it proposes is possible, not that it is definitely true.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The paper, “&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1080/07481187.2025.2547244"&gt;Attachment anxiety, loneliness, and death anxiety in problematic social media use,&lt;/a&gt;” was authored by Alessandro Musetti, Alessandro Alberto Rossi, Mattia Pezzi, Stefania Mannarini, Vittorio Lenzo, and Adriano Schimmenti.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>PsyPost</author><pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 20:07:04 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilwFBVV95cUxQOG9oM3ZBQjhHYjFzVGwxSEJua3h0X3Q1bUljaGo4dks2Q0l4SU5Jc3I2VlRtNWF0RUpqOHVHejdvSEJkeXA2emdHS0w1LTNpa2RtT2pFc3N2Zk00UEsybG5VOW1zWE81VkVvUVVFQ2E4WUlFN1NxYU9icXJLV1R0RGlCUElWclpDVWhpakVPbnZaeXNtWUsw</guid></item><item><title>医院外科医生成为精神病学的受害者-美国疯狂</title><link>https://www.madinamerica.com/2025/11/a-hospital-surgeon-falls-victim-to-psychiatry/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="td-post-content tagdiv-type"&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="dropcap dropcap2"&gt;I&lt;/span&gt;n 2010, I had been a consultant obstetrician and gynaecologist for 22 years in Bristol, the 8th largest city in England. I had been the chairman of the medical committee in the hospital, the largest hospital ’trust’ in the Southwest (one of the loveliest areas in England). My wife and I had recently celebrated our 30th wedding anniversary. We had two children doing well at school and captaining their sports teams. I had worked extremely hard to get to this prestigious position, 120 hours per week at work in my junior hospital doctor days.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Then my world started to collapse. Many bad life events over three years culminating in understandable distress and an appointment with a psychiatrist.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" class="aligncenter wp-image-266500" src="https://www.madinamerica.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/shutterstock_2697259849-1024x672.jpg" alt="" srcset="https://www.madinamerica.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/shutterstock_2697259849-1024x672.jpg 1024w, https://www.madinamerica.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/shutterstock_2697259849-300x197.jpg 300w, https://www.madinamerica.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/shutterstock_2697259849-150x99.jpg 150w, https://www.madinamerica.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/shutterstock_2697259849-768x504.jpg 768w, https://www.madinamerica.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/shutterstock_2697259849-1536x1009.jpg 1536w, https://www.madinamerica.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/shutterstock_2697259849-696x457.jpg 696w, https://www.madinamerica.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/shutterstock_2697259849-1392x914.jpg 1392w, https://www.madinamerica.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/shutterstock_2697259849-1068x701.jpg 1068w, https://www.madinamerica.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/shutterstock_2697259849-741x486.jpg 741w, https://www.madinamerica.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/shutterstock_2697259849-500x328.jpg 500w, https://www.madinamerica.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/shutterstock_2697259849.jpg 2010w" sizes="(max-width: 609px) 100vw, 609px"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In 2008, I had been on holiday in New York when I received a call from a local GP asking me if I could see a woman with intermittent bleeding months after a second elective caesarean section. She had a condition called an isthmocoele, a gap between the two scars from the caesareans. She eventually asked for a hysterectomy as the only definitive solution to stop the bleeding. This was unusual for a young woman of 26 but she demanded it. We went ahead, and all went well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Years later she had some bowel complaints and was referred to the colorectal surgeons. She saw a Dr Dixon. He told her she had a degree of rectal prolapse, which was very unlikely in a young woman with no previous vaginal deliveries. He recommended a new operation called a LVMR, using polypropylene mesh inserted laparoscopically. He carried this out, but ran into operative difficulties with surgically induced bleeding. She had to return to the operating theatre and ended up with a bowel resection and a colostomy. She sought to sue him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He tried to blame his problems on my simple hysterectomy years earlier. All complete fabrication and nonsense. He manufactured a medicolegal case against me, using well-known biased experts for the prosecution.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This all happened suddenly, and if his claims were proven, I faced a threat to my practice and previously unblemished reputation. I had never been sued before. I knew I had done nothing wrong and advised the hospital to get expert reports from two top colorectal surgeons and gynaecologists. When investigated, Dr Dixon was found to be responsible for all of the young woman’s surgical disasters, and was subsequently dismissed by both the NHS trust and the private hospitals. He was eventually found responsible for 460 cases of surgical negligence and was finally struck off the medical register. He also had falsified medical follow-up records in an attempt to embellish the results of his procedures.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All this caused me enormous distress, and I had to take extended leave to help prove the case against him. I had previously considered medicine to be a noble, empathetic profession without such deceitful individuals. This whole process had a profound effect on me. I had never been in such a situation before and it shocked me to the core.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I was really low during this time and eventually decided after some months to take early retirement, as my faith in medicine was shaken and waning. I wondered if I could possibly have a psychiatric breakdown and saw the head of the psychiatric trust for a consultation. He assured me I was just low because of all that was happening to me, and did not have any psychiatric disorder. That year my wife lost her father, and her mother had to be admitted to a dementia home as he had been her carer. My wife had a medical scare too, and stopped her hormone replacement therapy abruptly so she was not feeling great either, entering into an abrupt menopause. Everything was getting so bad over such a short time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Even though I had been reassured about my psychiatric normality, a ‘friend’ suggested I see another psychiatrist who, although retired, had looked after ‘troubled doctors’ before. A little reluctantly, I did see this second psychiatrist. It was an awful mistake. He came to my house and after just half an hour pronounced that I had ‘agitated depression’. He recommended that I start paroxetine straight away. No discussion of other solutions. The only answer was drugs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From then on, I was snared into a world of psychiatry that I had no knowledge of. I was then given mirtazapine, and over the course of a few weeks, other antidepressants and then antipsychotics too. My family were told, mainly by occupational therapists, that I had various forms of psychiatric problems and was very unwell. Although my son was an orthopaedic surgeon, like me he had no experience of psychiatry so he could not challenge the psychiatric management.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I was now drugged and beside myself with confusion and anger about the way I was being treated. It was all alien to me, and most discourteous. The psychiatrists seemed to enjoy the role reversal with a previously highly successful surgeon as a patient. Psychiatrists hate successful conventional doctors, especially surgeons who make so much indisputable difference. They were particularly aggressive with me because of my position. The increase and changes of drugs were awful. I was soon seen at home for a MHA assessment and I was fine, so was not committed. However, they said instead that I had to see the ECT psychiatrist, to discuss ECT treatment. I did not know anything about it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When I saw Hewitt, who was in charge of the ECT service, he encouraged me to have it. This was early on in my ‘treatment’. Hearing more about it, I was sure it had no scientific value, so I refused it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My wife was very upset on many grounds, and was convinced by the psychiatric picture being painted. She was annoyed with me for not believing all they were saying, but I knew that my distress and sadness were due to all that was happening in my life, and were not a disease. My wife, however, was frantic and threatening to leave me, and my son was saddened that his dad was not able to help him in their shared profession. He was in the process of applying for consultant posts. It was all a terrible dream. All due to unnecessary drugs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Community care was continued, with forced medication. One day my wife became very angry and we fell out badly. She threatened to leave me again. I had always been her anchor and the head of the family. Eventually it was decided that I needed inpatient care and I was admitted. No formal MHA assessment was made prior to admission which made it illegal. In hospital, I was on a mixed ward and started on a number of new drugs including lithium. No diagnoses were made but all sorts of drugs were added. I was discharged after a few weeks, on a collection of drugs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Because I was not improving on the medication, I was seen privately by a psychopharmacologist from Bristol University who decided I needed to try old-fashioned antidepressants and prescribed a MAOI and a tricyclic, together with a strong benzodiazepine, clonazepam. The latter made me sleep for eight hours during the day after one dose, so I stopped it. No alterations to my diet were made which I knew were necessary in view of the MAOI.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After attending my son’s wedding in a daze, I was feeling awful on the new collection of drugs and I was snatched from my home to be admitted to a psychiatric ward in my own hospital trust. Once again, no formal MHA assessment was made. I was just ‘put away’.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This ward was close to the obstetric wards where I had worked for 22 years. My medication was changed again to olanzapine at a maximum dose of 20 mg, and a high dose of escitalopram. The consultant spent no time discussing my problems, just talking about the DSM categories. Soon after my admission I had serious flank pain which I knew was renal colic, having had an endoscopic stone removal years before. The ward staff didn’t believe me and offered additional diazepam as treatment. I asked for some diclofenac (voltarol) suppositories and gloves to self-medicate. Sadly, I developed a fever and then my temperature fell to 35 degrees celsius with threatened sepsis. The mental health nurse who took my temperature asked for advice, and I was offered paracetamol (acetaminophen).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the end, I had to call the urology registrar on call for proper help. I was seen, given antibiotics and an MRI. A large stone was diagnosed, and I had to have an urgent endoscopic lithotripsy. Without my actions I could have had full-blown sepsis. No wonder the death rate in psychiatric hospitals is alarmingly high.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The psychiatrist then said I should have twice-weekly ECT. He did not discuss the benefits and drawbacks of ECT. A single sheet of information about ECT was left on my bed in the evening. No discussion at all. The sheet said it was a successful treatment but did not specify what for. The only side effects listed were a possible mild headache. That’s all.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I refused the ECT. I was informed that a second psychiatrist would come to see me as a second opinion. A SOAD, as it turned out: Second Opinion Approved Doctor. He agreed with my considered opinion of ECT and my reasons for refusing it. Despite this, however, I was told later that I was going to have it anyway.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the UK, ECT is the only coercive procedure that can be forced upon an individual without fully informed consent.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I was subsequently driven in a blacked-out car to the ECT unit on the other side of the city at 9 am. On the first day of treatment, I was starved from 5 pm the day before. On arrival I waited my turn to take a very brief test of instant recall before the shock. Memory tests to assess the effect of ECT must be performed after the seizure, not before and should test memory of past events, not instant recall. After the first ‘treatment’ I awoke confused, as all epileptics do after a fit. There is little difference except that the initiating electric shock was at a much higher voltage.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Further sessions of ECT followed, with worsening memory, for fifteen weeks. The side effects got worse. After the 30th I was losing my memory for all past events. I had complained regularly at the clinic but they planned to continue. To finally stop this, I made sure that I ate on the ECT mornings so that I was not allowed to have an anaesthetic. They stopped the ECT.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I attended a tribunal. The chairman seemed amused, saying that he had never seen a surgeon at an NHS tribunal before.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I won the tribunal and was released.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I spent time at home but was not able to do much with all the memory loss. I was visited at home by the crisis team who watched me take a new antipsychotic and another pill each day. I don’t know what they were and was not informed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;During the pandemic and lockdown my wife delivered food and drink every few days. I was alone. My daughter got married whilst I was having ECT and I missed her wedding, my speech and everything she and I had dreamed of. She has supported me with phone calls, but was told that I was to blame for not having more ‘treatments’. She is a paediatric physiotherapist now. My deterioration caused her great sadness. I have four grandchildren now but don’t know them, really.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We had been a very loving, close and successful family. Summer holidays at my wife’s parents’ place in Mallorca where they lived, and skiing every winter across the Alps. The children and my wife became black run skiers. Great times. All magical. I had worked very long and hard to afford it all. NHS and private clinics. My wife gave up nursing to be a homemaking, all-attentive mother. A 1950’s type wife and mother. She was great for them, but lost out on a career and a life of her own. A mistake, in retrospect. I had to work evenings privately to make up for the lost second income.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I was not coping well at home with virtually no memory. After a time, I was so drugged up and confused that I was sectioned again and admitted to a small hospital in a small seaside town called Weston-super-Mare. It was like a scene from &lt;i&gt;One Flew Over the Cuckoo’s Nest&lt;/i&gt; and I was Jack Nicholson. I spoke to and helped my fellow inmates and encouraged the staff to introduce scrambled egg for breakfast as an alternative to the ubiquitous cereal and toast.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The consultant was an Indian locum (a temporary healthcare professional) who didn’t really understand English. He relied on his junior trainee. I explained to her that I was not psychiatrically ill but just drugged to the hilt. She began to believe me and I stopped taking psychiatric drugs. The consultant tried to reintroduce them but I refused them successfully. The consultant wanted to investigate me with a CT and genetic blood tests, all of which I had already had years before. Using my better knowledge of medicine I was able to disprove his explanations for the need for further investigations. I realised he was not very well informed and his junior was the more sensible doctor. After three weeks, they had to interview me again with a view to moving me onto a treatment section of the Mental Health Act, so they could enforce medication again.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I had previously had a small heart attack during my enforced treatment at home and was admitted to the cardiac assessment unit. The investigations seemed to me to confirm a MCI with raised troponin levels. I should have had an urgent angiogram as there were changes on my ECG as well. It was then revealed in the hospital computer notes that I had a ‘psychiatric history’ and had been on numerous medications. Because of this, my whole case and presentation were questioned and I was just given analgesics and observed overnight, waiting for a consultant review in the morning.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The chest pain increased and more morphine was needed to alleviate it. At the morning ward round, my serum troponin was elevated further and ECG abnormalities were obvious. The cardiac consultant who reviewed me at 8 am was annoyed and angry that I had been overlooked because of a psychiatric history. He agreed with my assessment that I indeed had suffered a heart attack and gave me more analgesics, ordering an angiogram ASAP. I had the angiogram and a stent at 2 pm the next day, missing the agreed ‘presentation to stent target’ by many hours. I had a cardiac MRI later that week and was put on the usual cardiac prophylaxis drugs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cardiac events are more common in patients treated with antipsychotics. Especially olanzapine.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Back to Weston-super-Mare. I was called to face an MHA assessment to decide if I was to move to a level 2 section with enforced medication, etc. This assessment was a shambles but concluded that I should move to a level 2 section. I knew my rights and called for a proper tribunal. For this the consultant had to provide a report and treatment plan. In addition, reports from a community mental health nurse and an inpatient psychiatric nurse were required. I was to read these pre-tribunal. Neither nurse had met me before!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On the day of the tribunal it was postponed as the medical report was inadequately prepared. At a subequent tribunal I was informed that the consultant was ‘away’ and a substitute was requested, who I had never met before. At the tribunal I was able to argue successfully against my collection of diagnoses and the plan for treatment, and the tribunal was dismissed. I was allowed to leave the hospital. I later found out that the Indian locum had been investigated by the General Medical Council and had ‘left the hospital’.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I spent another year at home again with community visits to provide medication. Sadly, at home on drugs I deteriorated again and was admitted back to the Callington Road Main ‘Mental Health’ hospital. Here I was treated worse than ever. I was under the ECT consultant again. When at home I had previously stated that I never wanted ECT ever again. An Advance Statement to this effect banned him from giving me ECT again unless I lost ‘capacity’ and needed it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fortunately, he did not enforce ECT again. Instead, he made my time as awful as possible with cold showers and having me hoisted in and out of bed with straps, which has had residual effects on my musculoskeletal system. I eventually had to use a wheelchair. He then transferred me to a men-only ward filled with very disturbed men. Likely criminals avoiding prison by claiming a mental health defence. Here I was given weekly depot antipsychotic injections at twice the normal dose. These made me feel worse than ever. I was returned to the Hewitt-led Aspen ward, next door to the ECT unit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hewitt needed to get me off his hands. He then decided to state that I did not have a psychiatric disorder after all, but was suffering from a less common form of dementia instead (Fronto Temporal Dementia). He therefore told my family to move me into a residential home out of NHS care. Thus no clinical or financial responsibility for him or the mental health trust. I was moved by my family to a home nearer to the family homes. He also put a Deprivation of Liberty (DOL) order on me so that I was effectively still ‘imprisoned’.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have now had a cognitive function test and passed with a 90% score. I have asked a social worker to apply for a lifting of my DOL restriction. No progress there yet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now off all medications for 18 months I have regained my cognitive capacity again, except for the severe memory loss due to the multiple ECTs. I also still have the mobility problems due to a lack of exercise, muscle wasting and the hoisting effects from Callington Road Hospital physical abuse. I am still trying to get my family to listen to all the truth about psychiatry here in Bristol.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="td_block_template_1 awac-wrapper"&gt;&lt;div class="td_block_template_1 awac widget text-9"&gt;			&lt;div class="textwidget"&gt;&lt;p&gt;***&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Mad in America hosts blogs by a diverse group of writers. These posts are designed to serve as a public forum for a discussion—broadly speaking—of psychiatry and its treatments. The opinions expressed are the writers’ own.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;        &lt;/div&gt;


        &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Mad In America</author><pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 19:38:13 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiwFBVV95cUxPTGhVd21Nc3NiTVJHQ21FVS1zQVFPWGRuQnE5X0dVSlZWOFRsLXJwclp3bHBhZlJrYUNqaS0tMmlWYm9NNXBMS3BpaFN4OERvb202ZVB0Z2pRUjh6bU0zTWxIN1BXTGNHdnB5VkZ2cVg4cWloejRQUnJyVjlmZnVFa3h6TEY0WUVRYlU4</guid></item><item><title>根据心理学， 8种创造性技能可以让你的大脑年轻7岁- VegOut</title><link>https://vegoutmag.com/things-to-do/z-8-creative-skills-that-may-keep-your-brain-7-years-younger-according-to-psychology/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="page__content mt-4"&gt;
							&lt;p&gt;We all want to stay sharp as we move through life.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’ve written a lot about mental fitness before, but this one struck me personally. A new international study found that people who regularly engage in creative practices have brains that look &lt;em&gt;seven years younger&lt;/em&gt; than their actual age. Seven years. That’s not small.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The researchers, from the Max Planck Institute for Empirical Aesthetics, used neuroimaging data to study brain “age gaps.” They discovered that adults who frequently &lt;a href="https://www.aesthetics.mpg.de/en/research/research-group-neural-circuits-consciousness-and-cognition/news/news-detailseite/article/creative-minds-younger-brains-new-study-shows-creative-experiences-delay-brain-aging.html?.com"&gt;take part in creative activities&lt;/a&gt; such as music, writing, dance, or crafts tend to show younger neural profiles than their peers. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That means creativity isn’t just about expression; it’s a kind of brain exercise. Below are eight creative skills that may literally keep your brain younger, backed by psychology and science, with a few observations from my own experience thrown in.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;1) Playing a musical instrument&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If there’s one creative activity that shows up again and again in brain-aging research, it’s music.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When you play an instrument, you’re not just moving your hands; you’re processing pitch, rhythm, timing, and emotion. You’re reading or remembering notes, coordinating muscle movement, and listening closely for feedback. That’s multiple brain regions working together in real time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A 2024 &lt;em&gt;eLife&lt;/em&gt; paper found that musicians tend to &lt;a href="https://www.eurekalert.org/news-releases/1100848?.com"&gt;maintain stronger white-matter integrity&lt;/a&gt; and higher neural efficiency in older age.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I started revisiting my old music-blogger roots and picked up a ukulele last year. I won’t be winning any Grammys, but the process of learning new chords and strumming patterns feels like mental yoga. It forces focus and flexibility in equal measure.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Even 10 to 15 minutes of practice a few times a week can make a difference. The goal isn’t mastery; it’s engagement.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;2) Visual arts (painting, drawing, digital art)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If music isn’t your thing, pick up a pencil. Or a stylus.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Visual arts such as painting, drawing, sculpting, or even digital illustration light up brain regions tied to spatial awareness, visual memory, and creative planning. Studies show that people who regularly engage in artistic expression have &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41591-025-00063-3?.com"&gt;better cognitive flexibility&lt;/a&gt; and stronger emotional regulation. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;During a trip to Costa Rica a few years ago, I took a one-day outdoor sketching class. I was awful at it. But here’s what surprised me: focusing on the interplay of light and shadow, seeing how colors shift at different times of day, it changed how I noticed the world afterward.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Creativity rewires perception. That’s what keeps the brain young; it keeps it curious.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;3) Dance and movement arts&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ever noticed how dancers seem ageless? There’s science behind that.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dancing doesn’t just engage the body; it stimulates the cerebellum, hippocampus, and motor cortex, all areas tied to coordination and memory. Tango dancers, in particular, have shown&lt;a href="https://www.smithsonianmag.com/smart-news/creative-hobbies-could-help-keep-your-brain-young-180987476/?.com"&gt; slower cognitive decline&lt;/a&gt; compared to non-dancers. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dance blends rhythm, movement, emotion, and improvisation. It’s one of the most “whole-brain” creative practices out there.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’m not naturally coordinated, but a few summers ago, I joined a friend for a salsa class in Los Angeles. Between laughing at my two left feet and trying to follow the beat, I realized how alive I felt. My brain was firing on all cylinders, anticipating, reacting, adapting.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You don’t have to join a dance troupe. Even a weekly class, or moving freely to your favorite song in your living room, counts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;4) Photography and visual composition&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Photography gets overlooked in the creative skill conversation, but it shouldn’t.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When you compose a shot, you’re making a thousand micro-decisions: where to focus, what to include, what to leave out. You’re adjusting light, color, and angle. You’re engaging visual-spatial reasoning, memory, and intuition simultaneously.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’ve been doing street photography around Los Angeles lately. Carrying a camera changes the way I walk. I’m scanning for patterns, reflections, small stories in motion. It’s not just about taking a photo; it’s about learning to &lt;em&gt;see&lt;/em&gt;. That mental habit of curiosity keeps the brain active and alert.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you’re new to it, start with your phone. Limit yourself to one theme, say, reflections or textures, and shoot three photos a day. It’s like mindfulness training with a creative edge.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;5) Improvisational writing or storytelling&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Writing is another powerful way to keep your brain elastic.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But here’s the key. It has to be creative writing, not just work emails or to-do lists. When you write stories, poems, or reflective essays, you’re engaging what psychologists call &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Divergent_thinking?.com"&gt;divergent thinking&lt;/a&gt;, the ability to generate many ideas from one prompt. That’s one of the cognitive abilities most strongly linked to creative intelligence. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When I travel, I sometimes write short micro-stories about the people I meet, a cab driver in Bangkok, a barista in Lisbon, a musician in Oaxaca. It’s not about publishing them; it’s about connecting dots and seeing meaning in small moments.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Want to try it? Open your notes app, pick a random object near you, and write a short story that begins with, “This object has a secret.” Don’t edit yourself. Just write for five minutes. Your prefrontal cortex will thank you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;6) Strategic games or creative gaming&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let’s clear something up. Video games, board games, and puzzles can be good for your brain if they’re strategic or creative.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A 2024 review of over 20 studies found that people who regularly played complex games like chess, strategy video games, or world-building sims had &lt;a href="https://www.realsimple.com/how-creative-hobbies-keep-your-brain-young-11836947?.com"&gt;improved cognitive flexibility&lt;/a&gt; and delayed signs of brain aging. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The reason? Strategy games demand decision-making, pattern recognition, and adaptation, all cognitive skills that tend to decline with age if left unchallenged.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When I was traveling in Japan, a friend introduced me to Go. I didn’t know the rules, but once I started, I was hooked. The strategic depth is unreal. You think ten moves ahead, and it humbles you every time. That’s what the brain thrives on, challenge with feedback.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So yes, if you play thoughtful games regularly, it’s not wasting time. It’s brain training disguised as fun.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;7) Crafting or building things (DIY)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you prefer something tangible, crafting and DIY projects are gold.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These activities such as woodworking, sewing, gardening, or building furniture combine problem-solving with fine motor control. Research from the Mayo Clinic found that older adults who frequently engaged in hands-on creative activities had &lt;a href="https://time.com/3814104/adults-arts-and-crafts/?.com"&gt;a 30 percent lower risk&lt;/a&gt; of developing mild cognitive impairment. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Last year I built a small bookshelf for my vegan cookbook collection. It took twice as long as expected, and the paint job wasn’t perfect, but I noticed how mentally stimulating it was. I had to plan, measure, visualize, and adjust. Every mistake was a mini-lesson in spatial reasoning.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The satisfaction you get when you finish something with your hands isn’t just emotional; it’s neurological. It tells your brain, “We can still learn new tricks.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;8) Multimodal creative mixing (combining skills)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This last one is where things get interesting.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Researchers call it &lt;a href="https://arxiv.org/abs/1508.00073?.com"&gt;cross-domain creativity&lt;/a&gt;, combining two or more creative modes, like music and art, or photography and writing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;People who engage in multimodal creative projects show higher integration between brain networks that don’t usually talk to each other. That cross-activation is believed to buffer against cognitive aging.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For example, I once challenged myself to write a short instrumental track, photograph an image that matched its mood, and write a short essay connecting the two. It was clumsy, but it was fun. And the mental engagement was next-level.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The point isn’t perfection; it’s exploration. Try mixing two creative hobbies you already enjoy. You’ll stretch different neural circuits at once, which is exactly what the science says keeps the brain youthful.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;How to start if you feel “non-creative”&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here’s the secret: creativity isn’t a talent; it’s a muscle.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can build it gradually by choosing small, doable actions:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Play a short piece on an instrument you already have at home.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sketch one object from your day before bed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Take one creative photo a day for a week.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Journal using prompts like “What did I notice today that I usually ignore?”&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Learn a simple dance routine on YouTube.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Build or repair something small with your hands.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Blend two of the above.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The goal is to engage curiosity, not to perform.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After a few weeks, you’ll likely notice your attention feels sharper, your mood lighter, and your perspective wider. Those are all signs that your brain is adapting, and that’s exactly what keeps it youthful.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;My takeaway&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As someone who writes about psychology and decision-making, I find this body of research oddly reassuring. It means our hobbies aren’t distractions from real life; they’re part of maintaining it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The older I get, the more I realize creativity isn’t about making art; it’s about staying awake to the world. It’s how we keep seeing beauty in small things, keep questioning, keep inventing. And it just so happens that those same habits might help our brains stay seven years younger.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, whatever creative spark you’ve been ignoring, pick it up. Nurture it. Let it grow messy and unpredictable.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Your future self and your brain will thank you for it.&lt;/p&gt;
						&lt;/div&gt;
					&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>VegOut</author><pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 19:33:41 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMivAFBVV95cUxOandEUG5PQjE2bklUam91Z200clFpRDBJX0xVMFlmSTRkQ1pvVnBCSzhYdS1rT3poVDBwMjhPREtDTTQ0b012SjlRTFFQNGNIbUtaV2Z2cm15SXY0UkdZTFM5RUs5cW5Eb0Z0c0RMMmJieWdyRWlndDRKckYzUWNnaW5ST3JuREF3LTJIZnNBTVJVZkZTb1F3Slg2S1JSdHdLcHhXcGlUSjRvUzk5UmJHOUpZUm1veUoydGIxWg</guid></item></channel></rss>