<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>GNews Health</title><link>https://news.google.com/</link><description></description><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>助听器可将痴呆风险降低61% ，研究称- KSL.com</title><link>https://www.ksl.com/article/51409291/hearing-aids-may-reduce-dementia-risk-by-61-study-says</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="articleContainer"&gt;&lt;p&gt;SALT LAKE CITY — Only about one in five adults who could benefit from hearing aids actually uses them. But new research shows that treating hearing loss early may do more than improve hearing — it could also protect your brain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A 20-year &lt;a href="https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jamaneurology/fullarticle/2837714?guestAccessKey=a1f9c4ab-a0ae-4ca9-afa5-cb8c5e77afc3&amp;amp;utm_source=For_The_Media&amp;amp;utm_medium=referral&amp;amp;utm_campaign=ftm_links&amp;amp;utm_term=081825#xd_co_f=OWUxNzI0Y2UtNzczMi00Y2JlLTg4YWItNDQyNzVmZmZkYzc2~" rel="nofollow" target="_blank"&gt;study&lt;/a&gt; published in the Journal of the American Medical Association found that adults who started using hearing aids before age 70 had a 61% lower risk of developing dementia. The study followed thousands of people and found the strongest benefits in those who treated their hearing loss early, before it became severe.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Hearing loss can be gradual or it can be quickly overnight," said Richard Phillips, a hearing instrument specialist with House of Hearing in Moab.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He said untreated hearing loss forces the brain to work overtime, which can speed up cognitive decline.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Scott Patterson has lived with hearing loss for 20 years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I was always a little concerned about, well, I don't want people to see that I have hearing aids, I don't want to look older," he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He recalled the moment he first received his hearing aids.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I still remember getting back in my car and turning on the music and almost coming to tears because I could actually hear the full sound," Patterson said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Experts say hearing aids won't prevent every case of dementia, but they may be one of the simplest tools to improve communication, reduce isolation and support long-term brain health. They can even help with balance issues, reducing the risk of falls.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"What we've noticed is the ones that wear them all the time, you can just tell, their cognitive skills seem to be sharper, more alert," Phillips said. "It improves your life and makes the people around you a lot happier, also."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Health providers recommend getting a hearing test starting around age 60 — and many clinics offer free screenings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="kt_disclaimer"&gt;
                                    The Key Takeaways for this article were generated with the assistance of large language models and reviewed by our editorial team. The article, itself, is solely human-written.
                                &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>KSL.com</author><pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 18:22:49 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilgFBVV95cUxPam5fb0V2NXZVc1VncWV2YUdTNmR1N2E4dGt3eHduODlyLXRwY0NQUDhFa3Zvalg2d1dXbE04N0NWb1U1SnJYaUV3a3hmeU9HRVZ2aGt1ZVNYbDVFTzlyWmtUMTBRSEdrRnZQQU1CQlE2U2c2ajA1ekVPc0pZeGc1b2VsOXI3N0Rrc3U3NDV6MlRBQ18yVHc</guid></item><item><title>糖尿病前期可以在2年内逆转：当你继续欺骗时，你的身体会产生安静的新陈代谢变化-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/prediabetes-can-be-reversed-within-2-years-the-quiet-metabolic-changes-your-body-makes-when-you-stay-consistent/articleshow/125500852.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Prediabetes has become an increasingly important area of focus in public health, largely because it sits at a crossroads between normal metabolic function and type 2 diabetes. It is defined by raised blood glucose levels that fall short of the diagnostic threshold for diabetes, yet indicate a shift in how the body processes sugar. This stage often develops quietly, particularly in urban populations where dietary habits, long work hours and reduced movement are common. Although the condition signals an elevated risk, emerging evidence shows that it remains a phase in which the body can still respond positively to sustained lifestyle improvements. Understanding how reversal occurs and why it often takes around two years helps clarify both the biological process and the practical steps that support long-term change.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="5"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="6"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;How metabolic flexibility helps the body reverse prediabetes&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="7"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Prediabetes develops when the body begins to lose its usual glucose handling efficiency, yet retains enough metabolic flexibility to recover with time and effort. Many people at this stage still show partial insulin sensitivity, particularly in muscle cells, which means that healthier behaviours can help the body use glucose more effectively. By reducing excess calorie intake, improving sleep and incorporating moderate movement across the week, glucose fluctuations become less severe and insulin production faces less pressure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; These shifts allow the pancreas and liver to adjust gradually rather than react to constant metabolic stress. Recovery is often subtle and may involve extended periods where progress feels slow, although the internal changes accumulate steadily over months.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="11"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;What this means for metabolic recovery:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="13"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="14"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="15"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prediabetes involves impaired but still responsive glucose regulation.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Partial insulin sensitivity helps the body react positively to lifestyle adjustments.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Improvements in diet, sleep and activity reduce the strain on insulin production.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Recovery unfolds slowly, which explains why noticeable change takes time.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="16"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="17"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Long term evidence showing &lt;keyword id="28344744" type="General" weightage="20" keywordseo="prediabetes-reversal" source="Orion"&gt;prediabetes reversal&lt;/keyword&gt; in two years&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="18"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;A decade-long retrospective cohort study from an urban Indian community &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://link.springer.com/article/10.1007/s40200-025-01790-7" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;published in Journal of Diabetes and Metabolic Disorders&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, examined how prediabetes progressed in real-world conditions. The results demonstrated that many individuals reverted to normal glucose levels within roughly two years when they maintained routine screening and reasonable lifestyle improvements. The study highlighted that dramatic changes were not essential. Instead, the most influential factor was consistency, even when actions were modest. Regular checks kept individuals informed, which helped them stay engaged with their progress, while simple adjustments such as reducing portion sizes or adding short walks had measurable metabolic effects. The study’s timeline of around two years reflects the period needed for pancreatic function, body weight and glucose processing to adapt to healthier patterns.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="26"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Key insights from the long-term evidence:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="28"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="29"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="30"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Regular screening helps people track gradual shifts in blood sugar.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Steady lifestyle adjustments deliver significant metabolic benefits.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Biological changes in glucose control align with a two-year adaptation period.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Community-based data shows that sustained habits outperform short-term interventions.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="31"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="32"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;How urban living affects prediabetes reversal&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="33"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Urban environments create a blend of challenges and opportunities for individuals hoping to reverse prediabetes. Long commutes, high stress and sitting for extended hours often contribute to rising glucose levels. At the same time, cities offer health resources that can support recovery, including nutrition counselling, regular medical facilities, fitness centres and organised screenings. People who manage to integrate small changes into their daily routines, such as replacing processed meals with nutrient-rich alternatives or incorporating regular brisk walking, usually show more stable glucose patterns over time. Even modest shifts create a favourable environment for the body to regulate blood sugar more effectively, especially when combined with periodic check-ups that track progress and encourage accountability.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="37"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;How urban factors influence reversal:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="39"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="40"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="41"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;City living contains risk factors such as inactivity and high stress but also valuable health resources.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Small behavioural shifts, like daily walking, help improve glucose management.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Access to medical guidance and screening increases the likelihood of reversal.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Habit formation across two years helps counter the metabolic effects of urban routines.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="42"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="43"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;How the body adapts slowly during prediabetes reversal&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="44"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Reversing prediabetes takes time because metabolic function adapts gradually, not instantly. When individuals increase physical activity, their muscles become more capable of pulling glucose out of the bloodstream. Meanwhile, long-term improvements in diet reduce stored fat in the liver, lowering insulin resistance and giving the pancreas the support it needs to produce insulin more efficiently. Fat tissue itself undergoes changes, becoming less inflamed and more responsive to hormonal signals that regulate glucose. These internal adjustments require continuous reinforcement, which is why brief bursts of effort followed by lapses tend to halt progress. Consistent behaviour is the most reliable driver of improvement, and the two-year timeframe mirrors the natural pace at which tissues recover healthier function.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="51"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Important take-homes about long-term adaptation:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="53"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="54"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="55"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Muscles, liver and fat tissue depend on repeated signals to improve glucose handling.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Long-term behaviour patterns produce more durable results than short, intense efforts.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Insulin sensitivity recovers slowly, which aligns with the two-year reversal trend.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Gradual biological readjustment makes consistent lifestyle habits essential.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="56"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="57"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;How shared routines and guidance help sustain improvement&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="58"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Reversal of prediabetes also depends on the environment surrounding an individual, not just personal habits. Access to supportive community networks, group-based wellness activities and culturally relevant dietary guidance can make lifestyle shifts easier to maintain. Many people benefit from social reinforcement, whether through neighbourhood walking groups, workplace health initiatives or family routines that encourage more balanced meals. These forms of support help individuals stay motivated across the long period required for the body to readjust. Health systems that offer regular follow-up visits, early screening and clear communication further increase the likelihood of improvement, particularly in settings where diabetes risk is widespread and long-term prevention is a public health priority.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="63"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;What strengthens the chance of reversal:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="65"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="66"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="67"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Social support helps people maintain lifestyle changes consistently.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Group activities and shared routines create accountability.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Regular follow-up visits reinforce long-term motivation.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Community access to health education strengthens early prevention efforts.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="68"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="em" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Disclaimer: This article is for informational purposes only and should not be considered medical advice. Please consult a healthcare professional before making any changes to your diet, medication, or lifestyle.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="70"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="71"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Also Read | &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/diet/could-a-low-glutamate-diet-help-reduce-migraines-for-people-living-with-frequent-headaches/articleshow/125491500.cms" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;Could a low-glutamate diet help reduce migraines for people living with frequent headaches&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Times of India</author><pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 14:40:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMitgJBVV95cUxPNDBoRDFCUVhYeldNZTFWeHVpdGh4akVkNkpreWVLT19uRW9jalRsb2h2NjNMNzU2Q3EyM2hTbXZnQ2I2Skw0ZWhDTGxtQ01xWGpGSDhUMjhrYmVvSzVkSFI0ZkFhYk42V29pZXlSeGg3WG9XeE9kOVF3U1Y0R2hGU0tEcVVZRE1UNFE4cnVlVFBNY2s5LUluNmZDVzB6b3RrWFlXYl9ld05OY3didkZtMHhrdUIwNnhtaU1fUkdBWEF3Q05pSVktTVFUQ2kxcDhTQThaXzI5aXpnT3B5QU1KWGRiS3ZLb19DZ0xxb3VCVkRiaFJFUlZubGFla0JvRVRENkZmc1FYNEo4OVRYa3EtazJXdFNrSHZ5N2dHZ0FJWHZHQ3pXWWxZbDFhN0ktUXVybDVCZEN30gG7AkFVX3lxTE9RS3VnSDE1aEJhLWRaU0c2ZFY4QXpQMHd1eGVLaXdNbTNOdWF6RHc1NWc1UXhqVVNxQ2xKTW51eTlqMkM1Wm5nd0pjUm1uT0ZYUkV1ejVoYmpQejBhZXN2RGxtMW4zd2VIWVJ2LW96em9xVTlucVp4Tmp2NlJBZmhRelktYUFMeW5TbHBFcEtQZlpzSExDVm02UVpEem0zS0RsRTdxb0d1dFQ4X1JiZlpHdERMcTZDb3lDOWVIQ2ZGSl9CdnZvckNaS1JVbzhfRTNxWVRJd0Y4MnI0dmRzaTNpcFpsUDVnam1xUDhwMmc2NEZkUzYtMnE2dm9lNVBDRlRUTDlJd2xjYXpFZUZ4cmtWbm5UOXFyc0VvTUMzV3VFNEtQRjBLWHJMbnZSUW1mVjVMdUotanAxdlRPOA</guid></item><item><title>给予实验性混合治疗的小鼠治愈的1型糖尿病- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/type-1-diabetes-cured-in-mice-given-experimental-hybrid-treatment</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;A specially devised hybrid treatment has shown tremendous potential for treating &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/type-1-diabetes-may-be-triggered-by-bacterial-infections-scientists-find"&gt;type 1 diabetes&lt;/a&gt; in mice, scoring full marks at preventing the condition in prediabetic animals and at reversing the condition in animals with fully developed  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/diabetes" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73018" data-postid="182304" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;diabetes&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What makes the new approach stand out is that it successfully combines immune system cells from both the patient mouse and a donor mouse, encouraging them to live in harmony without a need for &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Immunosuppressive_drug"&gt;immunosuppressive drugs&lt;/a&gt; for at least four months.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers behind the work, led by a team from the Stanford School of Medicine, are hopeful the same approach could be successful in humans too. The treatment might also have potential for other procedures where &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/uks-first-liver-transplant-for-advanced-bowel-cancer-removes-all-traces-of-the-disease"&gt;transplants are required&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/breakthrough-diabetes-treatment-may-deliver-insulin-through-a-skin-cream"&gt;Breakthrough Diabetes Treatment May Deliver Insulin Through a Skin Cream&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We believe this approach will be transformative for people with type 1 diabetes or other autoimmune diseases, as well as for those who need solid organ transplants," &lt;a href="https://med.stanford.edu/news/all-news/2025/11/type-1-diabetes-cure.html"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; developmental biologist Seung Kim, from the Stanford School of Medicine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Type 1 diabetes is caused by the body's own &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/4-out-of-5-autoimmune-patients-are-female-the-x-chromosome-could-explain-why"&gt;immune system malfuncting&lt;/a&gt;, triggering an attack on pancreatic cells called beta islets, which produce insulin. While healthy donor islets can be transplanted into the body, they also risk being attacked, if not completely rejected.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_182308" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-182308" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/TransplantAbstract.jpg" alt="Transplant abstract" class="wp-image-182308 size-full" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/TransplantAbstract.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/TransplantAbstract-600x520.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-182308" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Animals were given a conditioning treatment to prepare their immune systems for the cell transplant. (Bhagchandani et al., &lt;em&gt;J. Clin. Invest.&lt;/em&gt;, 2025)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;In this recent experiment, researchers subtly rebooted the mice's immune systems, preparing them before the transplant with an immune system inhibitor, a low dose of radiation, and a few select  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/antibody" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73081" data-postid="182304" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;antibodies&lt;/a&gt;, as well as combining blood  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/stem-cells" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73034" data-postid="182304" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;stem cells&lt;/a&gt; and islet cells from another animal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As a result, the transplanted cells weren't attacked as foreign invaders, and the immune system began &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/scientists-have-discovered-a-special-type-of-immune-cell-that-slows-aging"&gt;functioning normally&lt;/a&gt; again. While a small subset of islet cells showed some signs of inflammation, this critical tissue also wasn't attacked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We need to not only replace the islets that have been lost but also reset the recipient's immune system to prevent ongoing islet cell destruction," &lt;a href="https://med.stanford.edu/news/all-news/2025/11/type-1-diabetes-cure.html"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; Kim. "Creating a hybrid immune system accomplishes both goals."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/newsletter?utm_source=promo_health"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/health-newsletter-subscribe-promo-final-642x337.jpg" alt="Subscribe to ScienceAlert's free fact-checked newsletter" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-181305" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/health-newsletter-subscribe-promo-final-642x337.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/health-newsletter-subscribe-promo-final-768x403.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/health-newsletter-subscribe-promo-final-600x315.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/health-newsletter-subscribe-promo-final.jpg 850w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The experiment represents a number of wins. The treated mice had their diabetes prevented or reversed, and none of them developed the &lt;a href="https://my.clevelandclinic.org/health/diseases/10255-graft-vs-host-disease-an-overview-in-bone-marrow-transplant"&gt;graft-versus-host disease&lt;/a&gt; that often occurs in humans when cells are transplanted between people.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What's more, mixing donor and recipient immune cells has been shown to work for transplants before, including in &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1126/scitranslmed.aax8863"&gt;previous studies&lt;/a&gt; by some of the same research team, which bodes well for human trials.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All of that said, plenty of challenges remain. For example, islet cells can only be donated after death, and must come from the same person as the blood stem cells. It's also unclear just how many of these cells would be needed for the procedure to be successful.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers say they're currently looking at ways of getting more of the donated cells to survive, or figuring out ways of producing them in the lab from &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41392-024-02090-x"&gt;pluripotent human stem cells&lt;/a&gt;. We can't &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/new-treatment-may-cure-severe-type-1-diabetes-study-finds"&gt;cure type 1 diabetes yet&lt;/a&gt; – but &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/first-of-its-kind-cell-transplant-brings-a-cure-for-diabetes-closer"&gt;we're getting closer&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The possibility of translating these findings into humans is very exciting," &lt;a href="https://med.stanford.edu/news/all-news/2025/11/type-1-diabetes-cure.html"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; Kim.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The key steps in our study – which result in animals with a hybrid immune system containing cells from both the donor and the recipient – are already being used in the clinic for other conditions."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The research has been published in the &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1172/JCI190034"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Journal of Clinical Investigation&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 14:04:12 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimgFBVV95cUxPNll2M09GdzREaDNhMkN3TzdlcHFQSGZBelA5RnVYSWZTb0xXZG82Z1NDLWg2amUtTkFJMUVlRTF6dXZGTkV3WFVudEc5alFuYWk5bTUyazM1bDM1RHQ2UEJhRFRYbzZ2MjNldHRTMmtQNThLakZtRS1Hd0VEVjlCQTlsTThlZzh3bnZTR19TNEI4VEozTmRkUlFn</guid></item><item><title>研究人员发现你的大脑“入睡”的确切时刻–从字面上看–印度防御评论</title><link>https://indiandefencereview.com/researchers-exact-moment-brain-falls-sleep/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="dynamic-entry-content"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A team of researchers from&lt;strong&gt; Imperial College London&lt;/strong&gt; has pinpointed the exact moment when the brain “falls” asleep, marking a sharp drop in brain activity just before sleep sets in. This discovery could improve treatments for sleep disorders and have significant implications for public safety, particularly in high-risk situations like driving.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Until now, sleep was often thought to be a slow transition, much like drifting into a dream. However, according to neuroscientist &lt;strong&gt;Nir Grossman&lt;/strong&gt;, who led the research, the change from wakefulness to sleep happens suddenly, much like falling off a cliff. Using EEG monitoring, the researchers observed a distinct point where brain activity sharply declines, signaling the start of sleep. This shift occurs in the final moments before sleep begins, offering a precise definition of the transition from wakefulness to sleep.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;A Sudden Drop in Brain Activity&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;For decades, scientists believed sleep began gradually, with brain activity slowly fading until sleep took over. But Grossman’s team found that the transition is much more dramatic. By monitoring&lt;strong&gt; EEG data&lt;/strong&gt;, they identified a specific moment when brain activity drops sharply, signaling the start of sleep. This sharp decline happens just before sleep sets in and is a clear, measurable point that had previously been hard to define, reports &lt;a href="https://www.popularmechanics.com/science/a69451485/your-brain-literally-falls-asleep/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Popular Mechanics&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;This discovery offers a more accurate understanding of how the brain shifts from wakefulness to sleep, providing valuable insight into how we process the transition. Grossman emphasized the importance of this finding, saying, in a study recently published in the journal &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41593-025-02091-1" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Nature Neuroscience&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;blockquote class="wp-block-quote is-layout-flow wp-block-quote-is-layout-flow"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“&lt;em&gt;The tipping point accurately defines the critical time during the transition from a steady wake state into a steady sleep state.&lt;/em&gt;”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;


&lt;div class="wp-block-image"&gt;
&lt;figure class="aligncenter size-large"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="" alt="Graphical Illustration Of The Computational Framework" class="wp-image-96261" data-lazy-srcset="https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/graphical-illustration-of-the-computational-framework-1200x727.jpg 1200w, https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/graphical-illustration-of-the-computational-framework-380x230.jpg 380w, https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/graphical-illustration-of-the-computational-framework-520x315.jpg 520w, https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/graphical-illustration-of-the-computational-framework-1536x931.jpg 1536w, https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/graphical-illustration-of-the-computational-framework.jpg 1980w" data-lazy-sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" data-lazy-src="https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/graphical-illustration-of-the-computational-framework-1200x727.jpg"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/graphical-illustration-of-the-computational-framework-1200x727.jpg" alt="Graphical Illustration Of The Computational Framework" class="wp-image-96261" srcset="https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/graphical-illustration-of-the-computational-framework-1200x727.jpg 1200w, https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/graphical-illustration-of-the-computational-framework-380x230.jpg 380w, https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/graphical-illustration-of-the-computational-framework-520x315.jpg 520w, https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/graphical-illustration-of-the-computational-framework-1536x931.jpg 1536w, https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/graphical-illustration-of-the-computational-framework.jpg 1980w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px"&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;figcaption class="wp-element-caption"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Graphical illustration of the computational framework – © Nature Neuroscience&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;


&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Sleep-Onset Disorders and Public Safety&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The new findings have important implications for people suffering from sleep disorders, particularly &lt;strong&gt;those who struggle to fall asleep &lt;/strong&gt;or stay awake during critical activities. &lt;a href="https://indiandefencereview.com/how-sleep-deprivation-affects-your-brain/" data-type="post" data-id="76260"&gt;Sleep&lt;/a&gt;-onset disorders, where it takes a long time to fall asleep, can severely impact someone’s health and quality of life. By identifying the exact point when sleep begins, this research could lead to more effective treatments for these disorders, helping individuals to fall asleep faster and enjoy better rest.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Moreover, this discovery has public safety implications. &lt;strong&gt;Sleep deprivation &lt;/strong&gt;can be dangerous, especially in situations where alertness is required, such as driving or operating machinery. Understanding when the brain falls asleep could lead to better ways to monitor and address sleep issues, ultimately reducing the risks associated with sleep-deprived individuals.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;figure class="wp-block-image size-large"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="" alt=" Fold Bifurcation Of Eeg Dynamics During Falling Asleep Transition" class="wp-image-96263" data-lazy-srcset="https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/fold-bifurcation-of-eeg-dynamics-during-falling-asleep-transition-1200x727.jpg 1200w, https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/fold-bifurcation-of-eeg-dynamics-during-falling-asleep-transition-380x230.jpg 380w, https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/fold-bifurcation-of-eeg-dynamics-during-falling-asleep-transition-520x315.jpg 520w, https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/fold-bifurcation-of-eeg-dynamics-during-falling-asleep-transition-1536x931.jpg 1536w, https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/fold-bifurcation-of-eeg-dynamics-during-falling-asleep-transition.jpg 1980w" data-lazy-sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" data-lazy-src="https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/fold-bifurcation-of-eeg-dynamics-during-falling-asleep-transition-1200x727.jpg"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/fold-bifurcation-of-eeg-dynamics-during-falling-asleep-transition-1200x727.jpg" alt=" Fold Bifurcation Of Eeg Dynamics During Falling Asleep Transition" class="wp-image-96263" srcset="https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/fold-bifurcation-of-eeg-dynamics-during-falling-asleep-transition-1200x727.jpg 1200w, https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/fold-bifurcation-of-eeg-dynamics-during-falling-asleep-transition-380x230.jpg 380w, https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/fold-bifurcation-of-eeg-dynamics-during-falling-asleep-transition-520x315.jpg 520w, https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/fold-bifurcation-of-eeg-dynamics-during-falling-asleep-transition-1536x931.jpg 1536w, https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/fold-bifurcation-of-eeg-dynamics-during-falling-asleep-transition.jpg 1980w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px"&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;figcaption class="wp-element-caption"&gt; Fold bifurcation of EEG dynamics during falling asleep transition – &lt;em&gt;© Nature Neuroscience&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;The Role of Brain Nuclei in the Sleep Transition&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The process of &lt;strong&gt;falling asleep &lt;/strong&gt;involves more than just a decrease in brain activity; it is also controlled by specific clusters of neurons called nuclei. Some nuclei promote wakefulness, while others are responsible for initiating sleep. As the brain transitions, certain &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC4660253/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;nuclei&lt;/a&gt; are turned off, causing a sudden shift in how neurons communicate. This change in neural activity leads to the rapid drop in brain activity observed right before sleep.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;One key finding from the study was that the&lt;strong&gt; brain’s occipital cortex&lt;/strong&gt;, which processes visual information, reaches the sleep transition point earlier than the frontal cortex, which is responsible for thinking, memory, and emotional regulation. This explains why some people take longer to fall asleep but experience a quicker shift into sleep once they pass the “&lt;em&gt;falling&lt;/em&gt;” phase. By studying this process, Grossman and his team were able to predict when sleep would occur with remarkable accuracy.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Indian Defence Review</author><pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 13:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigAFBVV95cUxQTG11dHhFQUdxbHlTYWVTUGd5WDlnWnYzZnVfMzU3OWdRX2paNGRSVjNOaHRxY2ozRVdhRTNLb3RyMTBQVFJKR0VUZ0RqSFdzZk5TZHpHT3dPQVFqZDFKcjJLeV81MTJkWC1hem5wUjlVRmRiLS1KRnNTNEE1aHBkWg</guid></item><item><title>华盛顿州居民在H5N5感染后死亡- DW</title><link>https://www.dw.com/en/washington-state-resident-dies-after-h5n5-infection/a-74847177</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div data-tracking-name="rich-text" data-tracking-skip="true" class="c17j8gzx rc0m0op r1ebneao s198y7xq rich-text l1evdo4u blt0baw s16w0xvi rcjjkz7 w128axg5 b1fzgn0z"&gt;&lt;p&gt;A person believed to be the first confirmed case of H5N5 avian &lt;a class="internal-link" href="/en/influenza/t-71362030"&gt;influenza&lt;/a&gt; in humans has died, health authorities in &lt;a class="internal-link" href="/en/united-states-of-america/t-19065189"&gt;US&lt;/a&gt; state of Washington said Friday.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The deceased was a Grays Harbor County resident, according to the Washington State Department of Health. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote class="fb-post embed" data-facebook="true" data-href="https://www.facebook.com/photo?fbid=1285430896959179&amp;amp;set=a.221538120015134"&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;What have health authorities said?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The department said it would not be releasing specific details relating to the deceased's name, gender or age out of respect for the family's privacy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They did confirm that the person was an older adult with pre-existing health conditions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;"The risk to the public remains low. No other people involved have tested positive for avian influenza," state health authorities said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;"Public health officials will continue to monitor anyone who was in close contact with the patient for symptoms to ensure that human-to-human spread has not occurred," the department said and added: "There is no evidence of transmission of this virus between people."&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;According to the health department statement, the person had a backyard flock of domestic birds which they said was the likely source of infection.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="vjs-wrapper embed big"&gt;&lt;h2 aria-label="Embedded video — Bird flu wreaks havoc on US poultry farms" class="headline"&gt;&lt;svg xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 20 20"&gt;&lt;g fill-rule="evenodd"&gt;&lt;path d="M14.114 7.599H13.5l.002 4.706h.601l4.582 3.25-.005-11.11zM11.084 4.444l-9.007.002-1.336.797.002 9.514 1.334.793 9.007.006 1.509-.799-.004-9.516z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/g&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;Bird flu wreaks havoc on US poultry farms&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;video id="video-72067212" controls playsinline="" preload="none" poster="data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAAAEAAAABCAQAAAC1HAwCAAAAC0lEQVR42mNkYAAAAAYAAjCB0C8AAAAASUVORK5CYII=" data-id="72067212" data-posterurl="https://static.dw.com/image/71985603_605.webp" data-duration="02:36"&gt;&lt;source src="https://hlsvod.dw.com/i/dwtv_video/flv/je/je20250328_Superchickens09E_,AVC_480x270,AVC_512x288,AVC_640x360,AVC_960x540,AVC_1280x720,AVC_1920x1080,.mp4.csmil/master.m3u8" type="application/x-mpegURL"&gt;&lt;source src="https://tvdownloaddw-a.akamaihd.net/dwtv_video/flv/je/je20250328_Superchickens09E_AVC_1920x1080.mp4" type="video/mp4"&gt;&lt;p class="vjs-no-js"&gt;To view this video please enable JavaScript, and consider upgrading to a web browser that &lt;a href="https://videojs.com/html5-video-support/" target="_blank"&gt;supports HTML5 video&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/source&gt;&lt;/source&gt;&lt;/video&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;What is H5N5 avian flu?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;H5N5 is a sub-type of &lt;a class="internal-link" href="/en/h5n1-bird-flu-spreading-to-poultry-via-migratory-cranes-germany-denmark-netherlands-usa-europe/a-74527770"&gt;avian flu that is not believed to be a greater threat to human health&lt;/a&gt; than the H5N1 virus that has been behind a wave of 70 reported human infections in the US in 2024 and 2025.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Most of those have been mild illnesses in workers on dairy and poultry farms.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The distinction between H5N5 and H5N1 lies in a protein involved in releasing the virus from an infected cell and promoting spread to surrounding cells.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;According to the Washington State Department of Health website the first human cases of H5 avian influenza were reported in Washington state in October 2024.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The department says that to date, there is no evidence of person-to-person transmission of avian influenza in Washington state.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Health authorities say birds and other animals infected with avian influenza shed the virus in their saliva, mucous and feces.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="vjs-wrapper embed big"&gt;&lt;h2 aria-label="Embedded video — German bird flu outbreak sparks fear among farmers" class="headline"&gt;&lt;svg xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 20 20"&gt;&lt;g fill-rule="evenodd"&gt;&lt;path d="M14.114 7.599H13.5l.002 4.706h.601l4.582 3.25-.005-11.11zM11.084 4.444l-9.007.002-1.336.797.002 9.514 1.334.793 9.007.006 1.509-.799-.004-9.516z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/g&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;German bird flu outbreak sparks fear among farmers&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;video id="video-74576972" controls playsinline="" preload="none" poster="data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAAAEAAAABCAQAAAC1HAwCAAAAC0lEQVR42mNkYAAAAAYAAjCB0C8AAAAASUVORK5CYII=" data-id="74576972" data-posterurl="https://static.dw.com/image/74510479_605.webp" data-duration="02:38"&gt;&lt;source src="https://hlsvod.dw.com/i/vps/webvideos/ENG/2025/BUSI/BUSIENG251103_QWIBirdfluCMS_01SMW_,AVC_480x270,AVC_512x288,AVC_640x360,AVC_960x540,AVC_1280x720,AVC_1920x1080,.mp4.csmil/master.m3u8" type="application/x-mpegURL"&gt;&lt;source src="https://tvdownloaddw-a.akamaihd.net/vps/webvideos/ENG/2025/BUSI/BUSIENG251103_QWIBirdfluCMS_01SMW_AVC_1920x1080.mp4" type="video/mp4"&gt;&lt;track src="https://www.dw.com/media/subtitles/74598849" srclang="en" label="ENGLISH" default&gt;&lt;p class="vjs-no-js"&gt;To view this video please enable JavaScript, and consider upgrading to a web browser that &lt;a href="https://videojs.com/html5-video-support/" target="_blank"&gt;supports HTML5 video&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/track&gt;&lt;/source&gt;&lt;/source&gt;&lt;/video&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Edited by: Saim Dušan Inayatullah, Karl Sexton&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>DW</author><pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 13:10:29 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijAFBVV95cUxQSVZRMjUtTWxyejQ1ZU1oRklvTVZvVDA3QTlYeUhvN0tkcnRGMzA2cUFWNkVsVGlONlY3UU1iREphdU9jejhYWkNCLWZfWXZicFpLcDIzLTBpNnk4dXpFS3dGd09HWTBYVGJIRWZBWXIyVDlncEtHdGJzRlRxa0xnY3FCZ08ybmU0TEtoX9IBjAFBVV95cUxQMWR5c3V4OHhGMmlMc1JhUDQ5WEItRmNYYkF3TExvT0tHaGNoYklFN3JiMm9vV3NXdGhwTFBvYjVjRVVVbmhQUDZmZ2ZzaHRNZkJlQnZ0Um00cDZpTlJ4VEh2ak5uTVRaWmNYUnpqXy03Nll4LXRrU1lsR0d4aEFCamtmSzF6OTFLajJreA</guid></item><item><title>“日落”是我们谈论不够的痴呆症症状- HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffpost.com/entry/sundowning-is-the-dementia-symptom-we-dont-talk-about-enough-g_l_691f838ce4b047290e295f4b</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;section class="entry__content-list js-entry-content js-cet-subunit"&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;During certain times of the day, some people with dementia may become more confused and disoriented. Referred to by neuropsychologist &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.braincenterindy.com/drkrowel" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="April Krowel" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="691f838ce4b047290e295f4b" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.braincenterindy.com/drkrowel" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="0"&gt;&lt;span&gt;April Krowel&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;span&gt;as “a constellation of symptoms rooted in confusion and disorientation,” this condition is called ”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.alz.org/help-support/caregiving/stages-behaviors/sleep-issues-sundowning" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="sundowning" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="691f838ce4b047290e295f4b" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.alz.org/help-support/caregiving/stages-behaviors/sleep-issues-sundowning" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="1"&gt;&lt;span&gt;sundowning&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“Typically, people will start to experience the symptoms in the late afternoon, early evening, the time when the sun is setting,” Krowel, who specializes in assessments of adults with neurological disorders, told HuffPost. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Sometimes, the symptoms occur quite late into the evening, said Dr. Victor Diaz, a neurologist at Orlando Health Neuroscience Institute&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.frontiersin.org/journals/neuroscience/articles/10.3389/fnins.2020.00910/full" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Approximately 1 in 5 people" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="691f838ce4b047290e295f4b" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.frontiersin.org/journals/neuroscience/articles/10.3389/fnins.2020.00910/full" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="2"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Approximately 1 in 5 people&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; with dementia experience sundowning. It affects people with different forms of dementia, like Alzheimer’s and Lewy body dementia, Diaz said. “Episodes can last anywhere from a few minutes to a few hours, and in some cases, can extend into the night.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Sundowning is not something that a person with dementia may notice in themselves, Krowel noted. Rather, it is typically caregivers who pick up on the change in their loved one’s behavior and mental state. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;It can happen at any stage of dementia, though it “tends to peak in the middle stages of dementia and lessens as the disease progresses,” according to the &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://alzheimer.ca/en/help-support/im-caring-person-living-dementia/understanding-symptoms/restlessness-or-confusion" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Alzheimer Society of Canada" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="691f838ce4b047290e295f4b" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://alzheimer.ca/en/help-support/im-caring-person-living-dementia/understanding-symptoms/restlessness-or-confusion" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="3"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Alzheimer Society of Canada&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The symptom is distressing for the person experiencing it. “They don’t know where they are, where they live, they don’t feel safe, which creates an anxiety within them, which can lead to restlessness and irritability,” Krowel explained. They may also experience difficulties with sleeping, Diaz said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;There are ways to manage these symptoms so the person with dementia feels more at ease. Ahead, experts share how to identify sundowning, and how to best support a person going through it:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why does sundowning happen in dementia? &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;To date, no clear cause of sundowning has been identified, both experts said. Some &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.frontiersin.org/journals/medicine/articles/10.3389/fmed.2016.00073/full" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="researchers" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="691f838ce4b047290e295f4b" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.frontiersin.org/journals/medicine/articles/10.3389/fmed.2016.00073/full" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="4"&gt;&lt;span&gt;researchers&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; believe it partly has to do with a &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC4344830/" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="disrupted circadian rhythm" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="691f838ce4b047290e295f4b" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC4344830/" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="5"&gt;&lt;span&gt;disrupted circadian rhythm&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;. Almost every tissue in your body follows a circadian rhythm, which is the body’s internal clock. This process follows the cycle of day and night, to prime your body for alertness in the day and sleepiness at night.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;When disrupted in dementia, it &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC7494756/" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="can potentially cause" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="691f838ce4b047290e295f4b" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC7494756/" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="6"&gt;&lt;span&gt;can potentially cause&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; a person to have increased physical activity later during the day, or remain awake for longer after the sun sets. A &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC7494756/" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="2020 paper " data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="691f838ce4b047290e295f4b" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC7494756/" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="7"&gt;&lt;span&gt;2020 paper &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;noted that circadian rhythms can play a role in influencing emotions and moods. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.uwyo.edu/zoology/people/todd.html" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Researchers" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="691f838ce4b047290e295f4b" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.uwyo.edu/zoology/people/todd.html" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="8"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Researchers&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; are still trying to pinpoint exactly what is happening in the brain to affect the circadian rhythm in dementia. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.frontiersin.org/journals/medicine/articles/10.3389/fmed.2016.00073/full#B33" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="In addition to the above" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="691f838ce4b047290e295f4b" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.frontiersin.org/journals/medicine/articles/10.3389/fmed.2016.00073/full#B33" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="9"&gt;&lt;span&gt;In addition to the above&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;, if a person has afternoon fatigue, pain, hunger, inadequate exposure to sunlight during the day, anxiety, depression, side effects from medications, hearing loss or sight impairment, these may increase their likelihood of experiencing sundowning.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What are the signs of sundowning?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Disorientation and confusion underpin most of the other sundowning symptoms and behaviors. As the day is ending, people may start to be uncertain and confused about what’s going on in their environment. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“For example, if their family is preparing dinner, the patient might be thinking, ‘What are these people doing?’ They don’t understand the activity around preparing the meal,” Diaz said. They may also feel that they are in the &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.dementia.org.au/living-dementia/mood-and-behaviour-changes/restlessness" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="wrong place" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="691f838ce4b047290e295f4b" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.dementia.org.au/living-dementia/mood-and-behaviour-changes/restlessness" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="10"&gt;&lt;span&gt;wrong place&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Because of this, they may become agitated and restless. “They might pace around or rock in the chair, things like that, where there’s visibility, an inability to relax,” Krowel said. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The person may become anxious, irritable, upset or aggressive. They may also have difficulty falling asleep or staying asleep, Diaz said. “Relatives may say they observe the patient wandering at night, because they’re not sleeping at night and reversing the day with the night.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Symptoms “present differently from patient to patient, because there is more than one form of dementia,” Diaz noted. Visual or auditory hallucinations are more common in those with Lewy body Dementia, for example. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;It’s important to learn to tell sundowning apart from delirium, though, as symptoms can appear similar.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Delirium may mean the person is going through a condition that is critical and in some cases, life-threatening, so being able to identify its root cause is essential. “Disorientation in delirium [may mean] the patient is in a critical condition. It could be a bad infection, sepsis, a severe and sudden spike in blood pressure, very high blood sugar, or a manifestation of stroke in patients who are older,” Diaz said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The main way to distinguish between delirium and sundowning is by remembering that the latter typically occurs around the time the sun is setting or at a specific time of day, whereas delirium occurs abruptly at any time of the day, Diaz explained. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“For the most part, once you find out what is causing the delirium, and treat it or get it under control, the delirium will subside,” he noted. Sundowning tends to recur, though there are ways to ease its symptoms when it does.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;If you suspect your loved one is experiencing delirium, Krowel advised seeing your primary care physician or going to emergency care, “depending on how severe the symptoms are at the time.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure class="cli cli-image js-no-inject"&gt;&lt;p class="cli-image__spacer"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="cli-image__source-wrapper"&gt;&lt;div class="cli-image__credit" aria-label="Image Credit: Ippei Naoi via Getty Images"&gt;&lt;p class="credit-container"&gt;&lt;span class="credit"&gt;Ippei Naoi via Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption class="cli-image__caption caption-cli"&gt;Social interaction, especially at night, can help reduce fear and anxiety associated with dementia and reduce sundowning confusion.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What can worsen sundowning? &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Below, Diaz and Krowel shared a list of common factors that can worsen sundowning, and their advice to ease it. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Before running through this list with your loved one, it is a good idea to make sure all of the person’s basic needs are met first: Could they be hungry? Thirsty? Uncomfortable? Tired? They may be agitated because of an unmet need, Krowel said. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lack of routines and changing the environment.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“When you don’t have any routines, move furniture or objects around, change the person’s caregiver, or introduce any other new developments, this disorients the person more,” Diaz said. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Krowel and Diaz advise creating a steady daily routine, sticking to it and minimizing changes to a person’s living environment. Take familiar, comforting objects, like photographs of family, along if the person is going somewhere new and out of their usual routine, as these can help to ground them and make them feel more at ease, Krowel said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Certain types of medications and timing of medications.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Narcotics and certain psychotropic drugs can exacerbate sundowning symptoms, Diaz said. In general, psychotropic drugs to stay away from include &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.frontiersin.org/journals/neurology/articles/10.3389/fneur.2021.644317/full" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="anticholinergic" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="691f838ce4b047290e295f4b" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.frontiersin.org/journals/neurology/articles/10.3389/fneur.2021.644317/full" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="11"&gt;&lt;span&gt;anticholinergic&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; and &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.frontiersin.org/journals/medicine/articles/10.3389/fmed.2016.00073/full" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="benzodiazepine" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="691f838ce4b047290e295f4b" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.frontiersin.org/journals/medicine/articles/10.3389/fmed.2016.00073/full" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="12"&gt;&lt;span&gt;benzodiazepine&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; medications. If the person needs a drug to manage their pain, Diaz recommended staying away from narcotics, and consulting your treating physician for alternatives. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Diaz also said that sometimes the timing and dosing of medications can exacerbate symptoms of sundowning. If you’re noticing symptoms worsening, start to keep track of the person’s medications, “what time you’re giving the medication, what you’re doing differently, and report this to your primary care doctor.” &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;It may be worth having a medication review done by a physician to make sure your prescribed drugs aren’t worsening your sundowning symptoms, Krowel noted.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Poor management of pain, stress or anxiety.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Pain, stress and anxiety can worsen the symptoms of sundowning, Krowel noted. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Monitor the person for any signs that they are in pain, experiencing stress or are anxious, and seek the input of the treating physician and neuropsychologist on how to manage these appropriately. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Poorly lit environment and sight impairment.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“As we get older, we tend to have problems like cataract or diminished visual acuity, so good lighting is very important. If you have a poorly lit place, patients can have a lot of difficulty seeing objects, which can lead to confusion. If the person has visual problems, make sure that these are addressed as well,” Diaz said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;As it gets darker outside, make sure the person’s room is well-lit with artificial lights and lamps so they can see their surroundings clearly. At night, it may be helpful to install a small &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.mayoclinic.org/diseases-conditions/alzheimers-disease/expert-answers/sundowning/faq-20058511" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="night light" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="691f838ce4b047290e295f4b" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.mayoclinic.org/diseases-conditions/alzheimers-disease/expert-answers/sundowning/faq-20058511" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="13"&gt;&lt;span&gt;night light&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Overstimulating environments, especially in the late afternoon.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“Environments that are too noisy can hyperstimulate the patient and overwhelm them,” Diaz said. “And that can lead to them becoming more agitated, confused, and even afraid.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“After around 5 in the afternoon, it’s important to create an environment that is calm, low noise, and comfortable so the person won’t be overstimulated,” Diaz added. Noise can be everything from music and television to conversations and clattering of cutlery. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lack of exposure to sunlight during the daytime.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Sunlight helps to regulate the circadian rhythm and prepares the body to sleep when it turns dark. “Having a lack of exposure to sunlight is something that &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.frontiersin.org/journals/medicine/articles/10.3389/fmed.2016.00073/full" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="research" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="691f838ce4b047290e295f4b" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.frontiersin.org/journals/medicine/articles/10.3389/fmed.2016.00073/full" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="14"&gt;&lt;span&gt;research&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; shows might worsen sundowning symptoms,” Krowel said. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;As much as possible, make sure the person is exposed to sunlight during the daytime, whether it is sitting by a window or &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1111/opn.12292" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="walking outside" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="691f838ce4b047290e295f4b" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1111/opn.12292" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="15"&gt;&lt;span&gt;walking outside&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lack of sleep and fatigue.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Tiredness and sleep difficulties worsen the severity of sundowning. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;If the person is having sleep difficulties at night, sometimes introducing a melatonin supplement around 5 p.m. can be helpful for some patients, according to Diaz. Melatonin, a hormone which helps maintain the circadian rhythm and causes sleepiness at night, has been &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.frontiersin.org/journals/medicine/articles/10.3389/fmed.2016.00073/full" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="found to be lower" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="691f838ce4b047290e295f4b" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.frontiersin.org/journals/medicine/articles/10.3389/fmed.2016.00073/full" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="16"&gt;&lt;span&gt;found to be lower&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; in individuals with Alzheimer’s dementia. Make sure to check with a physician before starting this, however.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;He also recommended correcting any issues that can disrupt sleep, like &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/entry/sleep-latency-fall-asleep-quickly-ano_l_66f2d831e4b0199dbefb13f5" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-internal-link" data-vars-item-name="obstructive sleep apnea" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="691f838ce4b047290e295f4b" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="66f2d831e4b0199dbefb13f5" data-vars-target-content-type="buzz" data-vars-type="web_internal_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="17"&gt;&lt;span&gt;obstructive sleep apnea&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;, and avoiding excessive caffeine or sugar as these can be stimulating.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lack of interaction.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“One way that families might deal with sundowning is by leaving the person alone in their bedroom until they finish having their episode. That is not advisable, because the more isolated the patient is, it feeds into their fear and anxiety and disorientation,” Diaz said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Instead, he advised calmly redirecting the person. “When the person becomes agitated or disoriented, say ‘You are in: [insert name of where they are]. This is what we are doing: [insert explanation of what is happening].’ This reassures the person and explains in that moment what is going on, which helps you avoid the cycle of the person becoming disoriented, anxious and agitated.” &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>HuffPost</author><pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 12:09:14 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMivAFBVV95cUxNSkdhXzZQT0tlRFAyRVF4ZGgxTDlIVm13UWpNS2JiRmpiS1JvUFN0Z3hFZUFRdVRhek5McjQ1RW5tT2NZVGJxN2N2eTNoeEFUemYxRmdZNVRiaDNaRnlJdXR2cTVQdFdVVkprTUhsTkVQU0hoY1JrWkZBLXVxUXVuZDM3VWhFWlVQa29pc0Rfc1JZZTEwWXpuWjdIWGtsTkd3amxoeDNwN2VZdk1jZk05ZVh4M3VkblRObkRFa9IBwgFBVV95cUxNTVVxYmlJQWcxbG1kMUhZYUhuZ1d1QTFURFRselloNlNSeVp2MldKYktPNEdTT29aVTJvV3czRmtUcmc2ZUZtd2RLR1V3Qk1sUnhvNnY1bDNucmtFTXhWRDJBeWQ4OElxLS12WnNCN09pS09HdTllaHl5QTRKdjlpM3k1M2ZNMms3blYwMGxWaFgxSWMxU19QanI0eGpBSFhRc051aXpFbFZrWDJYS2tuU1oyT0lQZlBpRk9mSW1iNFVudw</guid></item><item><title>长期COVID症状有8种模式。它们是什么- Axios</title><link>https://www.axios.com/2025/11/22/long-covid-symptoms-timeline-how-long</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Axios</author><pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 12:01:45 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiekFVX3lxTE53TmRxSFZlTjU5Z2N1SlpSODJGZTBpVmNRbjNlZ3JjdWFlNVBGN2NLX29zZ3Z6cldFZkVLOHlWUjNpREdyaUlkVW9ObkxrUktIdC1XT0duSURSczk4c3BlSGNURjNiekJVWjNPVWd4U09ERjZDZGY4QmtB</guid></item><item><title>我是一名美食医生。这是如果我有胃痛，我永远不会做的一件事。- HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffpost.com/entry/stomach-pain-doctor-advice-goog_l_691de9cde4b073def3ef4c84</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;section class="entry__content-list js-entry-content js-cet-subunit"&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s pretty common to utter the phrase “my stomach hurts.” You’ve probably had stomach pain at some point in your life, whether it’s discomfort after eating, stress-related pain, menstrual cramps or a larger medical issue.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Abdominal pain, just those two words, is the most common diagnosis we have seen in our ER actually,” said &lt;a href="https://www.vanderbilthealth.com/doctors/sarker-shabnam" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Dr. Shabnam Sarker" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="691de9cde4b073def3ef4c84" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.vanderbilthealth.com/doctors/sarker-shabnam" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="0"&gt;Dr. Shabnam Sarker&lt;/a&gt;, a gastroenterologist at Vanderbilt Digestive Disease Center in Nashville. “I would think it was something like chest pain or something else, but abdominal pain is [the most common].”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;As anyone with a stomach condition likely knows, it can often take some time to pinpoint exactly what is wrong. Why? Because “th&lt;span&gt;ere are many causes of stomach pain,” &lt;a href="https://www.orlandohealth.com/physician-finder/sunina-nathoo-md#/overview" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Dr. Sunina Nathoo" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="691de9cde4b073def3ef4c84" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.orlandohealth.com/physician-finder/sunina-nathoo-md#/overview" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="1"&gt;Dr. Sunina Nathoo&lt;/a&gt;, a g&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;astroenterologist at the Orlando Health Digestive Health Institute, told HuffPost via email — like gallstones, ulcers, Crohn’s disease, irritable bowel syndrome, appendicitis and more.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;But there is one thing doctors say they never do (and you should never do) when it comes to any kind of stomach pain. Here’s what they said:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;They don’t ignore pain — especially if it’s sudden.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“If there is stomach pain that just does not feel right, I recommend seeing a primary care doctor and gastroenterologist to figure out what is going on,” Nathoo said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you can’t get in with a gastroenterologist for some time, Sarker said just seeing a primary care doctor is just fine, too. “You don’t really want to delay if you are uncomfortable,” Sarker noted. Stomach issues can be debilitating and can even cause further issues for your bowel movements and eating habits.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“The bottom line is all pain is real and should be evaluated,” Nathoo said. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;But the type of pain you’re feeling should dictate your next steps, as some symptoms are more serious than others ― specifically if you have sudden, new pain.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“If people experience severe and acute onset pain, they should go to the ER. The concern would be that the pain could be due to a cause that requires emergent intervention,” Nathoo explained. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Certain symptoms that can accompany stomach pain should also be addressed as soon as possible.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“If it’s a new symptom, then we always say you should probably consult with somebody,” Sarker said. This is especially true if certain GI “alarm factors,” which Sarker says are new abdominal pain, bleeding from the bowels and weight loss, coincide with the pain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;While a one-off stomach ache can happen, if you have mild, chronic stomach pain, you should see a doctor if the pain is non-debilitating and continues for more than a week or two, Nathoo said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s also important to take any pain or symptoms seriously if you have a family history of stomach cancer, esophageal cancer or colon cancer, according to &lt;a href="https://profiles.hopkinsmedicine.org/provider/ekta-gupta/2703764" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Dr. Ekta Gupta" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="691de9cde4b073def3ef4c84" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://profiles.hopkinsmedicine.org/provider/ekta-gupta/2703764" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="2"&gt;Dr. Ekta Gupta&lt;/a&gt;, a gastroenterologist at Johns Hopkins Medicine in Baltimore.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Colorectal cancer &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/entry/colon-cancer-young-people-symptoms_l_63fcc67de4b0735bf879341f" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-internal-link" data-vars-item-name="is becoming more and more" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="691de9cde4b073def3ef4c84" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="63fcc67de4b0735bf879341f" data-vars-target-content-type="buzz" data-vars-type="web_internal_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="3"&gt;is becoming more and more&lt;/a&gt; common in young people, according to a recent American Cancer Society report. Colorectal cancer diagnoses increased from 11% in 1995 to 20% in 2019 in people under 55, so it’s something everyone should take seriously.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Abdominal pain, rectal bleeding and blood in your stool are all signs of the disease, making it important to report any and all gut-related symptoms to a doctor.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure class="cli cli-image js-no-inject"&gt;&lt;p class="cli-image__spacer"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="cli-image__source-wrapper"&gt;&lt;div class="cli-image__credit" aria-label="Image Credit: Westend61 via Getty Images"&gt;&lt;p class="credit-container"&gt;&lt;span class="credit"&gt;Westend61 via Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption class="cli-image__caption caption-cli"&gt;Everything from serious diseases like colon cancer to daily stress can cause stomach pain.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bottom line: Don’t dismiss stomach issues or self-diagnose.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;From gallstones to menstrual cramps to colon cancer to appendicitis and more, there are many, many causes of abdominal pain, which means it’s always a good idea to see a doctor; you won’t always be able to tell just from your symptoms alone.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;And even if you’ve dealt with certain abdominal discomfort for weeks or months doesn’t mean you have to just keep ignoring it. Sarker recommended keeping a log of the characteristics and associations of the pain, which can help you better get the picture across to your provider.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Doctors say you should also be aware of the lifestyle behaviors that can aggravate stomach pain, too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I tend to suggest to my patients that they should stay away from NSAIDs, which are medications that help with pain in general and so commonly used mindlessly, like Aleve, Motrin, Ibuprofen,” Gupta said. These medications are known to irritate your stomach lining.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stress is also linked with stomach ulcers, and spicy and acidic foods can also be the culprit for stomach discomfort, Gupta explained.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Suffice to say, there are lots of reasons people have stomach pain, but the pain — no matter how mild or frequent — shouldn’t be discounted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I think instead of trying to self-diagnose, seeking care sooner than later is helpful, especially if it is affecting the quality of your life, or it is acute, just like, hit you all of a sudden and this is definitely out of the norm for you,” Sarker said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>HuffPost</author><pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 12:00:17 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikwFBVV95cUxQZDd0VDREdnJRem4wUEhBVjVWRVlRLVVZY3Qyd2pWWC1tanl3bGNkY01aS0V3T0JpZmVGNk9UNzBQRlhjZW5hMTJnUEtSV3Nwa1JxSnZNMVFfTmRoT3pxY3NDTFNWT3JUQWJZajFtQlhCM3dKMUJSUlpXOGR2TUdPUkllODlKcFJWdmFRbG0zb295V1nSAZgBQVVfeXFMUFlYTkhKc3pMV1c5UVZncjl6Yy1oR1ZNcGVBckFIWkJfaXdlUWhZbHhlM2NrMGk1Yzh0c09qcGxuSVNEZWRTeW14SmdmQzhBRUxCdDRQSG40RFE5NVVDSWpGYmVibnNpVlNBREVtd1VOYW0yZVpoaHF3cmtFTGZFS0hRZHE2c0otdXZRdjdodkwyNGh4cnkxM1k</guid></item><item><title>美国有失去麻疹消除地位的风险吗？ - ABC新闻</title><link>https://abcnews.go.com/Health/us-risk-losing-measles-elimination-status/story?id=127763508</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="xvlfx ZRifP TKoO eaKKC EcdEg bOdfO qXhdi NFNeu UyHES " data-testid="prism-article-body"&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao MvWXB TjIXL aGjvy ebVHC "&gt;As measles continues to spread across the United States, questions have emerged about whether the country will retain its measles elimination status.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;The U.S. is currently experiencing the highest number of measles cases reported in more than three decades, in large part due to an outbreak in western Texas that infected more than 700 people and spread to New Mexico and Oklahoma.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Meanwhile, an outbreak in Arizona and Utah currently shows no signs of slowing down and a separate outbreak in South Carolina has sent dozens of students into quarantine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;If spread of the virus continues into late January, it will mean the U.S. has seen a year of continuous transmission, which could lead to a loss of the country's elimination status. Measles would once again be considered endemic or constantly circulating.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;The threat of the U.S. losing its elimination status is looming after &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://abcnews.go.com/Health/canada-loses-measles-elimination-status-amid-year-long/story?id=127373379" target="_blank" dir="ltr"&gt;Canada lost its measles elimination status&lt;/a&gt; following a struggle to contain a year-long measles outbreak, public health experts told ABC News.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;"I do think that the likelihood that we're going to lose status, especially if things continue the way that they're going, is I think pretty high," Dr. Tony Moody, a professor of pediatrics in the division of infectious diseases at Duke University Medical Center, told ABC News.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="oLzSq QrHMO fnRUo pvsTF EhJPu vPlOC zNYgW OsTsW RMeqy daRVX ISNQ sKyCY eRftA acPPc MENS nFwaT MCnQE mEeeY SmBjI xegrY rPLsU iulOd NIuqO zzscu lzDCc aHUBM IEgzD OjMNy eQqcx SVqKB GQmdz jaoD VWDdR ONJdw vrZxD OnRTz gbbfF roDbV GPGwb oMlSS gfNzt oJhud eXZcf zhVlX "&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="InlineImage GpQCA lZur asrEW " data-testid="prism-inline-image"&gt;&lt;figure class="kzIjN GNmeK pYrtp dSqFO " data-testid="prism-figure"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;div class="nMMea bNYiy Mjgpa dGwha DDmxa jgKNG RGHCC aBIU PriDW lZur " data-testid="prism-caption"&gt;&lt;p class="HXPPJ barbu yKsXL IzgMt VcHIt uhSzI YGNMU cRAsZ xqMcl QtRul "&gt;&lt;span class="hsDdd OOSI GpQCA lZur VlFaz " data-testid="prism-truncate"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="gtOSm FbbUW tUtYa vOCwz EQwFq yCufu eEak Qmvg nyTIa SRXVc vzLa jgBfc WXDas CiUCW kqbG zrdEG txGfn ygKVe BbezD UOtxr CVfpq xijV soGRS XgdC sEIlf daWqJ "&gt;Signs point the way to measles testing in the parking lot of the Seminole Hospital District across, Feb. 27, 2025, in Seminole, Texas.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="qinlA IpWvx oqZz tylGM lyWxS nWcVF UhTug PPcLh YxlyB "&gt;&lt;span class="gtOSm FbbUW tUtYa vOCwz EQwFq yCufu eEak Qmvg nyTIa SRXVc vzLa jgBfc WXDas CiUCW kqbG zrdEG txGfn ygKVe BbezD UOtxr CVfpq xijV soGRS XgdC sEIlf daWqJ YNujN JGtjI aZFDu rkKLh "&gt;Jan Sonnenmair/Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;&lt;strong class="vtkaO "&gt;State of measles in the U.S.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;As of Wednesday, there have been 1,753 confirmed cases across 42 states this year, according to the &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://www.cdc.gov/measles/data-research/index.html#cdc_data_surveillance_section_10-measles-cases-in-2025" target="_blank" dir="ltr"&gt;Centers for Disease Control and Prevention&lt;/a&gt; (CDC).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;There have been 45 outbreaks, so far this year compared to 16 outbreaks all last year, CDC data shows.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Additionally, 92% of cases have been among those who are unvaccinated or whose vaccination status is unknown, according to the CDC.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;There have been three measles deaths this year -- the first fatalities due to the disease in a decade -- including among &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://abcnews.go.com/Health/child-measles-dies-texas-hospital-officials/story?id=120539137" target="_blank" dir="ltr"&gt;two unvaccinated school-aged children&lt;/a&gt; in Texas and one &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://abcnews.go.com/Health/unvaccinated-new-mexico-resident-tests-positive-measles-after/story?id=119529919" target="_blank" dir="ltr"&gt;unvaccinated adult&lt;/a&gt; in New Mexico.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;The CDC currently &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://www.cdc.gov/measles/vaccines/index.html" target="_blank" dir="ltr"&gt;recommends&lt;/a&gt; that people receive two doses of the measles, mumps, rubella (MMR) vaccine, the first at ages 12 to 15 months and the second between 4 and 6 years old. One dose is 93% effective, and two doses are 97% effective against measles, the CDC says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;However, CDC data shows vaccination rates have been lagging in recent years. During the 2024-25 school year, &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://www.cdc.gov/schoolvaxview/data/index.html" target="_blank" dir="ltr"&gt;92.5% of kindergartners received the MMR vaccine&lt;/a&gt;. This is lower than the 92.7% seen the previous school year and the 95.2% seen in the 2019-20 school year, prior to the COVID-19 pandemic.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Even in states with high MMR vaccine uptake, pockets of unvaccinated or under-vaccinated communities can lead to rapid spread.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;For example, in Texas, 94.3% of kindergartners were up to date on their MMR vaccine for the 2023-24 school year, &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://www.cdc.gov/mmwr/volumes/73/wr/mm7341a3.htm#T1_down" target="_blank" dir="ltr"&gt;CDC data&lt;/a&gt; shows. However, in Gaines County -- the epicenter of this year's outbreak -- 17.6% of kindergartners were exempt from at least one vaccine during the 2023-24 school year, one of the highest exemption rates in the state, according to &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://www.dshs.texas.gov/immunizations/data/school/conscientious-exemptions" target="_blank" dir="ltr"&gt;state health data&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;"It's kind of like you have a very dry forest, so any spark that comes in can burn down the entire forest," Dr. Peter Chin-Hong, a professor of medicine and infectious diseases specialist at the University of California, San Francisco, told ABC News. "That's what's happening, which is fewer people being vaccinated, as evidenced by the drop in in people entering kindergarten."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;He said one case of measles is like a spark that quickly turns into a blaze as it spread through an unvaccinated community "and that's why it's hard to put out the fire."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;&lt;strong class="vtkaO "&gt;How loss of status is determined&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;The loss of status is determined by the Pan American Health Organization (PAHO, an agency of the U.N. that oversees international health in the Americas.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;An independent body of experts established by the PAHO -- known as the Measles, Rubella, and Congenital Rubella Syndrome Elimination Regional Monitoring and Re-Verification Commission (RVC) -- meets at least once a year to monitor and re-verify measles and rubella elimination among countries in the Americas.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="oLzSq QrHMO fnRUo pvsTF EhJPu vPlOC zNYgW OsTsW RMeqy daRVX ISNQ sKyCY eRftA acPPc MENS nFwaT MCnQE mEeeY SmBjI xegrY rPLsU iulOd NIuqO zzscu lzDCc aHUBM IEgzD OjMNy eQqcx SVqKB GQmdz jaoD VWDdR ONJdw vrZxD OnRTz gbbfF roDbV GPGwb oMlSS gfNzt oJhud eXZcf zhVlX "&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="InlineImage GpQCA lZur asrEW " data-testid="prism-inline-image"&gt;&lt;figure class="kzIjN GNmeK pYrtp dSqFO " data-testid="prism-figure"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;div class="nMMea bNYiy Mjgpa dGwha DDmxa jgKNG RGHCC aBIU PriDW lZur " data-testid="prism-caption"&gt;&lt;p class="HXPPJ barbu yKsXL IzgMt VcHIt uhSzI YGNMU cRAsZ xqMcl QtRul "&gt;&lt;span class="hsDdd OOSI GpQCA lZur VlFaz " data-testid="prism-truncate"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="gtOSm FbbUW tUtYa vOCwz EQwFq yCufu eEak Qmvg nyTIa SRXVc vzLa jgBfc WXDas CiUCW kqbG zrdEG txGfn ygKVe BbezD UOtxr CVfpq xijV soGRS XgdC sEIlf daWqJ "&gt;Instructions for a Measles vaccination is seen outside of the Lubbock Public Health facility, April 9, 2025, in Lubbock, Texas.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="qinlA IpWvx oqZz tylGM lyWxS nWcVF UhTug PPcLh YxlyB "&gt;&lt;span class="gtOSm FbbUW tUtYa vOCwz EQwFq yCufu eEak Qmvg nyTIa SRXVc vzLa jgBfc WXDas CiUCW kqbG zrdEG txGfn ygKVe BbezD UOtxr CVfpq xijV soGRS XgdC sEIlf daWqJ YNujN JGtjI aZFDu rkKLh "&gt;Brandon Bell/Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;A person familiar with how PAHO determines loss of elimination status told ABC News that there would have to be compelling evidence that there has been continuous spread of measles in the U.S. since January, when the first cases were reported in Texas and that other outbreaks may trace back to the Texas outbreak.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;The person said the committee will get together in mid-2026 to look at the data, write its next report and formally submit it to the PAHO for review. The annual meeting will likely take place in late 2026, unless a previously unplanned meeting is convened beforehand.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;"The RVC holds annual meetings with all member states, conducts visits to priority countries, reviews national sustainability reports, and issues recommendations to the Director of PAHO," a spokesperson for PAHO told ABC News. "It may also convene extraordinary meetings with member states to provide recommendations on specific topics or to follow up on outbreak situations. At this time, no extraordinary meeting has been scheduled for next year specifically to assess the U.S. or Mexico situation, but such a meeting could be convened if the epidemiological situation warrants."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Between April 2025 and October 2025, Mexico has seen 4,550 cases, according to the &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://www.cdc.gov/global-measles-vaccination/data-research/global-measles-outbreaks/index.html" target="_blank" dir="ltr"&gt;WHO&lt;/a&gt;, which could also lead to the loss of its elimination status.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Moody explained that the U.S. having measles elimination status, which it received in 2000, is less of a formal declaration and more of a statement that a county has a relatively low number of cases and no sustained transmission.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Loss of status would similarly be a statement that a country has sustained transmission and that the virus is constantly present, he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;"What does it mean from a public health perspective, or a parent's perspective, it means that we have a higher risk for seeing transmission, and that if someone goes to a place where there is sustained transmission, there's kind of an increased risk and, truthfully, you can pick it up just about anywhere," Moody said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;&lt;strong class="vtkaO "&gt;Canada's loss of elimination status&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Earlier this month, the &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://www.canada.ca/en/public-health/news/2025/11/statement-from-the-public-health-agency-of-canada-on-canadas-measles-elimination-status.html" target="_blank" dir="ltr"&gt;Public Health Agency of Canada said&lt;/a&gt; it was informed of the elimination status loss by PAHO after more than 12 months of continuous measles transmission. Canada's outbreak began in late October 2024, and the county has seen more than 5,200 confirmed and probable cases since then, data from the health agency shows.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;As a result, the Americas region lost elimination status as well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Canada can re-establish its measles elimination status if measles transmission related to the current outbreak is "interrupted" for at least 12 months, according to the county's health officials.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="oLzSq QrHMO fnRUo pvsTF EhJPu vPlOC zNYgW OsTsW RMeqy daRVX ISNQ sKyCY eRftA acPPc MENS nFwaT MCnQE mEeeY SmBjI xegrY rPLsU iulOd NIuqO zzscu lzDCc aHUBM IEgzD OjMNy eQqcx SVqKB GQmdz jaoD VWDdR ONJdw vrZxD OnRTz gbbfF roDbV GPGwb oMlSS gfNzt oJhud eXZcf zhVlX "&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="InlineImage GpQCA lZur asrEW " data-testid="prism-inline-image"&gt;&lt;figure class="kzIjN GNmeK pYrtp dSqFO " data-testid="prism-figure"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;div class="nMMea bNYiy Mjgpa dGwha DDmxa jgKNG RGHCC aBIU PriDW lZur " data-testid="prism-caption"&gt;&lt;p class="HXPPJ barbu yKsXL IzgMt VcHIt uhSzI YGNMU cRAsZ xqMcl QtRul "&gt;&lt;span class="hsDdd OOSI GpQCA lZur VlFaz " data-testid="prism-truncate"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="gtOSm FbbUW tUtYa vOCwz EQwFq yCufu eEak Qmvg nyTIa SRXVc vzLa jgBfc WXDas CiUCW kqbG zrdEG txGfn ygKVe BbezD UOtxr CVfpq xijV soGRS XgdC sEIlf daWqJ "&gt;A family supports a young child as he receives the MMR vaccine at a vaccine clinic put on by Lubbock Public Health Department, March 1, 2025, in Lubbock, Texas.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="qinlA IpWvx oqZz tylGM lyWxS nWcVF UhTug PPcLh YxlyB "&gt;&lt;span class="gtOSm FbbUW tUtYa vOCwz EQwFq yCufu eEak Qmvg nyTIa SRXVc vzLa jgBfc WXDas CiUCW kqbG zrdEG txGfn ygKVe BbezD UOtxr CVfpq xijV soGRS XgdC sEIlf daWqJ YNujN JGtjI aZFDu rkKLh "&gt;Jan Sonnenmair/Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;"Given that we share one of the longest borders in the world with Canada. It's not as if there's some magic barrier between U.S. and Canada," Moody said. "If there's transmission in Canada, we're going to get it in the United States. ...  I'm not saying that Canada has put us at risk. We've kind of put ourselves at risk but ... I do see it as being a highly likely thing that we're going to see continued transmission."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Canada will present and implement an action plan under PAHO's regional framework to increase immunization coverage, reinforce surveillance systems and ensure rapid outbreak response to stop spread. This shows what the U.S. would likely experience if it lost its status.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;"If we lose our status, it'll be hard to regain it," Chin-Hong said, noting how many workers have been laid off at HHS that might have helped control large outbreaks. "Not only loss of expertise, but just loss of the workforce in general, the people who go out and do the surveillance and contain the epidemic by vaccination efforts and all that. ... It just denotes how fragile public health gains are. In general, it's easy to lose it and hard to get it back."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;&lt;strong class="vtkaO "&gt;How to prevent further spread&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Public health experts told ABC News there are several steps that can be taken to help control the spread of measles in the U.S. including increasing funding to public health for monitoring and surveillance as well as spreading awareness about how dangerous measles can be.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;However, they add that the best way to stop the spread is through vaccination, both to protect yourself and the most vulnerable individuals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;"We can't control the people who are unable to get vaccines because they're being treated for cancer, because they are born with an immunodeficiency," Dr. Aaron Milstone, pediatric director of infection prevention at Johns Hopkins Health System, told ABC News. "What we can control is everyone else in the community who is eligible for a vaccine, who does not take it, and that's the reason that measles is spreading, in part, because the herd protection from our community has gone down."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;As an extra step, public health agencies have &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://www.cdc.gov/han/php/notices/han00522.html?CDC_AA_refVal=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.cdc.gov%2Fhan%2F2025%2Fhan00522.html" target="_blank" dir="ltr"&gt;previously recommended&lt;/a&gt; early MMR vaccination for infants living in outbreak areas or traveling internationally.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;This would result in three doses overall: an early dose between age 6 months and 11 months and then the two regularly scheduled doses at age 1 and between ages 4 and 6.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Milstone said the recommendation to give a child their first MMR dose at age one was under the assumption that they likely would not be exposed to measles before then and that antibodies passed in utero would help protect them during their first year of life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Now, with the continuous spread being seen, "are we going to have to rethink our recommendations for when to vaccinate kids in the U.S.?" Milstone said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC eTIW sUzSN "&gt;&lt;em class=" "&gt;ABC News' Youri Benadjaoud contributed to this report.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ABC News</author><pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 11:07:53 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilAFBVV95cUxQNS1WWGhHbWpHVkQtcEtSUU9wajBldGo5ZzRRdGVKMk83ZU14OGh6cVpiUTcydUVIdTFYNkhwQnJuakN4WnZQN2lPaU9mSENpRmdZdzRnY0pYY0xVVjJhZkZpWkpwVDFSYUZRTXhwZTRib09xWW1IMWNzbEdmNUlmaDZOQjhrWm1sZ0R0TFRUNHBaa1BF0gGaAUFVX3lxTFB0VjFWMGRNSkdRTFFFb1E5OWw2WGlXTzkyTVF6anl0UTFKTHg4RW5la1ZzM3hOdnMydkhhMkxhZmJDbnU3ZFpyM1BNUnBxX041RGV3dHg1RkZnSXk5Rlo3TjhyclhmVHlpVTdTNU5TUnl4ZlRfUzF6ZVNEUEZ5dmRHRTdjTjVKVmpTTTRWdmJvZWdUdndfclY2T2c</guid></item><item><title>与老年人大脑加速衰老相关的促炎饮食- PsyPost</title><link>https://www.psypost.org/pro-inflammatory-diets-linked-to-accelerated-brain-aging-in-older-adults/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="content-inner "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Recent research suggests that the food we eat may influence the biological aging of our brains. A study involving over 20,000 adults indicates that consuming a diet high in pro-inflammatory foods is associated with accelerated brain aging. This effect appears to be most pronounced in older adults. The findings were published in the &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1007/s10654-025-01318-6" target="_blank"&gt;European Journal of Epidemiology&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chronic systemic inflammation is increasingly recognized as a contributing factor to various health issues, including neurodegenerative diseases. As people age, levels of inflammatory markers in the blood typically rise. Elevated levels of these markers often correlate with a higher risk of cognitive decline and conditions such as dementia. Scientists have established that diet is a primary way to regulate inflammation in the body.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Certain dietary patterns, such as the Western diet, are known to promote inflammation. These diets usually contain high amounts of red meat, processed foods, and high-fat dairy products. In contrast, diets rich in vegetables, fruits, and whole grains tend to lower inflammation. While previous studies have linked pro-inflammatory diets to memory problems and specific brain changes, the impact on overall brain aging remained less clear.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers behind this new study aimed to fill this gap in knowledge. They sought to determine if a diet that promotes inflammation is linked to a comprehensive measure of brain health known as “brain age.” They also wanted to understand if this relationship varied based on a person’s chronological age or their genetic risk for dementia. Additionally, the team investigated whether systemic inflammation in the body acted as a bridge connecting diet to brain health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“There is growing evidence to suggest that diet may play an important role in brain and cognitive health, and specifically that inflammation from an unhealthy diet could be one contributing mechanism. However, whether dietary inflammation is associated with a comprehensive measure of brain health has not been previously examined,” explained study author Michelle M. Dunk, a researcher at the Aging Research Center and Division of Neurogeriatrics at the Karolinska Institutet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“One way to measure someone’s overall brain health is by measuring their ‘brain age’ from MRI scans. We can then calculate the “brain age gap” by comparing a person’s brain age to their chronological age. When someone’s brain looks older than their actual age, it may signal an increased risk for cognitive decline or dementia.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Data for this analysis came from the UK Biobank, a large-scale biomedical database. The study included 21,473 participants who were between the ages of 40 and 70. None of these individuals had neurological disorders at the beginning of the study. This exclusion helped ensure that the results reflected typical aging rather than the progression of pre-existing brain diseases.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To assess dietary habits, the researchers used a web-based questionnaire called the Oxford WebQ. Participants reported their food and drink consumption from the previous twenty-four hours. This assessment was administered up to five times over a period of several years. The repeated assessments allowed for a more accurate estimation of habitual dietary intake than a single questionnaire would provide.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;From this dietary data, the investigators calculated a Dietary Inflammatory Index score for each participant. This index is based on the intake of thirty-one specific nutrients and dietary components. The researchers looked at nutrients that either increase or decrease inflammation levels. For instance, components like fiber, omega-3 fatty acids, and certain vitamins are considered anti-inflammatory. Conversely, saturated fats and carbohydrates are often classified as pro-inflammatory.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Based on these scores, participants were divided into four distinct groups. Group 1 consisted of individuals with the most anti-inflammatory diets. Group 4 included those with the most pro-inflammatory diets. This categorization allowed the researchers to compare brain health outcomes across different levels of dietary quality.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Approximately nine years after the initial dietary assessments, participants underwent magnetic resonance imaging (MRI) scans of their brains. The researchers used these scans to estimate the biological age of each participant’s brain. They employed a machine learning model to analyze 1,079 different structural and functional measures from the MRI data. This advanced technology can detect subtle patterns of aging that might be missed by traditional analysis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The team then calculated a metric called the “brain age gap.” This was done by subtracting the participant’s chronological age from their estimated brain age. A positive gap indicates that the brain appears older than expected for the person’s actual age. A negative gap suggests the brain appears younger and healthier. This metric serves as a proxy for general brain integrity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study also utilized blood samples collected at the beginning of the research period. The investigators measured several biomarkers of systemic inflammation, including C-reactive protein and white blood cell counts. These markers were combined into a composite inflammation score. This score allowed the team to test if inflammation in the body explained the link between diet and brain changes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The results revealed a significant association between dietary habits and brain aging. Individuals who consumed the most pro-inflammatory diets had a larger brain age gap compared to those who ate anti-inflammatory diets. Specifically, those in the most pro-inflammatory group had brains that appeared about half a year older on average than those in the healthiest diet group. This suggests that poor dietary quality may accelerate the biological clock of the brain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This association was dependent on the age of the participants. The link between a pro-inflammatory diet and older brain age was much stronger in adults aged 60 and older. In this older demographic, a pro-inflammatory diet was associated with an advanced brain age of nearly a full year. This implies that older adults might be more vulnerable to the negative effects of a poor diet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers also found that systemic inflammation played a measurable role in this relationship. Statistical analysis showed that the composite inflammation score accounted for about 8 percent of the association between diet and brain age. This finding provides evidence that pro-inflammatory foods may harm the brain in part by increasing overall inflammation in the body. The remaining effect is likely due to other mechanisms not captured by the inflammation score.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Genetic risk factors were also considered in the analysis. The researchers looked at polygenic risk scores for Alzheimer’s disease and the presence of the APOE4 gene. The association between diet and brain age was generally consistent regardless of genetic risk. However, the link appeared somewhat stronger in individuals who were not carriers of the APOE4 gene. This suggests that diet remains a relevant factor for brain health across different genetic profiles.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These findings align with previous research showing that healthy diets support cognitive function. Diets like the Mediterranean or MIND diet emphasize the same anti-inflammatory foods identified in this study. These include plant-based foods rich in polyphenols and healthy fats. The current study adds to the literature by using a global measure of brain structure rather than focusing on specific regions like the hippocampus.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“We found that those eating more pro-inflammatory diets had a significantly larger brain age gap – meaning they had an older, less healthy brain than would be expected based on their chronological age,” Dunk told PsyPost. “Those consuming the most pro-inflammatory diets had an advanced brain age by half a year compared to those with the most anti-inflammatory diets. This association was stronger in adults 60 years of age or older, suggesting that older adults may benefit most from an anti-inflammatory diet.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“We were also able to confirm that systemic inflammation partially accounted for this association, by using a composite score of several inflammatory markers in the blood. In other words, those consuming more pro-inflammatory diets tended to have higher levels of circulating inflammatory biomarkers, which were in turn associated with older brain age. This finding suggests that an anti-inflammatory diet could potentially support brain health in part by promoting lower levels of inflammation in the body.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But there are some limitations to this study. The UK Biobank participants are generally healthier and wealthier than the average population. This selection bias might affect how well the results apply to the general public. The study is also observational in nature. It can show a connection between diet and brain age but cannot definitively prove that diet causes the aging.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another limitation involves the dietary assessment method. Self-reported data is subject to memory errors and may not perfectly reflect actual intake. Additionally, the Dietary Inflammatory Index focuses on nutrients rather than whole foods. People consume complex combinations of foods, not isolated nutrients. However, the index is a validated tool that generally correlates well with healthy eating patterns.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The Dietary Inflammatory Index is calculated based on a person’s consumption of a variety of macronutrients, micronutrients, whole foods, and spices,” Dunk noted. “Because this index isn’t primarily based on whole foods, it might not be immediately obvious what a pro- or anti-inflammatory diet actually looks like.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Some of the anti-inflammatory components include dietary fiber (found in whole plant foods), omega 3 fats, onion, garlic, ginger, turmeric, green and black tea, isoflavones (soy), polyphenols (especially high in berries), and many vitamins and minerals. On the other hand, foods high in saturated fat, trans fat, or cholesterol tend to be pro-inflammatory.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“This scoring is generally consistent with healthy dietary patterns we often hear about – like the Mediterranean, MIND, or whole food plant-based diets. Each of these dietary patterns are high in healthy plant foods (fruits, vegetables, whole grains, legumes, nuts, seeds) and limit foods like red and processed meat, deep-fried and ultraprocessed foods, and other animal-based foods to varying degrees, which are higher in saturated fat and cholesterol.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Future research is needed to confirm these findings in more diverse populations. It would be beneficial to investigate whether switching to an anti-inflammatory diet can reverse accelerated brain aging. Clinical trials could provide stronger evidence of a causal relationship. For now, the results suggest that choosing anti-inflammatory foods may be a practical strategy for maintaining brain health as we age.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study, “&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1007/s10654-025-01318-6" target="_blank"&gt;The association between a pro-inflammatory diet and brain age in middle-aged and older adults&lt;/a&gt;,” was authored by Michelle M. Dunk, Huijie Huang, Jiao Wang, Abigail Dove, Sakura Sakakibara, Jie Guo, Adrián Carballo-Casla, David A. Bennett, and Weili Xu.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>PsyPost</author><pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 11:04:16 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMingFBVV95cUxORzlWVnRudUMySFNsaFhTSlRrMnlUNE9hdy1BN0RLaDVObFJ0NVhnT1dqeEVORUZmN0d4NjVGUjA0c25mWGNpUnFQaFZNaVpWdld5N0hHTC1NZkFRVHFMN19jblY3SmNFR2l3YUl5OFFiekRVYmdkbjJydUJqZUdUSGc4R1lQbVZRaks5UmdYRHowY0lxTjhDN3FxYTJKUQ</guid></item><item><title>“皮肤癌集群”的Pa.区域部位- PennLive.com</title><link>https://www.pennlive.com/life/2025/11/pa-area-site-of-skin-cancer-cluster.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content   "&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="MBVHZELWMRBXPLZWSGZ53U6DNA"&gt;Researchers at&lt;a href="https://www.pennlive.com/health/" target="_blank" rel=""&gt; the Penn State Cancer Institute&lt;/a&gt; have been analyzing cancer registry data from over the past five years or so.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-1" data-gaid="inarticle-1"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="E2VDW2S37JH3ZIONELXNKK5AQM"&gt;What they found is that there’s a &lt;a href="https://www.pennlive.com/" rel="" target="_blank"&gt;15-county &lt;/a&gt;stretch in Pennsylvania where adults of a certain age have a higher chance of getting melanoma.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-2" data-gaid="inarticle-2"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="6QKRHVLZSRDAFORAEBZN7WQ5KU"&gt;Published last week, &lt;a href="https://www.psu.edu/news/research/story/skin-cancer-cluster-found-15-pennsylvania-counties-or-near-farmland" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;the report&lt;/a&gt; — published in &lt;a href="https://ascopubs.org/doi/10.1200/CCI-25-00160" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;the JCO Clinical Cancer Informatics&lt;/a&gt; — states that this “skin cancer cluster” is situated in the south central region of the state. This includes Lycoming and York counties, among others. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-3" data-gaid="inarticle-3"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="VRPCFACXGREDTJN5LBUXO2SWGQ"&gt;It’s in this cluster that those over the age of 50 have a 57 percent higher likelihood of developing the disease. It also involves both rural and metropolitan areas, indicating that these cases are not necessarily confined to remote places or those with the most outdoor exposure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-4" data-gaid="inarticle-4"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="XYPEHTEEYZBURIV2ARJR3X2YX4"&gt;“Melanoma is often associated with beaches and sunbathing, but our findings suggest that agricultural environments may also place a role,” said associate professor of dermatology at Penn State Health and study co-author, Charlene Lam, via press release. “And this isn’t just about farmers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-5" data-gaid="inarticle-5"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="5SARJ3YDSBC2FBGGZAAEUYOZJA"&gt;“Entire communities living near agriculture, people who never set foot in a field, may still be at risk.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-6" class="middleParagraph" data-gaid="inarticle-6"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="TMTEX7S4EFHOLLFAPD42PFIXZM"&gt;As for why this might be happening, sunlight, of course, has been considered as a factor. So, too, have cultivated cropland and herbicide usage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-7" data-gaid="inarticle-7"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="ONFJD5C5FJFGBN33Z2Y5RT3UHM"&gt;“Pesticides and herbicides are designed to alter biological systems,” explained emeritus professor of public health sciences at the school and the paper’s senior author. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-8" data-gaid="inarticle-8"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="432YZLZYYBEBRLJ2GSBLWEIHQM"&gt;“Some of those same mechanisms, like increasing photosensitivity or causing oxidative stress, could theoretically contribute to melanoma development.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-9" data-gaid="inarticle-9"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="JET2METT2NBH7G3PPJR6AN4EO4"&gt;Lam added that she lops to better understand these factors in relation to public health. And encourages everyone to get their annual skin check. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-10" data-gaid="inarticle-10"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-enter:VIQEJ3AIPZAN3GX7EWUYVMZ324" data-fusion-component="VIQEJ3AIPZAN3GX7EWUYVMZ324"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-exit:VIQEJ3AIPZAN3GX7EWUYVMZ324" data-fusion-component="VIQEJ3AIPZAN3GX7EWUYVMZ324"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-11" data-gaid="inarticle-11"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--center skimlinks"&gt;If you purchase a product or register for an account through a link on our site, we may receive compensation.&lt;span&gt; By using this site, you consent to our &lt;a href="https://www.advancelocal.com/advancelocalUserAgreement/user-agreement.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;User Agreement&lt;/a&gt; and agree that your clicks, interactions, and personal information may be collected, recorded, and/or stored by us and social media and other third-party partners in accordance with our &lt;a href="https://www.advancelocal.com/advancelocalUserAgreement/privacy-policy.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Privacy Policy.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>PennLive.com</author><pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 10:11:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihAFBVV95cUxPcHgwelRXNllrQmhVZzVwSXpyejgwemxEc1I5SWV1MVMyRm1xYnRmM3VtdlFhallOaE1sc1JMV3ZTdUphblo0YVB3NzBKVzRYVTJEbjFFbGk0NmIxWE5mamswNmlwU2JOQ0Etem5SelVGQXBIdFdzWklZeEJjYl8wWF8wa0jSAZgBQVVfeXFMT0FlbEJNd3BkaVlySTlnQlhCdkhOS1dIamk5Yk55TW9PQnkzZDVFcXU1eVU3MmNXRlc2VmhHY1lzUm9sODc3M2txdUtudUVfbjl6TkhVdXdRakhpRmloQUd2TFJSeW44cXlWNXBLaF9uNEx0RGZEdEVkUEl6T3Z2MkxLb1Fpd3J2VXJfN0FTMW5mYjdreEZ5RFk</guid></item><item><title>卫生部门称，华盛顿州居民死于首例确诊的H5N5禽流感病例-路透社</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/washington-state-resident-dies-first-confirmed-h5n5-bird-flu-case-health-2025-11-22/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Reuters</author><pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 09:58:03 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi3AFBVV95cUxNQzdhRXBDNmpKdEFwbGp3RGtCWlVlMXRCS3dBMko0Q3FFMy1IVXd6QmJqUE1leFYzSXZNelc2anJDY1o2OGRVbHVMOVNpYkhzZUF1bUllLXhiRThyZDctX2JTR1lYSUlBTnZOTENfWVlsblA3REdYMjE1dXE1RFJfSDdPMVBZWVpLemc0dHgzZlEzVVVJVFVhc3NCcHJLNW9JTmhlMjlpZnV2blpLMmMzZzVXTVE0ZExMOEUtSlEyXzJibHBrRGNSeEJWVmEzNjFNS1VvS3ZWcDQycGhf</guid></item><item><title>大便中出现的结直肠癌的4个早期预警迹象-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/4-early-warning-signs-of-colorectal-cancer-that-appear-in-poop/articleshow/125444726.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Colorectal cancer is increasingly recognised as a major public health challenge, with rising incidence rates not only in older adults but also among younger populations. Despite its prevalence, early-stage CRC frequently remains asymptomatic, or manifests through subtle gastrointestinal changes that are easily attributed to benign causes. According to a &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jamanetworkopen/fullarticle/2819248" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;study in JAMA Network&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, some symptoms are associated with early-onset colorectal cancer. Take a closer look...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="5"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="6"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Why early detection is crucial&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="7"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to the American Cancer Society, the 5‑year relative survival rate for colorectal cancer diagnosed when the disease is localized, i.e. has not spread, is about 90%, but this drops sharply when diagnosed at later stages to around 73% for regional spread and around 13% for distant metastases. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="9"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="lOvcW vdo_embedd"&gt;&lt;div class="k7lcu"&gt;&lt;p class="efT4r"&gt;Cancer is curable if detected early: Signs to pay attention to&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="11"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Early detection of colorectal cancer isn’t just a technical benefit, it massively improves the chances of survival, lowers recurrence risk, and offers a real shot at a cure. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="15"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="17"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Here are evidence-based early warning signs of colorectal cancer that appear in stool. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="19"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;1. Pencil thin or narrow stool&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="21"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;A sudden and persistent shift to thin, ribbon-like, or pencil-thin stools could be a red flag. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="23"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to the&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cancer.org/cancer/types/colon-rectal-cancer/detection-diagnosis-staging/signs-and-symptoms.html" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;American Cancer Society&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, a change in stool caliber that lasts more than a few days may indicate a tumour narrowing the passage. Physiologically, as per &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.mayoclinic.org/diseases-conditions/colon-cancer/in-depth/colon-cancer-stool/art-20586915" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;Mayo Clinic&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, when a tumour grows on the inner wall of the colon or rectum, it can constrict the space through which stool passes, leading to thinner stools. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="30"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;2. Mucus in the stool&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The intestines naturally produce a small amount of mucus to lubricate the colon lining. But a noticeable increase in slime or jelly-like substance coating stool can be a warning sign.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="33"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Medical guidelines from &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/books/NBK279199/" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;NCBI&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;also list “bleeding or secreting mucus” from the back passage as one of the signs to monitor. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="37"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="39"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;3. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Blood in stool&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="42"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="43"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The presence of blood in stool, either bright red or dark, tarry, is one of the most recognized early warning signs of colorectal cancer. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.mayoclinic.org/diseases-conditions/colon-cancer/in-depth/colon-cancer-stool/art-20586915" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;Clinical studies&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; indicate that up to 50–60% of early-stage CRC patients present with some form of rectal bleeding.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="48"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Importantly, while hemorrhoids, anal fissures, and gastrointestinal infections can also cause bleeding, persistent or recurrent blood in stool, especially when accompanied by other CRC warning signs, warrants immediate medical evaluation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="50"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;4. Persistent diarrhoea or constipation &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="52"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="53"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Changes in bowel habits, such as persistent diarrhea, constipation, or alternating patterns, can be an early indicator of colorectal cancer. According to &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.moffitt.org/cancers/colorectal-cancer/signs-symptoms/" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;MOFFITT cancer center&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, adults over 50 presenting with sustained changes in bowel habits are at higher risk for colorectal neoplasia, making this symptom an important cue for early evaluation. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="58"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Although dietary changes, infections, and irritable bowel syndrome are more common causes, the persistence of these symptoms should prompt timely diagnostic testing such as colonoscopy. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="60"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="61"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Younger adults are facing higher risk of &lt;keyword id="12135154" type="General" weightage="100" keywordseo="Colon-cancer" source="Orion"&gt;colon cancer&lt;/keyword&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="62"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;A major &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2024/12/241211190108.htm" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;epidemiological analysis&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;published in The Lancet Oncology shows that early‑onset colorectal cancer rates are increasing in 27 out of 50 countries, between the age of 25 to 49. Lifestyle factors are also implicated. According to &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.mdpi.com/2227-9059/13/7/1572" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;MDPI&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, early antibiotic use, consuming ultra-processed diets, and obesity are emerging as important risk contributors. Researchers warn that shifting dietary patterns, reduced physical activity, and rising metabolic disorders may further accelerate this trend if not addressed early.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="68"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="em" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Disclaimer: This article is intended for general informational purposes only and is not a substitute for professional medical advice, diagnosis, or treatment.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 09:08:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi9AFBVV95cUxPTDVRaldMMVJvdnBjUDZENWNpSjFXdXB1bDZtOFJyUE93OWZJdENWNXNvZUNoSFFOY2RxNmJkdHc2dmxuQVkyR0dCeXh1eFRpamM0VUhOZ0pnazdIcWwzSkZQeU5RNGhxREFnOWh2LWN6MVZFQ2FDcC04NWFqUkVqa2xaQldLRW5MY1g2ajRnZFNOUGNaRENfWlNHVGs1bkpVckRvbnF2ZUo1YUxxRF9wMHlIdW16a1dEd2VuV0FraUtEVGFvZEVCM0RKSGhhY2dEYmcyZkhmLXN6WDItYVBrSWk2VllrUVZBMmZ0TGhsMkRSNnlk</guid></item><item><title>最初难以识别的胃癌的5个警告标志-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/5-warning-signs-of-stomach-cancer-that-are-difficult-to-recognise-at-first/photostory/125500687.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="COQxt" data-ua-type="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;The first signs of stomach cancer manifest as mild stomach discomfort, which patients experience in their upper abdominal region. The abdominal pain from stomach cancer starts as a dull sensation, which moves between different locations, and feels like pressure instead of sharp pain. People commonly treat this symptom as heartburn, ulcers or muscle strain. Medical studies demonstrate that stomach cancer warning signs include ongoing abdominal pain, which intensifies, while patients experience bloating and feel full after eating. Medical professionals should perform early medical tests to identify stomach cancer before the pain reaches severe or persistent levels.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These initial warning signs present as mild symptoms, which most people identify as typical digestive issue, thus making their identification challenging. Patients who experience ongoing indigestion, early satiety, nausea, unexplained weight loss or abdominal pain, should seek medical help when their symptoms do not improve or worsen. The detection of stomach cancer at its early stages, leads to better treatment results and increased patient survival rates, so patients need to monitor these hard-to-detect symptoms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Disclaimer: This article is informational only and not a substitute for medical advice&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 08:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi8wFBVV95cUxPWHFjSTVtd1VwQVZHUkhfN3Y0MkNxWndWTkdYekozaWFNT2h3cFlTTEJISzV3RDNVYjlqMGJ1dDdUM3Q4LUtKeUdSSTdSY2dkUkc1aUFjV1hBYks5NnMtRHlHS0Z6aFpDSDN4TXQwLUdIb2RQQjhPZVZyclhkUlZQcHc3TkJjMDkzZG5HRmQ4T3ZyQzZ0b1pyME90WnR4X1JIR1lRUTBtRzVuOGZSUklKQkdwWl82NDcxLWREMThBNXJoN0FEcGdIZkx4YnE4YXVvRVJlenhDN3N0Q0FkZ09KQUxwTk5HWXVUVzlpQnY1X0pKUk3SAfsBQVVfeXFMTWZoMVVPdWd0V3ZjeGhWZXhrUmM2LWlrdzNDTzlFbmkwWW5OZ3hjcmpHeldjWEo4ME90bzFOVTM0TlRReVFHbG5Jc0tkb3Y1WHVlal9DMmhiNGszSnItOF9yeVZscmY5alItLWtNNVY5b3E3a1NPbUxNbFhjcE4xX1JhSWs0X2NPaG8yN0ZYTm1wY1hzTjk5SkhWZC12c3lYMVgtMTM1MzNtOEFEMC1QbV9FYVFfQWdVeGtvN3NpbE5Rai1QZDRSSDNoMEdkRnJKQUE1ZXc2YUlsN1lZTGxWaThZSF9ReUV2MWJ6ekRWVDBFbTN2ckVCLUFrTm8</guid></item><item><title>顶级心脏病专家揭示了导致心脏病发作次数最多的一个早晨习惯-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/top-cardiologist-reveals-the-one-morning-habit-that-causes-the-maximum-number-of-heart-attacks-within-the-first-10-minutes-of-waking-up-not-food-or-stress/articleshow/125386959.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most heart attacks happen in the early morning hours, between 6 and 10 a.m., and the reasons go beyond traditional risk factors like cholesterol or age. Dr. Heigl, a senior cardiologist at Vienna General Hospital, who studied over 12,000 cardiac cases, points to how people start their day abruptly as a key trigger for heart attacks, that includes the science behind morning cardiac events, the role of cortisol and nervous system stress. Let’s see how…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="3"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Why morning is the riskiest time&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="5"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to Dr. Heigl, most heart attacks happen between 6:00 and 10:00 a.m - not because of breakfast or weather, but because of a single act: abrupt stimulation. He said, “It starts with the first ten minutes after waking-how violently people enter their own day. People wake up and flood their system,” he said. “They reach for the phone, switch on blue light, read stress before oxygen. The body hasn’t even synchronized blood pressure yet-and they shock it with urgency.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="11"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="lOvcW vdo_embedd"&gt;&lt;div class="k7lcu"&gt;&lt;p class="efT4r"&gt;India's Silent Killer: Heart Surgeon Unmasks Root Cause Of Heart Attack Crisis&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="13"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="15"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Why this happens&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="17"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Multiple &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.news-medical.net/news/20250423/Researchers-uncover-link-between-heart-attack-severity-and-circadian-rhythm.aspx" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;studies&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; show a spike in heart attacks in the early morning hours. This period coincides with a natural rise in blood pressure, heart rate, and cortisol (the stress hormone) due to the body’s internal clock or circadian rhythm. These physiological changes increase the strain on the heart and the likelihood of artery blockages, plaque rupture, and cardiac events. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Research from diverse populations confirms the highest rates of heart attacks occur between 6 a.m. and 10 a.m., with some studies citing as much as a 40% higher risk compared to other times.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="24"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Cortisol’s role in morning heart stress&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="26"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cortisol, as we know is the stress hormone, that can raise blood pressure and heart during mental or emotional stress. The cortisol surge lowers heart rate variability. Dr. Heigl, showed data from continuous ECG monitors: in patients with cardiac &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://my.clevelandclinic.org/health/articles/22187-cortisol" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;events&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, heart rate variability dropped sharply within minutes of waking. The trigger wasn’t effort-it was cortisol spikes caused by instant mental engagement. “The nervous system needs five calm minutes to reenter gravity,” Heigl said. “But we hand it a war instead.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="32"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;What should one do instead&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="34"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr. Heigl says, “Don’t open the day. Let the day open you.” He teaches his patients to stay horizontal for three slow breaths, sit up gradually, drink water before words, and delay screens by ten minutes. After six weeks, 70% of patients showed lower morning blood pressure and improved vagal tone- a direct shield against cardiac stress.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="38"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Heart attacks,” he said, “aren’t just plumbing failures. They’re scheduling errors.” So the next time your alarm goes off, remember: it’s not the day that kills the heart -it’s how abruptly we force it to start running.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="40"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="42"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Practical tips to protect your heart in the morning&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="44"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="45"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;• Avoid checking your phone or engaging in stressful mental activities immediately after waking.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;• Take at least 5 minutes to wake gently with slow breathing and gradual movement.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;• Stay hydrated by drinking water before caffeine or food.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;• Follow a calm morning routine that eases your body into activity.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;These small, mindful changes can significantly lower early-morning cardiac stress and reduce heart attack risk, especially for people with hypertension, diabetes, or existing heart disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="47"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="49"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Times of India</author><pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 06:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi3wJBVV95cUxQQVF6WEk2Q1pEeERpWFZheTh5cVBBd3pGMlVBNWw5TzUzWm83TnBsN0VocEJEWDhDRFJxd0R4d2s5eGJJSm0wZFUzVVJyUFVFRDZPSmt3ZkdxbnBmbU5zcHRiSkVZMUt6Vk1iZHFNMFVESmE3MVdRNl9NbjU3ODZoUExDbkFKdVNBaERoT0k1QUZBSkJzdGJoSUhLSkxMNElDQV9aZjU1cVF3R3U3Ul9kN21WR0lSeEM4a3c3NGt5TWtRM3BRdlNyOHd1NXNJdnFvNEJ0Yk1kQ1JzaVpLRHRxblE1dEhrSVAtdDU0UmZHSm9sdnE3bTlEWDFGQUpYRU9HYmtrZjlmOFdTZXFxZzBvdlg4dXVvdzVkR1FHaDk4TUxQX1k4LUNTNXJQbTVXWTdKN3F5TGh0blpzbDJhaGdocGljWU9sTUQyNjVNbkRURU5YYllkZUhISjgwT2NHNkk</guid></item><item><title>华盛顿州居民被认为是第一个死于罕见禽流感的人-美联社新闻</title><link>https://apnews.com/article/bird-flu-infection-washington-h5n5-c8148b46cf9cc8a4f1e5562923086298</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="LeaderBoardAd-Mobile "&gt;
                                    
                                        
                                            
                                        
                                    
                                &lt;/p&gt;
                            
                            
                                
                                
                                    &lt;div class="RichTextStoryBody RichTextBody"&gt;
                                        &lt;p&gt;GRAYS HARBOR COUNTY, Wash. (AP) — A Washington state resident is believed to be the first person to die from a &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://apnews.com/article/bird-flu-infection-washington-h5n5-b8921d13aa7d96330654a960f80453c3"&gt;rare strain of bird flu&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;, but state health officials said Friday the risk to the public is low.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The person, an older adult with underlying health conditions, was being treated for a bird flu called H5N5 after becoming seemingly the first known human infected by the strain, according to a statement from the Washington State Department of Health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The person from Grays Harbor County, about 78 miles (125 kilometers) southwest of Seattle, had a backyard flock of domestic poultry that had been exposed to wild birds, health officials said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The risk to the public remains low,” the statement from state health officials said. “No other people involved have tested positive for avian influenza.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Health officials said they will monitor anyone who came in close contact with the person, but “there is no evidence of transmission of this virus between people.”&lt;/p&gt;
    
&lt;p&gt;Earlier this month, the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention issued a statement about the infection that said no information would suggest “the risk to public health has increased as a result of this case.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;H5N5 is not believed to be a greater threat to human health than the H5N1 virus behind a wave of 70 reported human infections in the U.S. in 2024 and 2025. Most of those have been mild illnesses in workers on dairy and poultry farms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="optimizelyHubpeekId" class="optimizelyHubpeekClass"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The distinction between H5N5 and H5N1 lies in a protein involved in releasing the virus from an infected cell and promoting spread to surrounding cells.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;___&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This story has been corrected to remove references stating the person who died was a man. Officials have not released the person’s gender.&lt;/p&gt;
                                    &lt;/div&gt;
                                
                            

                            
                    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>AP News</author><pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 05:54:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimgFBVV95cUxPZEs3MWNIa255QVE2Q2M0QXM0b0lfdVpSdi01d2xYcnJ1MDNVeUxjWUtOUUk4MDNaTExlc0NLbW11MlJGcFpHR3J4U2gwREtzUkV5cTRaVGk0OXdBTmg1dzUwb1pHUy0yS3VLRXFybGhNU19xbkplS25NS0l6NG1pMGVINkc5dTNiSEpoTnJWTTBEOE5UZDlVeEd3</guid></item><item><title>肯尼迪说，他告诉疾病预防控制中心改变网站关于自闭症和疫苗的语言- KSL.com</title><link>https://www.ksl.com/article/51409008/kennedy-says-he-told-cdc-to-change-websites-language-on-autism-and-vaccines</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="articleContainer"&gt;&lt;p&gt;WASHINGTON — Health Secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr. said in an interview with the New York Times that he personally instructed the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention to change its long-standing position that vaccines do not cause autism.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Countering decades of science showing vaccines to be safe, the public health agency's website was changed to say, "The claim 'vaccines do not cause autism' is not an evidence-based claim because studies have not ruled out the possibility that infant vaccines cause autism."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the interview, Kennedy said that while the large-scale epidemiological studies of the measles, mumps and rubella vaccine had found no link to autism, and that studies of the mercury-based preservative thimerosal had also shown no link, there are gaps in the vaccine safety science.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The whole thing about 'vaccines have been tested and there's been this determination made,' is just a lie," Kennedy said in his first interview with a major print publication.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kennedy is a longtime vaccine skeptic and not a scientist. Before he took up his role as head of Health and Human Services, the CDC was a key opponent of growing global anti-vaccine sentiment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The phrase 'vaccines do not cause autism' is not supported by science," Kennedy said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Public health experts, doctors and scientists have decried &lt;a href="https://www.ksl.com/article/51408073" rel="follow" target="_blank"&gt;the update&lt;/a&gt; as the kind of misinformation the CDC has fought for decades as it promoted the use of lifesaving childhood vaccines both in the U.S. and abroad.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The World Health Organization and other health agencies around the world have repeatedly said evidence shows vaccines do not cause autism.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Many large-scale studies in hundreds of thousands of children across the world have thoroughly investigated the claim that vaccines cause autism and found no link between vaccines and autism. Based on existing evidence, vaccines do not cause autism," the European Centre for Disease Prevention and Control said on Thursday.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the interview, Kennedy said he ordered the CDC to change its guidance in part because high-quality large studies had not been conducted to examine a potential link between autism and other shots given in the first year of life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Those include the hepatitis B vaccine and a combination shot that protects against diphtheria, tetanus and pertussis, commonly known as whooping cough.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A revamped committee that advises the CDC on vaccine policy is scheduled to meet early next month to consider new recommendations for hepatitis B vaccines.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kennedy also said he had spoken with Sen. Bill Cassidy, who disagreed with the decision, about the website changes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="kt_disclaimer"&gt;
                                    The Key Takeaways for this article were generated with the assistance of large language models and reviewed by our editorial team. The article, itself, is solely human-written.
                                &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>KSL.com</author><pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 04:49:32 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMisgFBVV95cUxPRHdyTUxuSU94RGgzeXNvbWlMdXNING9aNWxFdHp6cVdYZjhTNVVYdnNrVXg5X0t3MHRpX0xaSlUwalRTWGpMSWVWM1Z3Y1F4MzJHeE8xamZPTXVyRE5tRTdHOVhTX1VlYzRJYUxnUFFxY1ZCSkhlaHVGZ3FHTGRxZzdzYWJjT3VZZllYcy1KcGVtMXNSMGkybEZnWllVWjNEYkY5UzJQRVQ2YXdnRmd5S2pR</guid></item><item><title>你很少注意到的最致命的癌症：医生解释为什么胰腺癌如此难以捕捉-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/the-deadliest-cancer-you-rarely-notice-doctor-explains-why-pancreatic-cancer-is-so-hard-to-catch/articleshow/125479473.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pancreatic cancer is quietly becoming a major global worry. According to the IARC (the WHO’s cancer research arm), about 510,000 people were diagnosed in 2022, and nearly 470,000 died from it the same year, making it one of the most deadly cancers around. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="3"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;What’s especially concerning? The number of new cases has more than doubled in recent decades. And unlike some cancers, pancreatic cancer is notoriously hard to detect early, which means many people are diagnosed only when it’s already advanced. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="5"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="lOvcW vdo_embedd"&gt;&lt;div class="k7lcu"&gt;&lt;p class="efT4r"&gt;Cancer is curable if detected early: Signs to pay attention to&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="7"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;This isn’t just a problem in wealthy countries, incidence is rising globally, including in low- and middle-income regions. Plus, risk factors like aging populations, diabetes, obesity, and tobacco use are contributing to this alarming trend. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="11"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Because pancreatic cancer has such a poor prognosis (very low survival rates), health experts are sounding the alarm. We at TOI spoke to &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Dr. Ganesh Nagarajan&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;, Senior Director - Hepatobiliary Pancreatic &amp;amp; Gastrointestinal Oncosurgery, Institute of Cancer Care, Nanavati Max Hospital, Mumbai about pancreatic cancer and what makes this disease a silent killer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="15"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="16"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Pancreatic cancer is often described as a “silent killer.” What makes this disease so difficult to detect early?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pancreatic cancer is known as a ‘silent killer,’ due to the lack of distinctive warning signs. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As pancreas are located deep in the abdomen, there are no visible lumps. Some people experience vague symptoms such as mild stomach discomfort, back pain, tiredness, loss of appetite or minor weight loss, which cannot directly indicate cancer. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="20"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;At least at present, we do not have simple diagnostic tests that can detect pancreatic cancer at an early or curable stage and very early tumours are usually too small to be visible on standard imaging. As a result, patients get diagnosed at advanced stages of cancer when it has already blocked the bile duct, leading to jaundice, or has spread to nearby or distant organs, in which case, surgery is no longer possible. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="24"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Are you seeing a rise in pancreatic cancer cases in recent years, and if so, what factors are driving this trend?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="26"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The number of pancreatic cancer cases have been steadily rising globally, specially in western countries. With a general lifespan increasing, more individuals reach the age groups where pancreatic cancer is more common. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="30"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Moreover, rising sedentary habits such as cigarette smoking, alcohol, obesity, low or no physical activity and specific dietary patterns, high in saturated fats and processed meats and minimum consumption of fruits and vegetables are also somewhat linked to rising cases of pancreatic cancer. Chronic type 2 diabetes and pancreatitis may raise the risk of developing cancer as well, and heavy alcohol use can contribute indirectly by causing chronic pancreatitis. Altogether, these risk-factors are responsible for an estimated 30% of pancreatic cancer cases, which points out that lifestyle-modifications are very important. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="34"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="35"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What are the biggest misconceptions people still have about pancreatic cancer?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The most common misconception is that pancreatic cancer has no connection to lifestyle. While in many cases, a direct correlation is not possible to establish; smoking, obesity, low physical activity, certain dietary habits, chronic pancreatitis and long-term diabetes are considered as high risk factors for developing all types of cancer, including pancreatic cases. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="38"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Secondly, people don’t usually connect jaundice, severe pain or major weight loss to the cancer, until the tumour is at an advanced stage. This is why it’s important that senior citizens with such unexplained symptoms should get themselves checked and not ignore them. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="40"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="41"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Is pancreatic cancer hereditary?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While there is no proven scientific causality indicating pancreatic cancers to be inherited, the family history does matter. Patients do report at least one close relative with pancreatic cancer, indicating possible higher risk as compared to the general population. Some inherited genetic syndromes may also increase the risk of pancreatic cancer, especially when compared with those who do not carry such a mutation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="45"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="46"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Are there any high-risk groups who should undergo preventive screening even without symptoms?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As discussed there is no specific screening tool for pancreatic cancer due to the low overall lifetime risk. However, there are some high-risk groups who have comparatively a higher chance of developing the cancer than general population such as: &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="48"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Familial pancreatic cancer history with multiple close relatives. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="51"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Inherited high risk gene mutations, such as BRCA2, PALB2, CDKN2A (p16), STK11, ATM, PRSS1. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="53"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Moreover, it is advisable to control the modifiable risk factors like smoking, alcohol intake or obesity to reduce the chances of developing any type of cancers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Times of India</author><pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 04:44:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiogJBVV95cUxNc0dackZURjROUU1uUURGaE82VnNVSGQxY21hTUxjbjI3ZnZUTmVYVzk0bUU4T0k2RG5jZExGV19IcTZtVzNlRTNNU3JPdGtmU0h3VXJIVU01QXl1SWNicmJFOUdGdHJXc29oTVRjV0dwM0g1SG14TkhYclFVTHBlWW9TRjdsVmQtV1NfYjc2MWV5ZFJsNE1ZU050azZxSXk3SC1nYzhxZ0FNVklqaU9GWlRzZ2JjdEFXdm1lRE13dGZHR1BSallXRDBCRTdLYVl0UGlhamtCeWxNSnhOSTlHREtTcTk2U2RJWGpuMnBoWnE0cDVVS1hMYzQ1d1lGUF8tSk1iQURiRG1Ta0lpWlZ2X3VKR3VhajlzRUt3VU1BVUFIUdIBpwJBVV95cUxOdXJNenZjVTlLQnM0dXVoVXlJOUlFVllCdTE5U2dwY0xsU2dwa2JaVlc4MkdXQ1hzUExqUGVxNEFIQnVSaXdzMkMtc2QtRW1FU3JnQS1BaTBoV21MOEY3MGFhUlpuY3FTdHZQazc5NjA5a0k0Y1YxTU40a0lsSTYybzFkQ3lfZE9Idm5TRjNjcEJRMGlCQnBHRlpjTUVzRGxfX2lXeVhOU2dYOVJXWmpXeWVmM3NIaFNKcmdlMV9XdWVsY1l2S0J6eFItcWtRVUROeHhwblM4TFl0Sjh3anJWNWdlOTNTc2dYM2FuVnV6NUhTdjBvRk5nUDI5c1FwNmZ0RG9QYW05TnE4M0p4SlY5MS12RENGck9DM01zWTJSNmtRZ1prU09R</guid></item><item><title>禽流感：罕见H5N5病毒株首次在美国死亡-卫报</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/world/2025/nov/22/bird-flu-first-death-h5n5-strain-us</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body-commercial-selector article-body-viewer-selector dcr-hdpgoq"&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;A person in the US is believed to be the first human to die from a rare strain of &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/bird-flu" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;bird flu&lt;/a&gt;, but state health officials said on Friday the risk to the public is low.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The person in &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/washington-state" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;Washington&lt;/a&gt; state, an older adult with underlying health conditions, was being treated for a bird flu strain called H5N5 after becoming seemingly the first known human infected by the strain, according to a statement from the Washington State Department of Health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="sign-in-gate"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The patient had been in hospital with the disease since early November after developing a high fever, confusion and respiratory problems, health officials said earlier.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The person – from Grays Harbor county, about 78 miles (125km) south-west of &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/seattle" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;Seattle&lt;/a&gt; – had a backyard flock of domestic poultry that had been exposed to wild birds, health officials said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="9ca100fe-52a6-4e07-bade-b6e5b82f0f17" data-spacefinder-role="richLink" data-spacefinder-type="model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.RichLinkBlockElement" class="dcr-47fhrn"&gt;&lt;gu-island name="RichLinkComponent" priority="feature" deferuntil="idle" props='{"richLinkIndex":4,"element":{"_type":"model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.RichLinkBlockElement","prefix":"Related: ","text":"Former CDC leaders condemn RFK Jr for endangering Americans’ health","elementId":"9ca100fe-52a6-4e07-bade-b6e5b82f0f17","role":"richLink","url":"https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2025/sep/01/former-cdc-officials-rfk-jr-endangering-americans-health"},"ajaxUrl":"https://api.nextgen.guardianapps.co.uk","format":{"design":0,"display":0,"theme":0}}'&gt;&lt;/gu-island&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“The risk to the public remains low,” the statement from state health officials said. “No other people involved have tested positive for avian influenza.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/society/health" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;Health&lt;/a&gt; officials said they would monitor anyone who came in close contact with the man, but “there is no evidence of transmission of this virus between people”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Earlier this month, the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention issued a statement about the infection that said no information would suggest “the risk to public health has increased as a result of this case”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;H5N5 is not believed to be a greater threat to human health than the H5N1 virus behind a wave of 70 reported human infections in the US in 2024 and 2025. Most of those have been mild illnesses in workers on dairy and &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2025/mar/28/bird-flu-us-poultry-farms-vaccines" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;poultry farms&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The distinction between H5N5 and H5N1 lies in a protein involved in releasing the virus from an infected cell and promoting spread to surrounding cells.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Guardian</author><pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 03:42:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiAFBVV95cUxPMFpZUFlZbWpranR0VzhuQTBuUzY1Y1hETnpBaWo3eUdBR1pLTU5HTkxqQkdaNm1GdXByZllwOGJEWmJoTU40QWQ4LVZHRnBKaE5QRkxFaGxudXkyY05sdXJubXI4d1FPQjBCUUZkRmwxVHVEaHBGNUNmcjViaWt6V3pMMExzSmhL</guid></item><item><title>华盛顿州居民死于新型H5N5禽流感-洛杉矶时报</title><link>https://www.latimes.com/science/story/2025-11-21/washington-state-resident-dies-of-new-h5n5-form-of-bird-flu</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div data-element="story-body" class="ct-rich-text-children font-cms-font-brand-text font-normal text-lg leading-7.75 [&amp;amp;_&amp;gt;p]:text-cms-story-body-color-text clearfix mb-10 md:max-w-170 md:mx-auto" data-subscriber-content&gt; &lt;p&gt;The first person infected with the H5N5 bird flu has died, according to health officials in Washington.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The person, who lived in Grays Harbor County, had been hospitalized earlier this month in Kings County, where Seattle is located.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Officials from the Washington State Department of Health did not release the person’s name, age or gender. According to a &lt;a class="link" href="https://doh.wa.gov/newsroom/grays-harbor-county-resident-tests-preliminarily-positive-avian-influenza" target="_blank"&gt;news release&lt;/a&gt; from Grays Harbor County health officials last week, the person was considered “older” and had underlying health conditions. Their symptoms included a high fever, confusion and trouble breathing. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The person had a backyard flock consisting of mixed domestic poultry.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Testing by the health department found virus in the “environment of the flock ... making exposure to the domestic poultry, their environment, or wild birds the most likely source of exposure for this patient.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Officials at the state’s health department said they were monitoring other people who were exposed to the flock and environment. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This particular strain of bird flu, H5N5, had never been seen in a person before. It appeared first in 2023, infecting birds and mammals in eastern Canada. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to &lt;a class="link" href="https://www.cell.com/cell-reports/fulltext/S2211-1247(24)00808-8" target="_blank"&gt;research published last year&lt;/a&gt; on the novel strain, some infected animals carried a key mutation in the virus that allows it to transfer more easily between mammals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Epidemiologists and virologists worry that avian influenza could generate a pandemic if allowed to spread and mutate. For instance, the H5N1 virus circulating in dairy cattle in North America &lt;a class="link" href="https://www.latimes.com/environment/story/2024-12-05/just-one-mutation-can-make-h5n1-a-threat-to-humans"&gt;is one mutation away&lt;/a&gt; from being able to spread easily between people.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Every time a bird flu virus infects a person, concerns grow that it could change, becoming more transmissible or more deadly. For instance, if a sickened person also has another flu virus replicating in their body, there’s concern the viruses could exchange genetic material. Just by having an opportunity to replicate and evolve millions of times in the human body, it could acquire deadly mutations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Health officials say the risk to the public remains low and that no other people involved have tested positive for avian influenza. They say there is no evidence of transmission of the virus between people, but they are monitoring anyone who was in close contact with the patient.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Los Angeles Times</author><pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 02:39:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMirAFBVV95cUxNY184WXQweVc4Uk9IUHl1MzhBaTVubTBmRUs2QTNPZ2ZBSmFaNmdhTnh5bDZiaTBEWW1ZeHRjZU5JU1JkVFdUSXhLOFhpbEI4Zi1zc3dpbFFTN1FyenVRTF9XLTVHdGZZY2pqV00zZTRQaEhhT2xPeGdLVTJHY0FLaGJJN2RoZDBqbV9YbzZmLU9yczZBSzl5QVNER3dIVXNJX2UwZ3Ixc0VuaDlm</guid></item><item><title>华盛顿居民死于人类从未报告过的禽流感病毒并发症- CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2025/11/21/health/washington-bird-flu-death</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article__content" data-editable="content" itemprop="articleBody" data-reorderable="content"&gt;
                
    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmi9lp3qj000x26qj2pithhh8@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            A Washington resident died of complications from an infection with a bird flu strain never before reported in humans, the state Department of Health said on Friday.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmi9mldq900083b6qgyj2dqqp@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The patient was an older adult with underlying health conditions who had been hospitalized and undergoing treatment for infection with H5N5 avian influenza.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmi9mldq900093b6q0mu8mpw2@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            It’s the first reported case of bird flu in a human in the US in nine months and only the second reported human death from the virus in the United States, but the US Centers for Disease Control and Prevention has said that the risk to the general public from the virus remains low.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmi9mldq9000a3b6qsu6ummey@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Officials continue to monitor others who were in close contact with the person, but no one else has tested positive for bird flu, and no evidence of human-to-human transmission has been found.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmi9mldq9000b3b6qvuzxqja6@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “The person had a backyard flock of mixed domestic birds,” the Washington State Department of Health said in &lt;a href="https://doh.wa.gov/newsroom/grays-harbor-county-resident-dies-complications-avian-influenza" target="_blank"&gt;a statement&lt;/a&gt;. “DOH sampling identified avian influenza virus in the environment of the flock, making exposure to the domestic poultry, their environment, or wild birds the most likely source of exposure for this patient.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmi9mldq9000c3b6q3fi93x27@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Bird flu has been infecting wild birds around the world for decades, but the latest US outbreak started in January 2022 and has featured more spread among mammals than in past years.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmi9mldq9000d3b6quizvx8rq@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Seventy other human cases of bird flu have been reported in the US as part of the outbreak, according to the CDC. Another elderly person with underlying conditions died in January after a bird flu infection.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmi9mldq9000e3b6q4ia8sboo@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Although a handful of cases have been severe, most people who have been infected have had mild illness, the CDC said, with symptoms like red eyes and fever.  The majority of those who have caught bird flu work closely with animals. There have been 41 cases in people who work with cattle and 24 cases among poultry workers. Two other cases have had some other animal exposure that the CDC does not list, and in three cases, the exposure was unknown.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmi9mldq9000f3b6qa6ajnuy7@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The CDC recommends that anyone who works closely with animals wear appropriate protective equipment and use caution around animal feces.  Officials also advise using caution when cleaning bird feeders or other areas exposed to bird feces. Avoid contact with sick or dead wildlife.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmi9mldq9000g3b6qnakkdg1i@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The Washington health department also recommends flu shots for anyone who may come into contact with domestic or wild birds. Although the regular influenza vaccine can’t protect against bird flu, it reduces the slight chance that someone could get sick with both viruses at once and cause the bird flu virus to mutate into something that would spread easily among humans.
    &lt;/p&gt;

              &lt;/div&gt;
                  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>CNN</author><pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 02:18:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMicEFVX3lxTE05Z21jQ1FMUDctcGk4T2R5RXZUZjZNVjJiN01KT2RaU0s1VE96bHYybUNoNTRiNFEybExsUWJOeEI0LWxLLVNKZUxabzQ3ZXBGQWpQNUM0UEQxWENfWFlDRDlTZW04cUM2S09HUmxGd3Y</guid></item><item><title>寒冷暴跌和康普茶：冬季健康趋势有效吗？ - BBC</title><link>https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/c5y4yk4nv5yo</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article&gt;&lt;p data-component="headline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 hNbOGD"&gt;&lt;h1 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 idLnWK"&gt;Cold plunges and kombucha: Do winter wellness trends really work?&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 eRlINq"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="hero-image" class="sc-5340b511-1 cMIbKV"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20251110-152207-94080fba49-web-2.33.2-3/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 gUePlo hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/2fe7/live/24239ce0-c637-11f0-a892-01d657345866.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/2fe7/live/24239ce0-c637-11f0-a892-01d657345866.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/2fe7/live/24239ce0-c637-11f0-a892-01d657345866.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/2fe7/live/24239ce0-c637-11f0-a892-01d657345866.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/2fe7/live/24239ce0-c637-11f0-a892-01d657345866.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/2fe7/live/24239ce0-c637-11f0-a892-01d657345866.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/2fe7/live/24239ce0-c637-11f0-a892-01d657345866.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/2fe7/live/24239ce0-c637-11f0-a892-01d657345866.jpg.webp" loading="eager" alt="Getty Images Family having a moment together messing about while winter sea swimming " class="sc-5340b511-0 hLdNfA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 jVqbAn"&gt;Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Every winter, the search for the secret to staying well seems to intensify. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Supermarket shelves fill with "immune-boosting" shots, cold water swimming groups grow and social media becomes crowded with tips on how to fend off seasonal bugs. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;But with so many remedies promising to keep colds and flu at bay, how much of it actually works and is it even possible to boost your immune system in the first place?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 hNbOGD"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 gXmhTb"&gt;Cold water swimming: A buzz, not a boost&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 GunZh"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 cMIbKV"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20251110-152207-94080fba49-web-2.33.2-3/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 gUePlo hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/c209/live/e6c375b0-c545-11f0-88be-3bc2aea1a256.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/c209/live/e6c375b0-c545-11f0-88be-3bc2aea1a256.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/c209/live/e6c375b0-c545-11f0-88be-3bc2aea1a256.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/c209/live/e6c375b0-c545-11f0-88be-3bc2aea1a256.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/c209/live/e6c375b0-c545-11f0-88be-3bc2aea1a256.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/c209/live/e6c375b0-c545-11f0-88be-3bc2aea1a256.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/c209/live/e6c375b0-c545-11f0-88be-3bc2aea1a256.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/c209/live/e6c375b0-c545-11f0-88be-3bc2aea1a256.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Getty Images Sick young woman lying on the couch holding a blister pack with antibiotics. " class="sc-5340b511-0 hLdNfA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 jVqbAn"&gt;Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Cold water swimming has surged in popularity, with some enthusiasts convinced it keeps winter illnesses at bay.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Immunologist professor Eleanor Riley tells &lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.bbc.co.uk/sounds/play/m00274wy" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;BBC Radio 4's Inside Health podcast&lt;/a&gt; that the post-swim "high" is real, but it's driven by adrenaline and endorphins.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"If you take a blood sample before and after a cold swim, white blood cell levels do rise," she explains. "But that's because the body thinks an infection might be coming, so cells move into the bloodstream. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"Within hours the levels go back to normal so your body hasn't created any more white blood cells." &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Professor Riley adds that part of the benefit of cold water swimming comes from building a social connection. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Feeling "brighter, more alert and more connected" has real physiological effects.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Professor John Tregoning, a vaccine immunologist, says the benefits are mostly indirect and much of what makes people feel healthier in winter may come down to stress.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"It reduces stress because you're outdoors with nice people in nice places. But you could get the same from dancing, singing or going for a run."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Being in nature can lower your blood pressure and stress hormones that can dampen immune responses. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;GP Dr Margaret McCartney explains that moderate exercise does show evidence of reducing viral infections, but that could be any form of exercise, not just cold water swimming. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 hNbOGD"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 gXmhTb"&gt;Kombucha: Interesting but little evidence&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 GunZh"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 cMIbKV"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20251110-152207-94080fba49-web-2.33.2-3/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 gUePlo hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/d78f/live/c27a67e0-c748-11f0-ad8e-3f3e719de832.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/d78f/live/c27a67e0-c748-11f0-ad8e-3f3e719de832.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/d78f/live/c27a67e0-c748-11f0-ad8e-3f3e719de832.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/d78f/live/c27a67e0-c748-11f0-ad8e-3f3e719de832.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/d78f/live/c27a67e0-c748-11f0-ad8e-3f3e719de832.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/d78f/live/c27a67e0-c748-11f0-ad8e-3f3e719de832.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/d78f/live/c27a67e0-c748-11f0-ad8e-3f3e719de832.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/d78f/live/c27a67e0-c748-11f0-ad8e-3f3e719de832.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Getty Images Young woman drinking a refreshing beverage from a plastic bottle " class="sc-5340b511-0 hLdNfA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 jVqbAn"&gt;Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Many people turn to fermented drinks like kombucha which promises to boost the microbiome and, by extension, the immune system.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;But Dr McCartney remains cautious. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"There are lots of theories about why a diverse microbiome is good, but we don't have strong enough real-world evidence to recommend kombucha to patients."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Professor Tregoning adds that while it's true that the microbiome changes during infections, it usually returns to its previous state afterwards.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Dr McCartney says while drinks like kombucha present "interesting ideas about the role of the microbiome", there isn't a clear link with how it can help boost your immune system. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 hNbOGD"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 gXmhTb"&gt;Supplements: Just expensive urine&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 GunZh"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 cMIbKV"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20251110-152207-94080fba49-web-2.33.2-3/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 gUePlo hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/c0dc/live/c553c6a0-c748-11f0-ad8e-3f3e719de832.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/c0dc/live/c553c6a0-c748-11f0-ad8e-3f3e719de832.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/c0dc/live/c553c6a0-c748-11f0-ad8e-3f3e719de832.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/c0dc/live/c553c6a0-c748-11f0-ad8e-3f3e719de832.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/c0dc/live/c553c6a0-c748-11f0-ad8e-3f3e719de832.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/c0dc/live/c553c6a0-c748-11f0-ad8e-3f3e719de832.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/c0dc/live/c553c6a0-c748-11f0-ad8e-3f3e719de832.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/c0dc/live/c553c6a0-c748-11f0-ad8e-3f3e719de832.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Getty Images Woman's hand holding colorful pills against terracotta table background with shadows from home plant. Pile of different pills - white, red, yellow, blue, green at the hand. " class="sc-5340b511-0 hLdNfA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 jVqbAn"&gt;Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Vitamin C has long been sold as a winter essential, but according to Dr McCartney, the evidence simply isn't strong enough to recommend it when it comes to fighting off colds. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;She says the same goes for multi-vitamins which do very little beyond giving you "expensive urine". &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;However, Vitamin D is slightly different as "there's theoretical evidence of a small decrease in respiratory infections". &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;But, she explains that not everyone will see a benefit if they take it and it's only people "with low vitamin D and pre-existing respiratory diseases" who will likely benefit. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Many people in the UK remain deficient in Vitamin D and Professor Tregoning suggests that winter sunlight and getting outdoors can help. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 hNbOGD"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 gXmhTb"&gt;Vaccinations: The only boost that works&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 GunZh"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 cMIbKV"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20251110-152207-94080fba49-web-2.33.2-3/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 gUePlo hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/a60f/live/c90c61d0-c748-11f0-ad8e-3f3e719de832.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/a60f/live/c90c61d0-c748-11f0-ad8e-3f3e719de832.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/a60f/live/c90c61d0-c748-11f0-ad8e-3f3e719de832.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/a60f/live/c90c61d0-c748-11f0-ad8e-3f3e719de832.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/a60f/live/c90c61d0-c748-11f0-ad8e-3f3e719de832.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/a60f/live/c90c61d0-c748-11f0-ad8e-3f3e719de832.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/a60f/live/c90c61d0-c748-11f0-ad8e-3f3e719de832.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/a60f/live/c90c61d0-c748-11f0-ad8e-3f3e719de832.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Getty Images Smiling nurse giving elderly patient injection for flu vaccination campaign in a medical center to fight winter illnesses or infections" class="sc-5340b511-0 hLdNfA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 jVqbAn"&gt;Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The likes of turmeric shots, ginger drinks and fancy nasal sprays do nothing to boost your immune system, according to Dr McCartney.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Professor Tregoning says that a nasal spray can help with a blocked nose but all you need is a simple saline spray which is just salt and water. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"The solution can dilute the blocked nose, stimulate turnover of mucus and relieve inflammation." &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;All three experts agree that ultimately only one intervention can strengthen the immune system and that's vaccination.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Professor Riley recommends the flu jab which takes from seven to 10 days after the jab to take effect.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;While you can't boost your immune system in the dramatic way winter wellness trends often promise, the experts advise supporting it by avoiding smoking, maintaining a healthy weight, finding a regular sleep routine and doing any activity that helps reduce stress. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Dr McCartney says you can also reduce your risk of colds by being in well ventilated spaces and washing your hands regularly and properly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BBC</author><pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 02:13:52 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiWkFVX3lxTE1JRC1UTjJIeEVWMnd0OWZKMzFEWEdDYkpWYXRaS1dvV0gzQTdfekdVX3IxMk1GSzVGeEJjTjE5YXRVbVpGZThDV0E4T255V2I1Ti0xelo5YThGUdIBX0FVX3lxTE92dllZMFRYUlAtREFqTEw2NWRBUl9jUE0wOEg4cUtqLUVOYnRaR25ZaG93cWZPWDIwX3NvUDhXSkM3eDZ2blpqdlBzSjg1RDJ4Yk9ISmJkMmtnenhDdzUw</guid></item><item><title>寒冷暴跌和康普茶：冬季健康趋势真的有效吗？ - BBC</title><link>https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/c5y4yk4nv5yo</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article&gt;&lt;p data-component="headline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 hNbOGD"&gt;&lt;h1 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 idLnWK"&gt;Cold plunges and kombucha: Do winter wellness trends really work?&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 eRlINq"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="hero-image" class="sc-5340b511-1 cMIbKV"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20251110-152207-94080fba49-web-2.33.2-3/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 gUePlo hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/2fe7/live/24239ce0-c637-11f0-a892-01d657345866.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/2fe7/live/24239ce0-c637-11f0-a892-01d657345866.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/2fe7/live/24239ce0-c637-11f0-a892-01d657345866.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/2fe7/live/24239ce0-c637-11f0-a892-01d657345866.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/2fe7/live/24239ce0-c637-11f0-a892-01d657345866.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/2fe7/live/24239ce0-c637-11f0-a892-01d657345866.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/2fe7/live/24239ce0-c637-11f0-a892-01d657345866.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/2fe7/live/24239ce0-c637-11f0-a892-01d657345866.jpg.webp" loading="eager" alt="Getty Images Family having a moment together messing about while winter sea swimming " class="sc-5340b511-0 hLdNfA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 jVqbAn"&gt;Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Every winter, the search for the secret to staying well seems to intensify. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Supermarket shelves fill with "immune-boosting" shots, cold water swimming groups grow and social media becomes crowded with tips on how to fend off seasonal bugs. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;But with so many remedies promising to keep colds and flu at bay, how much of it actually works and is it even possible to boost your immune system in the first place?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 hNbOGD"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 gXmhTb"&gt;Cold water swimming: A buzz, not a boost&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 GunZh"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 cMIbKV"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20251110-152207-94080fba49-web-2.33.2-3/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 gUePlo hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/c209/live/e6c375b0-c545-11f0-88be-3bc2aea1a256.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/c209/live/e6c375b0-c545-11f0-88be-3bc2aea1a256.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/c209/live/e6c375b0-c545-11f0-88be-3bc2aea1a256.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/c209/live/e6c375b0-c545-11f0-88be-3bc2aea1a256.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/c209/live/e6c375b0-c545-11f0-88be-3bc2aea1a256.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/c209/live/e6c375b0-c545-11f0-88be-3bc2aea1a256.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/c209/live/e6c375b0-c545-11f0-88be-3bc2aea1a256.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/c209/live/e6c375b0-c545-11f0-88be-3bc2aea1a256.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Getty Images Sick young woman lying on the couch holding a blister pack with antibiotics. " class="sc-5340b511-0 hLdNfA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 jVqbAn"&gt;Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Cold water swimming has surged in popularity, with some enthusiasts convinced it keeps winter illnesses at bay.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Immunologist professor Eleanor Riley tells &lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.bbc.co.uk/sounds/play/m00274wy" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;BBC Radio 4's Inside Health podcast&lt;/a&gt; that the post-swim "high" is real, but it's driven by adrenaline and endorphins.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"If you take a blood sample before and after a cold swim, white blood cell levels do rise," she explains. "But that's because the body thinks an infection might be coming, so cells move into the bloodstream. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"Within hours the levels go back to normal so your body hasn't created any more white blood cells." &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Professor Riley adds that part of the benefit of cold water swimming comes from building a social connection. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Feeling "brighter, more alert and more connected" has real physiological effects.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Professor John Tregoning, a vaccine immunologist, says the benefits are mostly indirect and much of what makes people feel healthier in winter may come down to stress.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"It reduces stress because you're outdoors with nice people in nice places. But you could get the same from dancing, singing or going for a run."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Being in nature can lower your blood pressure and stress hormones that can dampen immune responses. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;GP Dr Margaret McCartney explains that moderate exercise does show evidence of reducing viral infections, but that could be any form of exercise, not just cold water swimming. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 hNbOGD"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 gXmhTb"&gt;Kombucha: Interesting but little evidence&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 GunZh"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 cMIbKV"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20251110-152207-94080fba49-web-2.33.2-3/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 gUePlo hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/d78f/live/c27a67e0-c748-11f0-ad8e-3f3e719de832.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/d78f/live/c27a67e0-c748-11f0-ad8e-3f3e719de832.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/d78f/live/c27a67e0-c748-11f0-ad8e-3f3e719de832.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/d78f/live/c27a67e0-c748-11f0-ad8e-3f3e719de832.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/d78f/live/c27a67e0-c748-11f0-ad8e-3f3e719de832.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/d78f/live/c27a67e0-c748-11f0-ad8e-3f3e719de832.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/d78f/live/c27a67e0-c748-11f0-ad8e-3f3e719de832.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/d78f/live/c27a67e0-c748-11f0-ad8e-3f3e719de832.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Getty Images Young woman drinking a refreshing beverage from a plastic bottle " class="sc-5340b511-0 hLdNfA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 jVqbAn"&gt;Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Many people turn to fermented drinks like kombucha which promises to boost the microbiome and, by extension, the immune system.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;But Dr McCartney remains cautious. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"There are lots of theories about why a diverse microbiome is good, but we don't have strong enough real-world evidence to recommend kombucha to patients."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Professor Tregoning adds that while it's true that the microbiome changes during infections, it usually returns to its previous state afterwards.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Dr McCartney says while drinks like kombucha present "interesting ideas about the role of the microbiome", there isn't a clear link with how it can help boost your immune system. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 hNbOGD"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 gXmhTb"&gt;Supplements: Just expensive urine&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 GunZh"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 cMIbKV"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20251110-152207-94080fba49-web-2.33.2-3/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 gUePlo hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/c0dc/live/c553c6a0-c748-11f0-ad8e-3f3e719de832.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/c0dc/live/c553c6a0-c748-11f0-ad8e-3f3e719de832.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/c0dc/live/c553c6a0-c748-11f0-ad8e-3f3e719de832.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/c0dc/live/c553c6a0-c748-11f0-ad8e-3f3e719de832.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/c0dc/live/c553c6a0-c748-11f0-ad8e-3f3e719de832.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/c0dc/live/c553c6a0-c748-11f0-ad8e-3f3e719de832.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/c0dc/live/c553c6a0-c748-11f0-ad8e-3f3e719de832.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/c0dc/live/c553c6a0-c748-11f0-ad8e-3f3e719de832.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Getty Images Woman's hand holding colorful pills against terracotta table background with shadows from home plant. Pile of different pills - white, red, yellow, blue, green at the hand. " class="sc-5340b511-0 hLdNfA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 jVqbAn"&gt;Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Vitamin C has long been sold as a winter essential, but according to Dr McCartney, the evidence simply isn't strong enough to recommend it when it comes to fighting off colds. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;She says the same goes for multi-vitamins which do very little beyond giving you "expensive urine". &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;However, Vitamin D is slightly different as "there's theoretical evidence of a small decrease in respiratory infections". &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;But, she explains that not everyone will see a benefit if they take it and it's only people "with low vitamin D and pre-existing respiratory diseases" who will likely benefit. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Many people in the UK remain deficient in Vitamin D and Professor Tregoning suggests that winter sunlight and getting outdoors can help. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 hNbOGD"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 gXmhTb"&gt;Vaccinations: The only boost that works&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 GunZh"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 cMIbKV"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20251110-152207-94080fba49-web-2.33.2-3/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 gUePlo hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/a60f/live/c90c61d0-c748-11f0-ad8e-3f3e719de832.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/a60f/live/c90c61d0-c748-11f0-ad8e-3f3e719de832.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/a60f/live/c90c61d0-c748-11f0-ad8e-3f3e719de832.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/a60f/live/c90c61d0-c748-11f0-ad8e-3f3e719de832.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/a60f/live/c90c61d0-c748-11f0-ad8e-3f3e719de832.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/a60f/live/c90c61d0-c748-11f0-ad8e-3f3e719de832.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/a60f/live/c90c61d0-c748-11f0-ad8e-3f3e719de832.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/a60f/live/c90c61d0-c748-11f0-ad8e-3f3e719de832.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Getty Images Smiling nurse giving elderly patient injection for flu vaccination campaign in a medical center to fight winter illnesses or infections" class="sc-5340b511-0 hLdNfA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 jVqbAn"&gt;Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The likes of turmeric shots, ginger drinks and fancy nasal sprays do nothing to boost your immune system, according to Dr McCartney.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Professor Tregoning says that a nasal spray can help with a blocked nose but all you need is a simple saline spray which is just salt and water. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"The solution can dilute the blocked nose, stimulate turnover of mucus and relieve inflammation." &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;All three experts agree that ultimately only one intervention can strengthen the immune system and that's vaccination.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Professor Riley recommends the flu jab which takes from seven to 10 days after the jab to take effect.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;While you can't boost your immune system in the dramatic way winter wellness trends often promise, the experts advise supporting it by avoiding smoking, maintaining a healthy weight, finding a regular sleep routine and doing any activity that helps reduce stress. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Dr McCartney says you can also reduce your risk of colds by being in well ventilated spaces and washing your hands regularly and properly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BBC</author><pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 02:13:52 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiWkFVX3lxTE1JRC1UTjJIeEVWMnd0OWZKMzFEWEdDYkpWYXRaS1dvV0gzQTdfekdVX3IxMk1GSzVGeEJjTjE5YXRVbVpGZThDV0E4T255V2I1Ti0xelo5YThGUQ</guid></item><item><title>新研究提供了降低心脏病风险的见解- WRAL</title><link>https://www.wral.com/news/local/new-studies-insight-reducing-heart-disease-risk-american-heart-association-november-2025/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body"&gt;
					&lt;p id="font-resize" class="font-resize-container"&gt;
						&lt;button id="small-font-button"&gt;
							&lt;svg aria-hidden="true" focusable="false" data-prefix="fas" data-icon="text-height" class="fa-text-height fa-w-18 svg-inline--fa small-buttom-font-svg" role="img" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 576 512"&gt;
								&lt;use href="#i-text-height"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;
							&lt;/svg&gt;
						&lt;/button&gt;
						&lt;button id="medium-font-button"&gt;
							&lt;svg aria-hidden="true" focusable="false" data-prefix="fas" data-icon="text-height" class="fa-text-height fa-w-18 svg-inline--fa" role="img" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 576 512"&gt;
								&lt;use href="#i-text-height"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;
							&lt;/svg&gt;
						&lt;/button&gt;
						&lt;button id="large-font-button"&gt;
							&lt;svg aria-hidden="true" focusable="false" data-prefix="fas" data-icon="text-height" class="fa-text-height fa-w-18 svg-inline--fa" role="img" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 576 512"&gt;
								&lt;use href="#i-text-height"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;
							&lt;/svg&gt;
						&lt;/button&gt;
						
					&lt;/p&gt;

					
						&lt;p&gt;
New findings presented at the American Heart Association’s Scientific Sessions
are highlighting new efforts to prevent heart disease. &lt;/p&gt;
						
							
							
							
						
					
						&lt;p&gt;Dr. Nishant Shah, an American Heart Association volunteer and
associate professor of medicine at Duke University Medical Center, said this
year’s conference showcases “groundbreaking technologies” with a growing focus
on stopping heart disease before it starts.&lt;/p&gt;
						
							
								
							
							
							
						
					
						&lt;p&gt;“One of the studies I was excited to see was called the
Vesalius-CV trial. That was looking at the impact of a novel cholesterol
lowering medication,” said Shah. &lt;/p&gt;
						
							
							
							
						
					
						&lt;p&gt;The medication is already on the market, but researchers
tested it in people who have not yet had a heart attack or stroke. Shah
explained it’s a population group that doesn’t typically get this aggressive treatment
up front.&lt;/p&gt;
						
							
							
							
						
					
						&lt;p&gt;The physician shared the trial found “profound reductions”
in cardiovascular events within these patients.&lt;/p&gt;
						
							
							
							
						
					
						&lt;p&gt;Shah noted the study reinforces the importance of
identifying cardiovascular risk at every stage, including before someone has had
an event. Prevention efforts also focused on managing obesity, hypertension,
and lifestyle factors, which are all contributing factors to rising rates of heart
attacks in young patients.&lt;/p&gt;
						
							
							
							
						
					
						&lt;p&gt;“There are many reasons why younger people are getting heart
attacks,” said Shah. “We need to be proactive rather than reactive. The science
is moving in that direction and discovering drugs or strategies to lower risk
to avoid early onset heart disease.”&lt;/p&gt;
						
							
							
								&lt;p class="opscoad-Mobile_In_Content" data-unit="wral-v4/news/local/new-studies-insight-reducing-heart-disease-risk-american-heart-association-november-2025"&gt;
								&lt;/p&gt;
								&lt;p class="opscoad-article_in_read" data-unit="wral-v4/news/local/new-studies-insight-reducing-heart-disease-risk-american-heart-association-november-2025/"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
							
							
						
					
						&lt;p&gt;AHA sessions also featured new gene-editing technologies for
cholesterol and alternative forms of available cholesterol therapies, aimed at
better prevention. &lt;/p&gt;
						
							
							
							
						
					
						&lt;p&gt;Other research looked at whether a daily cup of coffee might
prevent abnormal heart rhythms from returning after treatment, but doctors
caution additional studies are needed.&lt;/p&gt;
						
							
							
							
						
					
						&lt;p&gt;“A lot of these studies are early in the investigational phases,
so we can’t jump the gun too much. We still need to get more data, understand
the methodology of these studies, and understand how it will move the clinical
needle forward,” advised Shah. &lt;/p&gt;
						
							
							
							
						
					
						&lt;p&gt;For his patients, Shah’s message is simple: there’s exciting
science in the pipeline, but it needs to be personalized. The physician
encourages patients to review their individual risk of cardiovascular disease
with their providers to see how these findings might apply to them. &lt;/p&gt;
						
							
							
							
						
					
						&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
						
							
							
								&lt;p class="opscoad-Mobile_In_Content" data-unit="wral-v4/news/local/new-studies-insight-reducing-heart-disease-risk-american-heart-association-november-2025"&gt;
								&lt;/p&gt;
								&lt;p class="opscoad-article_in_read" data-unit="wral-v4/news/local/new-studies-insight-reducing-heart-disease-risk-american-heart-association-november-2025/"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
							
							
						
					
					
				&lt;/div&gt;


				&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>WRAL</author><pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 02:08:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMivgFBVV95cUxNVzBNQm1FLWd6MTlRVFNENjZ1bXZhelliVVEtd1J2bnpmZ3J4U2gxTFFtdWZKSE1wUlpsM1lYODRkRjdWemlNX29fZVJkajRaTWVBOGtYSW1TOU1Mdk1tOTZxTmVRdlpRb0w5S012b25XQ1RQb0VTWnlHVkU0V25rbUw2dFNka0FYazE3UjhUM3FrZnZ1blg0TUpzZDRQaG55d3k0ZVB3THJ6Y21zQUF5dXQ2SGZxRUNwaHFGaGlB</guid></item><item><title>马尔堡病毒病-埃塞俄比亚-世界卫生组织（ WHO ）</title><link>https://www.who.int/emergencies/disease-outbreak-news/item/2025-DON585</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article class="sf-detail-body-wrapper don-revamp"&gt;
        

                

    
        &lt;h3 class="don-section"&gt;Situation at a glance&lt;/h3&gt;
        &lt;p class="don-content"&gt;
            On 12 November 2025, WHO noted a press release from the Ethiopian Ministry of Health (MoH), and the Ethiopian Public Health Institute (EPHI), announcing suspected viral hemorrhagic viral fever (VHF) in Jinka town, South Ethiopia Regional State, Ethiopia. 
On 14 November 2025, the Ministry of Health of Ethiopia confirmed that the cases previously reported as suspected VHF were Marburg virus disease (MVD). Molecular testing conducted by the National Reference Laboratory at EPHI identified Marburg virus (MARV) in patient samples. As of 20 November 2025, 33 laboratory tests have been conducted, of which six confirmed cases, including three deaths, have been reported. Of the six confirmed cases, three are currently alive and on treatment. In addition to the lab-confirmed cases, a further three epidemiologically linked cases could not be tested; all three are deceased and recorded as probable cases. A total of 206 contacts have been identified, and contacts are under active follow-up. The number of contacts will continue to change as the response evolves.
The source of the infection has not yet been identified. This marks the first confirmed outbreak of MVD in the country. Initial investigation by the one health team in Ethiopia show the presence of the natural host of the virus, fruit bats, in the area. 

MVD is a severe, often fatal illness, transmitted from bats to humans, and clinically similar to Ebola virus diseases. The disease has a case fatality ratio of up to 88%, but it can be much lower with good and early patient care.

Under the leadership of the MoH, WHO is working alongside the Ethiopian response teams to enhance coordination, surveillance (including outbreak investigation, contact tracing, and alert management), case management, infection prevention and control measures, laboratory capacity, risk communication and community engagement. 

WHO assesses the public health risk posed by the outbreak as high at the national level, moderate at the regional level and low at the global level. Ethiopia is facing concurrent emergencies and multiple disease outbreaks, including of cholera, measles, dengue, which results in stretched health capacity.
        &lt;/p&gt;


        &lt;p class="don-images d-block d-lg-none"&gt;
        &lt;/p&gt;

    
        &lt;h3 class="don-section"&gt;Description of the situation&lt;/h3&gt;
        &lt;div class="don-content"&gt;

            &lt;p&gt;As of 20 November 2025, 33 laboratory tests have been conducted, of which six confirmed cases, including three deaths, have been reported. Of the six confirmed cases, three are currently alive and on treatment. In addition to the lab-confirmed cases, a further three epidemiologically linked cases could not be tested; all three are deceased and recorded as probable cases. A total of 206 contacts have been identified, and contacts are under active follow-up. The number of contacts will continue to change as the response evolves.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Clinically, patients have presented with high-grade fever, headache, vomiting, abdominal pain, and watery or bloody diarrhoea. Haemorrhagic manifestations, including nose bleeding and vomiting blood were observed in five cases, consistent with multi-organ failure. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As this is the first time Ethiopia is reporting MVD, WHO recommends that samples be shared with a reference laboratory for inter-laboratory comparison. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Figure 1: Map of Ethiopia showing location of Jinka town&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img sf-image-responsive="true" src="https://cdn.who.int/media/images/default-source/products/disease-outbreak-news/mvd-in-ethiopia.jpg?sfvrsn=e861d6ce_3" title="MVD in Ethiopia" alt="MVD in Ethiopia" sf-size="52862"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;


        &lt;p class="don-images d-block d-lg-none"&gt;
        &lt;/p&gt;

    
        &lt;h3 class="don-section"&gt;Epidemiology&lt;/h3&gt;
        &lt;div class="don-content"&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;Marburg virus disease (MVD) is a severe hemorrhagic fever caused by either of two closely related viruses, Marburg virus and Ravn virus, which are closely related to the Ebola viruses. MVD has a high case fatality rate, ranging from 24% to 88% from previous outbreaks The case fatality rate can be lowered with good and early patient care. The virus is initially transmitted to humans from fruit bats (&lt;em&gt;Rousettus aegyptiacus&lt;/em&gt;) and then spreads among people through direct contact with bodily fluids, contaminated surfaces, or infected materials. Healthcare workers, caregivers, and individuals involved in burial practices are particularly at risk when infection prevention and control measures are not in place. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;MVD symptoms typically begin abruptly after an incubation period of two to 21 days and include high fever, severe headache, malaise, muscle aches, and progressive gastrointestinal symptoms such as diarrhea and vomiting. In severe cases, patients may experience bleeding from multiple sites and die from shock and organ failure within a week of symptom onset.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;There are no approved treatment or vaccines for MVD, although supportive treatment and early supportive care improves survival. Some candidate vaccines and therapeutics are currently under investigation.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Nineteen outbreaks of MVD have previously been reported globally. The most &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.who.int/emergencies/disease-outbreak-news/item/2025-DON552"&gt;recent&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; outbreak was reported from the Republic of Tanzania between January and March 2025. Additional countries that have reported outbreaks of MVD in the African Region include Angola, the Democratic Republic of the Congo, Equatorial Guinea, Ghana, Guinea, Kenya, Rwanda, South Africa, and Uganda. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;


        &lt;p class="don-images d-block d-lg-none"&gt;
        &lt;/p&gt;

    
        &lt;h3 class="don-section"&gt;Public health response&lt;/h3&gt;
        &lt;div class="don-content"&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;Local and national health authorities in Ethiopia have implemented the following public health measures:  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;A National Taskforce has been established at the Ministry of Health to provide strategic guidance, make decisions and mobilize resources. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A costed national three-month response plan has been developed and launched by the MoH/EPHI.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The MoH is regularly providing information on the MVD outbreak to the general public and partners.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Emergency Operational Centres (EOCs) have been activated at national and regional levels, with incident management structures established to coordinate the response. Daily coordination meetings are ongoing at the national and subnational EOCs. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The Ministry of Health, in collaboration with EPHI and regional health offices, is conducting integrated surveillance and response activities. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Community surveillance, contact tracing, house-to-house visits, and medical service delivery are being enhanced. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Two hospitals have been designated as treatment centres, with dedicated health workers deployed to manage cases. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Field assessments are being conducted by a rapid response team (RRT). One RRT was deployed to Jinka to conduct contact tracing and epidemiological investigation while a second team is strengthening infection prevention and control (IPC) in health facilities managing suspected cases.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Risk Communication and Community Engagement (RCCE) teams are disseminating MVD prevention messages, developing activity plans for targeted interventions, monitoring social media to address misinformation, and assessing trusted communication channels to enhance public awareness.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;


        &lt;p class="don-images d-block d-lg-none"&gt;
        &lt;/p&gt;

    
        &lt;h3 class="don-section"&gt;WHO risk assessment&lt;/h3&gt;
        &lt;div class="don-content"&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;This is the first confirmed MVD outbreak in Ethiopia.  The public health risk posed by the MVD outbreak is assessed as high at the national level due to several concerning factors: &lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;The outbreak involves six laboratory-confirmed cases; there have been a total of six deaths and there are three confirmed cases under treatment.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;All deaths involved unsupervised burials, posing a risk of potential additional community transmission. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The presence of healthcare workers among the confirmed cases suggests potential occupational exposure risks within health facilities.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Although investigations are ongoing, information on the source of the outbreak, geographical extent and epidemiology is limited.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt; &lt;p&gt;Although no international transmission has been confirmed to date, the potential risk for spread remains. The affected area, Jinka, while distant from Ethiopia’s capital or major international airports, is connected by road transportation networks, including to neighbouring Kenya and South Sudan. Therefore, the public health risk posed by this event is assessed as moderate at the regional level. It is considered low at the global level.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;


        &lt;p class="don-images d-block d-lg-none"&gt;
        &lt;/p&gt;

    
        &lt;h3 class="don-section"&gt;WHO advice&lt;/h3&gt;
        &lt;div class="don-content"&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;Human-to-human transmission of Marburg virus is primarily associated with direct contact with the blood and/or other bodily fluids of infected people. Strengthening and reinforcing IPC measures is essential to prevent further transmission and reduce the likelihood of amplification.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;WHO advises the following risk reduction measures to be taken as an effective way to reduce MVD transmission to control the outbreak.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Prevention:&lt;/strong&gt; Protective measures individuals should take to reduce human exposure to the virus include:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul type="disc"&gt;&lt;li data-list="0" data-level="1"&gt;Reduce the risk of human-to-human transmission in the community arising from      direct or close contact with infected patients, particularly with their      body fluids including blood, feces and vomit. Close physical contact with      MVD patients should be avoided.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-list="0" data-level="1"&gt;Persons with symptoms compatible with MVD should immediately seek care in health      facilities, and patients suspected or confirmed to have MVD should be      isolated in a designated treatment centre for early care and to avoid      transmission at home.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-list="0" data-level="1"&gt;Community and family members should avoid caring for symptomatic individuals at home      and avoid touching bodies of people deceased with MVD symptoms. They      should avoid touching other potentially contaminated items and surfaces.  &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-list="0" data-level="1"&gt;Reduce the risk of bat-to-human transmission arising from prolonged exposure to      mines, caves or dwellings inhabited by fruit bat colonies. During work or      research activities or tourist visits in mines or caves inhabited by fruit      bat colonies, people should wear gloves and other appropriate protective      clothing (including masks). During outbreaks, all animal products (blood      and meat) should be thoroughly cooked before consumption.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Coordination:&lt;/strong&gt; Multisectoral coordination and pillar meetings at all levels and sharing of detailed situation reports is encouraged. Involvement of different stakeholders and partners in preparedness and response activities is also encouraged. To ensure an effective and sustained response, resource mobilization efforts within the government and with partners are recommended.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Risk communication and community engagement:&lt;/strong&gt; Raising public awareness and engaging with communities are important for successfully controlling MVD outbreaks. This includes raising awareness of symptoms, risk factors for infection, protective measures and the importance of seeking immediate care at a health facility. Sensitive and supportive information about safe and dignified burials is also crucial. This awareness should be increased through targeted campaigns and direct work with communities. Special attention should be given to high-risk groups, such as traditional healers, clergy, and community leaders, who may inadvertently facilitate disease spread, and who are important sources of information for the community. Misinformation and rumours should be addressed to foster trust and promote early symptom reporting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Surveillance:&lt;/strong&gt; Active case detection, contact tracing, and alert management across affected and neighbouring regions should be intensified. Community-based surveillance systems should be strengthened to promptly identify and report new cases, particularly in high-risk areas. Close monitoring of healthcare workers, family members and individuals who have had contact with suspected cases or other high-exposure settings should be ensured. Surveillance capacities should also be intensified at relevant points of entry and borders to reduce the risk of further spread, including internationally.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Infection prevention and control (IPC) measures: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Critical infection prevention and control measures should be implemented and/or strengthened in all health care facilities, per &lt;a href="https://www.who.int/publications/i/item/WHO-WPE-CRS-HCR-2023.1" target="_blank" data-sf-ec-immutable=""&gt;WHO’s Infection prevention and control guideline for Ebola and Marburg disease&lt;/a&gt;, which highlighted the importance of the rapid implementation of the IPC ring approach, including but not limited to IPC rapid assessment, decontamination of health facilities and households and early detection and identification of the cases through the screening and isolation of the suspected cases to minimize the transmission risk. Patients meeting the case definition for suspected MVD should be treated with appropriate precautions for MVD, regardless of whether the clinical suspicion suggests a more common ailment with similar symptoms, such as malaria. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul type="disc"&gt;&lt;li data-list="0" data-level="1"&gt;Health workers caring for patients with confirmed or suspected MVD should      apply &lt;a href="https://www.who.int/publications/i/item/WHO-UHL-IHS-IPC-2022.2" target="_blank" data-sf-ec-immutable=""&gt;transmission-based precautions&lt;/a&gt; in addition to &lt;a href="https://www.who.int/publications/i/item/WHO-UHL-IHS-IPC-2022.1" target="_blank" data-sf-ec-immutable=""&gt;standard precautions&lt;/a&gt;, including appropriate use of personal protective equipment (PPE) and hand      hygiene according to the &lt;a href="https://cdn.who.int/media/docs/default-source/integrated-health-services-(ihs)/infection-prevention-and-control/your-5-moments-for-hand-hygiene-poster.pdf?sfvrsn=83e2fb0e_21%22%20%EF%B7%9FHYPERLINK%20%22https://cdn.who.int/media/docs/default-source/integrated-health-services-(ihs)/infection-prevention-and-control/your-5-moments-for-hand-hygiene-poster.pdf?sfvrsn=83e2fb0e_21" target="_blank" data-sf-ec-immutable=""&gt;WHO 5      moments&lt;/a&gt;, to avoid contact with patient’s blood and other body fluids and with      contaminated surfaces and objects. Waste generated in healthcare      facilities must be safely segregated, safely collected, transported,      stored, treated and finally disposed. Follow the national guidelines,      rules and regulations for safe waste disposal or follow the &lt;a href="https://iris.who.int/server/api/core/bitstreams/4daece5e-1220-47f5-903c-8c2a14fcd778/content" target="_blank" data-sf-ec-immutable=""&gt;WHO’s guidelines on safe waste management&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul type="disc"&gt;&lt;li data-list="1" data-level="1"&gt;Patient-care activities should be undertaken in a clean and hygienic environment that      facilitates practices related to the prevention and control of      health-care-associated infections (HAIs) as outlined in &lt;a href="https://www.who.int/publications/i/item/9789241547239" target="_blank" data-sf-ec-immutable=""&gt;Essential environmental health standards in health care.&lt;/a&gt; Safe water, adequate      sanitation and hygiene infrastructure and services should be provided in      healthcare facilities. For details on recommendations and improvement,      follow the &lt;a href="https://www.who.int/publications/i/item/9789240043237" data-sf-ec-immutable=""&gt;WASH FIT implementation Package&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Laboratory testing:&lt;/strong&gt; The processing and analysis of samples should be expedited, with results promptly shared with responders and clinicians to guide patient management, containment strategies and broader response efforts. This includes genomic sequencing on positive samples. International referral of samples to a regional reference laboratory should be considered for inter-laboratory comparison. Laboratory workers handling specimens from patients suspected or confirmed to be infected with MARV should receive refresher training on laboratory biosafety; this includes taking appropriate precautions when drawing blood for a malaria rapid diagnostic test or other test not specific for MARV.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Evaluation of candidate medical countermeasures:&lt;/strong&gt; There are no licensed vaccines or therapeutics against MVD. Several candidate vaccines are in the pipeline and outbreaks offer an opportunity to assess their efficacy and safety. There are &lt;a href="https://www.who.int/teams/blueprint/ebolavirus" data-sf-ec-immutable=""&gt;protocols available&lt;/a&gt; and a network of experts in filoviruses ready to support national researchers.   &lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Safe and dignified burials:&lt;/strong&gt; Safe and dignified burial protocols should be implemented for persons who have died to minimize community exposure. Additional training and equipment for healthcare workers and burial teams should be provided to ensure safe management of MVD-related fatalities. Thorough community engagement is required to ensure that affected communities are empowered to adhere to the protocols.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Case management and mental health and psychosocial support:&lt;/strong&gt; Designated treatment centers should ensure adequate level of care for confirmed patients to improve the chance of survival. Isolation and treatment facilities should be adequately equipped to ensure the safety and efficacy of patient care, while simultaneously preventing the spread of the disease. Supportive care such as rehydration, symptom management, and psychological support for patients and their families is essential to improving survival rates and mitigating the outbreak's impact.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Border health and cross-border coordination:&lt;/strong&gt; Surveillance capacities should be strengthened at relevant at-risk points of entry, onboard conveyances, and in border regions to prevent further spread, including internationally. Cases, contacts and individuals in affected areas who present signs and symptoms compatible with case definition should be advised not to travel, in line with WHO’s border health and points of entry technical guidance for filovirus disease outbreaks. Collaboration with neighbouring countries should be enhanced to harmonize reporting mechanisms, conduct joint investigations, and share critical data in real-time. Countries at-risk of potential spread should enhance readiness activities to enable early case detection, isolation and treatment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Based on the current risk assessment, WHO advises against any travel and trade restrictions with Ethiopia.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;


        &lt;p class="don-images d-block d-lg-none"&gt;
        &lt;/p&gt;

    
        &lt;h3 class="don-section"&gt;Further information&lt;/h3&gt;
        &lt;div class="don-content"&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Citable reference:&lt;/strong&gt; World Health Organization (21 November 2025). Disease Outbreak News; Marburg virus disease in Ethiopia. Available at: &lt;a href="https://www/who.int/emergencies/disease-outbreak-news/item/2025-DON585" data-sf-ec-immutable=""&gt;https://www/who.int/emergencies/disease-outbreak-news/item/2025-DON585&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;


        &lt;p class="don-images d-block d-lg-none"&gt;
        &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/article&gt;


    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>World Health Organization (WHO)</author><pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 01:40:12 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiekFVX3lxTE80czJLbmFoSGVTUEh5d0YtUHFrcUJsakltYldKU3U3cGRxLWtGdmFRV2hQYUxYU0ppOHNxRkhPaDdUTWxFVm96Sk5BTy1HaEg0M25Zc2pfM0hQeXVsTzlFUGYtaW9uUWJwR0VhZnRoWWlmZzBxa1czT21B</guid></item><item><title>流感活动性较低，但专家担心新的流感病毒株和疫苗接种率- ABC新闻</title><link>https://abcnews.go.com/Health/wireStory/flu-activity-low-experts-worry-new-strain-vaccination-127770890</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="xvlfx ZRifP TKoO eaKKC EcdEg bOdfO qXhdi NFNeu UyHES " data-testid="prism-article-body"&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao MvWXB TjIXL aGjvy ebVHC "&gt;&lt;span class="oyrPY qlwaB AGxeB  "&gt;NEW YORK -- &lt;/span&gt;The U.S. flu season is starting slowly, and it's unclear if it will be as bad as &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://apnews.com/article/us-flu-season-cdc-a640e8fe0bffa4a8f6bdbd7ea8e5608a"&gt;last winter's&lt;/a&gt;, but some health experts are worried as U.S. Centers for Disease Control and Prevention data posted Friday shows a new version of the virus has emerged.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;An early analysis suggests current vaccines may still be somewhat effective against the new version of the flu, which has been the main driver of recent infections, CDC data shows.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Some scientists and medical professionals are more worried about disappointing vaccination rates, a main reason why flu hospitalizations and deaths were unusually bad during last year's flu season — one of the deadliest this century.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;“I think we’re going to see a really severe season," said Asefeh Faraz Covelli of the George Washington University School of Nursing. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Last winter, the overall flu hospitalization rate was the highest seen since the H1N1 flu pandemic 15 years ago. Flu was the underlying or a contributing cause of more than 18,000 deaths, and one seven-day stretch early this year saw more than 1,800 deaths — the highest one-week spike in at least a decade. &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://apnews.com/article/flu-deaths-children-cdc-e79b1e4169d629ad4bc1095d95d82110"&gt;Child flu deaths&lt;/a&gt; also were far higher than usual.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;CDC &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://www.cdc.gov/fluview/surveillance/usmap.html"&gt;data&lt;/a&gt; posted Friday showed low flu activity so far, with only one state — Louisiana — reporting moderate activity. Most of the reported infections have been in children, said the CDC's Alicia Budd, who tracks flu infections for the Atlanta-based agency.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Most also have been a new version of the type A H3N2 virus that historically has caused the most hospitalizations and deaths in older people. That type is responsible for most flu infections so far this year, and more than half have been a new subclade K variant that is different from the strain this year's flu shots were built to fight.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;A preliminary &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://assets.publishing.service.gov.uk/media/691349457a0ccd6a3aad7fa9/_Flu_interimVE_2526_.pdf"&gt;analysis&lt;/a&gt; from the United Kingdom suggests the shots do provide at least partial protection, although it will take some time for scientists to know exactly how effective they are. Experts say any protection that softens the blow of a flu infection is important to get.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Flu seasons tend to get bad between December and February, and illnesses likely will accelerate as people travel and gather for Thanksgiving, Covelli said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;“I think it’s going to start picking up here,” she said. “This is the ideal time to get vaccinated.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Researchers this year have been facing an unusual struggle to get a handle on how respiratory infection and vaccination rates have been trending.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;They usually rely on the CDC for data, but a recent government shutdown halted data collection and reporting just as respiratory infections started ramping up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Meanwhile, government efforts to promote disease-preventing shots have been more limited since U.S. Health Secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr. was put in charge of the CDC and other federal health agencies. Kennedy, a leading anti-vaccine activist, has fostered uncertainty about the safety of vaccines, including flu shots that contained a preservative called &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://apnews.com/article/cdc-acip-flu-vaccine-thimerosal-c5696bbc19f345323153d5336cb5e798"&gt;thimerosal&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Indeed, vaccination rates against COVID-19 clearly continue to plummet, with about 6% of children and 14% of adults up to date on their shots, according to &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://www.cdc.gov/respiratory-viruses/data/vaccination-trends.html"&gt;other CDC data&lt;/a&gt; posted Friday. Each figure is about 3 percentage points less than it was at this point last fall.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;For the flu, vaccination trends are a little muddier. Some sources have suggested flu vaccinations are down. Over two million fewer flu shots were given at U.S. pharmacies through the end of October compared to last year, according to data from IQVIA, a health information and research company.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;But the latest CDC data indicates that for children, the vaccination rate this year is about the same as it was at this point last fall, at 34%. And the vaccination rate for adults is up a few percentage points to about 37%, according to the CDC data, which relies on survey information.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;It is early in the season and too early to know if the increase will be sustained or what is causing it, CDC officials said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;As of the beginning of November, the U.S. flu hospitalization rate is about the same as it was at the same point in 2024. Hospitalization rates for COVID-19 and another respiratory virus, RSV, are lower so far this season, according to &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://www.cdc.gov/resp-net/dashboard/index.html"&gt;another set&lt;/a&gt; of CDC data.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;___&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;The Associated Press Health and Science Department receives support from the Howard Hughes Medical Institute’s Department of Science Education and the Robert Wood Johnson Foundation. The AP is solely responsible for all content.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ABC News</author><pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 00:48:39 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipgFBVV95cUxOcXNzSGlwWjZNZFBaUVdrbno3QzBweEVLZlA3M1hXMk1KZU94YnJHaGgtX29wZkJYYmFTWUZVUzRnUzNBU0E5UFlrdEVBYVdqUGhRYkswZXFScW9XZTN0V1dhVjFLaHVIX2xLMXdsdV9GNExKdHFGdlRrZHd5UzNsUkF5d1YycWV3S051TkFRck1vUm1LRUhObXA4Zi00MnZtRFg0R2xR0gGrAUFVX3lxTE1mS3ZNcTdUUmF1dkw2OThWQmlqTGdJZkIyRUl2LUF2WEduZHM2cUs3cng2LUlJYlk3LXgxOGlwUXVoQncxRmcxR1VEdTh3ZVlnTHU0dndURlZOaU1IeTJPTEpYSk9WcVV0RHRvY19EaGNiaFU4NUN6X1N3SmphcW50LWhQaFlPR1VFQVZqaDJEejBnS1EtUWFJc1UwcUFJYlhsTk9OWFJSS2d5OA</guid></item><item><title>流感活动较低，但专家担心新的流感病毒株和疫苗接种率-美联社新闻</title><link>https://apnews.com/article/flu-covid-vaccinations-7e437cc60e18e4d1c49b50c3b358a253</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="LeaderBoardAd-Mobile "&gt;
                                    
                                        
                                            
                                        
                                    
                                &lt;/p&gt;
                            
                            
                                
                                
                                    &lt;div class="RichTextStoryBody RichTextBody"&gt;
                                        &lt;p&gt;NEW YORK (AP) — The U.S. flu season is starting slowly, and it’s unclear if it will be as bad as &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://apnews.com/article/us-flu-season-cdc-a640e8fe0bffa4a8f6bdbd7ea8e5608a"&gt;last winter’s&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;, but some health experts are worried as U.S. Centers for Disease Control and Prevention data posted Friday shows a new version of the virus has emerged.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;An early analysis suggests current vaccines may still be somewhat effective against the new version of the flu, which has been the main driver of recent infections, CDC data shows.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some scientists and medical professionals are more worried about disappointing vaccination rates, a main reason why flu hospitalizations and deaths were unusually bad during last year’s flu season — one of the deadliest this century.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I think we’re going to see a really severe season,” said Asefeh Faraz Covelli of the George Washington University School of Nursing. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Last winter, the overall flu hospitalization rate was the highest seen since the H1N1 flu pandemic 15 years ago. Flu was the underlying or a contributing cause of more than 18,000 deaths, and one seven-day stretch early this year saw more than 1,800 deaths — the highest one-week spike in at least a decade. &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://apnews.com/article/flu-deaths-children-cdc-e79b1e4169d629ad4bc1095d95d82110"&gt;Child flu deaths&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; also were far higher than usual.&lt;/p&gt;
    
&lt;p&gt;CDC &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://www.cdc.gov/fluview/surveillance/usmap.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;data&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; posted Friday showed low flu activity so far, with only one state — Louisiana — reporting moderate activity. Most of the reported infections have been in children, said the CDC’s Alicia Budd, who tracks flu infections for the Atlanta-based agency.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Most also have been a new version of the type A H3N2 virus that historically has caused the most hospitalizations and deaths in older people. That type is responsible for most flu infections so far this year, and more than half have been a new subclade K variant that is different from the strain this year’s flu shots were built to fight.&lt;/p&gt;
    
    
    
&lt;p&gt;A preliminary &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://assets.publishing.service.gov.uk/media/691349457a0ccd6a3aad7fa9/_Flu_interimVE_2526_.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;analysis&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; from the United Kingdom suggests the shots do provide at least partial protection, although it will take some time for scientists to know exactly how effective they are. Experts say any protection that softens the blow of a flu infection is important to get.&lt;/p&gt;
    
&lt;p&gt;Flu seasons tend to get bad between December and February, and illnesses likely will accelerate as people travel and gather for Thanksgiving, Covelli said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I think it’s going to start picking up here,” she said. “This is the ideal time to get vaccinated.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Researchers this year have been facing an unusual struggle to get a handle on how respiratory infection and vaccination rates have been trending.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They usually rely on the CDC for data, but a recent government shutdown halted data collection and reporting just as respiratory infections started ramping up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Meanwhile, government efforts to promote disease-preventing shots have been more limited since U.S. Health Secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr. was put in charge of the CDC and other federal health agencies. Kennedy, a leading anti-vaccine activist, has fostered uncertainty about the safety of vaccines, including flu shots that contained a preservative called &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://apnews.com/article/cdc-acip-flu-vaccine-thimerosal-c5696bbc19f345323153d5336cb5e798"&gt;thimerosal&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Indeed, vaccination rates against COVID-19 clearly continue to plummet, with about 6% of children and 14% of adults up to date on their shots, according to &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://www.cdc.gov/respiratory-viruses/data/vaccination-trends.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;other CDC data&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; posted Friday. Each figure is about 3 percentage points less than it was at this point last fall.&lt;/p&gt;
    
&lt;p&gt;For the flu, vaccination trends are a little muddier. Some sources have suggested flu vaccinations are down. Over two million fewer flu shots were given at U.S. pharmacies through the end of October compared to last year, according to data from IQVIA, a health information and research company.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But the latest CDC data indicates that for children, the vaccination rate this year is about the same as it was at this point last fall, at 34%. And the vaccination rate for adults is up a few percentage points to about 37%, according to the CDC data, which relies on survey information.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It is early in the season and too early to know if the increase will be sustained or what is causing it, CDC officials said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As of the beginning of November, the U.S. flu hospitalization rate is about the same as it was at the same point in 2024. Hospitalization rates for COVID-19 and another respiratory virus, RSV, are lower so far this season, according to &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://www.cdc.gov/resp-net/dashboard/index.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;another set&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; of CDC data.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;___&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="optimizelyHubpeekId" class="optimizelyHubpeekClass"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Associated Press Health and Science Department receives support from the Howard Hughes Medical Institute’s Department of Science Education and the Robert Wood Johnson Foundation. The AP is solely responsible for all content.&lt;/p&gt;
                                    &lt;/div&gt;
                                
                            

                            
                    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>AP News</author><pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 00:34:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiigFBVV95cUxQZEVITndjN3NURnY5b29hVi15R2p4Tm1PUkhTTDByUUVLX0tGeFRRb3EtUGZLMTFKdklBRjVZemZ4cTZCbFlhdkluQVpyVnZzMWVrOUZLTlZVVHQwMDY0U3NuRW1qZXlaYTlfd0k3bHhsWVJocVFvQTJ0RjQ3bGlTUjluQl9ZZWwteHc</guid></item><item><title>为什么你不想在阴茎上得到结核病- Ars Technica</title><link>https://arstechnica.com/health/2025/11/why-you-dont-want-to-get-tuberculosis-on-your-penis/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content post-content-double"&gt;
          
          
&lt;p&gt;Miliary tuberculosis (MTB) is a severe form of tuberculosis in which the instigating bacteria— &lt;em&gt;Mycobacterium tuberculosis&lt;/em&gt; or potentially a relative that infects cows and deer, &lt;em&gt;Mycobacterium bovis&lt;/em&gt;—spread widely through the body and create small lesions. The name “miliary” dates back to 1700, when a physician noted that the specks resembled millet seeds.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While &lt;em&gt;Mycobacterium&lt;/em&gt; can spread through the air and are often found in the lungs, the bacteria can strike anywhere in the body. Still, penile tuberculosis is exceedingly rare. In fact, it’s uncommon to have tuberculosis erupt anywhere in the urinary and genital tracts. Among the infections that spring up in the region, penile infections account for less than 1 percent.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But, given the man’s lungs and his immunosuppressed status, the unusual presentation became their leading guess—and tests soon confirmed it. &lt;em&gt;Mycobacterium &lt;/em&gt;were identified in the man’s respiratory tract, and penile tissue tested also showed the bacteria, though the testing couldn’t identify what species of &lt;em&gt;Mycobacterium&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Treatment for tuberculosis requires a regimen of several antibiotics and takes months. In the man’s case, they customized his treatment with a 12-month, four-drug regimen that wouldn’t interfere with his transplant.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Still, the penile lesion got worse before it got better. He developed a large necrotic ulceration on the side of his penis, and his foreskin began to “break down.” Surgeons had to mechanically cut out the dead tissue. After 10 months, his infection appeared to have cleared, and his penile lesion had improved.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Unexplained exposure&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It remains unclear how the man got the infection. He told doctors he wasn’t aware of coming in contact with any tuberculosis patients and wasn’t in settings where the bacteria normally spread, such as prisons. It’s possible that the bacteria had been lurking in his transplanted kidney.&lt;/p&gt;

          
                  &lt;/div&gt;

              &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Ars Technica</author><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 23:15:05 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilgFBVV95cUxQU0QzYUl5dnk0T2F4VERqOEtMSTRRcEpzdTl1ckVUbTRjUF9uTjFON0JuODRXMTZlRC1xVFBmUEFBYnpMMnIxUmx2YkNhYWVtYjJ4NmNtc3lyQUwzWU9TSU5CS092RFkySzhoZ2VCQWJDaVI2blpjMWNUSy1lNU9mTHVTMG94TFpPanJVWW5RWjBHVXJkWFE</guid></item><item><title>小罗伯特· F ·肯尼迪（ Robert F Kennedy Jr ）指示疾控中心改变对疫苗和自闭症的立场--《卫报》</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2025/nov/21/rfk-jr-cdc-vaccine-autism</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body-commercial-selector article-body-viewer-selector dcr-hdpgoq"&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/robert-f-kennedy-jr" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;Robert F Kennedy Jr&lt;/a&gt;, the US health secretary, said in an interview with the New York Times that he personally instructed the federal Centers for Disease Control and Prevention (CDC) to change its longstanding position that vaccines do not cause autism.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Countering decades of science showing vaccines to be safe, the US public health agency’s website was changed to say: “The claim ‘vaccines do not cause autism’ is not an evidence-based claim because studies have not ruled out the possibility that infant vaccines cause autism.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="sign-in-gate"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;In &lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2025/11/21/us/politics/rfk-jr-cdc-vaccines-autism-website.html" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;the interview&lt;/a&gt;, Kennedy said that while the large-scale epidemiological studies of the measles, mumps and rubella vaccine had found no link to autism, and that studies of the mercury-based preservative thimerosal had also shown no link, there are gaps in the vaccine safety science.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“The whole thing about ‘vaccines have been tested and there’s been this determination made’, is just a lie,” Kennedy said in his first interview with a major print publication.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Public health experts, doctors and scientists have decried the update as the kind of misinformation the CDC has fought for decades as it promoted the use of life-saving childhood vaccines in the US and abroad.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Notably, the largest US county’s health department issued a statement on Friday saying “there is no new evidence to support” the CDC website’s change pertaining to vaccines and autism – and the statement added that the modification was “not accurate”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“For more than 25 years, researchers around the world have rigorously examined whether vaccines cause autism,” the statement from the Los Angeles county health department said. “Over 40 high-quality studies involving more than 5.6 million children have found no link between any routine childhood vaccine and autism. This conclusion is supported by leading health authorities, including the American Academy of Pediatrics, the California Department of Public Health, the World Health Organization, and leading research institutions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“The increase in autism diagnoses reflects improved screening, broader diagnostic criteria, and greater awareness – not a link to vaccines. The spread of this harmful myth stigmatizes members of the autism community and their families.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Guardian</author><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 22:36:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMifkFVX3lxTE9JSG1vZ1l3R25uU3o4dWtrN0xlZHFlOFFDSmNPTXZUSXg3LV9PMEc5TE5ROHdKZkFnQkFNTFhEYV9OTmdHV2l5bzFoNE5PZjUyckI2N19HM0xUc29UcW9iVU9OMDBqTzlqT3l0TmdYcWI5LU5qbmk2TVV2X2N1Zw</guid></item><item><title>减肥注射的危险和更好的替代方案- KSL.com</title><link>https://www.ksl.com/article/51408978/weight-loss-shots-research-indicates-dangers-from-starting-and-stopping</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="articleContainer"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Both starting and stopping this drug can be dangerous. Not only is the research clear about this but Dr. Roberts DC, at &lt;a href="https://app.gohighlevel.com/v2/preview/V4PKJFd02o0yv0Z3BF0e?utm_source=KSL&amp;amp;utm_medium=display" target="_blank" rel="sponsored"&gt;Heath Utah&lt;/a&gt;, is on the front lines helping prevent and resolve side effects. He reports seeing some of the problems patients are experiencing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One such case involved a 16-year-old girl. Roberts says, "She came into my clinic with excruciating pain. She couldn't even drink water without severe abdominal distress. Even though she was on Semaglutide for only a short time, the pain persisted for six months after she stopped injecting it. That's when she came to see me. Fortunately with care, her pain resolved within a few weeks. Incredibly she lost no weight throughout the whole ordeal."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some patients aren't so lucky. Their symptoms are more severe or longer lasting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt; Photo: N F/peopleimages.com/Adobe Stock&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Serious side effects of starting GLP-1 Agonists&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to &lt;a href="https://nypost.com/2024/09/09/health/report-ozempic-and-other-weight-loss-drugs-linked-to-162-us-deaths/#:~:text=Weight%20loss%20shots%20like%20Ozempic,over%20the%20past%20six%20months" target="_blank" rel="sponsored"&gt;an article&lt;/a&gt; in the New York Post, since 2018, a total of 10,000 serious or life-threatening reactions have been reported to the FDA Adverse Event Reporting System database (FAERS).  And sadly, medical professionals and manufacturers have reported that these shots were a factor in 162 deaths. The number of these deaths rose by an astonishing 40% over a recent six month period as more and more people started using them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Roberts says, "The reality is that the risk of death while taking these drugs is probably no greater than many other very common drugs. This just underscores the general principle that there are inherent risks in taking any kind of medication."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/9192250/" target="_blank" rel="sponsored"&gt;1997 study&lt;/a&gt; unfortunately found that, more often than not, doctors fail to tell their patients about the risks. So Roberts encourages patients to take on the responsibility of informing themselves, weighing the risks and considering all their options before taking a drug.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href="https://medlineplus.gov/druginfo/meds/a618008.html#:~:text=Semaglutide%20injection%20may%20increase%20the,swallowing;%20or%20shortness%20of%20breath" target="_blank" rel="sponsored"&gt;Semaglutide label&lt;/a&gt; lists the following potential side effects:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Pancreatitis.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Thyroid tumors, including cancer.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Severe gastrointestinal disease such as stomach paralysis and intestinal blockage.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Bloating, severe constipation, nausea, and vomiting.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Acute kidney injury.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Hypoglycemia.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Gallbladder disease including Gallstones and inflammation of the gallbladder.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Allergic reactions.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Vision changes.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Rapid or pounding heartbeat.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Suicidal behavior and ideation.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;More recent studies have found other concerning side effects not listed on the label. The following represent a couple of these studies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to a &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/38937282/" target="_blank" rel="sponsored"&gt;2024 study&lt;/a&gt; reported in the journal, Diabetes, Obesity and Metabolism, up to 60% of weight lost on Liraglutide is lean muscle mass, which can weaken physical function and slow metabolism. "That means that for every three pounds you lose, almost two of them could be from muscle," Roberts says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A &lt;a href="https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jamaophthalmology/fullarticle/2820255#google_vignette" target="_blank" rel="sponsored"&gt;2025 population study&lt;/a&gt; reported in JAMA Ophthalmology found there is approximately a threefold increased risk of a sudden vision loss called non-arteritic Anterior Ischemic Optic Neuropathy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A &lt;a href="https://www.medscape.com/viewarticle/clinical-trials-may-not-differentiate-data-show-women-more-2025a1000lb2?form=fpf" target="_blank" rel="sponsored"&gt;2025 article&lt;/a&gt; in Medscape reported FAERS analysis found incidences of anosmia, (loss of smell), dysgeusia (altered taste), tinnitus (ringing in the ears), dysphonia (voice changes), hearing disabilities and gastroesophageal reflux disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt; Photo: Kyrylo Ryzhov/Adobe Stock&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Stopping GLP-1 Agonists: Brace for weight regain&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you're thinking about stopping GLP-1 agonists, be prepared for what's likely to happen. Research published in Diabetes, Obesity and Metabolism showed that &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/35441470/" target="_blank" rel="sponsored"&gt;327 participants in the study&lt;/a&gt; regained two thirds of their weight within a year after discontinuing the shots.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Additional &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S2589537024000543" target="_blank" rel="sponsored"&gt;research published in Sciencedirect&lt;/a&gt; showed that the weight people regain after the shots has a higher fat-to-muscle ratio, leading to a lowered metabolic rate and increased metabolic dysfunction.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Anyone coming off these drugs must understand this near-certain outcome if they want to prevent it," Roberts says. "If people coming off the medications will treat the drugs as a jump start to optimal health and weight, rather than the means to it and then take certain steps, they can maintain the weight loss and continue to lose weight if necessary."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt; Photo: Dmitry Lobanov/Shutterstock.com&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;How to maintain weight loss after the shots&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The first step is to accept the fact that there is no short cut to optimal health and weight," Roberts says. "The laws of health cannot be circumvented with any kind of medication. You may have lost some weight with the shots, but it will all come back with a vengeance unless you adhere to those laws."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The second step is to identify any underlying health issues that may be causing your stubborn weight or contributing to conditions that cause it. "Depression, insomnia, hormone imbalances, bad bacteria in the gut, liver/gallbladder problems, insulin resistance, leptin resistance, toxins and deficiencies can all contribute to both weight gain and stubborn weight," Roberts says. &lt;a href="https://app.gohighlevel.com/v2/preview/V4PKJFd02o0yv0Z3BF0e?utm_source=KSL&amp;amp;utm_medium=display" target="_blank" rel="sponsored"&gt;At Health Utah&lt;/a&gt;, it is the first order of business to identify these.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Each patient undergoes a specialized non-invasive body scan. The scan is a functional state assessment of the body which provides an immediate overview of the patient's physiology, stress, fatigue, risk factors, and potential underlying conditions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Prior to every appointment at Health Utah, patients fill out a proprietary questionnaire that also can identify these underlying problems. The questionnaire is the result of Roberts' 30 years of experience and research. There is almost always a perfect correlation between the results of the scan and the questionnaire. Roberts uses both of these to guide him through a 40-minute consultation and evaluation with each patient.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The third step is to address all underlying health conditions through a customized protocol of care. A care plan can include therapies, supplementation, hypnotherapy, coaching and more.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The final step is to create a customized, healthy and sustainable food plan. Roberts says, "The shots work partially because they reduce the calories you eat. But the shots ultimately fail, like almost every other diet, precisely because they reduce the calories you eat. Calorie reduction never works long term because your body's metabolism slows down when threatened by reduced calories."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At Health Utah they don't cut calories, count calories, count macros or points. They don't have you cut out whole categories of food like carbs. They don't tell you to eat all meat or all fat or give you any other faddish diet. They customized your food plan according to your body.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Take these steps and you will likely be able to maintain the weight you lost while on the shots and get healthier at the same time, something the shots could never do," Roberts says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Special offer&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;In any health or weight loss journey, it is essential to have the help of family and friends. In a British study, researchers found that both men and women had almost twice as much success losing weight when they did it with a partner.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So &lt;a href="https://app.gohighlevel.com/v2/preview/V4PKJFd02o0yv0Z3BF0e?utm_source=KSL&amp;amp;utm_medium=display" target="_blank" rel="sponsored"&gt;Health Utah&lt;/a&gt; is offering this, their most popular weight loss package, for $59 for two people. You and a friend can get tested, receive a 17-page report, take the proprietary survey and get a consultation with Dr. Roberts. The scan alone is normally $300 for one person.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Call (801) 609-3478 or visit &lt;a href="https://app.gohighlevel.com/v2/preview/V4PKJFd02o0yv0Z3BF0e?utm_source=KSL&amp;amp;utm_medium=display" target="_blank" rel="sponsored"&gt;Health Utah&lt;/a&gt; today to schedule your appointment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The opinions and conclusions expressed in this article are the sponsor's own and do not reflect the views or opinions of KSL.com. This Site Does Not Provide Medical Advice. Any content on this Site, such as text, graphics, images, information obtained from, or contained on this Site are for informational purposes only. The content is not intended to be a substitute for professional medical advice, diagnosis, or treatment. Always seek the advice of your physician or other qualified health provider with any questions you may have regarding a medical condition. Never disregard professional medical advice or delay in seeking it because of something you have read on this site! The owner and operator of this site do not recommend or endorse any specific tests, physicians, products, procedures, opinions, or other information that may be mentioned on the site. Reliance on any information provided by the Operator, including their employees, contractors or others appearing on the Site at the invitation of the Operator, or other visitors to the Site is solely at your own risk. If you think you may have a medical emergency, call your doctor or 911 immediately.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>KSL.com</author><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 22:00:45 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMirAFBVV95cUxQVXJNRTdfZE83Z1RoeW1XRkFjMzVxWkhGZkJNcnp0ekFRYjhkaHdacDI3d2RINHFMRlQwa3JySWRPYWpSU2lEcFdGb0lMREU1eXc1Tk15Y3paT2tWYm1FSlNWWWYxdXh6MWx3Q241QVhGNXAyeGRMTlYzNGdEYndSM1ZKUmYzRHBOLWdrSER4ajRlb3hBeWhFeS00X1NvVUpaZzVLYjg3VEhseVEw</guid></item><item><title>什么触发发脾气？感觉过载可能是罪魁祸首-神经科学新闻</title><link>https://neurosciencenews.com/sensory-overload-tantrum-29968/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content body-color clearfix link-color-wrap"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary: &lt;/strong&gt;New research reveals a distinct brain activity signature in children who become overwhelmed by sensory input such as noise, touch, or bright lights. Using functional MRI, scientists found that overly sensitive children show reduced activation in outward-facing sensory and motor networks while increasing activation in inward-focused networks tied to cognition and impulse control.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This compensatory shift appears to help them manage emotional overload but also contributes to strong behavioral reactions. The results suggest that understanding each child’s unique neural pattern could guide more personalized and effective sensory therapies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Facts:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class="wp-block-list"&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Distinct Neural Pattern:&lt;/strong&gt; Over-responsive children display reduced sensory–motor network activity paired with heightened inward-focused cognitive network activity.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Opposite in Less Sensitive Kids:&lt;/strong&gt; Children who are not overwhelmed show the reverse activation pattern, indicating different neural strategies for processing input.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Therapeutic Potential:&lt;/strong&gt; Mapping these patterns may help clinicians tailor sensory interventions for children with sensory-induced emotional and behavioral challenges.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Source: &lt;/strong&gt;UCSF&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;In the search for a way to measure different forms of a condition called sensory processing disorder, neuroscientists are using imaging to see how young brains process sensory stimulation.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Now, investigators at UC San Francisco have found a distinctive pattern for overwhelm in some children who are overly sensitive to sound, touch, and visual information. The finding could one day help clinicians refine treatments for kids who have strong emotional and behavioral reactions, such as tantrums, to their sensory environment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sensory processing disorder affects how the brain understands and responds to sensory information but still lacks an official medical diagnosis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study, which was funded by the National Institutes of Health (NIH), appears in the &lt;em&gt;Journal of Neurodevelopmental Disorders&lt;/em&gt; on Nov. 21, 2025.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Researchers at UCSF studied 83 neurodivergent children between the ages of 8 and 12 years old. About half were highly sensitive to certain noises, lights, or tactile sensations, while the other half weren’t.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When scientists imaged their brains using functional MRI, which measures brain activity by detecting changes in blood oxygenation levels, they found significant differences between the two groups.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For over-responsive children, the activity in brain networks that govern so-called “outward” functions, such as motor skills and sensation, was low, while the activity in brain networks that regulate “inward” functions, like cognition and impulse control, was high. This was exactly opposite of the pattern that scientists observed in the less sensitive children.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“We think that when you are overstimulated by sensory input, you compensate by dialing up your brain’s inward-focused networks to gain self-control. You also dial down your outward-focused networks to minimize sensory input,” said Pratik Mukherjee, MD, PhD, a UCSF neuroradiology professor and co-senior author of the study with Elysa Marco, MD, a pediatric neurologist.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The kids who aren’t emotionally overwhelmed by the input — some are even under-responsive to it — do the opposite.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Past research indicates 5% to 12% of children in the U.S. have sensory processing challenges, and this may explain much of the emotional volatility in the school-age population. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Treatment for over-responsive children often focuses on gradually exposing them to sensory input over time so they learn to tolerate it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mukherjee said the team’s findings could help improve these therapies: “If we know an individual child’s brain patterns and how that maps to emotion and behavior, we may be able to use this to personalize treatments.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Funding:&lt;/strong&gt; The National Institutes of Health (5R01MH116950‐04).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Key Questions Answered:&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;div class="schema-faq wp-block-yoast-faq-block"&gt;&lt;div class="schema-faq-section" id="faq-question-1763761641408"&gt;&lt;strong class="schema-faq-question"&gt;Q: What brain pattern marks children who are overwhelmed by sensory input?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;p class="schema-faq-answer"&gt;A: Lower activity in outward sensory–motor networks and higher activity in inward cognitive-control networks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="schema-faq-section" id="faq-question-1763761643406"&gt;&lt;strong class="schema-faq-question"&gt;Q: How does this differ from children who are not overly sensitive?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;p class="schema-faq-answer"&gt;A: Less sensitive children show the opposite pattern, engaging outward networks more strongly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="schema-faq-section" id="faq-question-1763761642830"&gt;&lt;strong class="schema-faq-question"&gt;Q: How could these findings improve treatment?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;p class="schema-faq-answer"&gt;A: Individual brain patterns may help clinicians tailor sensory therapies to each child.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h3 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Editorial Notes:&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul class="wp-block-list has-background"&gt;&lt;li&gt;This article was edited by a Neuroscience News editor.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Journal paper reviewed in full.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Additional context added by our staff.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;About this neuroscience and neurodevelopment research news&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="has-background"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Author: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#73391600005d311601071b1c1f1733061000155d161706" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Jess Berthold&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Source: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://ucsf.edu" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;UCSF&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Contact: &lt;/strong&gt;Jess Berthold – UCSF&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Image: &lt;/strong&gt;The image is credited to Neuroscience News&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="has-background"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Original Research: &lt;/strong&gt;Open access.&lt;br&gt;“&lt;a href="https://jneurodevdisorders.biomedcentral.com/articles/10.1186/s11689-025-09656-y" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;A neural substrate for sensory over-responsivity defined by exogenous and endogenous brain systems&lt;/a&gt;” by Elysa Marco et al. &lt;em&gt;Journal of Neurodevelopmental Disorders&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr class="wp-block-separator has-text-color has-pale-cyan-blue-color has-alpha-channel-opacity has-pale-cyan-blue-background-color has-background"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Abstract&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A neural substrate for sensory over-responsivity defined by exogenous and endogenous brain systems&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Background&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Exogenous (outward-directed) and endogenous (inward-directed) neural systems are essential for cognition and behavior. However, how they are altered in neurodiverse (ND) children remains unanswered in part due to heterogeneity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sensory over-responsivity (SOR), the most prevalent form of sensory processing disorder (SPD), serves as a quintessential paradigm for investigating the interaction between exogenous and endogenous brain networks given that both basic and higher-order sensory processing are substantially implicated in this condition.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Methods&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Neurodiverse children ages 8–12 years old (&lt;em&gt;n&lt;/em&gt; = 83; 30 females and 53 males) were directly assessed for SOR using a structured clinical evaluation, the Sensory Processing 3 Dimensions Assessment (SP3D:A), and underwent 3 Tesla MRI. 39 ND children presented with SOR (ND/SOR) and 44 ND children presented without SOR (ND/NO-SOR).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Exogenous and endogenous functional connectivity networks (FCNs) were generated through independent component analysis and investigated with two local functional connectivity (FC) measures, fractional amplitude of low-frequency fluctuations (fALFF) and regional homogeneity (ReHo), as well as a long-range FC measure, dual regression (DR).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Moreover, we examined FC in the context of behavioral regulation as assessed through the Behavioral Assessment System for Children, 3rd edition (BASC-3), categorizing children as “resilient” or “dysregulated” through latent profile analysis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Results&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;In general, ND/SOR children exhibit reduced long-range exogenous FC. However, in terms of local FC, we find that ND/SOR children have reduced exogenous and elevated endogenous FC which is diametrically opposed to ND/NO-SOR children. Furthermore, this double dissociation is specific to ND children who are behaviorally resilient, while emotionally dysregulated ND children possess a distinct pattern.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Achieving optimal brain system connectivity—a balanced contrast—is influenced by sensory over-responsivity and essential for resilience.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p class="clear"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Neuroscience News</author><pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 21:53:14 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMibEFVX3lxTE03eFdzdnBleUVISXpFMXpZRlJfOUdHa1JaY3JMN3N0R3Q1VlA2SVVHQVVOUkFQVEJaWEZ0QWQtUkF0c3FObmg3T1h1UUFLVGt1MHdYbHQtTkpHbllBLWZwV2RONGVjZ1oxeDNSbw</guid></item></channel></rss>