<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>GNews Health</title><link>https://news.google.com/</link><description></description><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>犹他州的麻疹疫情调查被拒绝交谈的患者阻止- Ars Technica</title><link>https://arstechnica.com/health/2025/10/measles-outbreak-investigation-in-utah-blocked-by-patient-who-refuses-to-talk/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content post-content-double"&gt;
                      
                      
          &lt;p&gt;A measles investigation amid a large, ongoing outbreak at the Arizona-Utah border has hit a roadblock as the first probable case identified in the Salt Lake City area refuses to work with health officials, the local health department reported this week.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There have been over 150 cases collectively across the two states, mostly in northwestern Mohave County, &lt;a href="https://www.azdhs.gov/preparedness/epidemiology-disease-control/measles/index.php"&gt;Arizona&lt;/a&gt;, and the southwest health district of &lt;a href="https://avrpublic.dhhs.utah.gov/uwss/"&gt;Utah&lt;/a&gt;, in the past two months. Both areas have abysmally low vaccination rates: In Mohave County, only &lt;a href="https://apps.azdhs.gov/IDRREportStats"&gt;78.4 percent of kindergartners&lt;/a&gt; in the 2024–2025 school year were vaccinated against measles, according to state records. In the southwest district of Utah, &lt;a href="https://immunize-training.at.utah.gov/captivate/UtahSchoolsData_Kinder_UpdatedApr2025.html"&gt;only 80.7 percent&lt;/a&gt; of kindergartners in the 2024–2025 school year had records of measles vaccination. Public health experts say vaccination coverage of 95 percent is necessary to keep the disease from spreading in a community.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While the outbreak has largely exploded along the border, cases are also creeping to the north, toward Salt Lake County, which encompasses the city. Utah County, which sits just south of Salt Lake County, has identified eight cases, including &lt;a href="https://health.utahcounty.gov/2025/10/31/new-measles-case-in-utah-county/"&gt;a new case reported today&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Uncooperative case&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Salt Lake County likely has a new one, too—the first for the county this year—as well as possible exposures. But, they can’t confirm it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;County health officials said that a health care provider in the area contacted them late on Monday to tell them about a patient who very likely has measles. The officials then spent a day reaching out to the person, who refused to answer questions or cooperate in any way. That included refusing to share location information so that other people could be notified that they were potentially exposed to one of the most infectious viruses known.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“The patient has declined to be tested, or to fully participate in our disease investigation, so we will not be able to technically confirm the illness or properly do contact tracing to warn anyone with whom the patient may have had contact,” Dorothy Adams, executive director of Salt Lake County Health Department, said in &lt;a href="https://www.saltlakecounty.gov/health/news/probable-first-case-of-measles-in-salt-lake-county/"&gt;a statement&lt;/a&gt;. “But based on the specific symptoms reported by the healthcare provider and the limited conversation our investigators have had with the patient, this is very likely a case of measles in someone living in Salt Lake County.”&lt;/p&gt;

          
                      &lt;p class="ars-interlude-container in-content-interlude mx-auto max-w-xl"&gt;
            &lt;/p&gt;
                  &lt;/div&gt;

              &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Ars Technica</author><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 19:58:53 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiuAFBVV95cUxQOVBIWlRsVl93WGdzTUhwQlN0VVI5anBwa3c4OTNuOW5aa1ZvQ2NsNzZOaU9TT0JaT1FpaWhROE1rMGctQkpZelliRzdWVXloSGM0Y0J6enRPRDQxdE5kQ0NORUx0LVVYUlBVa2V6c3llU1VzUDNxZWJnTHJSX0tETjJLb0ZoY01KS0hjZ0JHb3Q2eGRybXpWcTVsLXQydkZraTY4ZDRGZHE2N3hta2JsNFU5cUo3RWYx</guid></item><item><title>抑郁症消失了，但性欲却没有回来：抗抑郁药的隐藏面- Ynetnews</title><link>https://www.ynetnews.com/health_science/article/r1xdqvzjbe</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div data-contents="true"&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="8tkqo" data-offset-key="oonn-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="oonn-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="oonn-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;In an era when depression and anxiety are described as global epidemics, SSRIs — selective serotonin reuptake inhibitors — have transformed psychiatry, helping millions recover and even saving lives. Yet alongside their proven benefits, awareness is growing of a lesser-known, often silenced side effect: sexual dysfunction that may persist long after patients stop taking the medication.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="8tkqo" data-offset-key="7782n-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="7782n-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="7782n-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;“I was on Cipralex for two and a half months,” wrote one man in an online support group. “While on it, I had almost no libido, trouble maintaining an erection, and less physical pleasure — even kisses felt dull. Months after stopping, some of that feeling returned, but not all of it. I later found out that for some people, the effects never go away. If I’d known this, I might have made a different decision — it’s wrong that psychiatrists don’t warn patients.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure data-block="true" data-editor="8tkqo" data-offset-key="2oktk-0-0" contenteditable="false"&gt;&lt;div class="ArticleImageComponenta full_wide firstImageInArticle firstImageInArticleBody"&gt;&lt;a class="gelleryOpener" aria-label="open article gallery" data-image-id="ArticleImageData.HkxUATwGk11l" id="image_ArticleImageData.HkxUATwGk11l"&gt;&lt;p class="galleryCounterExpand"&gt;&lt;span class="numOfImg"&gt;3&lt;/span&gt; View gallery &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="expand" aria-hidden="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img id="ReduxEditableImage_ArticleImageData.HkxUATwGk11l" src="https://ynet-pic1.yit.co.il/cdn-cgi/image/format=auto/picserver6/crop_images/2025/10/27/HJMJTAJTRgg/HJMJTAJTRgg_0_0_1000_527_0_x-large.jpg" alt="הפרעה בתפקוד המיני גבר" title="Sexual dysfunction that may persist long after patients stop taking the medication  (Photo: Shutterstock) " aria-hidden="false"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class="mobileView"&gt;&lt;img id="ReduxEditableImage_ArticleImageData.HkxUATwGk11l" src="https://ynet-pic1.yit.co.il/cdn-cgi/image/format=auto/picserver6/crop_images/2025/10/27/HJMJTAJTRgg/HJMJTAJTRgg_0_0_1000_527_0_x-large.jpg" alt="הפרעה בתפקוד המיני גבר" title="Sexual dysfunction that may persist long after patients stop taking the medication  (Photo: Shutterstock) " aria-hidden="false"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="ImageDetails"&gt;&lt;p class="ImageCaption"&gt;&lt;span disabled class="" contenteditable="false"&gt;Sexual dysfunction that may persist long after patients stop taking the medication &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="ImageCredit"&gt;(&lt;span disabled class="" contenteditable="false"&gt;Photo: Shutterstock&lt;/span&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="8tkqo" data-offset-key="13p2e-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="13p2e-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="13p2e-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;His post struck a nerve among thousands of patients — men and women — who take SSRIs. The lingering condition has a name: PSSD, or Post-SSRI Sexual Dysfunction. It describes sexual side effects that continue even after stopping the drug, including loss of libido, decreased pleasure, difficulty with arousal or orgasm, and numbness in the genitals.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="8tkqo" data-offset-key="ah9fh-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="ah9fh-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="ah9fh-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;A recent study in Epidemiology and Psychiatric Sciences found that in some patients, sexual function does not return to baseline even months or years after discontinuation — raising uncomfortable questions within psychiatry. Experts are divided: is this real, or the result of psychological factors?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="8tkqo" data-offset-key="6b0dk-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="6b0dk-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="6b0dk-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;According to Dr. Oren Tene, head of the psychiatric department at Tel Aviv’s Ichilov Hospital and director of the Mentalix Center for Mental Health, sexual side effects during SSRI use are well documented.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="8tkqo" data-offset-key="4o03o-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="4o03o-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="4o03o-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;“It’s a known phenomenon,” he says. “It’s almost a cruel trade-off — when serotonin levels rise and mood improves, sexual function often declines. Nearly all SSRIs do this, some more than others. It’s a class-wide effect.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="8tkqo" data-offset-key="714p7-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="714p7-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="714p7-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;The symptoms, he explains, vary. “We commonly see reduced libido and delayed orgasm. Men may experience erectile issues, and women may experience decreased lubrication. Ironically, this particular side effect is sometimes used therapeutically — SSRIs are prescribed to men with premature ejaculation. But when the delay is excessive, it becomes frustrating for both partners.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="8tkqo" data-offset-key="37t8t-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="37t8t-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="37t8t-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;Dr. Tene adds that anxiety and depression themselves can suppress sexual function: “I tell patients that depression and good sex don’t go hand in hand. Sometimes the net effect of treatment is still positive.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="8tkqo" data-offset-key="8ije5-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="8ije5-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="8ije5-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;While side effects during treatment are well established, what happens after stopping the medication remains contentious. “That’s where it gets controversial,” says Dr. Tene. “Does sexual dysfunction sometimes persist afterward? Literature increasingly suggests yes. It’s hard to study, but it seems to happen to a subset of patients, though we don’t know how many.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure data-block="true" data-editor="8tkqo" data-offset-key="fa8lo-0-0" contenteditable="false"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="8tkqo" data-offset-key="28ahu-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="28ahu-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="28ahu-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;Science has yet to pinpoint a cause. “Physiologically, there’s no clear explanation,” he says. “When the drug is in the system, we know serotonin interacts with dopamine and norepinephrine. But after discontinuation, theoretically, there’s no reason for ongoing symptoms. We just don’t know.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="8tkqo" data-offset-key="d0vsu-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="d0vsu-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="d0vsu-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;Underreporting is also likely, he adds. “Patients don’t always connect the dots. The most common complaints are reduced sensation, less pleasure, erectile issues, or delayed ejaculation. Many describe feeling ‘numb.’ Men seem to report it more, but women often describe more severe symptoms.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="8tkqo" data-offset-key="fnjau-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="fnjau-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="fnjau-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;Even within the medical community, there’s disagreement. “Some doctors argue patients misremember that their sexual function didn’t change much from before. The topic is difficult to study, and documenting every possible side effect is impossible.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="8tkqo" data-offset-key="80ks8-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="80ks8-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="80ks8-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;Dr. Tene stresses caution: “These are life-saving medications. Listing every rare or disputed side effect could scare patients away from treatment. On the other hand, patients deserve informed consent. It’s a delicate balance.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="8tkqo" data-offset-key="evmd5-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="evmd5-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="evmd5-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;What can be done when symptoms persist? “Unfortunately, we don’t have a specific treatment,” says Dr. Tene. “For most, it resolves — sometimes after weeks or months, occasionally longer. But there’s no guaranteed fix.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="8tkqo" data-offset-key="38fld-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="38fld-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="38fld-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;Yifat Mekler, a sexologist and couples therapist at Rambam Health Care Campus, agrees that the condition is real but often temporary. “In most cases, symptoms fade within weeks to two months. Stopping antidepressants abruptly can prolong recovery — it shocks the nervous system and delays adjustment,” she explains.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure data-block="true" data-editor="8tkqo" data-offset-key="4c7gi-0-0" contenteditable="false"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="8tkqo" data-offset-key="b4lo2-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="b4lo2-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="b4lo2-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;Even when the body recovers, the mind can keep the problem alive. “The physical and psychological aspects are intertwined,” Mekler says. “Men often develop performance anxiety — they focus on what might go wrong instead of being present in the moment. That stress raises cortisol and adrenaline, which suppresses the parasympathetic response needed for arousal. It becomes a vicious cycle.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="8tkqo" data-offset-key="4fd3r-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="4fd3r-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="4fd3r-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;Therapeutic support, she adds, is crucial. “Sex therapy helps men shift focus away from performance and back to sensuality and connection. Couples can explore intimacy that isn’t centered on intercourse. If anxiety persists, psychiatric follow-up or temporary use of medications like Viagra can help.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="8tkqo" data-offset-key="bo28o-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="bo28o-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="bo28o-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;The discussion around PSSD has exposed a painful dilemma for many patients: the fear of losing sexual vitality versus the desperation to escape depression and anxiety. The result is growing mistrust toward psychiatry — and confusion about what patients are told, and what remains unsaid.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="8tkqo" data-offset-key="7364d-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="7364d-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="7364d-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;But psychiatrists warn that public fear can have deadly consequences. “We encourage people who need these drugs to take them,” says Dr. Tene. “SSRIs can truly save lives and alter the course of illness.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="8tkqo" data-offset-key="dm69q-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="dm69q-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="dm69q-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;He cautions against alarmism. “When public discourse demonizes these medications, it drives people away from help. The vast majority of SSRI users experience mild or temporary side effects, and overall, the benefit far outweighs the risk.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="8tkqo" data-offset-key="8fta0-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="8fta0-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="8fta0-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;His message is one of balance. “Every medication has side effects. The key is weighing benefits against risks. SSRIs are among the safest and most effective treatments we have for depression and anxiety. They’ve improved — and saved — millions of lives. Awareness is important, but so is perspective.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Ynetnews</author><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 17:37:02 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiakFVX3lxTFByZ0hHS3liOUpDN21nSjFYdkpnQWtqYmhrZW1sNjE1MThZMEFNTnl4cFp1ek1KeXVqamJFN2w5REN2NU9KNzVwZXNvSzQ1V3FaX3BtRkl4QTRKeUFKX1hEN3lJYjVLWnBZNEE</guid></item><item><title>一种分子可以带来治疗癌症、糖尿病和遗传疾病的革命性药物--但美国正在背弃它--Live Science</title><link>https://www.livescience.com/health/medicine-drugs/one-molecule-could-usher-revolutionary-medicines-for-cancer-diabetes-and-genetic-disease-but-the-us-is-turning-its-back-on-it</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="article-body" class="text-copy bodyCopy auto paywall-locker"&gt;
&lt;p id="afc2c2a6-a8cc-493c-9f50-5190f54f823c"&gt;On Dec. 31, 2019, the first reports emerged about a mysterious pneumonia of unknown cause circulating in China. On March 11, 2020, the World Health Organization declared COVID-19 a pandemic.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="ad-unit-1" class="ad-unit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On March 16, the first COVID-19 vaccine entered clinical trials.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a id="elk-seasonal" href="" data-url="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p id="afc2c2a6-a8cc-493c-9f50-5190f54f823c-2" class="paywall" aria-hidden="true"&gt;And by Dec. 14, members of the American public were getting the first doses of COVID-19 vaccines outside of trials.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="mid-article-leaderboard" class="ad-unit sm:hidden block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="5d0d2728-7b20-496e-988f-b0e2cff2fc6a"&gt;The first coronavirus vaccines were paradigm-shifting because they went from conceptualization to mass production in mere months. But they were also unique because they used a new way to stimulate the immune system — one that had been thoroughly studied for decades in order to be ready for deployment at this crucial moment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="ad-unit-2" class="ad-unit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The key to these vaccines was messenger RNA (mRNA), DNA's less-famous cousin. The power of the mRNA platform is that vaccines can be produced exceptionally quickly once a pathogen's genetics have been analyzed; conventional vaccine manufacturing takes months or years whereas mRNA vaccines can be made in mere weeks. So while it was once the subject of high school biology classes and niche pockets of biomedical science, mRNA was suddenly thrust into the public eye — and once there, it inspired relentless misinformation and controversy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While mRNA-based COVID-19 vaccines are the best known application of the molecule, researchers around the world have found additional uses for mRNA technology beyond the realm of vaccines. They're exploring its use for groundbreaking treatments for cancer and autoimmune disease, as well as for gene-editing therapies for genetic disorders. But that promise may be unrealized in the United States, where the federal government has declared war against this promising technology.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This new stance runs counter to the Trump administration's prior embrace of mRNA vaccines.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div id="slice-container-newsletterForm-articleInbodyContent-UcxdGRtEU48juVgNsVDxYV" class="slice-container newsletter-inbodyContent-slice newsletterForm-articleInbodyContent-UcxdGRtEU48juVgNsVDxYV slice-container-newsletterForm"&gt;&lt;div data-hydrate="true" class="newsletter-form__wrapper newsletter-form__wrapper--inbodyContent"&gt;&lt;div class="newsletter-form__container"&gt;&lt;section class="newsletter-form__main-section"&gt;&lt;p class="newsletter-form__strapline"&gt;Get the world’s most fascinating discoveries delivered straight to your inbox.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.livescience.com/tag/science-spotlight" id="95381192-f180-4a10-83df-2af5bbc2f677" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.livescience.com/tag/science-spotlight"&gt;&lt;figure class="van-image-figure pull-right inline-layout" data-bordeaux-image-check&gt;&lt;figcaption itemprop="caption description" class="pull-right inline-layout"&gt;&lt;span class="caption-text"&gt;Science Spotlight takes a deeper look at emerging science and gives you, our readers, the perspective you need on these advances. Our stories highlight trends in different fields, how new research is changing old ideas, and how the picture of the world we live in is being transformed thanks to science. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p id="c1a5471e-e7c8-49f5-9dd5-277d979a4dd7"&gt;"We do really have to give President Trump credit for introducing the mRNA platform to the world through his leadership in &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.gao.gov/products/gao-21-319" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.gao.gov/products/gao-21-319" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Operation Warp Speed&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;," said &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.bme.jhu.edu/people/faculty/jeff-coller/" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.bme.jhu.edu/people/faculty/jeff-coller/" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Jeff Coller&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, the Bloomberg distinguished professor of RNA biology and therapeutics at Johns Hopkins University. "The president should be taking a victory lap." But instead, the second Trump administration is actively dismantling this legacy, Coller told Live Science.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Vaccine skeptic Robert F. Kennedy Jr. now heads the Department of Health and Human Services (HHS), and opponents of both conventional and mRNA-based vaccines hold seats on the &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.cidrap.umn.edu/anti-science/rfk-announces-new-acip-members-including-vaccine-critics" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.cidrap.umn.edu/anti-science/rfk-announces-new-acip-members-including-vaccine-critics" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;country's most influential vaccine advisory committee&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. Since Trump's inauguration, federal scientists have faced mass layoffs, funding freezes, and memos warning them to disclose their involvement in research areas the administration has targeted, &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://kffhealthnews.org/news/article/nih-grants-mrna-vaccines-trump-administration-hhs-rfk/" target="_blank" data-url="https://kffhealthnews.org/news/article/nih-grants-mrna-vaccines-trump-administration-hhs-rfk/" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;including mRNA vaccines&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="van-image-figure extended-layout" data-bordeaux-image-check id="3e49d50d-7119-4d66-95f1-3d1e04f756a3"&gt;&lt;figcaption itemprop="caption description" class=" extended-layout"&gt;&lt;span class="caption-text"&gt;The COVID-19 vaccines manufactured by Pfizer-BioNTech and Moderna use mRNA as their base. Their invention, initial authorization and later approval signaled a shift into a new era of medicine. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="credit" itemprop="copyrightHolder"&gt;(Image credit: SOPA Images via Getty Images)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p id="e008d11a-7bfb-4bea-8cbf-d90cd2ed75e9"&gt;These actions had an immediate chilling effect on mRNA research and development in the U.S., Coller told Live Science. And then, in August, HHS canceled &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.hhs.gov/press-room/hhs-winds-down-mrna-development-under-barda.html" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.hhs.gov/press-room/hhs-winds-down-mrna-development-under-barda.html" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;nearly half a billion dollars of investment&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; into mRNA vaccine development.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I was shocked to see this, frankly," said &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.bme.jhu.edu/people/faculty/jordan-j-green/" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.bme.jhu.edu/people/faculty/jordan-j-green/" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Jordan Green&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, head of the Biomaterials and Drug Delivery Laboratory at Johns Hopkins, whose lab is developing both mRNA therapies and delivery systems to get the molecule into the body.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The cuts are sending ripples through biotech, making stakeholders question whether it's safe to set up shop in the U.S., or whether their mRNA investments would be better spent abroad. "It's just a shame because it's an unforced error; there's no reason," Green said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For now, HHS appears to be retreating primarily from mRNA vaccines; it noted "&lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://go.redirectingat.com/?id=92X1590019&amp;amp;xcust=livescience_us_5902847107638732389&amp;amp;xs=1&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.nature.com%2Farticles%2Fd41586-025-03093-6&amp;amp;sref=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.livescience.com%2Fhealth%2Fmedicine-drugs%2Fone-molecule-could-usher-revolutionary-medicines-for-cancer-diabetes-and-genetic-disease-but-the-us-is-turning-its-back-on-it" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-025-03093-6" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" rel="sponsored noopener" data-hl-processed="skimlinks" data-placeholder-url="https://go.redirectingat.com/?id=92X1590019&amp;amp;xcust=hawk-custom-tracking&amp;amp;xs=1&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.nature.com%2Farticles%2Fd41586-025-03093-6&amp;amp;sref=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.livescience.com%2Fhealth%2Fmedicine-drugs%2Fone-molecule-could-usher-revolutionary-medicines-for-cancer-diabetes-and-genetic-disease-but-the-us-is-turning-its-back-on-it" data-google-interstitial="false" data-merchant-name="nature.com" data-merchant-network="SkimLinks"&gt;&lt;u&gt;other uses of mRNA technology&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;" would not be affected by the cuts. But "the industry doesn't trust that," Coller told Live Science.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://grant-witness.us/" target="_blank" data-url="https://grant-witness.us/" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Grant Witness&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, a project tracking scientific grants under the Trump administration, mRNA research unrelated to vaccines has already been hit by grant terminations and funding freezes. So even if it's not being explicitly targeted, it's not necessarily being preserved. The &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://grant-witness.us/nih-data.html" target="_blank" data-url="https://grant-witness.us/nih-data.html" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;project's database shows&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; that the National Institutes of Health (NIH), part of HHS, terminated grants for projects developing mRNA-based treatments for cancer, Alzheimer's, pulmonary arterial hypertension and HIV, as well as grants for basic research about how mRNA works in healthy and diseased cells.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Here's what the United States stands to lose if the federal government broadly divests of mRNA medicines after spending decades readying the technology for prime time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a id="elk-d2a3352a-cf55-470d-8689-dc2e7c1c225d" class="paywall" aria-hidden="true" href="" data-url="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;h2 id="cancer-treatment-3"&gt;Cancer treatment&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="342976b6-0ddd-46fd-bc41-c50cbf45d811"&gt;On a molecular level, mRNA is a close cousin of DNA — and human cells are stuffed with it. These ubiquitous "messengers" copy instructions from DNA and relay them to other locations in the cell — namely, to protein-construction sites where the complex molecules that do most of the work in cells get made. mRNA also performs other key jobs in cells, such as helping control which genes are switched on and to what degree.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For decades prior to the &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.livescience.com/tag/pandemic" data-auto-tag-linker="true" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.livescience.com/tag/pandemic"&gt;pandemic&lt;/a&gt;, dedicated scientists pored over mRNA, learning how this class of molecules works in the body and how it might be leveraged to heal the sick and guard against disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I started doing this when I was like 21, back in the '90s, back when about 10 people on Earth knew what mRNA were," Coller said. Findings from Coller's lab later helped inform the development of Spikevax, the COVID-19 vaccine made by Moderna. But while COVID-19 vaccines are the best-known application of mRNA to date, they're far from the first.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="van-image-figure extended-layout" data-bordeaux-image-check id="1dc1a4b0-1dfd-4ac5-83d4-9f709e4cfd4f"&gt;&lt;figcaption itemprop="caption description" class=" extended-layout"&gt;&lt;span class="caption-text"&gt;RNA has a similar structure to its cousin DNA, although it's composed of only one strand, rather than two twisted together. mRNA is a "messenger" that carries information from DNA out into the cell. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="credit" itemprop="copyrightHolder"&gt;(Image credit: CHRISTOPH BURGSTEDT/SCIENCE PHOTO LIBRARY via Getty Images)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p id="c8b08212-9c5a-4194-a632-1009a1e3f6bb"&gt;The &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.thermofisher.com/us/en/home/industrial/pharma-biopharma/nucleic-acid-therapeutic-development-solutions/mrna-research/history-in-vitro-transcription.html" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.thermofisher.com/us/en/home/industrial/pharma-biopharma/nucleic-acid-therapeutic-development-solutions/mrna-research/history-in-vitro-transcription.html" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;first mRNA therapeutics company&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; was founded in 1997, and rather than targeting infectious disease, it had its sights set on &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC2192710/" target="_blank" data-url="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC2192710/" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;cancer treatment&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. Its approach ultimately hasn't &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC9218214/#s5" target="_blank" data-url="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC9218214/#s5" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;panned out in human trials&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, but in the meantime, other approaches to mRNA-based cancer treatment have gained traction.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cancer vaccines are a standout example, but in this context, the term "vaccine" is "a bit of a misnomer," said &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.mskcc.org/cancer-care/doctors/vinod-balachandran" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.mskcc.org/cancer-care/doctors/vinod-balachandran" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Dr. Vinod Balachandran&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, a pancreatic cancer surgeon-scientist and director of &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.mskcc.org/research-programs/olayan-center-cancer-vaccines-msk" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.mskcc.org/research-programs/olayan-center-cancer-vaccines-msk" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;The Olayan Center for Cancer Vaccines&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; (OCCV) at Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center. Rather than being given preventatively, like a COVID vaccine, cancer vaccines are "given to patients as a treatment; it is a therapy," he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These therapies are similar to conventional vaccines in that they &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.livescience.com/health/cancer/what-are-cancer-vaccines" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.livescience.com/health/cancer/what-are-cancer-vaccines"&gt;&lt;u&gt;train the immune system to recognize antigens&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, which are substances that act as "red flags" for foreign invaders, toxins or diseased cells. These include, for example, the spike protein of SARS-CoV-2 — the virus that causes COVID-19 — and certain molecules on cancer cells. Balachandran and colleagues have focused on pancreatic cancer, which has a five-year &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://seer.cancer.gov/help/seerstat/survival-session/survival-statistic-tab/relative-survival" target="_blank" data-url="https://seer.cancer.gov/help/seerstat/survival-session/survival-statistic-tab/relative-survival" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;relative survival&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; rate of &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.cancer.org/cancer/types/pancreatic-cancer/detection-diagnosis-staging/survival-rates.html" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.cancer.org/cancer/types/pancreatic-cancer/detection-diagnosis-staging/survival-rates.html" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;only 13%&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; — meaning people newly diagnosed with pancreatic cancer are about 13% as likely to survive the next five years compared with the general population.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://go.redirectingat.com/?id=92X1590019&amp;amp;xcust=livescience_us_7531980444943488164&amp;amp;xs=1&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.nature.com%2Farticles%2Fnature24462&amp;amp;sref=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.livescience.com%2Fhealth%2Fmedicine-drugs%2Fone-molecule-could-usher-revolutionary-medicines-for-cancer-diabetes-and-genetic-disease-but-the-us-is-turning-its-back-on-it" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.nature.com/articles/nature24462" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" rel="sponsored noopener" data-hl-processed="skimlinks" data-placeholder-url="https://go.redirectingat.com/?id=92X1590019&amp;amp;xcust=hawk-custom-tracking&amp;amp;xs=1&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.nature.com%2Farticles%2Fnature24462&amp;amp;sref=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.livescience.com%2Fhealth%2Fmedicine-drugs%2Fone-molecule-could-usher-revolutionary-medicines-for-cancer-diabetes-and-genetic-disease-but-the-us-is-turning-its-back-on-it" data-google-interstitial="false" data-merchant-name="nature.com" data-merchant-network="SkimLinks"&gt;&lt;u&gt;The researchers&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://go.redirectingat.com/?id=92X1590019&amp;amp;xcust=livescience_us_1061614370701347779&amp;amp;xs=1&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.nature.com%2Farticles%2Fs41586-022-04735-9&amp;amp;sref=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.livescience.com%2Fhealth%2Fmedicine-drugs%2Fone-molecule-could-usher-revolutionary-medicines-for-cancer-diabetes-and-genetic-disease-but-the-us-is-turning-its-back-on-it" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41586-022-04735-9" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" rel="sponsored noopener" data-hl-processed="skimlinks" data-placeholder-url="https://go.redirectingat.com/?id=92X1590019&amp;amp;xcust=hawk-custom-tracking&amp;amp;xs=1&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.nature.com%2Farticles%2Fs41586-022-04735-9&amp;amp;sref=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.livescience.com%2Fhealth%2Fmedicine-drugs%2Fone-molecule-could-usher-revolutionary-medicines-for-cancer-diabetes-and-genetic-disease-but-the-us-is-turning-its-back-on-it" data-google-interstitial="false" data-merchant-name="nature.com" data-merchant-network="SkimLinks"&gt;&lt;u&gt;have found&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; that, in the rare long-term survivors of pancreatic cancer, the immune system can recognize the cancer and fight off its recurrence. The team hoped to re-create that immune recognition in other patients by analyzing the genetics of their tumors to see what unique antigens they express. They then create customized vaccines that target those molecules.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We felt at the time [when we started this work] — this is back in 2017 — that the best technology for rapid custom cancer vaccination for patients was to use RNA," Balachandran said. Once you know a given patient's cancer genetics, a personalized mRNA vaccine that targets multiple antigens can be crafted in a matter of weeks. Conventional vaccines that require the antigens to be grown in the lab and purified would take many months to make.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"For cancer vaccination, speed is essential," Balachandran said. "These are patients who are facing deadly cancers, who require rapid treatment. So we do not have the luxury of waiting."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="9ecaeac2-f738-458f-952d-05e7374abe83"&gt;So far, the team has seen some success. In &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://go.redirectingat.com/?id=92X1590019&amp;amp;xcust=livescience_us_3902368646691044877&amp;amp;xs=1&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.nature.com%2Farticles%2Fs41586-024-08508-4&amp;amp;sref=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.livescience.com%2Fhealth%2Fmedicine-drugs%2Fone-molecule-could-usher-revolutionary-medicines-for-cancer-diabetes-and-genetic-disease-but-the-us-is-turning-its-back-on-it" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41586-024-08508-4" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" rel="sponsored noopener" data-hl-processed="skimlinks" data-placeholder-url="https://go.redirectingat.com/?id=92X1590019&amp;amp;xcust=hawk-custom-tracking&amp;amp;xs=1&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.nature.com%2Farticles%2Fs41586-024-08508-4&amp;amp;sref=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.livescience.com%2Fhealth%2Fmedicine-drugs%2Fone-molecule-could-usher-revolutionary-medicines-for-cancer-diabetes-and-genetic-disease-but-the-us-is-turning-its-back-on-it" data-google-interstitial="false" data-merchant-name="nature.com" data-merchant-network="SkimLinks"&gt;&lt;u&gt;an early-stage trial&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, they treated 16 patients who had undergone surgery for pancreatic ductal adenocarcinoma (PDAC), the most common form of pancreatic cancer, which has a five-year survival rate of &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S1424390325000936" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S1424390325000936" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;about 10% to 12%&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, though they fare a bit better when their cancer &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S074879832300464X" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S074879832300464X" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;can be surgically removed&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Within nine weeks of surgery, Balachandran said, each patient's tumor tissue was analyzed and a personalized vaccine was crafted and delivered alongside post-surgery cancer treatments, like chemotherapy. Half of the patients responded to their vaccine, producing immune cells that have persisted for nearly four years so far, and estimates suggest they could last an average of seven years, "with some lasting even beyond a decade," Balachandran said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The vaccine responders had a significantly lower risk of recurrence in the following three years than those who didn't respond, with six showing no signs of recurrence in that time frame. A &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.mskcc.org/cancer-care/clinical-trials/23-136" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.mskcc.org/cancer-care/clinical-trials/23-136" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;mid-stage trial&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; is now testing the vaccine in about 260 people to see how well it delays or prevents recurrence compared with standard treatment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Anything we can do to improve outcomes for these patients who really need help I think will be transformative for the field, for them, for their families — it will mean a lot," Balachandran said. "All other immune therapies and all other therapies have largely failed."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In this initial trial, vaccine production took over two months, in part because samples had to be shipped to overseas collaborators at BioNTech. "We are confident this can happen much faster" in the future, perhaps within a month, Balachandran said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Other scientists are working on off-the-shelf cancer vaccines that can help bridge the gap until a patient gets a personalized one. These vaccines use a mix of mRNA molecules to stir up a generic, first-line immune defense against cancer. In mice with different kinds of solid tumors, researchers led by &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://ufhealth.org/doctors/elias-sayour" target="_blank" data-url="https://ufhealth.org/doctors/elias-sayour" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Dr. Elias Sayour&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, a pediatric oncologist at the University of Florida, demonstrated that such a vaccine &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.livescience.com/health/cancer/universal-cancer-vaccine-heading-to-human-trials-could-be-useful-for-all-forms-of-cancer" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.livescience.com/health/cancer/universal-cancer-vaccine-heading-to-human-trials-could-be-useful-for-all-forms-of-cancer"&gt;&lt;u&gt;triggers anti-cancer responses by itself&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. And when used in combination with another cancer treatment, the mRNA mix can boost the effects of that therapy, Sayour's team has found.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="van-image-figure extended-layout" data-bordeaux-image-check id="fffe3107-52f4-42dc-9139-0aa093571f2a"&gt;&lt;figcaption itemprop="caption description" class=" extended-layout"&gt;&lt;span class="caption-text"&gt;A researcher working on a lung cancer vaccine in the Ose Immunotherapeutics laboratory in Nantes, France. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="credit" itemprop="copyrightHolder"&gt;(Image credit: LOIC VENANCE via Getty Images)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p id="f7816f2c-104e-4b96-a5dc-95bc2c048719"&gt;That team has now moved on to human patients, &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://clinicaltrials.gov/study/NCT05660408" target="_blank" data-url="https://clinicaltrials.gov/study/NCT05660408" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;with a two-pronged approach&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;: an off-the-shelf cancer vaccine, followed by a personalized one. They have also run trials of personalized &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.livescience.com/health/cancer/new-mrna-vaccine-treats-deadly-brain-cancer-and-it-triggers-a-strong-immune-response" target="_blank" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.livescience.com/health/cancer/new-mrna-vaccine-treats-deadly-brain-cancer-and-it-triggers-a-strong-immune-response"&gt;&lt;u&gt;vaccines for the deadly brain cancer glioblastoma&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, finding that the shots mount a strong, targeted immune response against these tumors that are usually difficult for the immune system to "see." Meanwhile, at another lab, scientists are testing a personalized vaccine in late-stage trials for &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.merck.com/news/merck-and-moderna-initiate-phase-3-study-evaluating-v940-mrna-4157-in-combination-with-keytruda-pembrolizumab-for-adjuvant-treatment-of-patients-with-resected-high-riskstage-iib-iv-melanom/" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.merck.com/news/merck-and-moderna-initiate-phase-3-study-evaluating-v940-mrna-4157-in-combination-with-keytruda-pembrolizumab-for-adjuvant-treatment-of-patients-with-resected-high-riskstage-iib-iv-melanom/" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;the skin cancer melanoma&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.merck.com/news/merck-and-moderna-initiate-phase-3-trial-evaluating-adjuvant-v940-mrna-4157-in-combination-with-keytruda-pembrolizumab-after-neoadjuvant-keytruda-and-chemotherapy-in-patients-with-certain-ty/" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.merck.com/news/merck-and-moderna-initiate-phase-3-trial-evaluating-adjuvant-v940-mrna-4157-in-combination-with-keytruda-pembrolizumab-after-neoadjuvant-keytruda-and-chemotherapy-in-patients-with-certain-ty/" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;non-small cell lung cancers&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pancreatic cancer has historically been an elusive target for the immune system because, compared to cancers like melanoma, its cells carry relatively few antigens, Balachandran explained. But pancreatic cancer can be targeted with these vaccines. That bodes well for using mRNA approaches to treat potentially many other cancers, and "I think that's really the most exciting take-home," he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Beyond cancer vaccines, Green and colleagues are leveraging mRNA to fight the disease in a different way: by forcing tumors to raise their own red flags to the immune system. Using &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S014296122300193X" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S014296122300193X" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;mRNA packaged inside nanoparticles&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, the researchers introduce immune-cell genes into cancer cells, prompting tumors to expose their antigens and secrete molecules that call immune cells to the area.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We can program that tumor cell to now act like an immune cell that helps teach other immune cells what its antigens look like, how to recognize it, how to destroy it," Green told Live Science. In mouse models of breast cancer &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.jidonline.org/article/S0022-202X(23)01370-2/fulltext" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.jidonline.org/article/S0022-202X(23)01370-2/fulltext" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;and melanoma&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, they combined this approach with an existing immunotherapy and found that it helped shrink and clear tumors from the body while also extending survival.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If shown to work in people, "this could just be off the shelf," he said. It would be one injectable that could work on any patient's solid tumor, he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a id="elk-7d18f44d-0d28-4163-8f01-61dc40bba4a3" class="paywall" aria-hidden="true" href="" data-url="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;h2 id="immune-reprogramming-3"&gt;Immune reprogramming&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="38f86836-613d-467e-97d5-a5f3ece1cc21"&gt;In cancer, scientists are exploring different ways to launch an immune attack against tumor cells, whether by igniting a generalized response or enabling cells to spot specific red flags. But in some diseases, the immune system itself is the culprit — and in those instances, mRNA can help rein in turncoat immune cells.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Autoimmune diseases — type 1 diabetes, multiple sclerosis, Crohn's, colitis — these can be treated with these mRNA and genetic-based therapies," potentially, Green said. The goal of these treatments would be to "tune the immune system" so it stops attacking healthy tissues.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In type 1 diabetes, for example, the immune system attacks beta cells, which make insulin, leaving the body too little of the hormone to control blood sugar. Green and colleagues are in the early stages of developing an mRNA medicine to reprogram the immune system so it better tolerates beta cells, rather than attacking them. They aim to do this &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://reporter.nih.gov/project-details/10835326" target="_blank" data-url="https://reporter.nih.gov/project-details/10835326" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;by targeting special immune cells in the liver&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; that promote a tolerant environment in the organ.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The liver is constantly exposed to antigens from food and from microbes in the gut, so immune activity is dialed down to prevent an overreaction. The team's idea is to deliver mRNA that codes for beta-cell proteins to the liver, essentially marking those beta-cell proteins as "safe" to the immune system. This, in turn, can increase the number of &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.livescience.com/health/nobel-prize-in-medicine-goes-to-trio-for-their-work-on-immune-tolerance" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.livescience.com/health/nobel-prize-in-medicine-goes-to-trio-for-their-work-on-immune-tolerance"&gt;&lt;u&gt;regulatory T cells&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; that recognize the proteins as safe; regulatory T cells keep other immune cells in check, and could thus help ward off further attacks on beta cells.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The problem with autoimmunity is that [the immune system] thinks parts of its own body are foreign," so it's trying to attack them, Green explained. The hope is that "we can use these mRNA medicines to train the immune system so that it sees, 'Oh no, this is fine.'" The work is currently in preclinical stages, as the team runs experiments with cells and lab mice to refine their mRNA nanoparticles.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Green calls this approach of fine-tuning specific cells' activity "genetic surgery." Rather than using a "blunter instrument," like immunosuppressive drugs, to broadly suppress the immune system, the surgery makes a precise change to counter only harmful immune activity. In the long run, the lab is looking to apply this same approach to other autoimmune diseases beyond diabetes, &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.science.org/doi/10.1126/sciadv.add8693" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.science.org/doi/10.1126/sciadv.add8693" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;such as multiple sclerosis&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, in which immune cells target myelin, the insulation surrounding nerve fibers in the brain and spinal cord.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Meanwhile, BioNTech &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.science.org/doi/10.1126/science.aay3638" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.science.org/doi/10.1126/science.aay3638" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;has published data&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; from its own early tests of an mRNA vaccine designed to quell autoimmunity against myelin. In mice, the vaccine expanded populations of immune cells that then kept the myelin-attacking cells in check, suppressing their activity without hobbling the immune system as a whole.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Elsewhere, researchers including &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.kianilab.com/people.html" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.kianilab.com/people.html" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Dr. Samira Kiani&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; of the University of Pittsburgh School of Medicine and &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://scholars.cmu.edu/2621-kathryn-whitehead/publications" target="_blank" data-url="https://scholars.cmu.edu/2621-kathryn-whitehead/publications" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Kathryn Whitehead&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; of Carnegie Mellon University are using mRNA to counter off-the-rails immune responses, such as the extreme inflammation seen in sepsis. Their approach, &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.biorxiv.org/content/10.1101/2025.02.24.639996v1.full.pdf" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.biorxiv.org/content/10.1101/2025.02.24.639996v1.full.pdf" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;described in a preprint&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, packages mRNA inside a tiny bubble of fat called a lipid nanoparticle (LNP), which then ferries the mRNA into immune cells. From there, the mRNA instructs the cells to make proteins called "zinc finger repressors," which latch onto genes and suppress their activity. In this case, they repressed a key &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/gene/4615" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/gene/4615" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;gene involved in the immune signaling&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; that can lead to runaway inflammation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In experiments with cells in lab dishes and with mice, this type of "epigenetic engineering" showed promise as a potential method for tuning the activity of the immune system. One perk of mRNA is that it degrades quickly in the body, the study authors wrote, so in theory, once the harmful inflammation is subdued, the immune system can get back to defending the body against germs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a id="elk-ba6bdffe-2241-4078-bc22-b74c4c6583b7" class="paywall" aria-hidden="true" href="" data-url="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;h2 id="gene-editing-3"&gt;Gene editing&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="05cce102-276a-43d8-9af3-368890b6b184"&gt;mRNA is also being used in tandem with the gene-editing system &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.livescience.com/58790-crispr-explained.html" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.livescience.com/58790-crispr-explained.html"&gt;&lt;u&gt;CRISPR&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; to revolutionize treatments for genetic disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Classical CRISPR systems use molecular scissors to snip through DNA strands and enable scientists to tweak specific segments of the molecule. And now, a modified system called base editing can be used to precisely change just one "letter" in DNA's code.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But if you want to use CRISPR for &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.livescience.com/gene-therapy-everything-you-need-to-know-about-the-dna-tweaking-treatments" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.livescience.com/gene-therapy-everything-you-need-to-know-about-the-dna-tweaking-treatments"&gt;&lt;u&gt;gene therapy&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, you must first get the scissors, as well as a "guide" molecule that directs them to the right spot — into human cells. And, ideally, the scissors enter only the cells you need to edit, said &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.gmc.vu.lt/en/research/researcher-profiles/dr-giedrius-gasiunas" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.gmc.vu.lt/en/research/researcher-profiles/dr-giedrius-gasiunas" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Giedrius Gasiūnas&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, a senior researcher in the Life Sciences Center at Vilnius University in Lithuania.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That's where mRNA packaged in nanoparticles could be a game changer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"This technology could be important for&lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt;in vivo&lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt;delivery," meaning the delivery of gene editors directly into the body, said Gasiūnas, who is also chief scientific officer of the biotech company &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://caszyme.com/leadership/" target="_blank" data-url="https://caszyme.com/leadership/" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Caszyme&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.livescience.com/health/genetics/the-worlds-1st-crispr-therapy-has-just-been-approved-heres-everything-you-need-to-know" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.livescience.com/health/genetics/the-worlds-1st-crispr-therapy-has-just-been-approved-heres-everything-you-need-to-know"&gt;&lt;u&gt;first CRISPR-based therapy approved&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; in the U.S. involved editing cells outside the body. The therapy treats two blood disorders by disabling a gene called &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://go.redirectingat.com/?id=92X1590019&amp;amp;xcust=livescience_us_6653006954087882564&amp;amp;xs=1&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.nature.com%2Farticles%2Fng2108&amp;amp;sref=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.livescience.com%2Fhealth%2Fmedicine-drugs%2Fone-molecule-could-usher-revolutionary-medicines-for-cancer-diabetes-and-genetic-disease-but-the-us-is-turning-its-back-on-it" target="_blank" data-url="https://go.redirectingat.com/?id=92X1590019&amp;amp;xcust=livescience_us_1298655195241651907&amp;amp;xs=1&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.nature.com%2Farticles%2Fng2108&amp;amp;sref=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.livescience.com%2Fhealth%2Fgenetics%2Fthe-worlds-1st-crispr-therapy-has-just-been-approved-heres-everything-you-need-to-know" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" rel="sponsored noopener" data-hl-processed="skimlinks" data-placeholder-url="https://go.redirectingat.com/?id=92X1590019&amp;amp;xcust=hawk-custom-tracking&amp;amp;xs=1&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.nature.com%2Farticles%2Fng2108&amp;amp;sref=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.livescience.com%2Fhealth%2Fmedicine-drugs%2Fone-molecule-could-usher-revolutionary-medicines-for-cancer-diabetes-and-genetic-disease-but-the-us-is-turning-its-back-on-it" data-google-interstitial="false" data-merchant-name="nature.com" data-merchant-network="SkimLinks"&gt;&lt;u&gt;BCL11A&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;; patients have blood-making stem cells removed from their bone marrow, edited in the lab and then returned to their bodies. But this complex treatment involves a month-long hospital stay, during which the edited stem cells give rise to new blood cells. By comparison, mRNA approaches to gene therapy would be &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.genomicseducation.hee.nhs.uk/blog/in-vivo-and-ex-vivo-gene-therapies-explained/" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.genomicseducation.hee.nhs.uk/blog/in-vivo-and-ex-vivo-gene-therapies-explained/" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;easier to administer and thus more likely to be scalable&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, Gasiūnas said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;mRNA isn't the only vehicle for getting CRISPR therapies into the body. Some existing gene-editing treatments &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://luxturna.com/how-does-luxturna-work/" target="_blank" data-url="https://luxturna.com/how-does-luxturna-work/" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;instead use harmless viruses&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, such as adeno-associated virus (AAV) vectors, and this same approach is being &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.synthego.com/blog/delivery-crispr-cas9" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.synthego.com/blog/delivery-crispr-cas9" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;applied to CRISPR&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; in some &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.huidagene.com/new/news/72#:~:text=Dosing%20the%20first%20patient%20in,of%20immune%2Drelated%20adverse%20effects." target="_blank" data-url="https://www.huidagene.com/new/news/72#:~:text=Dosing%20the%20first%20patient%20in,of%20immune%2Drelated%20adverse%20effects." referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;emerging therapies&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. But mRNA packaged inside nanoparticles is emerging as a key player in the field.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This application made headlines in the case of KJ, an infant who became the &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.livescience.com/health/genetics/us-baby-receives-first-ever-customized-crispr-treatment-for-genetic-disease" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.livescience.com/health/genetics/us-baby-receives-first-ever-customized-crispr-treatment-for-genetic-disease"&gt;&lt;u&gt;first person to receive a personalized CRISPR treatment&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. "The CRISPR technology was introduced as an mRNA," Coller said. "That is the critical feature that was necessary to get this to work."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="f1e60c6e-3ddf-47a2-a05b-06314808c612"&gt;&lt;blockquote class="vanilla-quoteblock"&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It's foolish to condemn mRNA because people didn't like vaccine mandates or mask mandates or whatever they didn't like."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;cite&gt;Dr. Seth Berkley, Brown University School of Public Health&lt;/cite&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p id="5e376e70-d5a8-4352-9a09-f0de5a218062"&gt;KJ was born with a severe form of carbamoyl phosphate synthetase 1 (CPS1) deficiency, an inherited disease that causes ammonia to accumulate in the body and affects an estimated &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC4364413/" target="_blank" data-url="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC4364413/" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;1 in 1.3 million people worldwide&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. The condition arises from mutations in the CPS1 gene, but in different patients, the gene is broken in different ways. To fix KJ's specific mutation, scientists developed a customized gene therapy consisting of a guide and an mRNA that carried instructions for a base editor into his liver cells, where CPS1 is most active.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The editor is so large that it cannot easily be accommodated by an AAV vector," said &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.med.upenn.edu/cvi/musunuru-laboratory.html" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.med.upenn.edu/cvi/musunuru-laboratory.html" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Dr. Kiran Musunuru&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, co-developer of the therapy and a professor at the University of Pennsylvania's Perelman School of Medicine. Because other potential delivery systems are too early in development, "LNPs are currently the best option," Musunuru told Live Science in an email.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The therapy was ready to administer within six months of KJ's birth. By 9 months old, he had received several doses of the therapy and was thriving; he was hitting milestones he may have never reached otherwise, his medical team reported in May. Had he not received the treatment, he would have needed a liver transplant once he got big enough.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a id="elk-339c7a85-c589-4e26-9e0e-4660a34d04bb" class="paywall" aria-hidden="true" href="" data-url="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;h2 id="promising-technology-at-risk-3"&gt;Promising technology at risk&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="6cb9ae19-fafc-406b-845c-ea7ebfc150cd"&gt;When it comes to the future of mRNA medicines in the U.S., vaccines for infectious disease currently have the bleakest outlook due to political barriers being raised around the technology. Among mRNA tech, vaccines have been the primary target of the federal government's ire, despite &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.livescience.com/health/viruses-infections-disease/we-have-basically-destroyed-what-capacity-we-had-to-respond-to-a-pandemic-says-leading-epidemiologist-michael-osterholm" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.livescience.com/health/viruses-infections-disease/we-have-basically-destroyed-what-capacity-we-had-to-respond-to-a-pandemic-says-leading-epidemiologist-michael-osterholm"&gt;&lt;u&gt;experts' warnings&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.livescience.com/health/medicine-drugs/these-decisions-were-completely-reckless-funding-cuts-to-mrna-vaccines-will-make-america-more-vulnerable-to-pandemics" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.livescience.com/health/medicine-drugs/these-decisions-were-completely-reckless-funding-cuts-to-mrna-vaccines-will-make-america-more-vulnerable-to-pandemics"&gt;&lt;u&gt;that abandoning the shots&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; will leave us vulnerable to pandemics.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It's foolish to condemn mRNA because people didn't like vaccine mandates or mask mandates or whatever they didn't like," &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://pandemics.sph.brown.edu/people/seth-berkley-md" target="_blank" data-url="https://pandemics.sph.brown.edu/people/seth-berkley-md" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Dr. Seth Berkley&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, an epidemiologist and senior adviser to the pandemic center at the Brown University School of Public Health, told Live Science. "What we need to do is improve upon them [mRNA vaccines] and understand what the best use of them is," which can only be accomplished through investing in further research.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="van-image-figure extended-layout" data-bordeaux-image-check id="44e20df2-047f-410b-833e-338fe9a6e6a0"&gt;&lt;figcaption itemprop="caption description" class=" extended-layout"&gt;&lt;span class="caption-text"&gt;Under the leadership of Robert F. Kennedy Jr., HHS has withdrawn support from mRNA vaccine research. The future of other uses of the technology is uncertain, which has prompted stakeholders to reconsider their R&amp;amp;D strategies in the U.S. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="credit" itemprop="copyrightHolder"&gt;(Image credit: Kevin Dietsch via Getty Images)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p id="20fea12c-e0a3-4fd5-addc-1b4937e5ed87"&gt;For now, other applications of mRNA don't appear to be a focus for funding cuts, although some projects have nonetheless been caught in the crosshairs of reduced federal spending. For his part, Musunuru told Live Science he's been in discussions with the Food and Drug Administration regarding ways to get more patients access to personalized gene therapies like KJ's, so that the technology isn't used only in a handful of special cases. When asked about potential funding cuts, he added, "Vaccines and therapies are so different that I do not expect the latter to be affected."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Green, however, anticipates that divestments from vaccines would have unanticipated impacts across the field, because mRNA therapies and vaccines are ultimately composed of very similar genetic molecules and delivery systems.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Regarding nanoparticles, "the vaccine development is … at the pioneering edge of this technology platform," Green said. He argues that cuts to vaccine R&amp;amp;D will inevitably undermine the development of nanoparticles that could be really useful in treating cancer or genetic disease. "It's going to set us back in a very broad way," he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The hits to vaccine research also aren't happening in isolation. Myriad federal science grants have been terminated or frozen; NIH agencies &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.science.org/content/article/house-republicans-add-support-maintaining-nih-budget-2026" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.science.org/content/article/house-republicans-add-support-maintaining-nih-budget-2026" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;may be facing steep funding cuts&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;; and the government shutdown ushered mass layoffs across leading health institutions. Sayour, the oncologist whose lab is developing personalized and universal cancer vaccines using mRNA, said federal grants have historically been critical to his research.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"None of this would be possible without the support of the federal government," Sayour told Live Science. "That is most certainly, 100% true." And that goes for every stage of research, from studies in lab dishes to large clinical trials.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These widespread cuts and more-targeted cuts to mRNA vaccines will not only starve the academic environments where new biotechnologies are typically nurtured, Coller said; they will also drive prospective talent, investors and industry stakeholders in the mRNA space away from the U.S. "In biotech, we're going to see, over the next five to 10 years, a significant 'brain drain,' where other countries build up their infrastructure," he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Coller knows this because he is a founding member of the &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://mrnamedicines.org/about/" target="_blank" data-url="https://mrnamedicines.org/about/" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Alliance for mRNA Medicines&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; (AMM), a global organization aimed at advancing and advocating for mRNA medicines. In the spring, AMM &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://mrnamedicines.org/new-amm-survey-the-future-of-mrna-is-at-risk/" target="_blank" data-url="https://mrnamedicines.org/new-amm-survey-the-future-of-mrna-is-at-risk/" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;surveyed over 100 leaders in the field&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. They primarily represented U.S.-headquartered pharmaceutical and biotechnology organizations but also included some based in Europe, Canada or Asia. Even prior to the major HHS cuts in August, these stakeholders were feeling squeezed; nearly half reported "already experiencing direct impacts" from federal policy changes tied to mRNA funding.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="a2056a2e-5c98-4661-8ed0-60b22045f2f3"&gt;&lt;blockquote class="vanilla-quoteblock"&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Let's not fool ourselves: mRNA is one of the three most important molecules in the body, with the other two being DNA and protein. It's the intermediary between them."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;cite&gt;Jeff Coller, Johns Hopkins University&lt;/cite&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p id="690cba34-96a6-405b-bfa0-f633c7ac605d"&gt;The cuts caused projects to be scaled back, partnerships to be terminated, and jobs to be lost. About 30% of respondents said that, if faced with further cuts, they might pivot away from mRNA, and 30% said they'd consider moving their operations to other countries. Over 80% agreed that anti-mRNA policies would drive talent away from the U.S. and toward other locales.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even as scientists contend with these big-picture problems on the national and international stage, skirmishes have also been unfolding at the state level. These battles primarily concern public access to mRNA vaccines but could potentially have broader ripple effects.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.legis.iowa.gov/legislation/BillBook?ba=SF360" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.legis.iowa.gov/legislation/BillBook?ba=SF360" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;bill still in committee in Iowa&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; would make administering an mRNA vaccine in the state a misdemeanor with a fine of $500 for each shot given. Another bill in &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.scstatehouse.gov/billsearch.php?billnumbers=4262&amp;amp;session126&amp;amp;summary=B" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.scstatehouse.gov/billsearch.php?billnumbers=4262&amp;amp;session126&amp;amp;summary=B" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;committee in South Carolina&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; would prohibit the use of mRNA-based "gene therapies" in the state, but makes an exception for therapies for noninfectious diseases, such as cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="6e502651-12be-4847-870b-1ad5097f85ce"&gt;It may be that most bills of this ilk never become law and some, like the one raised in South Carolina and &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://capitol.texas.gov/BillLookup/History.aspx?LegSess=89R&amp;amp;Bill=HB5022" target="_blank" data-url="https://capitol.texas.gov/BillLookup/History.aspx?LegSess=89R&amp;amp;Bill=HB5022" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;two dead&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://capitol.texas.gov/BillLookup/History.aspx?LegSess=89R&amp;amp;Bill=SB1887" target="_blank" data-url="https://capitol.texas.gov/BillLookup/History.aspx?LegSess=89R&amp;amp;Bill=SB1887" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;bills in Texas&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, purposely make exceptions for certain uses of mRNA. However, &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.billtrack50.com/billdetail/1808897" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.billtrack50.com/billdetail/1808897" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;others have been worded in ways&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; that made it unclear whether any mRNA medicine is permissible. If any of such bills ultimately pass at the state level, that could sway where mRNA companies can manufacture products and run clinical trials, Coller said. So, while an exodus of expertise unfolds at a national level, we may see an echo of that at the state level.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="daaae7e4-b8c8-4b37-86a2-f8387141c502"&gt;The future of mRNA medicine in the U.S. rests on many "ifs," and the worst-case scenario may not come to pass. But in the face of staggering uncertainty, researchers in the field are starting to look for better bets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Let's not fool ourselves: mRNA is one of the three most important molecules in the body, with the other two being DNA and protein. It's the intermediary between them," Coller said. "When the federal government sends a message that mRNA-based medicine and research is not wanted, you're basically saying that there's a whole branch of science that is no longer welcome within the U.S."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Live Science</author><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihgJBVV95cUxNN0ZnM0d4RWRuYzAzamc0SkltTXNlWktxalRBRldvS3YyVXRkTVFuSHFOY3lndTVvaWtjSjdETmcwTzNXMHFpYWRrYmN1VFloeDZ5eklLTnhLM3BFeWpjUkRMcFJXOWdId1I4WWtlQ04wR0JyVU5tSE5ZVzk0SjB4R0pwcWVTYUVTRExmN2hJdFJ0dFNwdEtHbEJvOXlDZGh0XzVGWFBXS25Id3BEQ2x4TE9TcmpYVnNkMVNTV1VRSmtReWZvMzhnSnlYbk1wVEFKRWJfMFBRaFEzQ0x3a1FiWmFsd2NpblNWSTFnWHNxTktiNGNraV83Sk93Rk9hUWlKUEdHZUNB</guid></item><item><title>Ichilov医生在治疗未接种疫苗的儿童后感染麻疹-以色列国家新闻</title><link>https://www.israelnationalnews.com/news/417119</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-content-inside article-content" id="articleContent" data-v-2a4c3726 data-v-e580db1b-s&gt;&lt;p id="intext-1" class="sideInf" data-v-2a4c3726 data-v-e580db1b-s data-v-4bdf62d7&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-v-2a4c3726 data-v-e580db1b-s&gt;Israel's Health Ministry has reported an unusual incident in which a doctor at Ichilov Hospital in Tel Aviv contracted measles virus after treating a girl who was not vaccinated against the disease and contracted it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-v-2a4c3726 data-v-e580db1b-s&gt;At the same time, there is concern that two others on the medical staff were also infected.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-v-2a4c3726 data-v-e580db1b-s&gt;"The Health Ministry and Ichilov Hospital are conducting a thorough epidemiological investigation, and the matter is being investigated and followed," a statement read. "The Health Ministry reiterates its call for the public to get vaccinated."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="" album="true" data-v-2a4c3726 data-v-e580db1b-s&gt;Last week, &lt;a href="https://www.israelnationalnews.com/news/416818" target="_blank" data-v-2a4c3726 data-v-e580db1b-s&gt;an unvaccinated two-year-old girl died&lt;/a&gt; at Hadassah Ein Kerem Hospital in Jerusalem from complications caused by measles, raising the death toll of the ongoing outbreak of the disease to eight, all under the age of two and a half years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="intext-2" class="sideInf" data-v-2a4c3726 data-v-e580db1b-s data-v-4bdf62d7&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-v-2a4c3726 data-v-e580db1b-s&gt;The hospital stated that the toddler was hospitalized at the pediatric intensive care unit ten days ago in severe conditions with complications of measles and was connected to an ECMO machine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-v-2a4c3726 data-v-e580db1b-s&gt;Over 1,880 patients have been diagnosed with measles since the outbreak began in April.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-v-2a4c3726 data-v-e580db1b-s&gt;"We know that the illness is being underdiagnosed, and there are a few thousand additional patients with the disease," Sharon Alroy-Preis, Israel's chief epidemiologist, said. So far, 562 patients have been hospitalized, of whom 90% are children, the majority of whom are unvaccinated. "It is clear to us that the morbidity continues and will continue. We hope that we won't see an additional increase in scope, but we need to remember that there are still thousands of unvaccinated children in Jerusalem and other localities."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="z396inn" class="" data-v-2a4c3726 data-v-e580db1b-s&gt;



&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Israel National News</author><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 12:55:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiWkFVX3lxTFBuaU4wVTBpM2xBUmUwVF9IaW1zUWk2OUVDZDI3WmxJb1VmTlFaQXFwNWdBSXBSVVFfVE1XQlhfXzU5eFhLRXRTU09MUDBweFAtTGppMDd0Z19Ndw</guid></item><item><title>疾控中心员工因被解雇、重新雇用和再次解雇而陷入混乱： “陷入困境” -《卫报》</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2025/oct/31/cdc-employees-hiring-firing-limbo</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body-commercial-selector article-body-viewer-selector dcr-hdpgoq"&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;As layoff notices swept through the US Centers for Disease Control and Prevention (CDC) on 10 October, Aryn Melton Backus thought she would be safe this time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Then she received the email: she was part of a major reduction in force (RIF) during the US government shutdown. It wasn’t the first time she’d been fired from the CDC by email, nor the second.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="sign-in-gate"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Backus has been terminated and then reinstated three times &lt;em&gt;this year.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Her experience demonstrates the inefficiencies and tumult at US health agencies as leaders continue cutting into the workforce and ending programs vital for Americans’ health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The latest round of shutdown RIFs is illegal, &lt;a href="https://www.afge.org/publication/federal-employee-unions-file-expanded-lawsuit-challenging-trump-administrations-illegal-shutdown-firings/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;according&lt;/a&gt; to the American Federation of Government Employees (AFGE), which is among the unions representing federal workers that are suing the government to stop the layoffs. A quarter of the CDC has now been cut by multiple rounds of layoffs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="1a988aa5-7f8a-4ea5-8130-5c256b108904" data-spacefinder-role="richLink" data-spacefinder-type="model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.RichLinkBlockElement" class="dcr-47fhrn"&gt;&lt;gu-island name="RichLinkComponent" priority="feature" deferuntil="idle" props='{"richLinkIndex":5,"element":{"_type":"model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.RichLinkBlockElement","prefix":"Related: ","text":"New York declares state of emergency to issue food banks $65m amid shutdown","elementId":"1a988aa5-7f8a-4ea5-8130-5c256b108904","role":"richLink","url":"https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2025/oct/30/new-york-food-banks-emergency-shutdown"},"ajaxUrl":"https://api.nextgen.guardianapps.co.uk","format":{"design":10,"display":0,"theme":0}}'&gt;&lt;/gu-island&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Some employees who had to work without pay through the shutdown received RIF notices; others who were furloughed learned they would never return to their jobs. Employees who were supposed to be protected from RIFs by an ongoing lawsuit received them anyway. The human resources department at CDC was brought back from unpaid furlough in order to process about 1,300 layoffs – and then their own, as the entire HR department was eliminated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Some of the gutted departments are required by law to continue their work, despite having no employees. The ethics office and the institutional review board (IRB) were also ended, which means the CDC will no longer have oversight on ethical violations and research protocols.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The entire library staff at the CDC, an integral part of research and recommendations, was terminated. The Washington office, which developed policy briefings and provided information to Congress members, was eliminated as well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The National Center for Chronic Disease Prevention and &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/society/health" data-link-name="in body link" data-component="auto-linked-tag"&gt;Health&lt;/a&gt; Promotion, the national health and nutrition examination survey, and the staff focused on suicide prevention also suffered layoffs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The multiple cuts across the agency mean the CDC is not able to carry out much of its work, even as some employees remain, said Karen Remley, who previously ran the National Center on Birth Defects and Developmental Disabilities and was a state health official in Virginia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;In April, for instance, the entire team behind the Pregnancy Risk Assessment Monitoring System (Prams) was cut, which means a critical tool for understanding maternal and child health is now missing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“You can’t take out Prams and keep the registry and have all that work happen,” Remley said. “This artificial separating and splitting really means the work on the local level stops.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Meanwhile, CDC employees have endured attacks and harassment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;On 8 August, a gunman fired 500 rounds of ammunition at the CDC headquarters, killing David Rose, an officer, and traumatizing agency employees and their families.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Health agency employees have been doxed, with their identities and personal information revealed. Matthew Buckham, Kennedy’s acting chief of staff, was co-founder of the group that maintains a “DEI Watch List” targeting HHS employees. The agency has also been roiled by high-profile &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2025/sep/17/rfk-jr-senate-hearing-cdc-susan-monarez" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;departures&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“At the highest level of leadership in the CDC, there are no public health or medical professionals left to help guide CDC recommendations,” said Abigail Tighe, a former CDC employee and founding member of the National Public Health Coalition, which held a recent press conference where Backus and other former CDC employees spoke.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“Billions in contracts and direct funding to state and local public health agencies has been canceled or clawed back, and the American people are cued up to suffer. It is hard to succinctly put into words what the decimation of the CDC means for everyday Americans.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The first round of layoffs at CDC came on Valentine’s day. Probationary employees – who were in the first year or two of their jobs, either because they had been recently hired or had moved to new positions – along with &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2025/feb/20/trump-fired-health-employees" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;established senior employees&lt;/a&gt; received notices.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;A judge &lt;a href="https://storage.courtlistener.com/recap/gov.uscourts.cand.444883/gov.uscourts.cand.444883.261.0.pdf" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;ruled&lt;/a&gt; in September that the probationary terminations went too far and some of the employees were reinstated and placed on administrative leave.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;In the meantime, RIF notices went out on 1 April, eliminating entire offices such as the office on smoking and health, where Backus worked. She didn’t even receive the notice at first because her access to the CDC network, including email, had been cut off.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The lawsuit specifically prevents employees like Backus from being reorganized into new offices or terminated from the agency, she said. That’s why she thought she would be safe this time – but she still received a third layoff notice. That notice was rescinded after less than 24 hours. About 700 employees were reinstated, while 600 &lt;a href="http://theguardian.com/us-news/2025/oct/14/cdc-job-cuts-partial-reversal" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;remain terminated&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“I still remain on administrative leave, unable to do my job,” Backus said. “My situation just highlights the chaos and confusion that federal employees have experienced over the past year. I’m stuck in limbo, following court cases, gathering information, and trying to figure out what my next steps should be.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Charlotte Kent, former editor-in-chief of the Morbidity and Mortality Weekly Report (MMWR), said: “We have so many people who, if they’ve been [un-RIFed], have been on administrative leave. We have the inefficiency of so many government resources, our taxpayer dollars, going to fight the illegal activities that have been done by the administration.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The MMWR was among the departments completely gutted and then reinstated – which was particularly surprising, because the highly regarded scientific journal was specifically included in the president’s budget request for the first time this year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“To have it cut at this point is just shocking,” Kent said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“It’s like being in a strange game where there’s no rules,” said one former CDC employee who was RIFed on 10 October and spoke anonymously to avoid reprisal from the &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/trump-administration" data-link-name="in body link" data-component="auto-linked-tag"&gt;Trump administration&lt;/a&gt;. “It’s honestly like Squid Games – we don’t know what’s going to happen next.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;John Brooks, who retired last year from the CDC after 26 years and served as the chief medical officer for several emergency responses, said the RIFs demonstrated a “stunning level of incompetency”. Firing the CDC Washington staff means “Congress no longer has a means of direct access to the agency it funds when it needs information or briefings”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The Trump administration &lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/live-updates/government-shutdown-live-updates-as-military-poised-to-miss-first-paychecks-next-week/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;reportedly&lt;/a&gt; says about 700 of the terminations were a coding error.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“It is clear to us that this was not a coding error,” said Tighe. “This RIF was carried out just as all the other ones have been, where they fire as many people as they think they can get away with, there’s public outcry, there’s outcry from congressional members and then they bring back the things that they think people cannot get over.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;She called the firings “an intentional attack on the American people and the public’s health”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“Our country is on an uncertain and frankly frightening path,” Tighe said. “We would love to see Congress step in.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Guardian</author><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 12:02:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiAFBVV95cUxNejJUUTZISC1UOUtOdlVMOU5jczR0eHloTXZ6RFlpdjFnWVJMUjZ6aExyQURPNXNFeHFlVXVTaHFldGY2UkxHc0FBNnk4S1BIQUFDc2diSmJMMGd1c3YzaGpPd1EzREVEZmRxQmN4RjU3d3RmTXpaVzdJVVpZWVMzQi1BZ2taSE83</guid></item><item><title>科罗拉多州医生转诊的病人因踝关节手术、过夜住院而被$ 64,000的账单绊倒-《丹佛邮报》</title><link>https://www.denverpost.com/2025/10/31/surprise-medical-bill-colorado/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="body-copy"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;By Julie Appleby,&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;KFF Health News&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Physician Lauren Hughes was heading to see patients at a clinic about 20 miles from her Denver home in February when another driver T-boned her Subaru, totaling it. She was taken by ambulance to the closest hospital, &lt;a href="https://intermountainhealthcare.org/locations/intermountain-health-platte-valley-hospital"&gt;Platte Valley Hospital&lt;/a&gt; in Brighton.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A shaken Hughes was examined in the emergency room, where she was diagnosed with bruising, a deep cut on her knee, and a broken ankle. Physicians recommended immediate surgical repair, she said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“They said: ‘You have this fracture and a big gaping wound in your knee. We need to take you to the OR to wash it out and make sure there’s no infection,’” she said. “As a clinician, I thought, ‘Yes.’”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="s2nPlayer k-smyizmlx" data-type="float" data-s2n-api="dfm_stn_player_script_id_smyizmlx"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She was taken to the operating room in the early evening, then admitted to the hospital overnight.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A friend took her home the next day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Then the bills came.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;The Medical Procedure&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Surgeons cleaned the cut on her right knee, which had hit her car’s dashboard, and realigned a broken bone in her right ankle, stabilizing it with metal screws. Surgery is typically recommended when a broken bone is deemed unlikely to heal properly with only a cast.&lt;/p&gt;				
&lt;h4&gt;The Final Bill&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$63,976.35, charged by the hospital — which was not in-network with the insurance plan she got through her job — for the surgery and overnight stay.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;The Problem: Should I Stay or Should I Go?&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hughes’ insurer, Anthem, fully covered the nearly $2,400 ambulance ride and some smaller radiology charges from the ER, but denied the surgery and overnight stay charges from the out-of-network hospital.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Sixty-three thousand dollars for a broken ankle and a cut to the knee, with no head injury or internal damage,” Hughes said. “Just to stay there overnight. It’s crazy.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Insurers have broad power to determine &lt;a href="https://content.naic.org/sites/default/files/consumer-health-insurance-what-is-medical-necessity.pdf"&gt;whether care is medically necessary&lt;/a&gt; — that is, what is needed for treatment, diagnosis, or relief. And that decision affects whether and how much they will pay for it.&lt;/p&gt;				
&lt;p&gt;Four days after her surgery, Anthem notified Hughes that after consulting clinical guidelines for her type of ankle repair, its reviewer determined it was not medically necessary for her to be fully admitted for an inpatient hospital stay.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If she had needed additional surgery or had other problems, such as vomiting or a fever, an inpatient stay might have been warranted, according to the letter. “The information we have does not show you have these or other severe problems,” it said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To Hughes, the notion that she should have left the hospital was “ludicrous.” Her car was in a junkyard, she had no family nearby, and she was taking opioid painkillers for the first time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When she asked for further details about medical necessity determinations, Hughes was directed deep inside her policy’s benefit booklet, which outlines that, for a hospital stay, documentation must show “safe and adequate care could not be obtained as an outpatient.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It turns out the surgery charges were denied because of an insurance contract quirk. Under Anthem’s agreement with the hospital, all claims for services before and after a patient is admitted are approved or denied together, said Anthem spokesperson Emily Snooks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A hospital stay is not generally required after ankle surgery, and the insurer found Hughes did not need the kind of “comprehensive, complex medical care” that would necessitate hospitalization, Snooks wrote in an email to KFF Health News.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Anthem has consistently agreed that Ms. Hughes’ ankle surgery was medically necessary,” Snooks wrote. “However, because the ankle surgery was bundled with the inpatient admission, the entire claim was denied.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Facing bills from an out-of-network hospital where she was taken by emergency responders, though, Hughes did not understand why she wasn’t shielded by the &lt;a href="https://www.cms.gov/newsroom/fact-sheets/no-surprises-understand-your-rights-against-surprise-medical-bills"&gt;No Surprises Act&lt;/a&gt;, which took effect in 2022. The federal law requires insurers to cover out-of-network providers as though they are in-network when patients receive emergency care, among other protections.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“If they had determined it was medically necessary, then they would have to apply the No Surprises Act cost,” said Matthew Fiedler, a senior fellow with the Center on Health Policy at Brookings. “But the No Surprises Act is not going to override the normal medical necessity determination.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There was one more oddity in her case. During one of many calls Hughes made trying to sort out her bill, an Anthem representative told her that things might have been different had the hospital billed for her hospitalization as an overnight “observation” stay.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Generally, that’s when patients are kept at a facility so staff can determine whether they need to be admitted. Rather than being tied to the stay’s duration, the designation mainly reflects the intensity of care. A patient with fewer needs is more likely to be billed for an observation stay.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Insurers pay hospitals less for an observation stay than admission, Fiedler said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That distinction is a big issue for patients on Medicare. Most often, the government health program will not pay for &lt;a href="https://www.medicare.gov/coverage/skilled-nursing-facility-care#:~:text=You%20may%20not,for%20more%20information."&gt;any care needed in a nursing home&lt;/a&gt; if the patient was not first formally admitted to a &lt;a href="https://www.appliedpolicy.com/11-years-of-the-two-midnight-rule-how-a-controversial-policy-is-shaping-medicare-and-hospital-admissions-in-2024/#:~:text=The%20length%20of,patient%E2%80%99s%20financial%20responsibility."&gt;hospital for at least three days&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It’s a classic battle between providers and insurers as to what bucket a claim falls in,” Fiedler said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;The Resolution&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a physician and a &lt;a href="https://medschool.cuanschutz.edu/farleyhealthpolicycenter/who-we-are/farley-center-staff/lauren-hughes"&gt;director of a health policy center at the University of Colorado’s Anschutz Medical Campus&lt;/a&gt;, Hughes is a savvier-than-usual policyholder. Yet even she was frustrated during the months spent going back and forth with her insurer and the hospital — and worried when it looked like her account would be sent to a collection agency.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In addition to appealing the denied claims, she sought the help of her employer’s human resources department, which contacted Anthem. She also &lt;a href="https://kffhealthnews.org/send-us-your-medical-bills/"&gt;reached out to KFF Health News&lt;/a&gt;, which contacted Anthem and the Platte Valley Hospital.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In late September, Hughes received calls from a hospital official, who told her they had “downgraded the level of care” the hospital billed her insurance for and resubmitted the claim to Anthem.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In a written statement to KFF Health News, Platte Valley Hospital spokesperson Sara Quale said that the facility “deeply regrets any anxiety this situation has caused her.” The hospital had “prematurely” and erroneously sent Hughes a bill before working out the balance with Anthem, she wrote.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“After a careful review of Ms. Hughes’ situation,” Quale continued, “we have now stopped all billing to her. Furthermore, we have informed Ms. Hughes that if her insurance company ultimately assigns the remaining balance to her, she will not be billed for it.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anthem spokesperson Stephanie DuBois said in an email that Platte Valley resubmitted Hughes’ bill to the insurer on Oct. 3, this time for “outpatient care services.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;An explanation of benefits that was sent to Hughes shows the hospital rebilled for around $61,000 — about $40,000 of which was knocked off the total by an Anthem discount. The insurer paid the hospital nearly $21,000.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the end, Hughes owed only a $250 copayment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;The Takeaway&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are places where patients receiving emergency care at an out-of-network hospital may fall through the cracks of federal billing protections, in particular during a phase that may be nearly indistinguishable to the patient, known as “post-stabilization.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Generally, that occurs when the medical provider determines the patient is &lt;a href="https://www.cms.gov/medical-bill-rights/know-your-rights/using-insurance#notice-and-consent-poststabilization"&gt;stable enough to travel&lt;/a&gt; to an in-network facility using nonmedical transport, said Jack Hoadley, a research professor emeritus at the McCourt School of Public Policy at Georgetown University.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If the patient prefers to stay put for further treatment, the out-of-network provider must then ask the patient &lt;a href="https://www.cms.gov/medical-bill-rights/know-your-rights/using-insurance#notice-and-consent-poststabilization"&gt;to sign a consent form&lt;/a&gt;, agreeing to waive billing protections and continue treatment at out-of-network rates, he said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It’s very important that if they give you some kind of letter to sign that you read that letter very carefully, because that letter might give them your permission to get some big bills,” Hoadley said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If possible, patients should contact their insurer, in addition to asking the hospital’s billing department: Are you being fully admitted, or kept under observation status, and why? Has your care been determined to be medically necessary? Keep in mind that medical necessity determinations play a key role in whether coverage is approved or denied, even after services are provided.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That said, Hughes did not recall being told she was stable enough to leave with nonmedical transportation, nor being asked to sign a consent form.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Her advice is to quickly and aggressively question insurance denials once they are received, including by asking for your case to be escalated to the insurer’s and hospital’s leadership. She said expecting patients to navigate complicated billing questions while in the hospital after a serious injury isn’t realistic.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I was calling family,” Hughes said, “alerting my work colleagues about what happened, processing the extent of my injuries and what needed to be done clinically, arranging care for my pet, getting labs and imaging done — coming to grips with what just happened.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Bill of the Month is a crowdsourced investigation by &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="https://kffhealthnews.org/news/tag/bill-of-the-month/"&gt;&lt;em&gt;KFF Health News&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt; and &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/wellbeing/"&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Washington Post’s Well+Being&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt; that dissects and explains medical bills. Since 2018, this series has helped many patients and readers get their medical bills reduced, and it has been cited in statehouses, at the U.S. Capitol, and at the White House. Do you have a confusing or outrageous medical bill you want to share? &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="https://kffhealthnews.org/send-us-your-medical-bills/"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Tell us about it&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://kffhealthnews.org/about-us"&gt;KFF Health News&lt;/a&gt; is a national newsroom that produces in-depth journalism about health issues and is one of the core operating programs at KFF — an independent source of health policy research, polling, and journalism. Learn more about &lt;a href="https://www.kff.org/about-us"&gt;KFF&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://myaccount.denverpost.com/dp/preference"&gt;Sign up for The Denver Post’s weekly newsletter to get health news sent straight to your inbox.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

			&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Denver Post</author><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 12:00:17 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMieEFVX3lxTE9jamQ2T3dzdDhpdnF1am95OGdoWnNqSjFPMWlqRzFYX1lRZnplalhnUnZsckt3bmJVeGI1QUZCaUQtMEZnbUZTcDNmRTN2NXpsTzRfazBfME9PaTVuM2FZaV9fZmRIbTJ4ZTF5ZFNlcFh3akNEblJ4etIBfkFVX3lxTE1xRDB1bFBCdTBJWU1GYi1jcmlzQmhrVzJOSlFqVERtd0hhQ1RYeHhidnFqbFJTX0RMRXJtQmlkdmxKejgxc295c2R5MHljbl96Y3BuUldEdmM0TlBOTm5PYlVxVGZEWllQaDhmMmZQRld2OWt2WEY5T3JMbG13Zw</guid></item><item><title>我可能仍然患有前列腺癌，但我已经是幸存者- AL.com</title><link>https://www.al.com/news/2025/10/i-may-still-have-prostate-cancer-but-im-already-a-survivor.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content   "&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="MMBCSYCYONDKXDE4UWJO5PLRXA"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;b&gt;This is an opinion column.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-1" data-gaid="inarticle-1"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="MNZRLCJGQFFSXH254C5HOCLW5Y"&gt;Sometimes I get mixed up. That’s not unusual. Not at this age. You’d think, though, that I’d be crystal clear about my prostate cancer treatment. About the active surveillance treatment path that I chose to pursue &lt;a href="https://www.al.com/news/2025/07/johnson-i-have-prostate-cancer-and-the-faith-to-beat-it.html" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://www.al.com/news/2025/07/johnson-i-have-prostate-cancer-and-the-faith-to-beat-it.html"&gt;after being diagnosed with the disease&lt;/a&gt; this summer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-2" data-gaid="inarticle-2"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="E45CPNPCKRGARI3FSGPW7IKZ7M"&gt;Except sometimes I call it active &lt;i&gt;waiting&lt;/i&gt;, and it’s not the medically correct term.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-3" data-gaid="inarticle-3"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="WN7MXZIBEBDVDLSLZDNBF5SJXU"&gt;Active &lt;i&gt;surveillance &lt;/i&gt;is getting a PSA test every six months or so to measure the level of prostate-specific antigen in my blood. If it rises significantly, surgery and/or radiation are more aggressive treatment options. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-4" data-gaid="inarticle-4"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="UU5SG7KGFZAR5CFJ4ADJJU5LMU"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Read more of Roy’s ‘&lt;/b&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.al.com/topic/cancer%20chronicles/" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://www.al.com/topic/cancer%20chronicles/"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Cancer Chronicles&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;b&gt;.’&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-5" data-gaid="inarticle-5"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="3N3FPPSUJFE2NK6NHAH2VACUEQ"&gt;My PSA score in July was 4-almost-5, a spike from prior annual tests, which prompted my primary care physician to send me to a urologist. Weeks later, a biopsy confirmed prostate cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-6" data-gaid="inarticle-6"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="RRP4FZ357ZGZZPDJSK2VIDASAI"&gt;Damn.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-7" data-gaid="inarticle-7"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="TCAH4ZB43BCYHJH42OHOKHDNVQ"&gt;Yet I was not wholly surprised. One in eight men in America will be diagnosed with the disease this year, and one in six Black men. If a direct relative — a father or brother, for instance — had or has prostate cancer, you’re a near-lock to get it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-8" data-gaid="inarticle-8"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="L2SF3U7R4JA7ZAILMEQ5GDEH5M"&gt;My father died of prostate cancer when I was 11 years old. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-9" data-gaid="inarticle-9"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="C5WALNRQ75CTPNF6UVXVWEISDE"&gt;Again, not wholly surprised.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-10" data-gaid="inarticle-10"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="ICYMK2SLX5DUJAJTYDXQXXSAZU"&gt;That doesn’t mean I wasn’t scared more than at any time in my life (and I love roller-coasters). Scared to death when I heard the C-word referring to me. Scared &lt;i&gt;of&lt;/i&gt; death. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-11" data-gaid="inarticle-11"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="T4ANH6TRVJDVJBSRBAO2P3QAZ4"&gt;Weeks later, back in September &lt;a href="https://www.al.com/news/2025/07/johnson-i-have-prostate-cancer-and-the-faith-to-beat-it.html" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;when I first told you that I’ve been diagnosed with prostate cancer,&lt;/a&gt; I shared, too, that my faith gives me confidence that I’ll beat it. I’ve long held onto Isaiah 40:31 as one of my go-to scriptures, knowing that &lt;i&gt;those who wait upon the Lord shall renew their strength&lt;/i&gt;. It became my mantra as my wife and I navigated the waves of treatment options, including surgery and/or radiation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-12" data-gaid="inarticle-12"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="K6AN4O7TEJHFBHW7TGIPRM445Y"&gt;My cancer was deemed stage 2, a slow-moving cancer confirmed by a genetic test. And because I caught it early, thanks to regular PSA testing at annual checkups, active surveillance was a viable option.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-13" data-gaid="inarticle-13"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="ROPDRLCLXRH4VG4VRFRF2DQAXY"&gt;And it’s the one we chose.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-14" data-gaid="inarticle-14"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="XV4J4QFJVZG2FJBEHUTFIWW4FU"&gt;I am not alone, surprisingly. In September, &lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2025/09/24/well/live/prostate-cancer-treatment-explainer.html" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;The New York Times published an overview of prostate cancer treatments&lt;/a&gt; and I learned that “today &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/22335873/" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;nearly 60 percent of patients&lt;/a&gt; with low-risk cancers choose active monitoring instead of treatment — up from 26 percent in 2014. Some experts believe that number should be higher.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-15" data-gaid="inarticle-15"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="ALJHAIVNFVEL5PJOISPJNYAK5A"&gt;I am &lt;i&gt;far &lt;/i&gt;from alone.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-16" data-gaid="inarticle-16"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="4WBFLBILFVBUPNX7OKTXMSQHFY"&gt;So, yes, I am waiting because I know &lt;a href="https://www.biblegateway.com/passage/?search=2%20Corinthians%2012%3A9&amp;amp;version=NIV" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;His power is made perfect in our weakness&lt;/a&gt;. And cancer is a profound weakness that, even as treatments of almost all forms of the disease have drastically improved in my near-70 years of life, kills far too many. Far too many.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-17" data-gaid="inarticle-17"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="ABKLHLKDEFCQBMSFCJ5DEYJEIQ"&gt;My treatment, however, isn’t called waiting. It’s &lt;i&gt;surveillance&lt;/i&gt; — and my cancer was caught soon enough for me to pursue this path. Thank God.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-18" data-gaid="inarticle-18"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="LUHGWAQRLRCPTO7N6YEZPMFFEA"&gt;It’s been almost two months now since I revealed my diagnosis. Sixty days or thereabouts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-19" data-gaid="inarticle-19"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="4DKU3L5WHJAMBAUDUJKRKI44BE"&gt;I don’t recall how long I endured the expected waves of emotions — fear, sadness, grief and some feelings I don’t even remember — before peace won. Peace in the waiting. In the stillness of waiting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-20" data-gaid="inarticle-20"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="F3DLNEW24FFORHKNAFFRR2S3JI"&gt;Surviving in the waiting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-21" class="middleParagraph" data-gaid="inarticle-21"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="JVNLSAESDJGYDCELHXXZDOV3XQ"&gt;Which is why I sometimes get mixed up and describe my treatment as ... &lt;i&gt;waiting&lt;/i&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-22" data-gaid="inarticle-22"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="6FJPXVXMANHT5HY4UFZ57K3KJ4"&gt;I endured the emotional gauntlet, in part, thanks to the unmitigated support of my wife, children, family, my faith fam at Rock City Church, co-workers, and many, many people whom I did not know before sharing my diagnosis. People who are sharing their own personal cancer journeys with me. I find myself praying for as many as are praying for me.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-23" data-gaid="inarticle-23"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="E7DWV47KV5DVRADRHD4USODYTY"&gt;That’s why I consider myself a cancer survivor. I know the term. It’s generally meant for those who’ve rung the bell. For those who’ve undergone a bombardment of treatments — surgery and/or chemo or radiation or some treatment I never heard about before — and ultimately became cancer-free.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-24" data-gaid="inarticle-24"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="HMRFMDKYNJC5TN3BUMDGT6IDOE"&gt;Many such survivors reached out to me in the days following my initial Cancer Chronicle. I told each of them: I pray that I’ll be able to join you there.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-25" data-gaid="inarticle-25"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="AVPIIG4ZLZBOXP37JX4FC6TGTM"&gt;I already have. To be clear: I may still have cancer in my body. My next PSA test isn’t scheduled for a long while, but I am fully confident in this — I am a survivor.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-26" data-gaid="inarticle-26"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="OGY5VQB5XVBTLFHBYHQXFVKTSE"&gt;I survived anxiety. I survived fear. I survived grief. I survived the sadness. I now wake up each day with peace, joy, confidence, and expectation. And I live every moment with urgency.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-27" data-gaid="inarticle-27"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="ODT33MX4XBHYBBGQGZQUWHCYVM"&gt;I’ve got stuff to do. For me. For the people I love. For others.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-28" data-gaid="inarticle-28"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-enter:C2FOL3YYBFB7PEO7BGTDXWOEFA" data-fusion-component="C2FOL3YYBFB7PEO7BGTDXWOEFA"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-exit:C2FOL3YYBFB7PEO7BGTDXWOEFA" data-fusion-component="C2FOL3YYBFB7PEO7BGTDXWOEFA"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-29" data-gaid="inarticle-29"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="4ZFTSODVSFASRJ2IO5ZZHEN2AM"&gt;I recently joined a couple of organizations that are committed to elevating awareness about the need for prostate cancer testing, particularly among Black men. I joined the board of directors of the&lt;a href="https://mikeslivefoundation.org/" target="_blank" rel=""&gt; Mike Slive Foundation for Cancer Research&lt;/a&gt;, which provides early-stage grants for potentially groundbreaking efforts to cure for prostate cancer, and host free PSA testing at various events across Alabama and beyond.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-30" data-gaid="inarticle-30"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="5BY2KYGKONDF5IZVAXQNTOCOAY"&gt;I am also an ambassador for&lt;a href="https://nowincluded.com/" target="_blank" rel=""&gt; NowIncluded&lt;/a&gt;, an online community where people in underrepresented communities are heard and supported throughout their health journey.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-31" data-gaid="inarticle-31"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="GCDVMF2JDJD5TMI62V6QIOWB3A"&gt;Both entities are committed to saving lives. Our lives.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-32" data-gaid="inarticle-32"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="NSHM4PSXIZHKDKY4FQUIZBDN34"&gt;Because our families need us. Our community needs us. We are needed, gentlemen, to stand up to the challenges of today and tomorrow.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-33" data-gaid="inarticle-33"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="RFES6WJUHJDXHLIMRXU3LXFS74"&gt;To stand up for those who still look to us for guidance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-34" data-gaid="inarticle-34"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="L7PR7PHJMRFJ7CAP4CUJLQZCEA"&gt;Recently, I shared with one of the NowIncluded leaders that I’m already a prostate survivor. She smiled. “We call that thriving,” she said, “thriving with cancer.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-35" data-gaid="inarticle-35"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="6ZG2K5T4ANA73GJ3N6CGOJDXNY"&gt;It’s been long proven that a positive attitude can impact health outcomes. So, I’m going to be the healthiest person in every room I walk into. At least I’ll make you think so.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-36" data-gaid="inarticle-36"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="447CHTU22ZHOJBUZ4SFXUWK3X4"&gt;My pastor often says we can’t always control our circumstances, but we can always control how we view our circumstances. So each day while I actively survey &lt;i&gt;and&lt;/i&gt; wait, I count it all joy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-37" data-gaid="inarticle-37"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="2BS5QCDNYRGTJKAXNNYASM53ZU"&gt;In truth, I rarely think about my diagnosis. I almost forget I have (or may not) cancer – until someone asks, “How are you?!” Ask with that puppy-dog expression of someone who actually wants to know.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-38" data-gaid="inarticle-38"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="IXVFX2STAJDJHHQZ5DUUWX2LPM"&gt;“Great,” is my response. And my truth. Save for stiff knees and a back that’s been annoyingly aggravating lately, I really feel great. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-39" data-gaid="inarticle-39"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="WZPVEYONANGRRBYSOB6FA7VBVA"&gt;I step aside and let His power be made perfect in me, whether I still have cancer or not. Whether or not my PSA rises or falls. Whether I live all of my days with prostate cancer or ring the bell someday.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-40" data-gaid="inarticle-40"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="SNIED2J67RCUHHAOXJQPIV35CQ"&gt;In all ways, I am a survivor, thriving amid the battle.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-41" data-gaid="inarticle-41"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--center skimlinks"&gt;If you purchase a product or register for an account through a link on our site, we may receive compensation.&lt;span&gt; By using this site, you consent to our &lt;a href="https://www.advancelocal.com/advancelocalUserAgreement/user-agreement.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;User Agreement&lt;/a&gt; and agree that your clicks, interactions, and personal information may be collected, recorded, and/or stored by us and social media and other third-party partners in accordance with our &lt;a href="https://www.advancelocal.com/advancelocalUserAgreement/privacy-policy.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Privacy Policy.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>AL.com</author><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 11:10:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimwFBVV95cUxNXzhjUFNjYWlOT1A4d0JvU25WV1pqbDcwOF9KRzh5dTBKTW5fd2hFLUlTWGxoangtN21uRnVDdGN0aTJvUzVucG0tazVRSXh2U3F1ckhDX0RzcllKT1RMVWpVdGlPaTNBdVhndGIzVlByenduemRlMzNwSzJDTXB4ZzBiRVZRaHctQTcyMGRpQVRaWHFyUXpwd3JYUdIBrwFBVV95cUxObWh0UmRYMFZ5T01LdVc2Q3R5dy1udUd2YjVqcmoyQXIzWXZ2eGMwNXFBelFYcm9PUmJEOVlhMnpoamptdW0xTHNjQ2ZkNkNWY3ZCeHVqaDVScnVEeHh3Z1g2T2pGU1lVN3hFLUl6dEJGQkR2ZEJmbmpKaUk2eDlqc3I5SWVCenlRa1pfenFLTl95V0RNei1vVFVoZzNyd29HTm1oWURCWjFWVVoyaWxZ</guid></item><item><title>这些是成年人自闭症的9个主要指标，往往被完全忽视- Yahoo Lifestyle Canada</title><link>https://ca.style.yahoo.com/9-major-indicators-autism-adults-103104223.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="" data-article-body="true"&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;You may have seen &lt;a href="https://www.tiktok.com/@sunnygiovanni/video/7205024706439728426" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:videos;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;videos&lt;/a&gt; on social media where people detail the signs that made them realize they’re autistic. Viewers are finding them enlightening and comforting as many people  — mainly women — are undiagnosed as they reach adulthood.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;According to &lt;a href="https://neurodivergentinsights.com/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Dr. Megan Anna Neff;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Dr. Megan Anna Neff&lt;/a&gt;, a clinical psychologist based in Oregon, &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/35204992/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:a recent study;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;a recent study&lt;/a&gt; found that 80% of women with autism are still undiagnosed at age 18.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;There are many reasons for this: For starters, people learn to adjust their behavior to fit in with society. Additionally,&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;the autism diagnostic tools used today were developed exclusively on white boys from high socioeconomic status, said &lt;a href="https://www.stephaniegardnerwright.com/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Stephanie Gardner-Wright;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Stephanie Gardner-Wright&lt;/a&gt;, a licensed master social worker and certified autism clinical specialist in Michigan.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;There is also a huge focus on the external signs and not so much the internal symptoms of autism, Gardner-Wright said. And those internal symptoms are very different from person to person.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“There are so many ways that autism can show up and present,” Neff added. “I think there’s more diversity within autism than there is between autism and allistic.” (Allistic people are folks who aren’t on the autism spectrum.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;That said, there are a number of signs or thought patterns that undiagnosed autistic people may be able to relate to. HuffPost spoke with mental health professionals, including some people who are neurodivergent themselves, about the signs of autism in adulthood:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mb-4 text-xl font-bold md:text-2xl"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A Feeling Of Being ‘Different’ From Others&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;figure class="relative mb-4"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="relative text-sm mt-1 pr-2.5"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; Pixelcatchers / Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.buzzfeed.com/laurengarafano/doctors-share-little-things-people-ignore?utm_source=yahoo-recirc-links" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Doctors Are Sharing The 16 &amp;quot;Tiny&amp;quot; Health Things That Most People Ignore But 100% Shouldn't;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Doctors Are Sharing The 16 "Tiny" Health Things That Most People Ignore But 100% Shouldn't&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;All four experts shared that it’s common for autistic people to feel different. &lt;a href="https://effectiveartistry.com/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Brandon Tessers;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Brandon Tessers&lt;/a&gt;, the director of Effective Artistry, a therapy group that supports neurodivergent people, said some folks will describe it as “feeling like an alien sometimes,” while &lt;a href="https://gsapp.rutgers.edu/faculty/vanessa-bal" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Dr. Vanessa Bal;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Dr. Vanessa Bal&lt;/a&gt;, the director of the Center for Adult Autism Services Psychological Services Clinic at Rutgers University in &lt;a href="https://www.buzzfeednews.com/carolinekee/what-is-adenovirus" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:New Jersey;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;New Jersey&lt;/a&gt; said folks describe it as “a lifetime experience of feeling different.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The difference between this feeling and the occasional outsider feeling everyone deals with from time to time is that for autistic folks, this feeling does not come and go and is not only during one specific period, like middle school, Bal told HuffPost.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Gardner-Wright added that this is a big indicator and an internal experience at that — you cannot look at a person and know if they feel like an outsider. The feeling could be overpowering or could be more subtle, it depends on the person, she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;But, it’s important to know that autistic people don’t necessarily feel like outsiders all the time, Bal noted. They may find settings that are more inclusive for neurodivergent people. Additionally, some adults also say they feel more comfortable with who they are and worry less about differences, sometimes seeing them as strengths, as they get older, Bal said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mb-4 text-xl font-bold md:text-2xl"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Difficulty With Social Cues&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;figure class="relative mb-4"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="relative text-sm mt-1 pr-2.5"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; Oliver Rossi / Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Social cues are also another sign. Someone with undiagnosed autism may find they have trouble deciphering how much eye contact is appropriate or when they should stop smiling during a conversation, Gardner-Wright said. They may be able to mask these uncertainties by learning how much is appropriate, but it’s not an innate sense as it is with someone who is allistic, she added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mb-4 text-xl font-bold md:text-2xl"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A Confusing Relationship History — Both Romantically Or Platonically&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;figure class="relative mb-4"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="relative text-sm mt-1 pr-2.5"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; Peopleimages / Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;According to Neff, many undiagnosed autistic adults have a confusing and complicated social relationship history. Additionally, romantic relationships may feel tough to navigate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“There might be relationships that have that kind of suddenly burst apart but the autistic person doesn’t understand why,” she said. When it comes to the reason behind this complicated relationship history, it’s likely that the person with autism doesn’t know why their relationships fail when other people’s don’t.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mb-4 text-xl font-bold md:text-2xl"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sensory Differences&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.buzzfeed.com/scarymouse/doctors-sharing-mild-symptoms-actually-serious-medical-3?utm_source=yahoo-recirc-links" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk='slk:"Get To The Doctor Right Now" — People Are Revealing 24 "Mild" Medical Symptoms That Can Actually Be A Sign Of A Major, Major Issue;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas' class="link "&gt;"Get To The Doctor Right Now" — People Are Revealing 24 "Mild" Medical Symptoms That Can Actually Be A Sign Of A Major, Major Issue&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="relative mb-4"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="relative text-sm mt-1 pr-2.5"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; Simpleimages / Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Sensitivity to sensory input — like noise and sight — is another potential sign of autism, said Gardner-Wright, who added that this can mean being hyper-aware of a sound or totally unaware.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;People who are not autistic tend to be more or less responsive to sensory stimuli, she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;For example, an autistic person may find that they’re constantly aware of a ticking clock at a friend’s house or really sensitive to the sound of a loud siren, Gardner-Wright noted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mb-4 text-xl font-bold md:text-2xl"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A Desire For Routine&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;figure class="relative mb-4"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="relative text-sm mt-1 pr-2.5"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; Tatiana Maksimova / Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Many people with autism thrive on consistency. “The world we occupy is much more uncertain and unpredictable. So we go to routine as a way of self-soothing,” Neff said. When a routine is disrupted, strong &lt;a href="https://www.buzzfeed.com/evelinamedina/which-human-emotion-are-you" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:emotions;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;emotions&lt;/a&gt; may present, including intense irritability or anxiety.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Gardner-Wright added that the routine doesn’t need to be super strict, either; it’s a common misconception when people think about people with autism’s day-to-day schedule. Instead, it could be a strong preference for a certain mug every morning. Routine looks different for different people.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Additionally, big changes can be hard, too. “If they move [homes] or they move careers, this could create a season of insomnia or anxiety,” Neff said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Routine can extend to certain behaviors as well. It also includes repetitive body movements, which is known as stimming, Neff added. &lt;a href="https://www.research.chop.edu/car-autism-roadmap/stimming-what-is-it-and-does-it-matter#:~:text=%22%20Stimming%20%2C%22%20also%20known%20as,spectrum%20engage%20in%20routine%20stimming%20." rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:According to the Children’s Hospital of Pennsylvania’s Research Institute;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;According to the Children’s Hospital of Pennsylvania’s Research Institute&lt;/a&gt;, stimming behaviors can include body rocking, hand flapping, spinning, rubbing a specific surface, and squealing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mb-4 text-xl font-bold md:text-2xl"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A Need For Solitude &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.buzzfeed.com/lizmrichardson/doctors-health-lies-medical-myths?utm_source=yahoo-recirc-links" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:&amp;quot;There Is No Cure&amp;quot;: Doctors And Nurses Are Calling Out The Health &amp;quot;Lies&amp;quot; People Still Believe (But Really Shouldn't);elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;"There Is No Cure": Doctors And Nurses Are Calling Out The Health "Lies" People Still Believe (But Really Shouldn't)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="relative mb-4"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="relative text-sm mt-1 pr-2.5"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; Jordan Siemens / Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Another common sign? “Needing solitude to recharge after social situations or really overstimulating situations — and overstimulating could be different for everyone — but that is a very typical hallmark of [autism],” Gardner-Wright said. This could mean feeling totally exhausted after a work presentation or a family party.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Bal said this exhaustion comes from a term known as “camouflaging” or “masking.” “This is the idea that you have to really hide different facets of yourself or different behaviors in order to fit in what you think the expectations around you are.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;And while we all do this at times, the degree that autistic people have to camouflage aspects of themselves may result in a feeling of total drainage where afterward they report spending long periods of time alone or in dark and quiet places to recover, Bal said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Tessers added that, from the outside, people have no idea when someone is camouflaging. “They’re doing what everybody wants or expects of them to some successful degree.” This could look like behaving as you “should” at work but going home and crashing and dreading the idea of having to do this camouflaging all over again tomorrow, Tessers noted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mb-4 text-xl font-bold md:text-2xl"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;More Intense Interests&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;figure class="relative mb-4"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="relative text-sm mt-1 pr-2.5"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; Natalia Lebedinskaia / Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;A deep curiosity and passion for one particular activity or subject can also develop. “Our brains tend to gravitate with a lot of passion towards our area of interest and we become very invested in them and it’s also a way we self-soothe,” Neff said. This could mean building a career around a specific interest or knowing everything about a specific hobby.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;And while everyone has interests — and many people have strong interests — Neff said autistic folks likely find a way to relate everything to their specific interest. For example, this could look like finding a way to talk about a favorite TV show even when the conversation revolves around current events.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“Allistic people can have a special interest but then it doesn’t become their lens for their whole world,” Neff said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mb-4 text-xl font-bold md:text-2xl"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A Dislike Of Small Talk&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;figure class="relative mb-4"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="relative text-sm mt-1 pr-2.5"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; Tom Werner / Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.buzzfeed.com/lizmrichardson/doctors-health-warning-signs-symptoms-shouldnt-ignore?utm_source=yahoo-recirc-links" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Doctors And Nurses Are Revealing The &amp;quot;Small&amp;quot; Health Signs You Should Never Ignore, And It's Shocking;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Doctors And Nurses Are Revealing The "Small" Health Signs You Should Never Ignore, And It's Shocking&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Most people don’t love small talk, but for people with autism, small talk can feel totally exhausting or something that shouldn’t have to happen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“They typically don’t enjoy small talk and perhaps found ways to avoid it,” Neff said. “Maybe they structured their life or their career in a way that they don’t have to do a lot of that allistic communication.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Gardner-Wright added that people who are on the spectrum tend to prefer deep, meaningful conversations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mb-4 text-xl font-bold md:text-2xl"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A Desire For Direct Communication&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;figure class="relative mb-4"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="relative text-sm mt-1 pr-2.5"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; Manu Vega / Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;People with autism thrive on straightforwardness, with “really honest, clear communication being a strong preference,” Gardner-Wright said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Neff said autistic people tend to be pretty literal. For example, when you say the phrase “it’s raining cats and &lt;a href="https://www.buzzfeed.com/chelseamarshall/what-kind-of-dog-are-you" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:dogs;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;dogs&lt;/a&gt;,” she said autistic people may picture literal cats and dogs falling from the sky in their mind, but then realize the person speaking is referring to rain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“So, actually, I think it’s perhaps more precise to say we’re visual in our communication style versus literal, but it often shows up as being literal,” Neff said. Additionally, the communication style can be described as direct and honest. “What we say, we tend to say at face value,” Neff added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mb-4 text-xl font-bold md:text-2xl"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;If you think you have these signs, look to autistic voices for guidance.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Both Gardner-Wright and Neff recommend exploring the hashtag &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/explore/tags/actuallyautistic/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:#actuallyautistic;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;#actuallyautistic&lt;/a&gt; on social media to listen to lived experiences and hear from people in your specific community about how this exists for them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“Discovering that you’re autistic as an adult can be really validating,” Gardner-Wright said. It can help you more fully understand yourself and your life. “But there can also be a grieving process for that,” she said, where you may wish you had this information when you were a kid so certain situations could have been different.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“Feeling a mix of grief and also excitement is very, very normal,” Gardner-Wright said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Additionally, &lt;a href="https://embrace-autism.com/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:embrace-autism.com;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;embrace-autism.com&lt;/a&gt; is a helpful resource for free screening tools and tests to help you understand if you are autistic — though it is not diagnostic, they’re simply online guides to help arm you with information, Gardner-Wright noted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mb-4 text-xl font-bold md:text-2xl"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You can reach out to mental health professionals, too.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;figure class="relative mb-4"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="relative text-sm mt-1 pr-2.5"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; Olga Pankova / Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Neff said it can be helpful to connect with a therapist to talk about this new discovery, but she stressed that it’s important to find one who is neurodivergent-affirming or -informed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Bal agreed and said “we have a long way to go with respect to training medical professionals and mental health professionals about autism. I worry there’s a lot of misinformation and misconceptions out there.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Bal added that you can also look up autism centers near you for diagnosis or treatment, but noted that many have a yearslong waitlist and may focus only on children. If they can’t fit you in, Bal said, you can ask if they have resources they recommend, or look for community autism organizations to see if they have any resources.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Additionally, a community of supportive people can be helpful as well, which is where the #actuallyaustic hashtag — or other online communities — can be helpful.&lt;em&gt;This article originally appeared on&lt;/em&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/entry/the-9-biggest-signs-of-autism-in-adulthood-goog_l_68013c24e4b0b87197a6e18d" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:HuffPost.;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;&lt;em&gt;HuffPost.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Also in Goodful: &lt;a href="https://www.buzzfeed.com/alanavalko/unhinged-microfeminisms?utm_source=yahoo-recirc-links" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:&amp;quot;He Thinks This Is Hostile And He Is Correct&amp;quot; — Women Are Sharing The &amp;quot;Unhinged&amp;quot; Ways They Practice Microfeminism That Reaally Grind A Small Man's Gears;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;"He Thinks This Is Hostile And He Is Correct" — Women Are Sharing The "Unhinged" Ways They Practice Microfeminism That Reaally Grind A Small Man's Gears&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Also in Goodful: &lt;a href="https://www.buzzfeed.com/lizmrichardson/doctors-bad-health-habits?utm_source=yahoo-recirc-links" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk='slk:"They Had No Idea How Dangerous It Was." Doctors Are Calling Out The "Bad" Habits That Are Actually Ruining Your Health;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas' class="link "&gt;"They Had No Idea How Dangerous It Was." Doctors Are Calling Out The "Bad" Habits That Are Actually Ruining Your Health&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Also in Goodful: &lt;a href="https://www.buzzfeed.com/dannicaramirez/older-adults-are-sharing-the-difficult-truths-about-aging-fs?utm_source=yahoo-recirc-links" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk='slk:"Young People Would Be Surprised By This": 21 "Hard To Swallow" Truths About Getting Older That No One Talks About;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas' class="link "&gt;"Young People Would Be Surprised By This": 21 "Hard To Swallow" Truths About Getting Older That No One Talks About&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.buzzfeed.com/jillianwilson/biggest-signs-of-autism-in-adulthood-sc?utm_source=yahoo-recirc-links" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Read it on BuzzFeed.com;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Read it on BuzzFeed.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Yahoo Lifestyle Canada</author><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:31:04 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMif0FVX3lxTE94WHhZazRhMHlvbjhSMTVuSmM1MkU3SUNLZXduc3ExTnJxTHpRN1ZqVlNlOWw1QzBOQWFJaHU4alB6RWtBdDVGdDQyaWI1REJtaXJZN3N5N2o5MnRLQ2hZV0EyWFlkZmw5SFBMN1lUVkplNlNZeVFoTkI4RDhXTDA</guid></item><item><title>以下是成年人自闭症的9个主要指标，这些指标往往被完全忽视- BuzzFeed</title><link>https://www.buzzfeed.com/jillianwilson/biggest-signs-of-autism-in-adulthood-sc</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="subbuzz buzz-width--standard__subbuzz buzz-type--long__subbuzz subbuzz-text
  subbuzz-index-19
  
  
  
  
  " data-keywords="fast fashion" data-module="subbuzz-text"&gt;
  
  &lt;p id="139570589" class="subbuzz-anchor"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;





&lt;p&gt;People with autism thrive on straightforwardness, with “really honest, clear communication being a strong preference,” Gardner-Wright said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Neff said autistic people tend to be pretty literal. For example, when you say the phrase “it’s raining cats and &lt;a href="https://www.buzzfeed.com/chelseamarshall/what-kind-of-dog-are-you"&gt;dogs&lt;/a&gt;,” she said autistic people may picture literal cats and dogs falling from the sky in their mind, but then realize the person speaking is referring to rain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“So, actually, I think it’s perhaps more precise to say we’re visual in our communication style versus literal, but it often shows up as being literal,” Neff said. Additionally, the communication style can be described as direct and honest. “What we say, we tend to say at face value,” Neff added. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;If you think you have these signs, look to autistic voices for guidance.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Both Gardner-Wright and Neff recommend exploring the hashtag &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/explore/tags/actuallyautistic/" target="_blank" data-skimlinks-tracking="7965909"&gt;#actuallyautistic&lt;/a&gt; on social media to listen to lived experiences and hear from people in your specific community about how this exists for them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Discovering that you’re autistic as an adult can be really validating,” Gardner-Wright said. It can help you more fully understand yourself and your life. “But there can also be a grieving process for that,” she said, where you may wish you had this information when you were a kid so certain situations could have been different.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Feeling a mix of grief and also excitement is very, very normal,” Gardner-Wright said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Additionally, &lt;a href="https://embrace-autism.com/" target="_blank" data-skimlinks-tracking="7965909" data-affiliate="true"&gt;embrace-autism.com&lt;/a&gt; is a helpful resource for free screening tools and tests to help you understand if you are autistic — though it is not diagnostic, they’re simply online guides to help arm you with information, Gardner-Wright noted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You can reach out to mental health professionals, too.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BuzzFeed</author><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:31:04 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihAFBVV95cUxOVWRjZjJVZkRJSV9JRkc0ZVNRZ0ZnT3JwbDFHUV9oN3dLbktjTFVFWlRkUGRTVVBuczRXTlkxbHgzX2laeDZ6V0N2TnFPaDZJNXdtSEJvdXdRdWI2YWtuaEQ1ZWFIUmZpbTNMX0tBeUhkS19xdUxpM185V0x3bDJiMUI0Tm4</guid></item><item><title>食肉动物穴居人的神话- vox.com</title><link>https://www.vox.com/future-perfect/466465/hunter-gatherers-meat-myths-carnivore-paleo-maggots</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="zephr-anchor" class="_1agbrix10"&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup duet--article--standard-paragraph _1agbrixi lg8ac51 lg8ac50 xkp0cg1"&gt;Across the far right, a paranoid prophecy has been taking hold: the belief that globalist elites want to take meat off the menu and replace it with insects. The charge has been spouted in one version or another by provocateurs like &lt;a href="https://www.npr.org/2023/03/31/1167550482/how-a-conspiracy-theory-about-eating-bugs-made-its-way-to-international-politics"&gt;Tucker Carlson&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/Cernovich/status/1639677891716988928"&gt;Mike Cernovich&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href="https://x.com/jordanbpeterson/status/1692041185768902963"&gt;Jordan Peterson&lt;/a&gt;, and repeated by countless accounts on social media.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup duet--article--standard-paragraph _1agbrixi lg8ac51 lg8ac50 xkp0cg1"&gt;The &lt;a href="https://www.bbc.com/future/article/20250904-how-eating-insects-became-a-conspiracy-theory"&gt;claim&lt;/a&gt; has found its way into the sloganeering of major right-wing political parties around the world, from the &lt;a href="https://www.cbc.ca/news/politics/conservatives-accuse-liberals-wanting-canadians-eat-bugs-london-factory-1.7385019"&gt;Conservative Party of Canada&lt;/a&gt; to &lt;a href="https://caad.info/analysis/newsletters/caad-data-monitor-food-and-farming-weaponized-during-eu-elections/"&gt;Lega in Italy&lt;/a&gt;, and the &lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/world/europe/war-worms-polish-politicians-give-each-other-mouthful-over-edible-insects-2023-03-03/"&gt;Law and Justice party in Poland&lt;/a&gt;. Florida Governor Ron DeSantis &lt;a href="https://www.bbc.com/news/world-us-canada-68947766"&gt;invoked the specter of insect-eating&lt;/a&gt; when he banned the production and sale of cultivated meat in his state.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup duet--article--standard-paragraph _1agbrixi lg8ac51 lg8ac50 xkp0cg1"&gt;These claims frequently accompany advocacy for meat-heavy, protein-packed diets — ascendant within the so-called &lt;a href="https://newrepublic.com/article/171781/meat-culture-war-crickets"&gt;manosphere and&lt;/a&gt; across the right more broadly — that ostensibly hearken back to our Paleolithic ancestors, who, the thinking goes, dined on freshly-hunted prey instead of the processed slop churned out by our modern food system. Jordan Peterson, for instance, is a vocal proponent of an all-meat carnivore diet, which he &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=HLF29w6YqXs"&gt;compares favorably&lt;/a&gt; to the diets of hunter-gatherers and contrasts to contemporary diets he suggests have too many carbohydrates. “Maybe human beings should be in hunting mode all the time,” &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=12Sza90czz0"&gt;he said&lt;/a&gt; in 2022.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup duet--article--standard-paragraph _1agbrixi lg8ac51 lg8ac50 xkp0cg1"&gt;Our hunter-gatherer ancestors ate widely divergent diets shaped by climate, geography, and availability. And while they certainly ate meat, they had no guarantee of successful hunts and scant means of preserving fresh kills. In fact, according to a recent &lt;a href="https://www.science.org/doi/10.1126/sciadv.adt7466"&gt;paper&lt;/a&gt; in the journal &lt;em&gt;Science Advances&lt;/em&gt;, that presents a peculiar twist: Putrefying meat attracted flies, which laid eggs that hatched into maggots, which in turn probably provided a ready source of protein to early hunters.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup duet--article--standard-paragraph _1agbrixi lg8ac51 lg8ac50 xkp0cg1"&gt;Ironically, then, part of the Paleolithic diet likely &lt;em&gt;was&lt;/em&gt; bugs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup duet--article--standard-paragraph _1agbrixi lg8ac51 lg8ac50 xkp0cg1"&gt;Carnivore influencers misunderstand not just where ancient humans got their animal protein, but also how much of it they ate. In &lt;em&gt;The Meat Question&lt;/em&gt;, a sprawling history of humans’ relationship to meat, anthropologist Josh Berson &lt;a href="https://mitpress.mit.edu/9780262042895/the-meat-question/"&gt;writes&lt;/a&gt;: “if anything, it is ‘modern’ urban populations, particularly in the United States, that exhibit specialization for animal consumption — not the foragers so often held up as models of a meat-eating subsistence strategy.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup duet--article--standard-paragraph _1agbrixi lg8ac51 lg8ac50 xkp0cg1"&gt;In other words, those who suggest that we’ve fallen from pre-modern meat-eating &lt;em&gt;übermen&lt;/em&gt; to plant-gnawing and bug-curious &lt;em&gt;untermen &lt;/em&gt;have their history backward. It was only with the advent of modern factory farming that meat became so reliable and ubiquitous that Americans can now eat it three times a day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--block-placement _80slsf2 _80slsf0 duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--highlight _1agbrixl _1lbxzst0"&gt;&lt;p class="_1lbxzst1"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p id="read-more-vox-coverage-of-the-science-culture-and-politics-of-meat" class="_7ka5u1 _7ka5u0 _1lbxzst3 duet--article--standard-heading xkp0cg1"&gt;&lt;h2 class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup"&gt;Read more Vox coverage of the science, culture, and politics of meat&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup duet--article--standard-paragraph _1agbrixi lg8ac51 lg8ac50 xkp0cg1"&gt;Myths about how we used to eat and, perhaps, should eat again, matter politically now more than ever. The image of prehistoric man the hunter looms over contemporary “&lt;a href="https://www.jstor.org/stable/644298?seq=2"&gt;gastro-politics&lt;/a&gt;,” reflecting pervasive social and political anxieties about the food we eat. The Make America Healthy Again movement has been buoyed by a &lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2025/04/18/dining/meat-beef-restaurants-politics.html"&gt;growing cultural obsession&lt;/a&gt; with carnivore and paleo diets &lt;a href="/future-perfect/410565/protein-muscle-gain-weightlifting-plant-based-vegan"&gt;and&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2025/08/26/podcasts/the-daily/protein-bars-america.html"&gt;protein&lt;/a&gt; — entrails, tallow, and marrow &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2025/aug/19/maga-cow-products-beef-tallow"&gt;are all chic&lt;/a&gt;; there &lt;a href="https://www.wsj.com/opinion/meat-will-make-america-healthy-again-federal-guidelines-nutrition-reform-protein-eded2b3e"&gt;are calls&lt;/a&gt; to double down on meat in federal nutrition guidelines. All of it dovetails with &lt;a href="https://newrepublic.com/article/193307/nature-solutionism-vaccines-beef-climate"&gt;a romanticization&lt;/a&gt; of “natural” pre-modern food system and &lt;a href="/future-perfect/391795/ultra-processed-foods-science-vegan-meat-rfk-maha"&gt;a distrust&lt;/a&gt; of all things “industrial” and “ultra-processed.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup duet--article--standard-paragraph _1agbrixi lg8ac51 lg8ac50 xkp0cg1"&gt;And it’s hardly just a right-wing phenomenon. The use of Paleolithic humans as dietary role models isn’t so different from mainstream foodie mantras about ancestral diets like author Michael Pollan’s &lt;a href="https://time.com/archive/6677424/six-rules-for-eating-wisely/"&gt;famous advice&lt;/a&gt;: “Don’t eat anything your great-great-great-grandmother wouldn’t recognize as food.” More recently, Pollan has fretted that the environmental benefits of meat alternatives may be offset by vague concerns about the health and safety of their “&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/film/article/2024/jun/06/the-man-who-warned-us-about-upfs-michael-pollan-on-his-25-year-fight-with-the-food-industry"&gt;21 ingredients or whatever&lt;/a&gt;.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup duet--article--standard-paragraph _1agbrixi lg8ac51 lg8ac50 xkp0cg1"&gt;This sort of bias toward the traditional can sometimes result in what we might term “foodie horseshoe theory”: For instance, in his book &lt;em&gt;The Omnivore’s Dilemma&lt;/em&gt;, Pollan, a liberal Berkeley professor, idealizes the small-scale livestock rancher Joel Salatin, an anti-government agrarian who appears on carnivore diet advocate Jordan Peterson’s &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=QMjqphoMy0k"&gt;podcast&lt;/a&gt; to attack veganism, “globalists,” and processed food alike.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup duet--article--standard-paragraph _1agbrixi lg8ac51 lg8ac50 xkp0cg1"&gt;For both left and right, myths about a romanticized past bolster present-day identities, politics, and eating habits while shielding them from debate about the food future we ought to create. Of the many problems with the modern food system, a paucity of meat is not one; research on food’s environmental impacts &lt;a href="https://www.thelancet.com/journals/lancet/article/PIIS0140-6736(25)01201-2/abstract"&gt;points us toward&lt;/a&gt; the need to &lt;a href="/future-perfect/2024/3/20/24105735/peak-meat-livestock-emissions-plant-based-climate-deadline"&gt;massively reduce meat consumption&lt;/a&gt;. But tackling that problem, and many others, means we first need to abandon myths rooted in bad history.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p id="what-even-was-the-prehistoric-diet" class="_7ka5u1 _7ka5u0 duet--article--standard-heading xkp0cg1"&gt;&lt;h2 class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup"&gt;What even was the prehistoric diet?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup duet--article--standard-paragraph _1agbrixi lg8ac51 lg8ac50 xkp0cg1"&gt;Writing in &lt;em&gt;Scientific American&lt;/em&gt; in 2017, in the midst of the paleo diet craze, renowned paleontologist Peter Ungar challenged not just the diet itself but its very epistemological foundations. “What was the ancestral human diet? The question itself makes no sense,” he &lt;a href="https://www.scientificamerican.com/blog/guest-blog/the-true-human-diet/"&gt;wrote&lt;/a&gt;. What most distinguishes the human diet is its &lt;a href="https://www.americanscientist.org/article/meat-eating-among-the-earliest-humans"&gt;incredible adaptability&lt;/a&gt; across time and space. Our ancestors have, over the millennia, adapted to eating what was available in whatever quantities it was available. As Ungar noted, that can mean diets made up of almost entirely animal flesh and fat, or one consisting of mostly roots, tubers, and fruit. Trying to pin down a single “Paleolithic” or “ancestral” diet is impossible.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup duet--article--standard-paragraph _1agbrixi lg8ac51 lg8ac50 xkp0cg1"&gt;While the idea of Paleolithic eating summons images of humans as “&lt;a href="https://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/ajpa.24247"&gt;hypercarnivores&lt;/a&gt;,” or apex predators, humans are not naturally obligate carnivores like big cats. We are omnivores, capable of deriving nutrients from a vast variety of plant and animal sources. The role that meat played in our evolution, &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/0047248489900353"&gt;how much of it we ate&lt;/a&gt;, and how we got it (&lt;a href="https://www.jstor.org/stable/pdf/25801183.pdf"&gt;theories of scavenging carrion abound alongside those of near-constant hunting&lt;/a&gt;), &lt;a href="https://www.pnas.org/doi/full/10.1073/pnas.2115540119"&gt;remains the subject of vigorous debate among scholars&lt;/a&gt;, with plausible estimates, depending on the population, time period, and ecological context, ranging from &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC11090808/"&gt;very little&lt;/a&gt; to quite a bit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--block-placement _80slsf2 _80slsf0 duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-pullquote _1iohv3z0"&gt;&lt;p class="_1iohv3z1"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup _1iohv3z2 xkp0cg9"&gt;What was the ancestral human diet? The question itself makes no sense.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;cite class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup _1iohv3z3"&gt;— PETER UNGAR&lt;/cite&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup duet--article--standard-paragraph _1agbrixi lg8ac51 lg8ac50 xkp0cg1"&gt;Reconstructing ancient dietary patterns and quantities from scant fossilized remains, much less generalizing based on them, is &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/1601646"&gt;fraught detective work&lt;/a&gt;. It sometimes involves, quite literally, sifting through the trash of ancient peoples. &lt;a href="https://www.cambridge.org/core/books/vertebrate-taphonomy/46D04213E462D5EAFF36C106EA192978"&gt;Animal bones&lt;/a&gt; with damage from fire, &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S2352409X24001421"&gt;teeth&lt;/a&gt;, and butchering, for instance, can confirm animals were eaten, although it is difficult to determine frequency and quantity. While modern discussions of Paleolithic diets center on meat from a small number of livestock species farmed and eaten today, our ancestors ate a wide range of creatures, many now extinct or no longer used for food; the archeological record shows that rats, for example, were probably paleo-compliant.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup duet--article--standard-paragraph _1agbrixi lg8ac51 lg8ac50 xkp0cg1"&gt;Genomic and proteomic (protein) &lt;a href="https://royalsocietypublishing.org/doi/10.1098/rspb.2018.0977"&gt;analyses&lt;/a&gt; of fossilized material can also help shed light on ancient diets, and the chemical composition of human bones offers additional clues. The notion among some scholars that early humans ate a superabundance of meat comes not just from ideas about their hunting habits gleaned from the fossil record, but also from high levels of stable nitrogen isotopes in fossilized skeletons, which can suggest high consumption of offal. But science progresses on proposing and testing alternative explanations, and researchers have more recently suggested &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/24612646/"&gt;plants&lt;/a&gt; — and, now, maggots — as a source of all that nitrogen. The latter suggestion, put forth in the new &lt;em&gt;Science Advances&lt;/em&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.science.org/doi/10.1126/sciadv.adt7466"&gt;paper&lt;/a&gt;, is rooted in the theory that meat, a relatively scarce resource, would be kept around even as it rotted — not just to be eaten, but also to allow maggots to hatch to provide a steady source of fresh, bite-size protein.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup duet--article--standard-paragraph _1agbrixi lg8ac51 lg8ac50 xkp0cg1"&gt;Of course, much of this is educated guesswork. Thus, many theories about ancestral diets are also supplemented with evidence from the eating habits of contemporary &lt;a href="https://www.annualreviews.org/content/journals/10.1146/annurev-nutr-111120-105520"&gt;hunter-gatherer societies&lt;/a&gt;, who act as empirically studiable stand-ins for long-gone ancestors. Ungar, for instance, &lt;a href="https://www.scientificamerican.com/blog/guest-blog/the-true-human-diet/"&gt;contrasts&lt;/a&gt; the largely carnivorous fare of Alaska’s Tikiġaġmiut people with the plant-rich diets of the Gwi San people of the Kalahari. The authors of the &lt;em&gt;Science Advances&lt;/em&gt; paper back up their archaeological sleuthing with historical reports of 19th-century Arctic and subarctic hunter-gatherer societies eating maggots growing in stored animal carcasses. Both the fossil and ethnohistorical records, they conclude, reveal early human populations not as hypercarnivores but as omnivorous opportunists.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup duet--article--standard-paragraph _1agbrixi lg8ac51 lg8ac50 xkp0cg1"&gt;The closer we come to contemporary society, the more we know with greater certainty about what our ancestors ate. And here, too, the historical record fails to support ideas of persistent carnivory. If anything, the domestication of livestock, which first began to appear in the archaeological record 12,000 years ago, likely diminished meat’s role in human diets: Through millennia, farmed animals were often more valuable alive than dead, as a source of milk, wool, labor, and fertilizer, and as a store of wealth.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup duet--article--standard-paragraph _1agbrixi lg8ac51 lg8ac50 xkp0cg1"&gt;In medieval Europe, &lt;a href="https://www.laphamsquarterly.org/roundtable/ubiquitous-medieval-pigs"&gt;butchering pigs&lt;/a&gt; was a highly seasonal ritual, sometimes reserved for special occasions; in Imperial China, pigs &lt;a href="https://www.journals.uchicago.edu/doi/abs/10.1093/envhis/emq143"&gt;were a symbol&lt;/a&gt; of prosperity; throughout much of South Asia, cattle regularly supplied dairy and manure, but beef consumption was forbidden. Far from being a dietary staple, meat’s role was fluid: by turns a sacred offering, a show of wealth, or a winter fallback. And in most cases, meat intake remained relatively low, at least by modern standards, until the &lt;a href="https://cadmus.eui.eu/server/api/core/bitstreams/3f848502-2a76-5370-a58c-597de9f19d68/content"&gt;very recent past&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup duet--article--standard-paragraph _1agbrixi lg8ac51 lg8ac50 xkp0cg1"&gt;It wasn’t until around the turn of the 20th century that animal agriculture was industrialized. The adoption of assembly-line systems in slaughterhouses allowed for economies-of-scale killing of animals and standardization of cuts of meat, while selective breeding practices &lt;a href="https://books.google.de/books/about/Creating_Abundance.html?id=pjl7ywhnCCwC&amp;amp;source=kp_book_description&amp;amp;redir_esc=y"&gt;dramatically enhanced livestock productivity&lt;/a&gt;. As historian William Cronon &lt;a href="https://commonplace.online/article/natures-metropolis-at-30/"&gt;has shown&lt;/a&gt;, these advances, coupled with new technology like refrigerated rail cars and canning, quickly turned meat into a ubiquitous commodity. As crop agriculture also industrialized, animal feed became cheap, allowing for the advent of factory farms where animals like pigs and chickens were raised indoors for their entire lives and bred to grow to slaughter weight rapidly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup duet--article--standard-paragraph _1agbrixi lg8ac51 lg8ac50 xkp0cg1"&gt;These extremely recent changes remade humanity’s relationship to meat. Over the past century, the entire agricultural value chain has been redesigned to feed, raise, and kill animals on an ever-greater scale. In 1909, just over 150 million chickens were sold for slaughter in the US. By 1949, &lt;a href="http://www2.census.gov/prod2/decennial/documents/41667073v5p6ch4.pdf"&gt;that number was close to 600 million&lt;/a&gt;. In 2024, it was &lt;a href="https://downloads.usda.library.cornell.edu/usda-esmis/files/pg15bd88s/k356c167m/z029r057b/pslaan25.pdf"&gt;9.5 billion&lt;/a&gt;. Over the past half-century, American meat production has increased almost threefold and global meat production fivefold, a transformation that geographer Tony Weis has called the “&lt;a href="https://www.radicalphilosophy.com/commentary/towards-120-billion"&gt;meatification&lt;/a&gt;” of our food system.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup duet--article--standard-paragraph _1agbrixi lg8ac51 lg8ac50 xkp0cg1"&gt;Modern humans, as much as our Paleolithic ancestors, as much as our great-great-grandparents, adapt our diets to our surroundings. And surrounded by ever-greater quantities of cheap meat, we ate more of it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p id="can-we-please-be-serious-about-food-policy" class="_7ka5u1 _7ka5u0 duet--article--standard-heading xkp0cg1"&gt;&lt;h2 class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup"&gt;Can we please be serious about food policy?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup duet--article--standard-paragraph _1agbrixi lg8ac51 lg8ac50 xkp0cg1"&gt;Modern diets are fraught with anxiety, and with good reason. There is much about modernity and the modern food system to be anxious about, from its contribution to &lt;a href="https://www.frontiersin.org/journals/sustainable-food-systems/articles/10.3389/fsufs.2020.518039/full#h9"&gt;global climate change&lt;/a&gt; to the &lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2023/04/13/well/eat/food-additive-ban.html"&gt;potential health impacts of some food additives&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup duet--article--standard-paragraph _1agbrixi lg8ac51 lg8ac50 xkp0cg1"&gt;These are real problems, of course, but an anxious frame rooted in hyperbole, cliche, and nostalgia for free-grazing pigs doesn’t offer a clear perspective on what’s needed to address them. Instead, it serves up simplistic answers, like a wholesale rejection of modernity. But, ironically, hostility toward modern food technology and an effective regulatory state, whether by the foodie gurus, carnivore podcasters, &lt;a href="https://drjessicaknurick.substack.com/p/food-additives-and-the-maha-disconnect"&gt;MAHA&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="/24158356/raw-milk-pasteurization-h5n1-bird-flu-sales-consumption-government-trust"&gt;raw milk enthusiasts&lt;/a&gt;, or &lt;a href="https://www.raps.org/news-and-articles/news-articles/2025/4/thousands-of-fda-staff-fired-in-latest-rif"&gt;DOGE cost-cutters&lt;/a&gt;, might very well &lt;em&gt;increase&lt;/em&gt; the quantity of rotting meat (and perhaps maggots) in our food, &lt;a href="https://www.hup.harvard.edu/books/9780674728776"&gt;a problem in 19th-century America&lt;/a&gt; before the creation of the FDA and the widespread adoption of food refrigeration and preservation technologies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup duet--article--standard-paragraph _1agbrixi lg8ac51 lg8ac50 xkp0cg1"&gt;Consider that the modern food system is, on balance, a great thing. Diseases of malnutrition &lt;a href="https://academic.oup.com/book/27780/chapter-abstract/198026487?redirectedFrom=fulltext"&gt;like pellagra and rickets&lt;/a&gt; have been banished to the past, as have the dangers of eating &lt;a href="https://academic.oup.com/book/27780/chapter-abstract/198024009?redirectedFrom=fulltext&amp;amp;login=false"&gt;contaminated, toxic, spoiled, or adulterated foods&lt;/a&gt;. It is only because &lt;a href="https://www.jstor.org/stable/20752979?mag=decline-malnutrition-world-eats-now&amp;amp;seq=1"&gt;food is more abundant, affordable, and safe&lt;/a&gt; than at any other time in human history that we can spare any attention to the chronic, long-term problems to which modern diets contribute, like obesity and diabetes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup duet--article--standard-paragraph _1agbrixi lg8ac51 lg8ac50 xkp0cg1"&gt;Addressing those problems means embracing modernity rather than rejecting it. It requires actually engaging with the complexity of the food system, and facing up to a few uncomfortable truths, like the fact that it is meat in particular, and not food generally, that drives many of the food system’s harms. But in the face of complexity, a retreat to an unspoiled past offers both an escapist fantasy free of difficult tradeoffs and a handy justification for our worst dietary choices.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup duet--article--standard-paragraph _1agbrixi lg8ac51 lg8ac50 xkp0cg1"&gt;In an imagined past, meat consumption acts as a potent political signifier that binds us to our tribe. And food becomes a theater for performing politics and identity. For foodies who sneer at “&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/environment/2023/aug/02/mark-bittman-community-kitchen-restaurants"&gt;industrial food&lt;/a&gt;,” going back to small farms and eating supposedly “better” organic and regeneratively farmed meat may signal a commitment to &lt;a href="https://repprovisions.com/pages/why-rep-regenerative-beef-is-healthier-for-you?srsltid=AfmBOoo5pvvIi1MisWXWWH0l_VPhQ_SeHqrXjT8ThZAHNFyNSzbdFEDx"&gt;personal health and environmental justice&lt;/a&gt; that is &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/environment/2020/dec/23/organic-meat-production-just-as-bad-for-climate-study-finds"&gt;simply&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.frontiersin.org/journals/ecology-and-evolution/articles/10.3389/fevo.2021.816374/full"&gt;not&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.wri.org/insights/better-meat-sourcing-climate-environmental-impacts"&gt;borne&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://link.springer.com/article/10.1007/s13165-025-00493-w"&gt;out&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://newrepublic.com/article/163735/myth-regenerative-ranching"&gt;by&lt;/a&gt; science. On the right, the embrace of meat &lt;a href="https://newrepublic.com/article/171781/meat-culture-war-crickets"&gt;anchors a particular vision of politics&lt;/a&gt; — and &lt;a href="https://www.npr.org/2024/09/14/nx-s1-5003066/beef-climate-change-american-men-masculinity"&gt;masculinity&lt;/a&gt; — that is fundamentally anti-modern, anti-liberal, and anti-“woke.” And so the modern food system (junk), liberal men (soy boys), and scientists and experts (globalists) can all be framed as an assault on a fundamental and personal bodily practice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup duet--article--standard-paragraph _1agbrixi lg8ac51 lg8ac50 xkp0cg1"&gt;But rather than a transgressive return to a lost past, meat-heavy diets not only represent the status quo but also rely entirely on the modern food system and its globe-spanning networks of exchange, cutting-edge logistics and infrastructure, highly capitalized multinational corporations, and sophisticated biotechnologies. Close factory farms and industrialized cattle feedlots, &lt;a href="https://www.sentienceinstitute.org/us-factory-farming-estimates"&gt;and 99 percent of chicken, 98 percent of pork, and 75 percent of beef&lt;/a&gt; in the US disappear overnight, making mass-scale carnivory impossible.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--block-placement _80slsf2 _80slsf0 duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-pullquote _1iohv3z0"&gt;&lt;p class="_1iohv3z1"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup _1iohv3z2 xkp0cg9"&gt;As is often the case with myths, those about ancestral diets are more about the anxieties and identities of their purveyors than it is about a real past or even a real present.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup duet--article--standard-paragraph _1agbrixi lg8ac51 lg8ac50 xkp0cg1"&gt;Paradoxically, then, those who champion pre-modern diets can do so only because of the amenities and technologies of the modern world. At no other point in human history could someone opt for the meat of their choice for three meals every day, without getting any blood on their own hands, and then post about it on social media to claim they are living like their ancestors. If anything, the myth of meat’s transhistorical importance masks the fact that the meatiness of current diets is a historical flash in the pan, the result of a food system focused on overproducing meat, not an evolved set of inherent needs or preferences.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup duet--article--standard-paragraph _1agbrixi lg8ac51 lg8ac50 xkp0cg1"&gt;As is often the case with myths, those about Paleolithic, ancestral, and great-great-grandmotherly diets are more about the anxieties and identities of their purveyors than it is about a real past or even a real present. The very image of the primitive prehistoric hunter is less careful archeology and ethnography than it is a product of &lt;a href="https://www.americanscientist.org/article/refuting-a-myth-about-human-origins"&gt;modern misconceptions about human evolution&lt;/a&gt; mixed with &lt;a href="https://www.jstor.org/stable/683202"&gt;popular culture pastiche&lt;/a&gt;, which makes self-styled primitivism quintessentially post-modern, as if the “&lt;a href="https://knowyourmeme.com/memes/this-is-what-they-took-from-us-and-unbelievable-honkers-right-wing-nostalgia"&gt;this is what they took from us&lt;/a&gt;” meme was slapped over a picture of Fred Flintstone eating dinosaur ribs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup duet--article--standard-paragraph _1agbrixi lg8ac51 lg8ac50 xkp0cg1"&gt;History shows us that there is no single way humans have eaten and no predetermined way we should eat. Diets are a product of the world we live in. And in that world, the questions we should be asking are not about what our ancestors ate — and whether we should therefore eat meat, berries, or maggots — but about what rational decisions we can make about our future. That includes asking why meat is so cheap and easy to buy, and whether it ought to remain so. The answers lie in science, public health, and political economy, and not in myths. The diets of the long dead are a red herring at best, red meat for reactionary politics at worst.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>vox.com</author><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimAFBVV95cUxQbThIOVF5NmNCNE5WTUdOOHhtS2o2S2JRRjFNUWRqQmhneXM4QnNkVWR6YXoydFFLV2dYbmltWXpnN1FZN183Q0h1Z0U3ZEN2VzdNYXNOQVhJRmZBRTFUMWUyeFBTdEpScHFWZDRmTW1EazhZZ1A5cDFjWTFCRGo3X3h3RE5WX1U3cTgwWEVZZDNRRFE4MTVudA</guid></item><item><title>医疗保险覆盖范围的拟议变更威胁到使用用于治疗疼痛的程序- statnews.com</title><link>https://www.statnews.com/2025/10/31/medicare-coverage-peripheral-nerve-block-procedures/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content the-content wp-block-post-content is-layout-flow wp-block-post-content-is-layout-flow"&gt;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/39751180/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;1 in 5&lt;/a&gt; Americans suffering from chronic pain may soon lose access to evidence-based interventions that have &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/30612462/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;existed&lt;/a&gt; for decades.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Looming &lt;a href="https://asra.com/news-publications/asra-updates/blog-landing/asra-updates/2025/10/16/asra-pain-medicine-urges-action-on-proposed-medicare-coverage-limits-for-peripheral-nerve-blocks-and-other-chronic-pain-procedures" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;changes&lt;/a&gt; to Medicare coverage threaten access to local anesthetic blockade, or “peripheral nerve block” procedures. &lt;a href="https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jamainternalmedicine/fullarticle/2808074?utm_source=openevidence&amp;amp;utm_medium=referral" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Medicare administrative contractors&lt;/a&gt; across the country have &lt;a href="https://www.cms.gov/medicare-coverage-database/view/lcd.aspx?lcdid=40260" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;recently&lt;/a&gt; proposed eliminating coverage for these minimally invasive, non-opioid treatment options for chronic pain disorders. If approved, these coverage changes could drive patients back to opioids, exacerbating the overdose epidemic in the United States, and force patients to unnecessarily pursue invasive and expensive surgical interventions.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Chronic pain is a leading cause of disability in the United States. It is associated with depression, substance use disorders, an economic burden of &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40730349/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;$722.8 billion in medical costs&lt;/a&gt; annually, and lost productivity. Chronic pain diagnoses are &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40730349/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;more prevalent&lt;/a&gt; in veterans, women, adults living in poverty, and those residing in rural areas.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The challenge of balancing the treatment of chronic pain with addressing the opioid overdose epidemic remains one of the preeminent public health challenges in the United States. Guidelines issued by the American Society of Anesthesiologists’ Task Force on Chronic Pain Management &lt;a href="https://journals.lww.com/anesthesiology/fulltext/2010/04000/practice_guidelines_for_chronic_pain_management_.11.aspx" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;emphasize&lt;/a&gt; the importance of a multimodal approach to therapy including non-opioid pain medications, physical and psychological therapy, and minimally invasive procedures.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Peripheral nerve blocks are minimally invasive procedures that are &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/25794201/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;well-tolerated&lt;/a&gt; by patients. They are considered relatively low-cost interventions, especially when &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/35610642/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;compared&lt;/a&gt; with alternatives such as orthopedic surgery under general anesthesia or hospital admissions for severe pain requiring treatment with intravenous opioid medications. These interventions have broad applications for patients living with conditions that cause chronic pain, such as headache disorders and trigeminal neuralgia. Trigeminal neuralgia is a condition characterized by unpredictable &lt;a href="https://www.nejm.org/doi/full/10.1056/NEJMra1914484" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;attacks of facial pain&lt;/a&gt; that are so severe the condition is associated with depression and &lt;a href="https://www.nejm.org/doi/full/10.1056/NEJMra1914484" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;suicidal ideation&lt;/a&gt;. These patients frequently report immediate pain relief after a peripheral nerve block, with the &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/30119988/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;majority&lt;/a&gt; of patients experiencing &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/31208761" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;a greater than 50% reduction&lt;/a&gt; in their pain, which can last several months and allow patients to return to work and childcare responsibilities.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Similarly, peripheral nerve blocks have demonstrated efficacy in both reducing pain during &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/39432635/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;acute migraine attacks&lt;/a&gt; as well as &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/31568309/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;preventing chronic migraines&lt;/a&gt;. Migraine patients who undergo occipital nerve blocks experience &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/31568309/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;fewer headache days per month&lt;/a&gt;, which may lead to reduced consumption of pain medications (including opioids) and reduced migraine-associated disability. These procedures are also utilized for patients struggling with &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/38731163/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;chronic pelvic pain&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40681086/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;adhesive capsulitis (frozen shoulder)&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/36369781/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;knee osteoarthritis&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC5018589/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;complex regional pain syndrome&lt;/a&gt;. If patients experience pain relief from a peripheral block, some undergo the placement of &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/39565237/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;peripheral nerve stimulators&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/27051229/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;denervation&lt;/a&gt; procedures that reduce or eliminate the nerve’s ability to transmit pain signals, however diagnostic peripheral nerve blocks must precede these interventions. The symptom relief from these procedures can last from &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC8436449/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;months&lt;/a&gt; to years.&lt;/p&gt;





&lt;p&gt;Yet on Sept. 25, five of 12 Medicare administrative contractors (MACs) in the U.S., representing 24 states, &lt;a href="https://www.cms.gov/medicare-coverage-database/view/lcd.aspx?lcdid=40299&amp;amp;ver=2&amp;amp;stateRegion=all&amp;amp;contractorNumber=all&amp;amp;proposedStatus=all&amp;amp;sortBy=title&amp;amp;bc=11" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;announced&lt;/a&gt; their intention to dramatically restrict Medicare coverage for peripheral nerve blocks. Medicare contractors are private insurers that process claims for Medicare Parts A and B. Acting as intermediaries between the federal government and Americans insured by Medicare, these private entities make over &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S1546144005001638?via%3Dihub" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;90% of coverage decisions&lt;/a&gt; in the United States by issuing Local Coverage Determinations (LCDs). These policies define which procedures and medications are “&lt;a href="https://www.archives.gov/milestone-documents/social-security-act" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;reasonable and necessary&lt;/a&gt;” for Medicare coverage and influence other government payers and commercial insurance programs. While this change would only affect the 24 states governed by the five MACs initially, other states could follow suit, and private insurers often follow too.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Under the proposed LCDs, chronic pain procedures would be limited to three steroid injections for median nerve pain, two steroid injections for Morton’s neuroma, and radiofrequency neurolysis for trigeminal neuralgia. All other peripheral nerve blocks and denervation procedures would not be covered. Unless the MACs want more Americans to be unable to work, reliant on opioids, and suffering in pain, it’s hard to understand their motivation here. Eliminating peripheral nerve block coverage will not result in meaningful cost savings from these patients, and may lead to more frequent emergency department and clinic visits, increased use of opioids and other pharmacologic interventions, or more time spent on disability, ultimately &lt;a href="https://asipp.org/wp-content/uploads/Comment-Letter-to-MACs-Public-Comment-for-Proposed-LCD-Peripheral-Nerve-Blocks-and-Procedures-for-Chronic-Pain-10.24.2025.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;raising&lt;/a&gt; direct and indirect health care expenditures in the United States.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;These coverage changes have been met with concern from numerous professional groups including the &lt;a href="https://asra.com/news-publications/asra-updates/blog-landing/asra-updates/2025/10/16/asra-pain-medicine-urges-action-on-proposed-medicare-coverage-limits-for-peripheral-nerve-blocks-and-other-chronic-pain-procedures" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;American Society of Regional Anesthesia and Pain Medicine&lt;/a&gt; and the &lt;a href="https://asipp.org/wp-content/uploads/Comment-Letter-to-MACs-Public-Comment-for-Proposed-LCD-Peripheral-Nerve-Blocks-and-Procedures-for-Chronic-Pain-10.24.2025.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;American Society of Interventional Pain Physicians,&lt;/a&gt; who criticized the LCDs’ extremely restrictive criteria to evaluate the efficacy of peripheral nerve blocks. Medicare administrative contractor websites state that the new policy was developed to “&lt;a href="https://www.cms.gov/medicare-coverage-database/view/lcd.aspx?lcdid=40260" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;incorporate new procedures and literature&lt;/a&gt;.” However, the LCDs &lt;a href="https://asipp.org/wp-content/uploads/Comment-Letter-to-MACs-Public-Comment-for-Proposed-LCD-Peripheral-Nerve-Blocks-and-Procedures-for-Chronic-Pain-10.24.2025.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;exceed&lt;/a&gt; the standards for evidence used in even Cochrane reviews, which are known to reject greater than 90% of available treatments.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The analysis also ignores the ethical challenges of conducting randomized controlled trials, especially for procedures with &lt;a href="https://painmed.org/medicare-releases-proposed-lcd-on-peripheral-nerve-blocks/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;decades of clinical use&lt;/a&gt; and established benefits.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Additionally, the policies &lt;a href="https://www.cms.gov/medicare-coverage-database/view/lcd.aspx?lcdid=40260" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;include&lt;/a&gt; procedures that do not fit the definition of peripheral nerve blocks, stellate ganglion and cervical sympathetic nerve blocks, as well as &lt;a href="https://asipp.org/wp-content/uploads/Comment-Letter-to-MACs-Public-Comment-for-Proposed-LCD-Peripheral-Nerve-Blocks-and-Procedures-for-Chronic-Pain-10.24.2025.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;three&lt;/a&gt; irrelevant diagnostic procedure codes, which raises questions about the expertise of those writing the LCDs. Despite directives within the &lt;a href="https://www.govinfo.gov/content/pkg/COMPS-13005/pdf/COMPS-13005.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;21st Century Cures Act of 2016&lt;/a&gt; calling for increased transparency throughout the LCD process, it is difficult to determine the people and associated conflicts of interests involved in the authorship of these documents. Only two of five MACs list a physician on the LCD’s website, and &lt;a href="https://www.cms.gov/medicare-coverage-database/view/lcd.aspx?lcdid=40260" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;one&lt;/a&gt; of the two is an OB-GYN with no relevant advanced training.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Physicians and advocates concerned about the proposed coverage changes should contact their state senate and house of representative healthy policy committees, &lt;a href="https://asra.com/news-publications/asra-updates/blog-landing/asra-updates/2025/10/16/asra-pain-medicine-urges-action-on-proposed-medicare-coverage-limits-for-peripheral-nerve-blocks-and-other-chronic-pain-procedures" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;register&lt;/a&gt; and provide expert opinions at contractor meetings, and share their clinical expertise during public &lt;a href="https://asra.com/news-publications/asra-updates/blog-landing/asra-updates/2025/10/16/asra-pain-medicine-urges-action-on-proposed-medicare-coverage-limits-for-peripheral-nerve-blocks-and-other-chronic-pain-procedures" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;comment&lt;/a&gt; periods open now until Nov. 8.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Tricia Pendergrast, M.D., is an anesthesiology resident physician at the University of Michigan. You can find her on &lt;a href="https://www.tiktok.com/@triciapendergrastmd?lang=en" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;TikTok&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;/div&gt;

		&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>statnews.com</author><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 08:31:48 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikgFBVV95cUxOUzA3X3Z6Y0tzb0ZudTdLSWtjQ1YxTXh6YnlOT3pnZUhGSVp0dVowQmVTa3A3YTFseUs3Zlp4cUJEdzVfb05zZWhvM2VabkVJeEx5NGppR3VlWmFyWFMyZnpqZVlwS2hWMlBxcWJMUVFmdXVXUU15NDdyUmZBbGFCTEdfM19nNXprekVHWjNCNkZPdw</guid></item><item><title>隐藏在大脑深处的信号可以跟踪帕金森症状- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/a-signal-hidden-deep-in-your-brain-could-track-parkinsons-symptoms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;A search for  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/go/IYl" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73029" data-postid="179672" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;Parkinson's&lt;/a&gt; in the hiss of our brain's static has revealed measures of motor control that could one day &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/smart-brain-implants-can-now-adapt-to-optimize-parkinsons-treatment"&gt;fine-tune precise forms of stimulation therapy&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Led by the Max Planck Institute for Human Cognitive and Brain Sciences in Germany, an international team of scientists combined five sets of electrophysiological data taken from deep within the brains of 119 people with Parkinson's disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;By comparing specific brain-wave activity to the severity of individual patients' symptoms, the researchers were able to sift out patterns that could be confidently matched to the condition's impact on movement.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/restless-legs-treatment-slashes-increased-risk-of-parkinsons-disease"&gt;Restless Legs Treatment Slashes Increased Risk of Parkinson's Disease&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Parkinson's disease is fundamentally a &lt;a href="https://www.neurolab360.com/blog/basalgangliaandpd"&gt;breakdown in the functioning&lt;/a&gt; of a part of the brain called the &lt;a href="https://my.clevelandclinic.org/health/body/23962-basal-ganglia"&gt;basal ganglia&lt;/a&gt;, robbing people of the ability to filter information required to keep their body movements precise and steady. The result is slow, stiff, shaky motion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_179673" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-179673" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/basal_ganglia_PD_642.jpg" alt="basal ganglia" class="wp-image-179673 size-full" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/basal_ganglia_PD_642.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/basal_ganglia_PD_642-600x327.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-179673" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Location of the basal ganglia in the brain. (&lt;a href="https://www.canva.com/photos/MAC_WeBNVN4/"&gt;decade3d/Getty Images/Canva&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;In theory, &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/dopamine-doesnt-work-in-our-brains-quite-the-way-we-thought"&gt;changes in the basal ganglia's operation&lt;/a&gt; should be noticeable in their electrical activity, appearing as a general excess of &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/alpha-beta-theta-what-are-brain-states-and-brain-waves-and-can-we-control-them-219236"&gt;mid-to-high-range oscillations&lt;/a&gt; known as &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Beta_wave"&gt;beta waves&lt;/a&gt;, as well as an increase in spiking signals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1038/s41531-022-00443-3"&gt;Studies&lt;/a&gt; have captured &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1113/JP284768"&gt;plenty of beta-wave activity&lt;/a&gt; in the past through electrodes implanted deep in the brain as a means of treatment. Although it was evident that these waves varied with symptom severity, the methods used to interpret the buzz left a lot to be desired.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A mix of patient diversity, combinations of symptoms, and a lack of unaffected controls made it difficult to compare the brain-wave activity of diseased states with a 'healthy' standard.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;By pooling multiple datasets and comparing differences in similar activity between more-or-less affected basal ganglia in each brain hemisphere, the researchers behind this latest study could 'listen in' on harmonies hidden within the brain's roar.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/spark-into-space-comp"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro-642x272.jpg" alt="Win a $10,000 Space Coast Adventure Holiday" class="alignnone wp-image-177074 size-medium" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro-642x272.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro-768x326.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro-600x255.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro.jpg 844w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You can imagine the brain as a concert hall full of musicians before a rehearsal," &lt;a href="https://www.mpg.de/25632689/1030-nepf-noise-as-a-signal-a-new-electrical-signature-of-parkinson-s-disease-149575-x"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; lead author and neurologist Moritz Gerster.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Some groups play together, creating a distinct rhythm. Others practice on their own, merging into a non-rhythmic 'noise'. If you only measure the overall volume, you miss this distinction."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Identifying precise rhythms in the basal ganglia could eventually play a valuable role in &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/new-ultrasound-helmet-reaches-deep-inside-the-brain-without-surgery"&gt;treatments that use deep brain stimulation&lt;/a&gt;. This could help return a degree of motor control to those with Parkinson's by dynamically responding to changing rhythms – like a conductor who now knows what to listen out for.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This research was published in &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.ebiom.2025.105988"&gt;eBiomedicine&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 03:41:42 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimwFBVV95cUxNaTJBNTFRSGR2S2ZrblBoa0wzdGc0RXZQRktZdzJlT1FWYlEwZGU3STNtRTlUQTEyTi1QYU1JTG1mU3BGRFkyTS0yNVFaYXl1eFNjczBscElZWkJIRklCUURra0JjX0pEYXFDcmlOektWSEpIMW4yRFlUalpnNVpCMGdTVDJUMUMzZUFWcUp0WXNYRmo2SUNNZXIwRQ</guid></item><item><title>顶级心脏病专家揭示了有助于自然降低血压的运动类型-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/want-to-lower-blood-pressure-naturally-top-cardiologist-reveals-the-most-effective-exercise/articleshow/124980823.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;p&gt;High blood pressure, commonly referred to as hypertension, affects millions worldwide, and poses a serious health threat. It boosts the odds of heart disease, stroke and a host of complications. One of the best ways to bring down Blood Pressure naturally is aerobic exercise. Dr. Jeremy London, a cardiologist, explains how regular cardio, not only lowers blood pressure but also strengthens the heart.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="3"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;What is aerobic exercise&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="5"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aerobic exercise refers to any activity that lifts your heart rate and breathing for a stretch of time. Typical examples span walking, running, swimming, cycling and dancing. By tapping oxygen to power the muscles, these exercises boost the efficiency of your system-the heart and its network of blood vessels.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="8"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="lOvcW vdo_embedd"&gt;&lt;div class="k7lcu"&gt;&lt;p class="efT4r"&gt;Natural Ways to Control High Blood Pressure Effectively&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="10"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="12"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;How do they help&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="14"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to Dr. London, aerobic exercise "re‑trains the system " essentially coaxing the blood vessels into a supple, relaxed and responsive state. This shift eases the drag the vessels impose on the flow of blood. When the vessels dilate and unwind, the heart can pump with effort which in turn brings blood pressure down.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="16"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;When aerobic activity gets the body moving, the endothelial lining of the vessels releases oxide-a potent vasodilator. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That fleeting molecule gently unfastens the tension hugging the vessel walls, letting blood flow freely. This cascade of relaxation is a reason aerobic workouts tend to balance blood pressure, and strengthen the heart.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="20"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;What does science say&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="22"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a 2002 meta‑analysis that combined 54 randomised controlled trials and a total of 2,419 participants, researchers found that aerobic exercise consistently nudges both the systolic (the "top" number) and diastolic (the "number) of blood pressure downward. On average, systolic pressure fell by 3.8 mmHg, and diastolic, by about 2.6 mmHg and this modest reduction appeared in people with hypertension as well as those, with normal blood pressure. The effect was observed across the spectrum of categories from lean to overweight, to obese individuals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="27"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Recent investigations confirm those findings. In a 2025 meta‑analysis, aerobic exercise regimens were shown to shave off over five millimetres of mercury from blood pressure on average, with the most striking reductions observed in participants who started with elevated pressures. The study also highlighted that even a modest eight‑week period of activity can yield a drop.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="31"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The 2023 study reinforces those findings, revealing that moderate‑intensity aerobic exercise can lower blood pressure and improve heart function in adults by prompting vessels to dilate more and easing arterial stiffness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="33"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;See More: &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/doctor-shares-7-surprising-ways-to-lower-blood-pressure-naturally/articleshow/124997930.cms" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;Doctor shares 7 surprising ways to lower blood pressure naturally&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="36"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;How much exercise does one need&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="38"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The American Heart Association suggests that adults aim for 150 minutes of moderate‑intensity aerobic activity each week, which can be broken down into five 30‑minute sessions. A brisk walk, a bike ride or a swim, all count toward that goal. Dr. London stresses that weaving exercise into routines is the most reliable way to secure heart health, and keep blood pressure in check.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="42"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="44"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Supplementary health benefits&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="46"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Beyond pulling down blood pressure, aerobic workouts toughen the heart’s muscle letting it push blood through the vessels efficiently. They also rev up circulation, reduce LDL cholesterol, raise the HDL cholesterol and help keep weight and blood‑sugar levels in check. All of these benefits combine to slash the likelihood of heart disease, stroke and a host of ailments.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="50"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you’re new to exercise or trying to manage blood pressure, it helps to start with low‑impact moves-think brisk walking or an easy bike ride. As your fitness picks up, you can slowly stretch out the time you spend, and add a bit intensity. The real trick is to stay consistent; regular aerobic week after week, is what ultimately brings the drops in blood pressure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="53"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;How to protect your heart&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="55"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr. Jeremy London adds that looking after your heart beyond just the workout. He points out that what ends up on the plate matters a lot - aim for whole unrefined foods for roughly four‑fifths of the daily intake. By contrast the usual suspects-salty, sugary, fat‑laden processed fare-can eat away at your heart and the vessels that feed it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="57"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Staying hydrated is another piece of the puzzle-getting enough water helps keep blood flowing smoothly, and supports the heart’s overall performance. Dr. London advises cutting back on alcohol pointing out that it can be toxic to the cells in your body, including those that make up the heart. Likewise steering clear of smoking and handling stress, whether through mindfulness practices or leaning on a community, can provide a boost to heart health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="61"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Routine health check‑ups that track blood pressure, cholesterol and blood‑sugar levels can catch issues before they flare up. Prioritising sleep-sticking to a schedule and aiming for deep restorative rest-helps the heart repair itself, and cuts the risk of heart disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="63"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="65"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="67"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 02:43:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimwJBVV95cUxOWTBjRHFUbHFhYzdzc0ZHREVJSmZSVUpwWDNrblgzSWtWVkpGRkstQWNjTldLWDJiUDRlQVlTaHE5RThQSGdrc2hKMWs2VHJ5Z2dtdUx6S2YzY0VWbWNtanVRS2pHTEJaWjh6MGVubEtuSzNQNGNzQzNCZDhDR3pkZnVYUWRHZWNObnkxa3AyVjlFQUFNcmhNRlJhT0ktSVZMOVRRLWU0ZzZWY3k3TjVtdENsdTNnaHNfSVVhbVEyb0N1OTFnNmJSVHY4MWM3YmRhVVBRQzlub05Pd0RwR1pucDFSWWI4NlY4bDg2NW1sSlZ6RHRjV09xX3ZTWW1RWlpnTmRrWDNhX2lwdEJQVHBUUUdsZkF0TVBvZVRn</guid></item><item><title>大脑训练应用程序“扭转了关键大脑系统10年的衰退” - ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/brain-training-app-reverses-10-years-of-decline-in-a-key-brain-system</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;It's not just your body that needs to be 'worked out'. Your brain also needs &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/scientists-made-a-video-game-that-boosts-short-term-memory-in-older-adults"&gt;training&lt;/a&gt; to stay young and fit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A digital brain exercise, developed by the American biotech company &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Posit_Science_Corporation"&gt;Posit Science Corporation&lt;/a&gt;, has been put to the test by neurologists at McGill University in Canada, with some promising results.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a rigorous, double-blinded controlled trial, 82 healthy adults over the age of 65 were randomly assigned to play either Posit's 'BrainHQ' app or a recreational computer game for thirty minutes a day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;After 10 weeks, brain scans revealed that those who played BrainHQ, which focused on speed-based challenges, showed measurable increases in &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cholinergic"&gt;cholinergic&lt;/a&gt; activity, a type of &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/part-of-your-brain-acts-like-a-pause-button-that-freezes-your-whole-body"&gt;brain signalling&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This was seen in a part of their brain known as the &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Anterior_cingulate_cortex"&gt;anterior cingulate cortex&lt;/a&gt; (ACC) – which supports selective attention, inhibitory control, and memory.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Related: &lt;/b&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/one-type-of-activity-is-particularly-effective-at-keeping-your-brain-young"&gt;&lt;b&gt;One Type of Activity Is Particularly Effective at Keeping Your Brain Young&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The increase in cholinergic signaling was comparable in magnitude to how much the ACC usually shrinks over 10 years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The training restored cholinergic health to levels typically seen in someone 10 years younger," &lt;a href="https://www.mcgill.ca/newsroom/channels/news/researchers-neuro-show-brain-exercise-yields-benefits-368265"&gt;claims&lt;/a&gt; neurologist Etienne de Villers-Sidani from McGill.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"This is the first time any intervention, drug or non-drug, has been shown to do that in humans."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_179584" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-179584" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/double-decisioneasy-_easy_level_0-642x402.png" alt="Brain-Training App " class="wp-image-179584 size-medium" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/double-decisioneasy-_easy_level_0-642x402.png 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/double-decisioneasy-_easy_level_0-1077x675.png 1077w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/double-decisioneasy-_easy_level_0-768x481.png 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/double-decisioneasy-_easy_level_0-600x376.png 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/double-decisioneasy-_easy_level_0.png 1200w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-179584" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;In the Double Decision exercise in the BrainHQ app, participants identified images on a screen at increasing speed. (&lt;a href="https://www.mcgill.ca/newsroom/channels/news/researchers-neuro-show-brain-exercise-yields-benefits-368265"&gt;BrainHQ, Posit Science&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;The BrainHQ app is currently available for purchase via monthly and yearly subscriptions, and the company &lt;a href="https://www.brainhq.com/world-class-science/"&gt;claims&lt;/a&gt; it has developed the technology &lt;a href="https://www.brainhq.com/news/press-releases/hundreds-of-studies-show-efficacy-of-one-particular-brain-fitness-program/"&gt;based on scientific evidence&lt;/a&gt;, testing it in hundreds of &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.2196/53623"&gt;peer-reviewed&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1002/cam4.5904"&gt;papers&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Preliminary evidence does suggest that the app can impact the brain, and these changes might be beneficial, but it's unknown if those changes are lasting or if they translate to real differences in memory, attention, and learning in the everyday function of older individuals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The recent trial is only small, and it is incentivized by company profit, so there is reason to remain cautious. That said, it is rigorously designed and uses advanced brain scanning techniques in collaboration with McGill neurologists.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We used a rare technology," &lt;a href="https://www.mcgill.ca/newsroom/channels/news/researchers-neuro-show-brain-exercise-yields-benefits-368265"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; de Villers-Sidani. "The [Montreal Neurological Institute-Hospital] is one of the few centers worldwide that can produce the tracer and run the scan."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_179706" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-179706" class="wp-caption aligncenter"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Intervention-and-active-control-programs.jpg" alt="Schematic depicting the two tasks in the intervention" class="size-full wp-image-179706" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Intervention-and-active-control-programs.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Intervention-and-active-control-programs-600x458.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-179706" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;The intervention and active control tasks.  (Attarha et al., &lt;em&gt;JMIR Serious Games&lt;/em&gt;, 2025)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;The cholinergic system connects many parts of the brain, including the hippocampus – which is heavily involved in learning and memory. Theoretically, if this system is strengthened, it could improve common symptoms of aging, like memory loss.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Seeing changes to the cholinergic system following brain training is intriguing, but further trials among larger and more diverse cohorts are needed to understand more.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/spark-into-space-comp"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro-642x272.jpg" alt="Win a $10,000 Space Coast Adventure Holiday" class="alignnone wp-image-177074 size-medium" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro-642x272.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro-768x326.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro-600x255.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro.jpg 844w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Identifying and implementing effective strategies to support brain health has the potential to reduce health care costs, increase workforce participation and community engagement, and improve quality of life," the authors of the trial &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.2196/75161"&gt;conclude&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"These findings support the use of this promising, low-risk intervention and contribute to a mechanistic understanding of cognitive training that establishes a foundation for future trials."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study was published in &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.2196/75161"&gt;&lt;i&gt;JMIR Serious Games&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 02:03:46 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMinwFBVV95cUxNbU5DSm9FU1lJTTZMbTRmaHlSc2U1cTk5d3JCLUtFYjVXZWZFM0RHckpIeHllU0pPN0VScGtqMVpvM0ZnTDRZd21peUdHbmFDWXhXVFJUQVZUMnhqRWRkdEtJc3lINGdTTzZpZk9ENFVFdzFMOExJTG5ieWxQdVY1V3VHTFVMYktaLWYwTGRBR0tybWpYQ2FvM0hNVWZxdnc</guid></item><item><title>眼睛对健康的看法：营养师解码9个警告标志以及如何自然修复它们-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/what-the-eyes-say-about-health-dietitian-decodes-9-warning-signs-and-how-to-fix-them-naturally/photostory/124970884.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="COQxt" data-ua-type="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;While sleepless nights often get the blame, persistent dark circles can also signal low iron. Iron supports oxygen flow to tissues, and when it drops, the skin under the eyes darkens due to poor circulation.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;What helps: Dates, moringa powder, and soaked raisins are powerful iron-rich foods that help brighten under-eye areas from within.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 01:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMingJBVV95cUxOUWJwcFhZb3BWREhDQlgyMG80VF84b3VUdzY4ZV90ZllxWmpiellISUFEdEhzb2lFcHJLdE1nUU1FcEFxYXQwa3V5RXhTUmlYdGxZUklOeGlhdHdHMHljWGljUUgwclp5Vi0xR2pHWi1EVmxpZWtCVTVNSG1ETHpERHRyMVczRElCbk16N1VoVXpKTnVuV2l6OThtLXRTNnJDYklVSFpSS1g4YmNhNENJT0JVbXkzSVlhN2hoMXJ0Q2FnNDNRRWpES0owMTR5Q2xyMGJnT193Ujc5Rnp6cmY1bWNxRk1HRGNLWnlidFdpeXZjazhyelBZSXNvQVp2TmxxME1PdFNhRXNxTEV4YnFFNjM1S3VmcGZOVWZma09R0gGmAkFVX3lxTE9mbUFVdHhfNVRwelJJb0ktUnlId2picGlkN1JvdUNRYTBnSmZuMVBDa0RnVW1VWWdDN0tmX3NpTnppeV83eFhOckVPeW1IeFVVNk9Hb292TzFEdGxxVVFLSWlFdGhUWFJLWG1jZkNod3RDMXVHcTlvc0QwckR5Rk10LXpRVFphRklHUTQwTkkwTmttNnhBYlk5NGdHOVV4eVJOQmhGRTVCaFllamdLS2J4aXB3UC1IZmY2bnhTUFRRamJUaDhpV3VSa29pamc2ZTNjMHU3Q1AtVjI5ZmlTRXFZMFhmRGJ4TWtXM1BIOEx2c2kxMjNaazJSZHFTcUhoTFotWk1hanhlVmZCMjZzZzMxZ0FITURaMGxVelJwSk9kZlRlOENJQQ</guid></item><item><title>研究表明，怀孕期间感染新冠肺炎的母亲所生儿童的自闭症诊断率较高- CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2025/10/30/health/autism-covid-pregnancy</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article__content" data-editable="content" itemprop="articleBody" data-reorderable="content"&gt;
                
    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmhe174qo000x26oyhb4y4qof@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Children may be more likely to be diagnosed with autism and other neurodevelopment disorders if their mother had a Covid-19 infection while pregnant, according to a new &lt;a href="https://journals.lww.com/greenjournal/abstract/9900/neurodevelopmental_outcomes_of_3_year_old_children.1392.aspx" target="_blank"&gt;study&lt;/a&gt;.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmhe17gi300043b6nzxm4apar@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Researchers from Massachusetts General Hospital analyzed more than 18,000 births that occurred in the Mass General Brigham health system between March 2020 and May 2021, assessing records for laboratory-confirmed Covid-19 tests among the mothers and for neurodevelopment diagnoses among their children through age 3.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmhe17gi300053b6nl7sqz3df@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            They found that children born to mothers who had Covid-19 during pregnancy were significantly more likely to be diagnosed with a neurodevelopment disorder than those born to mothers who did not have an infection while pregnant: more than 16% versus less than 10%, or a 1.3 times higher risk after adjusting for other risk factors.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmhe17gi300073b6n1rgwvjnp@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Overall, differences in risks were more pronounced among boys and in cases where the mother had a Covid-19 infection during the third trimester. Previous studies have suggested that male fetal brains are more susceptible to maternal immune responses, according to the authors of the new study, and the third trimester is a “critical window for brain development.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmhe17gi300063b6na3bx6p6z@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The most common diagnoses included disorders in speech and motor function development and autism. About 2.7% of children born to mothers who had Covid-19 while pregnant were diagnosed with autism, compared with about 1.1% of others, according to the study, published Thursday in the journal Obstetrics and Gynecology.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmhe17gi300083b6nn0v0elm4@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The new findings are “particularly notable in light of their biological plausibility,” the researchers wrote. They build on previous research that identified potential pathways for a maternal Covid-19 infection to affect the developing fetal brain even without direct transmission.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmhe1l1ce00023b6n7tk5ji48@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “Parental awareness of the potential for adverse child neurodevelopmental outcomes after COVID-19 in pregnancy is key. By understanding the risks, parents can appropriately advocate for their children to have proper evaluation and support,” Dr. Lydia Shook, maternal-fetal medicine specialist at Massachusetts General Hospital and lead author of the study, said in &lt;a href="https://www.massgeneralbrigham.org/en/about/newsroom/press-releases/covid-19-during-pregnancy-linked-to-neurodevelopmental-disorders" target="_blank"&gt;a news release&lt;/a&gt;.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmhe17gi300093b6nvczsesgz@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            About 1 in 31 children in the US was diagnosed with autism by age 8 in 2022, according to a &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2025/04/15/health/autism-rate-cdc-report-2022"&gt;report&lt;/a&gt; published by the US Centers for Disease Control and Prevention that was published in April. The increase — up from 1 in 36 children in 2020 — continues a long-term trend that experts have largely attributed to better understanding of and screening for the condition.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmhe17gi3000a3b6npcnyzrw4@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Earlier this year, the US Department of Health and Human Services launched a “massive testing and research effort” to determine “what has &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2025/04/10/health/kennedy-autism-causes"&gt;caused the autism epidemic&lt;/a&gt;.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmhe1llo7000e3b6qgrzfaaue@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            In a news conference in September on the “&lt;a href="https://www.whitehouse.gov/videos/finding-the-cause-of-autism/" target="_blank"&gt;cause of autism&lt;/a&gt;,” President Donald Trump — flanked by HHS Secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr. and other federal health leaders – said that use of &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2025/09/22/health/trump-autism-announcement-cause-tylenol"&gt;Tylenol during pregnancy&lt;/a&gt; can be associated with a “very increased risk of autism,” despite decades of evidence that it is safe.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmhe17gi3000b3b6nzh9oih78@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Kennedy also has a history of comments linking autism and vaccines, despite strong evidence that the two are not connected.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmhe17gi4000c3b6n4nxeot91@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The timeframe of the new study – early in the pandemic, before vaccines were widely available – meant that ​the researchers were able to “isolate the association between SARS-CoV-2 infection and offspring neurodevelopment in an unvaccinated population.” About 93% of the mothers included in the assessment had not received any doses of Covid-19 vaccine. Strong infection-control policies at that time also helped reduce the potential for unreported or undetected Covid-19 cases, the researchers said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmhe1pk6x00053b6n5tc239vt@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “These findings highlight that COVID-19, like many other infections in pregnancy, may pose risks not only to the mother, but to fetal brain development,” Dr. Andrea Edlow, a maternal-fetal medicine specialist at Mass General Brigham and senior author of the new study, said in a news release. “They also support the importance of trying to prevent COVID-19 infection in pregnancy and are particularly relevant when public trust in vaccines – including the COVID-19 vaccine – is being eroded.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

              &lt;/div&gt;
                  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>CNN</author><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 01:06:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMibEFVX3lxTE5hT3E1anItcU82YzhNYnlHZXZES3RyNWlZcm01X2pIOV81QTIxVm9nTnNRMTdSdVBjdXJQVzFFMWh2RmpORXBlUVcxYVhGVGFma2NIV21BSUVoeEtPZU1OdEFPbnc5Ynd5OGVTNQ</guid></item><item><title>科学家说，这种未知的沙漠浆果可能是治疗糖尿病的秘密-SciTechDaily</title><link>https://scitechdaily.com/this-unknown-desert-berry-could-hold-the-secret-to-treating-diabetes-scientists-say/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>SciTechDaily</author><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 00:42:18 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMirgFBVV95cUxNdExjTm5UQ1lUNV8wTlhhOUFsWWVYRVhLdVZJYUJyREk1elYxcmZHUzUtdm1JOFFsZU1QNVFpWjZkNE1nX3ZQMHl2VUtQQXl3Y2ZLWmd6MFVHaDVUcldfOHRVZDlXT0xqcTV0WTkxeE9BUzBSNkdsVjRYSkJOa0ZTRGJCRVRsQjc3XzVZT3JhUmRwU0cyRGpRcWFTS096WTdUM3ZGc0EwVU9ncUtZT2c</guid></item><item><title>卫生官员在致命疾病到达热门旅游热点时发出警告： “非常令人担忧” -雅虎</title><link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/articles/health-officials-issue-warning-deadly-001000971.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="" data-article-body="true"&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;A popular Spanish resort town has been placed on alert after officials found mosquitoes carrying West Nile virus there.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="mb-4 text-lg font-bold"&gt;What's happening?&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The mosquitoes in question, the &lt;a href="https://www.express.co.uk/travel/articles/2120538/horror-spain-deadly-virus-tourist-hotspot" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Daily Express reported;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Daily Express reported&lt;/a&gt;, were discovered only a few feet from homes in Malaga, a popular tourist town in southern Spain's Andalusia region that is known for its breathtaking beaches.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The Andalusia Health and Consumer Department verified that the mosquitoes carried West Nile virus, which can, in rare cases, be fatal to humans. With that announcement came a four-week alert period, stretching through early November, that included higher levels of monitoring by local health teams.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Similar findings and warnings have also occurred in the Spanish towns of Tahivilla and La Luisiana.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="mb-4 text-lg font-bold"&gt;Why is West Nile virus concerning?&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;In most cases, West Nile virus doesn't show any symptoms in humans. But in rare cases, people can develop symptoms that last for months.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;"The symptoms presented like a stroke. It was really worrying," Jim Skinner, who decided to retire after contracting West Nile virus, &lt;a href="https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/c1w850qlx94o" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:told the BBC;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;told the BBC&lt;/a&gt;. "I had weakness down the left-hand side, palsy on the left-hand side, and I got tremors. … The weakness and tremors are still there a year on."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Even more concerning, however, is that West Nile virus cases appear to be increasing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Health officials say 13 European countries saw a total of &lt;a href="https://www.express.co.uk/travel/articles/2120538/horror-spain-deadly-virus-tourist-hotspot" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:989 cases;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;989 cases&lt;/a&gt; of West Nile — including 63 deaths — between June and September, higher than the 10-year average of 687. And in the United States, reported cases were about 40% higher than normal through early September.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;a href="https://guide.thecooldown.com/actions/explore-critical-climate-issues/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Human-caused pollution;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Human-caused pollution&lt;/a&gt; likely plays a role in that increase. That heat-trapping pollution has caused global temperatures to rise, which has led to more of the warm, wet conditions in which mosquitoes thrive. Mosquito season is now longer in many parts of the world, and the insects have reached places that were once too cold for them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="mb-4 text-lg font-bold"&gt;What can I do to avoid West Nile virus?&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;As the &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/west-nile-virus/prevention/index.html" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:U.S. Centers for Disease Control and Prevention;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;U.S. Centers for Disease Control and Prevention&lt;/a&gt; note, there is no vaccine or medicine available to prevent West Nile. Instead, the only way to prevent getting the virus is to avoid getting bitten by mosquitoes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Officials offer several tips on how to avoid those potentially dangerous bites. They advise people to wear long, loose-fitting shirts and pants when outside, to use screens on windows and doors, to avoid outdoor exposure between dusk and dawn, and to use approved insect repellent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Join our &lt;a href="https://www.thecooldown.com/future-newsletter/?reczp5UAUgwtvYBcd" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:free newsletter;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;free newsletter&lt;/a&gt; for &lt;strong&gt;good news&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;useful tips&lt;/strong&gt;, and don't miss &lt;a href="https://rb.gy/ivhzmj" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:this cool list;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;this cool list&lt;/a&gt; of easy ways to help yourself while helping the planet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Yahoo</author><pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 00:10:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikgFBVV95cUxQM0xWRjhPZUhHcHF1dDd3bVpUeGIxcXJyNXFRdUNOajdKamZuYXQ1d0pYQ3ZpOG5LWWxqaGZEdm45Z2RHSnBrLWZNOUZQekdwbjM1OGo2N2tFcF9kOVZqN0VKbFIxVFhVUHZJZmVyZ1pGeEhXVFNXTWNKVmctWE9LV002X2ZkeC01NjBpYklLNHlNdw</guid></item><item><title>前疾病预防控制中心官员，负责新的mpox病例和当前的联邦资源- The Hill</title><link>https://thehill.com/newsletters/health-care/5582409-former-cdc-official-on-new-mpox-cases-and-current-federal-resources/</link><description>&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;
    
    
    &lt;noscript&gt;
      
    &lt;/noscript&gt;
  &lt;/body&gt;
</description><author>The Hill</author><pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 23:54:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMivAFBVV95cUxQaTRQQ0hhaGdhLW9YLUs3cHlNbV9rV094V1hQbDBXUkREcVBSaThLVmt2RUloaFAwUXlncG5DSGlqYkhzZFJSV3pCUGMycW95bzBiYkhaVzBjRlpQSUxIZjFoT3QwbXlwLU5JdXdCeWZYMU1MS2xCT0R3NTNUVTNIcFVUbmgwdnJsVWlvTURIUmt0QkE2OC1oVm9MMDhTNzJJWHpiQTllSmxScWEzX1FrWUdKOENERDRnWnpiR9IBwgFBVV95cUxQS0lSNEY0b092aVJVY084aGRxak9Yb2w4eWNCbkhVQWVUZl80WnBoN0dlVFlMa1dqTGxacGg1R3d3OFB1N0M2anJ0d3c4azRObTBCS24tQWxlckNEeVZ5U0Q2OGR1Y2FCQm15NUdBZ0xqN25PbkxuY3doTnlmbzFoOUhKRnNndDFUc2U4X21aTzJFVWp6TzBOUDBuQkQ2a2lnSmVScFAzM2cxUjBacWNmRlBvcmR6Vjd5c1d0YjltSDE3UQ</guid></item><item><title>索诺玛县鸭子和蛋农场受到2025-26冬季首次禽流感爆发的打击-新闻民主党人</title><link>https://www.pressdemocrat.com/2025/10/30/large-sonoma-county-duck-farm-hit-with-first-avian-flu-outbreak-of-2025-26-winter/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="body-copy"&gt;&lt;p&gt;California’s first bird flu outbreaks of the 2025-26 winter season have hit close to home. The owner of Reichardt Duck Farm, which sits in the rolling hills between Petaluma and the Two Rock area, confirmed that his facility recently recorded positive cases of the dreaded virus.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And Thursday, the U.S. Department of Agriculture &lt;a href="https://www.aphis.usda.gov/livestock-poultry-disease/avian/avian-influenza/hpai-detections/commercial-backyard-flocks"&gt;added to its public database&lt;/a&gt; a second incidence of the highly virulent avian flu in Sonoma County, this one at an egg farm. The Press Democrat was unable to immediately confirm the location of that outbreak, which resulted in the deaths of 231,000 birds.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The timing is a wake-up call. Two winters ago, when Sonoma County poultry farms were &lt;a href="https://www.pressdemocrat.com/2024/01/12/sonoma-county-poultry-farmers-euthanize-thousands-more-birds-as-avian-flu-losses-devastate-local-industry/"&gt;ravaged by the spread of avian influenza&lt;/a&gt;, the first case didn’t hit until around Thanksgiving.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The latest outbreak is another blow to the Reichardt family. Their Middle Two Rock Road farm was also heavily affected in 2023-24, when it was &lt;a href="https://www.pressdemocrat.com/2023/12/01/250000-birds-to-be-killed-at-2-petaluma-poultry-farms-after-avian-flu-detected-2/"&gt;the first of multiple local facilities &lt;/a&gt;infected by the deadly and highly virulent avian flu virus, which typically requires producers to destroy all of their birds on site.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="s2nPlayer k-8p60lgsb" data-type="float" data-s2n-api="dfm_stn_player_script_id_8p60lgsb"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bird flu outbreaks hit flocks at nine other chicken, duck and egg-laying facilities in the county that season.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Phil Reichardt paused to talk to a reporter &lt;span&gt;Tuesday &lt;/span&gt;as his farm staff went about euthanizing 57,000 birds.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Look at the last six years now, with &lt;a href="https://www.pressdemocrat.com/2023/12/03/activism-prospective-ballot-fight-heighten-drama-of-sonoma-county-bird-flu-outbreak/"&gt;the DxE (animal liberation) raid&lt;/a&gt;, COVID, bird flu in ’23, now bird flu again in ’25. My older sister passed in 2020,” he said. “It’s been hit after hit. We’re looking for our fate to change at some point.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Reichardt Duck Farm is not to be confused with Liberty Ducks, a smaller Sonoma County&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;producer, owned by members of the same family but operating at a separate location.&lt;/p&gt;				
&lt;p&gt;The latest outbreak was detected after Reichardt Duck Farm staff noticed “a modest increase in mortality” — eight dead birds — in one of the barns last week, Phil Reichardt said. The next morning, there were a few more than that. They took a sample of birds to UC Davis for analysis, and received confirmation of Highly Pathogenic Avian Flu, or HPAI, on Oct. 24.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The duck farm began “depopulating” its flock Sunday, borrowing some machinery from Weber Family Farms, an egg facility that also was forced to put birds to death in 2023-24. Phil Reichardt expected to finish the grim task Wednesday.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That’s a departure from two years ago, when local ranchers knew much less about the spread of the pathogen and how best to block it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In that previous round, Reichardt said, the farm received instructions from the U.S. Department of Agriculture the day before Thanksgiving. Because of the holiday, and a lower sense of urgency, they didn’t begin depopulating for six days. This time, Reichardt expected to be done five days after confirmation, which he hoped would reduce the chances of the flu hopping to another facility.&lt;/p&gt;				
&lt;p&gt;“The industry, unfortunately, is getting very good at this,” he said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The report Thursday of another outbreak in one of the region’s bird farms demonstrates the limitations of that quick action.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rodrigo Gallardo, professor of poultry medicine at the UC Davis School of Veterinary Medicine and an expert in poultry RNA viruses, agreed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It’s definitely a concerted effort,” Gallardo said. “The California Department of Food and Agriculture usually helps with this, the USDA usually helps. We’re all at high alert. We’re approaching winter. And we have learned a lot of things about biosecurity and prevention. The hope is that we will reduce dissemination after one detection.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The recommendations on biosecurity measures haven’t changed based on the new appearance of HPAI, said Sue Ostrom, Sonoma County’s assistant agricultural commissioner, because — as Reichardt alluded — producers have gotten the work pretty buttoned down since their unprecedented local losses in the winter season two years ago.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“One thing that led to,” Ostrom said, “is that producers understand what needs to happen. How we dispose of carcasses, bedding and so forth. They can get to that faster now.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="article-slideshow" id="mng-gallery-acbb91da5dd2a61221fbbbb4f9e7b501"&gt;&lt;button class="icon-close mng-gallery-fullscreen-close" aria-label="Close fullscreen slideshow"&gt;&lt;/button&gt;&lt;ul class="mng-gallery-initialized mng-gallery-slider"&gt;&lt;button id="mng-gallery-prev" class="mng-gallery-prev mng-gallery-arrow" aria-label="Previous" type="button"&gt;&lt;/button&gt;&lt;div class="mng-gallery-list draggable"&gt;&lt;div class="mng-gallery-track"&gt;&lt;li data-index="1" class="mng-ge mng-gallery-active" id="mng-ge-0" aria-hidden="false" tabindex="0"&gt;&lt;div class="image-wrapper"&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" alt="Workers remove dirt from a cage-free chicken house at a..." class="size-article_inline" sizes="(max-width: 40em) 620px,(min-width: 40em) and (max-width: 50em) 780px,(min-width: 50em) and (max-width: 65em) 810px,(min-width: 65em) and (max-width: 80em) 1280px,(min-width: 80em) 1860px,1860px" srcset="https://www.pressdemocrat.com/wp-content/uploads/migration/2025/01/594dafea-c977-5b2b-a7f1-b3f60982c38b.jpg?w=620 620w,https://www.pressdemocrat.com/wp-content/uploads/migration/2025/01/594dafea-c977-5b2b-a7f1-b3f60982c38b.jpg?w=780 780w,https://www.pressdemocrat.com/wp-content/uploads/migration/2025/01/594dafea-c977-5b2b-a7f1-b3f60982c38b.jpg?w=810 810w,https://www.pressdemocrat.com/wp-content/uploads/migration/2025/01/594dafea-c977-5b2b-a7f1-b3f60982c38b.jpg?w=1200 1280w,https://www.pressdemocrat.com/wp-content/uploads/migration/2025/01/594dafea-c977-5b2b-a7f1-b3f60982c38b.jpg?w=1200 1860w"&gt;&lt;p class="slide-credit"&gt;Christopher Chung / The Press Democrat&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="slide-caption"&gt;Workers remove dirt from a cage-free chicken house at a Weber Family Farms facility in Petaluma, in January 2024. The farm had to destroy 550,000 chickens and 3.2 million eggs after an avian flu outbreak. (Christopher Chung / The Press Democrat)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-index="2" class="mng-ge" id="mng-ge-1" aria-hidden="true" tabindex="-1"&gt;&lt;div class="image-wrapper"&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" alt="Reichardt Duck Farm in the rolling hills of Two Rock,..." class="lazyload size-article_inline" data-sizes="auto" data-src="https://www.pressdemocrat.com/wp-content/uploads/migration/2023/12/ea7ae9c7-5470-5d06-8545-36e710f075b7.jpg?w=620" data-srcset="https://www.pressdemocrat.com/wp-content/uploads/migration/2023/12/ea7ae9c7-5470-5d06-8545-36e710f075b7.jpg?w=620 620w,https://www.pressdemocrat.com/wp-content/uploads/migration/2023/12/ea7ae9c7-5470-5d06-8545-36e710f075b7.jpg?w=780 780w,https://www.pressdemocrat.com/wp-content/uploads/migration/2023/12/ea7ae9c7-5470-5d06-8545-36e710f075b7.jpg?w=810 810w,https://www.pressdemocrat.com/wp-content/uploads/migration/2023/12/ea7ae9c7-5470-5d06-8545-36e710f075b7.jpg?w=1200 1280w,https://www.pressdemocrat.com/wp-content/uploads/migration/2023/12/ea7ae9c7-5470-5d06-8545-36e710f075b7.jpg?w=1200 1860w"&gt;&lt;p class="slide-credit"&gt;Kent Porter / The Press Democrat file&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="slide-caption"&gt;Reichardt Duck Farm in the rolling hills of Two Rock, west of Petaluma, Friday, December 2023. (Kent Porter / The Press Democrat file)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-index="3" class="mng-ge" id="mng-ge-2" aria-hidden="true" tabindex="-1"&gt;&lt;div class="image-wrapper"&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" alt="Law enforcement officers in riot gear wait to arrest animal..." class="lazyload size-article_inline" data-sizes="auto" data-src="https://www.pressdemocrat.com/wp-content/uploads/migration/2023/10/63373263-3937-466c-b073-2d3331343031.jpg?w=620" data-srcset="https://www.pressdemocrat.com/wp-content/uploads/migration/2023/10/63373263-3937-466c-b073-2d3331343031.jpg?w=620 620w,https://www.pressdemocrat.com/wp-content/uploads/migration/2023/10/63373263-3937-466c-b073-2d3331343031.jpg?w=780 780w,https://www.pressdemocrat.com/wp-content/uploads/migration/2023/10/63373263-3937-466c-b073-2d3331343031.jpg?w=810 810w,https://www.pressdemocrat.com/wp-content/uploads/migration/2023/10/63373263-3937-466c-b073-2d3331343031.jpg?w=1200 1280w,https://www.pressdemocrat.com/wp-content/uploads/migration/2023/10/63373263-3937-466c-b073-2d3331343031.jpg?w=1200 1860w"&gt;&lt;p class="slide-credit"&gt;photo by John Burgess/The Press Democrat&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="slide-caption"&gt;Law enforcement officers in riot gear wait to arrest animal welfare activists holding dead ducks they claim to have found inside the Reichardt Duck Farm on Middle Two Rock Road. (photo by John Burgess/The Press Democrat)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;button id="mng-gallery-next" class="mng-gallery-next mng-gallery-arrow" aria-label="Next" type="button"&gt;&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div class="caption mng-gallery-information-container"&gt;&lt;button class="caption-expand mng-gallery-caption-expand" aria-expanded="false" aria-label="Show caption"&gt;Show Caption&lt;/button&gt;&lt;p class="slideshow-credit mng-gallery-image-credit"&gt;Christopher Chung / The Press Democrat&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="slide-count"&gt;&lt;span class="current mng-gallery-current-image-number-display"&gt;1&lt;/span&gt; of &lt;span class="total"&gt;3&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="slideshow-caption mng-gallery-image-caption"&gt;Workers remove dirt from a cage-free chicken house at a Weber Family Farms facility in Petaluma, in January 2024. The farm had to destroy 550,000 chickens and 3.2 million eggs after an avian flu outbreak. (Christopher Chung / The Press Democrat)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="#" class="icon-enlarge mng-gallery-fullscreen-expand" aria-label="Expand fullscreen slideshow"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Expand&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The strain of bird flu detected in recent tests at Reichardt Duck Farm is the same as the one that swept Sonoma County two years ago, resulting in the &lt;span&gt;destruction of 1.2 million birds.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“We don’t have any real smoking gun,” Reichardt said. “We can only expect it was migratory birds flying overhead. We step into their droppings and enter the barns. We have foot pans in place, and we are careful to use them. But I guess we can’t hit everywhere.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Like viruses transmitted among humans, HPAI tends to peak during the cold winter months. It generally spreads from migrating waterfowl to domesticated flocks along the major north-south flyways, including the Pacific Flyway that travels above Sonoma County. Researchers estimate 1 billion birds fly south along the Pacific Flyway each fall, and north again in the spring.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It’s normal, in a certain sense, to think cases will go up in the winter,” Gallardo said. “Usually, respiratory infections in chickens are related to changes in temperature and humidity. With birds migrating south, we’re right at a time when this might happen.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While Reichardt Duck Farm was obligated to put down all of its birds, the business is not without prospects. Phil Reichardt estimated they have about 15,000 eggs currently incubating, and another 20,000-30,000 that are eligible to take that step soon. Those eggs must be moved off the property to raise elsewhere.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It’s an expensive process when no revenue is coming in,” Reichardt said. “But it’s all we know how to do. So we keep going even when it feels like we’re battering our heads against a brick wall.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Department of Agriculture &lt;a href="https://www.pressdemocrat.com/2025/01/21/why-local-poultry-farmers-say-10-million-bird-flu-reimbursement-falls-short-2/"&gt;has an indemnity program&lt;/a&gt; that compensates poultry farmers for income lost to avian flu. In the 2023-24 outbreaks, affected Sonoma County farms received a total of $10.6 million.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Reichardt said he’s appreciative of “anything that helps keep us afloat,” but noted that he and the department are far apart in their estimation of fair market value for the ducks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He also is hoping to open a discussion on USDA depopulation requirements. Because the flu is so highly transmissible, the federal agency insists on complete depopulation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Could we have euthanized the affected birds and monitored the others? And continue testing birds?” Reichardt wondered, noting that only a couple dozen were confirmed sick in the recent outbreak. “I think I understand USDA’s stance. This thing is terrible. When it takes hold, it’s like a wildfire. But I think there are other methods to put out the wildfire. It’s a depressing process to put down healthy, happy birds.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The duck farm must now wait four months before reintroducing birds, and it will takes months beyond that for young ducks to mature and become egg layers. Reichardt Duck Farm had yet to fully bounce back from late 2023, when the company was forced to euthanize more than 200,000 birds. The owner estimates that before getting the bad news last week, they were at about 40% of their pre-2023 levels.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Most depressing for Phil Reichardt is knowing there’s a good chance the staff members who have been handling the depopulation may soon find their hours slashed, or could even be laid off as some were two winters ago.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It really gets me emotional. Some of them are family to us,” Reichardt said. “These people are working their butts off to put themselves out of work.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The first big California outbreak of 2023-24 was also in late October, at a turkey meat facility in Merced County. By the end of that winter, at least 6.3 million commercial birds had been killed in the state. In Sonoma County alone, officials estimated the financial loss to producers at around $22 million. The effects were felt well beyond farm properties, with &lt;a href="https://www.pressdemocrat.com/2025/01/15/aftermath-of-bird-flu-lowers-supply-and-ups-cost-of-eggs-2/"&gt;egg prices skyrocketing in stores&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Last winter was far more devastating statewide, with more than 16.5 million dead birds. But that pandemic left Sonoma County unscathed. This winter already threatens to be different.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;You can reach Phil Barber at 707-521-5263 or phil.barber@pressdemocrat.com. On X (Twitter) @Skinny_Post.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

			&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Press Democrat</author><pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 23:24:55 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiwAFBVV95cUxNRVp6MUc1S01NTG4wNHJpSXFVcVNJaDZMdm9GamEwdndKM2thbW4tR093NktsTkRoQXlpdWVwYWdmcWhveDJwaDhDckM2c2JhVHdPT0htYXRLNUs5SlhEa19LdVhPVnp5RDRlNWQtazJjdTY2ZjFpRUNYbGk5eGR4anpCMzBUSlg4TG4yZ2E0UzUyYlY2ZlJsYjRZczNQVXFXSWtLWW85eWJYakdTaG9LcWF6MnFnUExPdjdDOHphSzk</guid></item><item><title>狗妈妈在篱笆下爬行以逃避被忽视—然后为她的小狗找到帮助-渡渡鸟</title><link>https://www.thedodo.com/daily-dodo/mama-dog-crawls-under-fence-to-escape-neglect-then-finds-help-for-her-puppies</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="NodeArticlestyles__ObscuredContentWrapper-sc-1rwhog1-6 eCcsQv"&gt;&lt;div class="ParagraphBodyTextstyles__BodyText-sc-zv221u-0 eJmGWQ page-element paragraph undefined " data-element-type="ParagraphBodyText" data-element-index="0"&gt;&lt;p data-element-index="0"&gt;Last month, Don Boston, founder of &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/asap.325/"&gt;Abilene Stray Animal Program&lt;/a&gt;, was out looking for an abandoned husky when he stumbled upon someone unexpected. He saw a dog wandering around all by herself on the side of a dirt road, looking hungry.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-element-index="1"&gt;Boston gave the dog some food while he tried to figure out who she was and where she’d come from. Once she’d eaten her fill and started walking away, Boston followed her around the corner — and saw her puppies behind a fence in someone’s yard.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure data-element-type="ParagraphImage" data-element-index="1" class="ParagraphImagestyles__ImageContainer-sc-puj0e1-0 hHKvH page-element paragraph-image "&gt;&lt;picture class="picture-tag picture-tag--lazy" data-testid="picture-tag"&gt;&lt;img class="" src="https://assets3.thrillist.com/v1/image/3200629/714x1012/scale;webp=auto;jpeg_quality=60.jpg" srcset="https://assets3.thrillist.com/v1/image/3200629/714x1012/scale;webp=auto;jpeg_quality=60.jpg 1000w, https://assets3.thrillist.com/v1/image/3200629/1428x2024/scale;webp=auto;jpeg_quality=60.jpg 2000w" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;img src="https://assets3.thrillist.com/v1/image/3200629/714x1012/scale;webp=auto;jpeg_quality=60.jpg"&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/picture&gt;&lt;figcaption class="Caption-sc-1do4sd3-0 kEEwas caption__paragraph-image"&gt;&lt;span class="Credit-sc-ke5nu1-0 jmSitH"&gt;Abilene Stray Animal Program&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div class="ParagraphBodyTextstyles__BodyText-sc-zv221u-0 eJmGWQ page-element paragraph undefined " data-element-type="ParagraphBodyText" data-element-index="2"&gt;&lt;p data-element-index="0"&gt;Boston could immediately tell that the yard was no place for dogs. There were sharp pieces of metal everywhere and no food anywhere in sight. Upon closer inspection, he saw that several of the dogs had flystrike on their ears.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-element-index="1"&gt;“They are hungry,” Boston said in a Facebook video. “Hungry, hungry, hungry.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-element-index="2"&gt;The mama dog and two of her puppies had escaped through a hole in the fence. Seeing how neglected they all were, all Boston wanted to do was take the whole family home with him. But he knew he had to talk to the property owner first.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="ConnatixVideostyles__ConnatixVideoWrap-sc-woid5f-0 ktIfME connatix-article-mobile"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="ParagraphBodyTextstyles__BodyText-sc-zv221u-0 eJmGWQ page-element paragraph undefined " data-element-type="ParagraphBodyText" data-element-index="5"&gt;&lt;p data-element-index="0"&gt;“[I]t broke my heart, honestly,” Boston told The Dodo.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-element-index="1"&gt;Boston learned from the owner that the dogs had originally belonged to his brother, who’d passed away. Since taking in the mama dog, she’d had multiple litters of puppies. Boston knew he couldn’t let that cycle continue.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-element-index="2"&gt;“I was like, ‘I have to help these guys,’” Boston said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-element-index="3"&gt;Boston was able to convince the property owner to rehome the puppies. Now that they’re with their new families, the puppies have a safe home environment, where they have access to the fresh water and food they need to grow big and strong.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="ParagraphBodyTextstyles__BodyText-sc-zv221u-0 eJmGWQ page-element paragraph undefined " data-element-type="ParagraphBodyText" data-element-index="7"&gt;&lt;p data-element-index="0"&gt;As for the mama dog, Boston talked her owner into letting him get her spayed. At the very least, he wanted to put a stop to her having any more puppies in that environment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-element-index="1"&gt;While Boston was preparing to take the mama to get spayed, he got a call from animal control that she’d been picked up by one of their officers after escaping through the fence again. They’d contacted her owner and never heard back, which meant Boston was allowed to foster her.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure data-element-type="ParagraphImage" data-element-index="8" class="ParagraphImagestyles__ImageContainer-sc-puj0e1-0 hHKvH page-element paragraph-image "&gt;&lt;picture class="picture-tag picture-tag--lazy" data-testid="picture-tag"&gt;&lt;img class="" src="https://assets3.thrillist.com/v1/image/3200635/792x1213/scale;webp=auto;jpeg_quality=60.jpg" srcset="https://assets3.thrillist.com/v1/image/3200635/792x1213/scale;webp=auto;jpeg_quality=60.jpg 1000w, https://assets3.thrillist.com/v1/image/3200635/1584x2426/scale;webp=auto;jpeg_quality=60.jpg 2000w" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;img src="https://assets3.thrillist.com/v1/image/3200635/792x1213/scale;webp=auto;jpeg_quality=60.jpg"&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/picture&gt;&lt;figcaption class="Caption-sc-1do4sd3-0 kEEwas caption__paragraph-image"&gt;&lt;span class="Credit-sc-ke5nu1-0 jmSitH"&gt;Abilene Stray Animal Program&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div class="ParagraphBodyTextstyles__BodyText-sc-zv221u-0 eJmGWQ page-element paragraph undefined " data-element-type="ParagraphBodyText" data-element-index="9"&gt;&lt;p data-element-index="0"&gt;As soon as the mama dog is cleared, Boston will be taking her home with him and helping her find a forever family. After everything she’s been through, Boston is looking forward to making her as comfortable and happy as possible.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-element-index="1"&gt;“We’re [going to] try to give her a happy life,” Boston said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="ParagraphEditorsNotestyles__EditorsNoteDiv-sc-tvi916-0 bBnoeL page-element paragraph undefined" data-element-type="ParagraphEditorsNote" data-element-index="10"&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you'd like to donate to Abilene Stray Animal Program, you can do so &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://venmo.com/u/asap325"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Dodo</author><pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 22:52:14 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMisgFBVV95cUxOZXVRcUp6UVY1WjBOWjVxdTlMblVBa3I3cXQ4bjZORkZBR3RXWDJIV1BlckhPMm5UQi05RUU0VnNTbUw3UF9RRGdxblFZM1Y3STU5aFRiSldUemVUY0d6YnU0RWlQUmVKN1dxUEV5dDdhNzYyYUd5RmRJUTFLczJja2w0b3pTVENETFpMbHNUalRpb0lNOVZpN1hfclAzYUl3a2RjNGFiTmJVY0JNNUY1UjZB</guid></item><item><title>多国mpox疫情，外部情况报告# 59 - 2025年10月30日-世界卫生组织（ WHO ）</title><link>https://www.who.int/publications/m/item/multi-country-outbreak-of-mpox--external-situation-report--59---30-october-2025</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="dynamic-content__description"&gt;
        &lt;h3&gt;Overview &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is the 59th situation report for the multi-country outbreak of mpox, which provides details on the global epidemiological situation for mpox, including an update on the epidemiological situation  with data on the global situation as of 30 September 2025, in Africa as of 19 October and the operational response updates as of 24 October 2025.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
     &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>World Health Organization (WHO)</author><pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 22:17:34 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiuwFBVV95cUxQSHF6SVRHQmZidlFXVnhaRk1UOHVwV1gwMXVWWTY5ajFtQ1RrRXE1UEY2aUtEWVl3cmJOOWRJREtERllPeE9Wc2hWZHdIaGFoM3J0OUE4djFpWm9hWkx0a09JQnJ6SDBUWlVHYm1HTVU5d3lXbkpGZjNDb0F2eEloS2RLVG5JOWxNeWdoU2lzMFdVbXVYamdtVW5MLWtEd1JaS0p5ek8zR0FVTjhRa0I0Q2pBVnlHR2ZQbElR</guid></item><item><title>研究人员在不安全的自恋者中发现了一种特殊的倾向- PsyPost</title><link>https://www.psypost.org/researchers-identify-a-peculiar-tendency-among-insecure-narcissists/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="content-inner "&gt;&lt;p&gt;A new study published in the journal &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://psycnet.apa.org/record/2020-11895-001" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Psychology of Aesthetics, Creativity, and the Arts&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; suggests that individuals with a combination of high narcissism and psychological insecurity are more likely to be “cultural omnivores,” consuming both highbrow and lowbrow art forms. This behavior appears to be a strategy to satisfy two distinct psychological needs: signaling social status and projecting a sense of personal integrity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Narcissism is often understood as a personality trait characterized by a grandiose sense of self, a persistent need for admiration, and a focus on one’s own importance. While this may project an image of supreme confidence, psychological research has shown that narcissism can exist alongside deep-seated feelings of insecurity, such as low self-esteem or a sense that one is not living as their “true self.” It is this particular combination of traits that interested the researchers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Traditionally, cultural taste was seen through the lens of social class. Sociologists argued that elites used their preference for “highbrow” culture, like classical music and fine art, to distinguish themselves from other social classes. In recent decades, however, this pattern has shifted. Observers have noted the rise of the “cultural omnivore,” an individual who appreciates both high-status cultural products and more popular, “lowbrow” forms like pop music or street art.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study’s authors proposed that this modern trend might be explained not just by social class, but by specific personality dynamics. They hypothesized that people high in narcissism but low in self-security might use cultural consumption as a tool. Liking highbrow culture could serve their need to signal superior status, while an appreciation for lowbrow culture, often seen as more authentic, could help soothe their inner feelings of inauthenticity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To investigate this idea, the researchers conducted two separate studies. In the first experiment, they surveyed 178 university students. Participants completed questionnaires designed to measure their levels of narcissism and self-esteem. They were then asked to rate how likely they would be to participate in a variety of cultural activities.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some of these activities were classified as highbrow, including attending a classical symphony or visiting art galleries. Others were categorized as lowbrow, such as going to pop concerts or viewing graffiti and street art. The researchers analyzed the data to see if there was a connection between the participants’ personality scores and their cultural intentions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The findings revealed a distinct pattern. For individuals who scored high on the narcissism scale, having lower self-esteem was associated with a stronger intention to participate in highbrow cultural activities. A similar relationship appeared for lowbrow culture. The participants with high narcissism and low self-esteem also expressed a greater interest in lowbrow activities.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This confirmed that the insecure narcissist profile was linked to being a cultural omnivore, showing an appetite for both ends of the cultural spectrum. The analysis also suggested that this behavior was connected to a general motivation for “distinction seeking,” or a desire to establish a unique and notable identity through their choices. This relationship held even when the researchers accounted for other factors, like a person’s openness to new experiences or their own perception of their social status.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The second study was designed to explore the specific motivations behind these dual preferences. The researchers wanted to confirm if status seeking was driving the interest in highbrow culture, while a need for integrity was behind the preference for lowbrow culture. This experiment involved 144 university students and used a slightly different approach.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Instead of measuring general self-esteem, the researchers measured a more specific form of insecurity known as self-alienation, which is the feeling of being out of touch with one’s true self. They also focused on a particular aspect of narcissism related to superiority and arrogance. Participants were then randomly assigned to read a biography of a fictional artist.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One version of the biography presented the artist as highbrow, noting that her paintings were exhibited in major museums around the world. The other version framed her as lowbrow, explaining that her work was given to family and friends before being discovered by an art dealer in her hometown. After reading one of the biographies, participants rated their interest in seeing the artist’s work. They also answered questions about their current motivations, including their desire to signal status and their need to project self-integrity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The results of this experiment provided clearer support for the researchers’ hypothesis. Among participants who read about the highbrow artist, those with the insecure narcissist profile showed greater interest in her work. This increased interest was statistically linked to a heightened desire for status at that moment. Consuming high-status art appeared to satisfy their need to be seen as having high status.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For the participants who read about the lowbrow artist, a different motivation was at play. In this case, the insecure narcissist group’s interest in the art was connected to their desire to signal self-integrity. The perceived authenticity of the lowbrow artist seemed to offer a way for these individuals to bolster their own shaky sense of self. The two studies together paint a nuanced picture of how personality can shape cultural tastes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This research provides a new psychological perspective on a phenomenon that has largely been studied through a sociological framework. It suggests that for some people, the choice of what art to consume is not merely a matter of taste but a complex strategy for managing their identity and internal insecurities.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The authors note that their findings are based on statistical associations, and future research could explore these mechanisms further. For instance, an experiment could temporarily change a person’s feelings of security to see if it directly affects their cultural preferences. Researchers could also examine whether this pattern of behavior extends to other domains, such as luxury consumption, social media use, or even charitable giving.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study, “&lt;a href="https://psycnet.apa.org/doi/10.1037/aca0000303" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;How Insecure Narcissists Become Cultural Omnivores: Consuming Highbrow Culture for Status Seeking and Lowbrow Culture for Integrity Signaling&lt;/a&gt;,” was authored by Hanna Shin and Nara Youn.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>PsyPost</author><pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 22:03:23 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilwFBVV95cUxON2c5TFNxeEx6Z2M3d0xpekt3RUozU1l1X05xQmdvaE9GRXNOMERPZXVmVUFjUjJfYVBLd0Y1a3JNVlg1bzBCTHAwbHpxeVhXcURDbU0xSU0zS3NpS1VYbmZkTHp0VjRnSEJnYmtnb29zeEU1bHZXTlAxOFpSQ0ttOXdWc095S1lzWk1SV0V6R0hhUU1CNzI0</guid></item></channel></rss>