<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>GNews Health</title><link>https://news.google.com/</link><description></description><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>在如何看待自己与世界如何看待自己方面存在最大差异的工作- BuzzFeed</title><link>https://www.buzzfeed.com/kellymartinez/people-are-sharing-the-jobs-with-the-biggest-discrepancies</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="subbuzz buzz-width--standard__subbuzz buzz-type--list__subbuzz subbuzz-text
  subbuzz-index-25
  
  
  
  
  " data-module="subbuzz-text"&gt;
  
  &lt;p id="139808518" class="subbuzz-anchor"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;h2 class="subbuzz__header subbuzz__header--standard subbuzz__title  "&gt;
    

    
      &lt;span class="js-subbuzz__title-text"&gt;Do you have a job that's actually totally different from the way society perceives it? Share your thoughts and experiences in the comments (or the anonymous form) below.&lt;/span&gt;
    
  &lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Note: Responses have been edited for length/clarity.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BuzzFeed</author><pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 04:31:02 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMingFBVV95cUxQczh4OVpwMG1aWXdTdDBvYThRM18zSmFGSFZuWUxQY2lVRmpXNEFZSmQzdVZJZlNCQ3haSnBUYWJHVjlUODVKckxtWUV3N3JKT3FZS1dRVWdYLWRKSm1QTEUzWnM5cDZTMm1JeDFIV0FvX3lHUTMtMG9qeWtXdXZYenZPMGFmbjN5NWNLOTB5SDVKQm03aHh5MjBWOFFsZw</guid></item><item><title>日本正面临痴呆症危机–技术可以提供帮助吗？ - BBC</title><link>https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/c4g9e34yzvgo</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article&gt;&lt;p data-component="headline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 hNbOGD"&gt;&lt;h1 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 idLnWK"&gt;Japan is facing a dementia crisis – can technology help?&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="byline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="byline-new" class="sc-573fa0e8-0 bWRWzH"&gt;&lt;span data-testid="byline-new-contributors" class="sc-573fa0e8-11 cOQNNv"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="byline-new-contributors-contributor-0" class="sc-573fa0e8-5 gXJgDY"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="sc-573fa0e8-7 gqeTMs"&gt;Suranjana Tewari&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-testid="byline-new-contributors-contributor-0-role-location" class="sc-573fa0e8-8 bIfajQ"&gt;Asia Business Correspondent, Tokyo&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 gtLOOD"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="hero-image" class="sc-5340b511-1 cMIbKV"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20251203-121739-f954f14c69-web-2.35.1-2/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 gUePlo hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/de17/live/7423b520-d188-11f0-8de5-0d4110f465fe.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/de17/live/7423b520-d188-11f0-8de5-0d4110f465fe.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/de17/live/7423b520-d188-11f0-8de5-0d4110f465fe.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/de17/live/7423b520-d188-11f0-8de5-0d4110f465fe.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/de17/live/7423b520-d188-11f0-8de5-0d4110f465fe.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/de17/live/7423b520-d188-11f0-8de5-0d4110f465fe.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/de17/live/7423b520-d188-11f0-8de5-0d4110f465fe.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/de17/live/7423b520-d188-11f0-8de5-0d4110f465fe.jpg.webp" loading="eager" alt="Getty Images An elderly woman crossing a dimly-lit street, pushing a stroller and a white plastic bag" class="sc-5340b511-0 hLdNfA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 jVqbAn"&gt;Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;Around seven million people suffer from dementia in Japan&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Last year, more than 18,000 older people living with dementia left their homes and wandered off in Japan. Almost 500 were later found dead.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Police say such cases have doubled since 2012, underscoring a growing strain on the world's oldest society.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The crisis is further compounded by a shrinking workforce and tight limits on foreign workers coming in to provide care.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Japan's government has identified dementia as one of its most urgent policy challenges, with the Health Ministry estimating that dementia-related health and social care costs will reach 14 trillion yen ($90bn; £67bn) by 2030 - up from nine trillion yen in 2025. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;In its most recent strategy, the government has signalled a stronger pivot toward technology to ease the pressure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Across the country, people are adopting GPS-based systems to keep track of those who wander.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Some regions offer wearable GPS tags that can alert authorities the moment a person leaves a designated area.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;In some towns, convenience-store workers receive real-time notifications – a kind of community safety net that can locate a missing person within hours.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 hNbOGD"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 gXmhTb"&gt;Robot caregivers and AI&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Other technologies aim to detect dementia earlier.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Fujitsu's aiGait uses AI to analyse posture and walking patterns, picking up early signs of dementia – shuffling while walking, slower turns or difficulty standing – generating skeletal outlines clinicians can review during routine check-ups.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"Early detection of age-related diseases is key," says Hidenori Fujiwara, a Fujitsu spokesperson. "If doctors can use motion-capture data, they can intervene earlier and help people remain active for longer."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Meanwhile, researchers at Waseda University are developing AIREC, a 150kg humanoid robot designed to be a "future" caregiver.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;It can help a person put on socks, scramble eggs and fold laundry. The scientists at Waseda University hope that in the future, AIREC will be able to change diapers and prevent bedsores in patients.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;Scientists at Waseda University in Tokyo are developing caregiving robots&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Similar robots are already being used in care homes to play music to residents or guide them in simple stretching exercises.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;They are also monitoring patients at night - placed under mattresses to track sleep and conditions - and cutting back on the need for humans doing the rounds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Although humanoid robots are being developed for the near future, Assistant Professor Tamon Miyake says the level of precision and intelligence required will take at last five years before they are safely able to interact with humans.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"It requires full-body sensing and adaptive understanding - how to adjust for each person and situation," he says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Emotional support is also part of the innovation drive.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Poketomo, a 12cm tall robot, can be carried around in a bag or can fit into a pocket. It reminds users to take medication, tells you how to prepare in real time for the weather outside and offers conversation for those living alone, which its creators say helps to ease social isolation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"We're focusing on social issues... and to use new technology to help solve those problems," Miho Kagei, development manager from Sharp told the BBC.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;Toshio Morita (R) works at the Restaurant of Mistaken Orders&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;While devices and robots offer new ways to assist, though, human connection remains irreplaceable.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"Robots should supplement, not substitute, human caregivers," Mr Miyake, the Waseda University scientist said. "While they may take over some tasks, their main role is to assist both caregivers and patients."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;At the Restaurant of Mistaken Orders in Sengawa, Tokyo, founded by Akiko Kanna, people stream in to be served by patients suffering from dementia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Inspired by her father's experience with the condition, Ms Kanna wanted a place where people could remain engaged and feel purposeful.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Toshio Morita, one of the café's servers, uses flowers to remember which table ordered what.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Despite his cognitive decline, Mr Morita enjoys the interaction. For his wife, the café provides respite and helps keep him engaged.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Kanna's café illustrates why social interventions and community support remain essential. Technology can provide tools and relief, but meaningful engagement and human connection are what truly sustain people living with dementia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"Honestly? I wanted a little pocket money. I like meeting all sorts of people," Mr Morita says. "Everyone's different - that's what makes it fun."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 gXrNRM"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 cMIbKV"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20251203-121739-f954f14c69-web-2.35.1-2/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 gUePlo hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/729d/live/1bd57a40-d18b-11f0-abf3-97535f35adb4.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/729d/live/1bd57a40-d18b-11f0-abf3-97535f35adb4.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/729d/live/1bd57a40-d18b-11f0-abf3-97535f35adb4.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/729d/live/1bd57a40-d18b-11f0-abf3-97535f35adb4.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/729d/live/1bd57a40-d18b-11f0-abf3-97535f35adb4.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/729d/live/1bd57a40-d18b-11f0-abf3-97535f35adb4.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/729d/live/1bd57a40-d18b-11f0-abf3-97535f35adb4.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/729d/live/1bd57a40-d18b-11f0-abf3-97535f35adb4.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Getty Images Lineup of Sharp Poketomo robots at Ceatec in Chiba, Japan" class="sc-5340b511-0 hLdNfA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 jVqbAn"&gt;Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;Sharp's Poketomo robot has been designed to give companionship to patients&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BBC</author><pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 01:04:33 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiWkFVX3lxTE1SLUtScW1DSExRZTZrU0pXblZMeFFFTTh3NFBnU1R2bXRqNUphOTM0Qk41X2NOUHZScDZUSmRNQW04RlRyU3Y4WlM5SENUbWJ5NFo1QWtha1p4UdIBX0FVX3lxTFBvNkQ2SS1NRVdVVXZfMTZhdEdtTHVhekdWQ3hyVUktb3l4ZXpkb21JSFltMnI0QU5wWGtrOVMwR2ttZXJqMXZncFZOVVNnVTZvZjZRQ1FTcTZiakdYTzVV</guid></item><item><title>事实核查疾病预防控制中心专家组放弃普遍新生儿乙型肝炎疫苗推荐的原因- PBS</title><link>https://www.pbs.org/newshour/health/fact-checking-the-cdc-panels-reasons-for-dropping-universal-newborn-hepatitis-b-vaccine-recommendation</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="body-text"&gt;
                    &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This article originally appeared on &lt;a href="https://www.politifact.com/article/2025/dec/05/hepatitis-b-vaccine-acip-cdc-hep-b-baby/"&gt;PolitiFact&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Since roughly 1991, the U.S. Centers for Disease Control and Prevention has recommended all babies get a dose of the hepatitis B vaccine at birth. The CDC committee that helps set vaccine policy voted Dec. 5 to overturn that decadeslong policy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Advisory Committee on Immunization Practices’ new recommendations say mothers who tested negative for hepatitis B should discuss the need for the vaccine with their doctors. For babies who do not receive a birth dose, the committee suggested the initial vaccine dose be given “no earlier than 2 months of age.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.pbs.org/newshour/show/rfk-appointed-cdc-panel-drops-hepatitis-b-vaccine-at-birth-recommendation"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WATCH:&lt;/strong&gt; RFK-appointed CDC panel drops hepatitis B vaccine at birth recommendation&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The committee is composed of members hand-picked by Health and Human Services Secretary Robert F. Kennedy, Jr., an anti-vaccine advocate who in June fired all 17 of the prior panel’s members.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here are four fact-checkable moments that stood out from ACIP’s Dec. 4 and 5 discussion leading up to the vote:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Many people are unaware they have hepatitis B&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Several ACIP committee members and health administrators questioned the need for vaccination among certain children who they described as “low-risk” for hepatitis B exposure.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But it can be hard to know a child’s exposure risk.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hepatitis B is &lt;a href="https://www.hepb.org/prevention-and-diagnosis/transmission/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;transmitted&lt;/a&gt; through &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/hepatitis-b/about/index.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;bodily fluids&lt;/a&gt; like blood, semen and vaginal fluids. But it is a highly infectious and &lt;a href="https://www.healthline.com/health/hiv/is-hep-b-more-contagious-than-hiv#risk-comparison" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;tough virus&lt;/a&gt; that can live &lt;a href="https://www.chop.edu/vaccine-education-center/vaccine-details/hepatitis-b-vaccine" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;on surfaces&lt;/a&gt; for up to a week. &lt;a href="https://www.chop.edu/vaccine-education-center/vaccine-details/hepatitis-b-vaccine" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Small amounts&lt;/a&gt; of dried blood on innocuous &lt;a href="https://www.pennmedicine.org/conditions/hepatitis-b" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;household items&lt;/a&gt; like &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/29395503/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;nail clippers&lt;/a&gt;, razors or toothbrushes could be enough.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hepatitis B infection is stealthy. It can be asymptomatic, sometimes for years. The &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/hepatitis-b/about/index.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;CDC&lt;/a&gt; estimates about 640,000 adults have a chronic infection, but about half of them do not know they are infected and contagious.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Even if a pregnant mother tests negative for the hepatitis B virus, her newborn can come in contact with it in other ways and through other people. Before the vaccine became recommended universally at birth, only &lt;a href="https://publications.aap.org/pediatrics/article/108/5/1123/63723/Childhood-Hepatitis-B-Virus-Infections-in-the" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;around half&lt;/a&gt; of children under 10 who were infected with hepatitis B contracted it from their mothers during birth.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Since many people are entirely unaware of their infections, it can be hard to know if a person is at elevated risk or resides in a community with infected individuals.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Vaccinations are to protect babies, who are most vulnerable to hepatitis B&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some ACIP members said that vaccinating all babies against hepatitis B at birth mainly protected other, higher risk people.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That’s misleading. Vaccination at birth aims primarily to protect newborns, who are &lt;a href="https://www.politifact.com/article/2025/sep/17/hepatitis-b-vaccine-babies-risk/"&gt;particularly vulnerable&lt;/a&gt; to hepatitis B.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The hepatitis B virus attacks the liver. Infected infants have a &lt;a href="https://www.hhs.gov/hepatitis/learn-about-viral-hepatitis/hepatitis-b-basics/index.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;90% chance&lt;/a&gt; of developing the disease’s more dangerous chronic form. A &lt;a href="https://www.aap.org/en/news-room/fact-checked/fact-checked-hepatitis-b-vaccine-given-to-newborns-reduces-risk-of-chronic-infection/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;quarter&lt;/a&gt; of those babies will go on to die prematurely from the disease when they become adults.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Untreated, chronic hepatitis B&lt;a href="https://www.hhs.gov/hepatitis/learn-about-viral-hepatitis/hepatitis-b-basics/index.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt; infections&lt;/a&gt; can cause cirrhosis and death. It is also one of the&lt;a href="https://www.cancer.org/cancer/types/liver-cancer/causes-risks-prevention/risk-factors.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt; leading causes&lt;/a&gt; of liver cancer. Patients can seek treatments to reduce the virus’ worst effects. But there is no cure.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“We used to have 18,000 or 20,000 kids a year being born with this, a quarter of them going on to have liver cancer,” &lt;a href="https://www.politifact.com/article/2025/sep/17/hepatitis-b-vaccine-babies-risk/"&gt;said Dr. James Campbell&lt;/a&gt;, pediatric infectious disease doctor at the University of Maryland. “We now have almost none.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Infection rates are low because the decades-old hep B vaccination strategy was working&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“This disease has become a victim of the vaccine,” said Dr. H. Cody Meissner, a committee member who voted against changing the recommendations. “We’re seeing disease rates go down because of the effectiveness of the vaccine.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Meissner is right that hepatitis B cases dropped dramatically following the introduction of birth-dose vaccination.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The hepatitis B vaccine uses&lt;a href="https://www.chop.edu/vaccine-education-center/vaccine-details/hepatitis-b-vaccine" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt; proteins&lt;/a&gt; from the surface of the hepatitis B virus to provoke an&lt;a href="https://vaccineknowledge.ox.ac.uk/hepatitis-b-vaccine#Ingredients" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt; immune response&lt;/a&gt; that gives the body a defense against future infection.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Before the vaccine, around 200,000 to 300,000 people were infected with hepatitis B&lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/mmwr/preview/mmwrhtml/mm5125a3.htm" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt; each year&lt;/a&gt;, including about 20,000 children.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Since hepatitis B vaccines began being universally administered to babies, overall cases are down to around&lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/hepatitis/php/npr-2025/hep-b-reduce-infections.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt; 14,000 annually.&lt;/a&gt; The change is&lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/hepatitis/statistics/2020surveillance/hepatitis-b/figure-2.4.htm" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt; especially dramatic&lt;/a&gt; among young people. In 2022, the CDC reported&lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/hepatitis-surveillance-2022/hepatitis-b/table-2-6.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt; 252 new chronic hepatitis B&lt;/a&gt; infections among people up to age 19, or 0.4 out of every 100,000 kids.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It’s a mistake to say that because we’re not seeing much disease, we can alter the roots or the frequency or the schedule for administration,” Meissner said. “Because we will see hepatitis B infections come back.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Many countries vaccinate for hepatitis B at birth; the U.S. is not an outlier&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Committee members repeatedly compared the United States’ guidance with other countries, including Denmark, as part of the rationale for walking back the universal recommendation to provide a hepatitis B vaccine dose at birth.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The U.S. is not a global outlier in recommending hepatitis B vaccines for newborns. In &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/acip/downloads/slides-2025-09-18-19/hep-b-birth-dose-briefing-508.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;September 2025, the CDC&lt;/a&gt; reported that “of the 194 WHO member states, 116 countries recommend universal hepatitis B birth dose vaccination to all newborns.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="attachment_541045" class="wp-caption aligncenter"&gt;&lt;img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-541045" class="size-large wp-image-541045" src="https://d3i6fh83elv35t.cloudfront.net/static/2025/12/Screenshot_2025-12-05_at_3.24.50PM-1024x544.png" alt="Screenshot_2025-12-05_at_3.24.50PM" srcset="https://d3i6fh83elv35t.cloudfront.net/static/2025/12/Screenshot_2025-12-05_at_3.24.50PM-1024x544.png 1024w, https://d3i6fh83elv35t.cloudfront.net/static/2025/12/Screenshot_2025-12-05_at_3.24.50PM-300x159.png 300w, https://d3i6fh83elv35t.cloudfront.net/static/2025/12/Screenshot_2025-12-05_at_3.24.50PM-768x408.png 768w, https://d3i6fh83elv35t.cloudfront.net/static/2025/12/Screenshot_2025-12-05_at_3.24.50PM-425x226.png 425w, https://d3i6fh83elv35t.cloudfront.net/static/2025/12/Screenshot_2025-12-05_at_3.24.50PM-1200x637.png 1200w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px"&gt;&lt;p id="caption-attachment-541045" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Hepatitis B vaccine birth dose vaccination policy by county as of September 2025. Graphic by Centers for Disease Control and Prevention&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Denmark’s &lt;a href="https://www.sst.dk/en/english/General-public/Children#:~:text=this%20page)-,Vaccinations,-The%20Danish%20Childhood" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;standard vaccination schedule&lt;/a&gt; includes vaccines protecting against 10 diseases, but hepatitis B is not one of them. Denmark recommends hepatitis B vaccines only for babies whose mothers are infected with the virus, &lt;a href="https://vaccine-schedule.ecdc.europa.eu/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;said&lt;/a&gt; the European Centre for Disease Prevention and Control.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Unlike Denmark, the U.S. does not have a national health care system, making it harder for Americans to access regular prenatal care and track patient records across doctors. The U.S. also has lower rates of prenatal screening for hepatitis B.&lt;/p&gt;

                                            &lt;div class="inline-invite inline-invite-type__funding inline-invite-style__default"&gt;
        
                    &lt;div class="inline-invite-funding__box"&gt;
                &lt;figure class="invite__logo default "&gt;
                    &lt;svg class="svg"&gt;&lt;use xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xlink:href="#pbs-newshour-horiz-refresh"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;
                &lt;/figure&gt;
                &lt;p class="invite_heading"&gt;
                    A free press is a cornerstone of a healthy democracy. 
                &lt;/p&gt;
                &lt;p class="invite_body"&gt;
                    Support trusted journalism and civil dialogue. 
                &lt;/p&gt;
                &lt;a href="https://give.newshour.org/page/88646/donate/1?ea.tracking.id=pbs_news_sept_2025_article&amp;amp;supporter.appealCode=N2509AW1000100" class="donation-link ga-click-funding ga-click-ender-funding"&gt;
                    &lt;button class="donate-button"&gt;Donate now&lt;/button&gt;
                    &lt;svg viewbox="0 0 16 16" fill="#000000" class="bi bi-arrow-right-short" version="1.1" id="svg1" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" xmlns:svg="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"&gt;
                    &lt;defs id="defs1"&gt;&lt;/defs&gt;
                    &lt;path fill-rule="evenodd" d="M4 8a.5.5 0 0 1 .5-.5h5.793L8.146 5.354a.5.5 0 1 1 .708-.708l3 3a.5.5 0 0 1 0 .708l-3 3a.5.5 0 0 1-.708-.708L10.293 8.5H4.5A.5.5 0 0 1 4 8z" id="path1"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;
                    &lt;/svg&gt;
                &lt;/a&gt;
            &lt;/div&gt;
            &lt;/div&gt;


                                    &lt;/div&gt;
            &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>PBS</author><pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 23:53:18 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi1AFBVV95cUxPUXpCanEtMDdHa1VJc1BkelZodGZQY0tlbC1VZGlVbmhneDIyU2daekZfX0J1QVIwZ0I1WEJWZ0xBaEtKOVUxVkFzYnZWbGtyWXR5OEQ0Z2dpR0o4cXAteVZURGFWOXE4dmV2WkYyaVJybWFqX3ZnM1lMZFBSRXZ5d3lpNWtuNllKZ1JkR3Bob284eGxhYU1qNVZEcDVfcG1UYWNSaFFqY0xwSlRnR3JHRHZXUDhjMFBFQi1BcTd1eHhrNXVWOHo1V1h3T2dFU2JFRjNDYQ</guid></item><item><title>“我们还没有接近解决的最大谜团是什么？” （ 39张照片） -无聊的熊猫</title><link>https://www.boredpanda.com/biggest-mysteries-still-unsolved/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="open-list-post-description"&gt;  &lt;p&gt;In this day and age, on the surface level, it seems like we &lt;a href="https://www.boredpanda.com/curiosities/facts/" class=" staff-link"&gt;know&lt;/a&gt; a lot about how the world, the human body, and the universe all work. And though we do know quite a bit, there’s still lots of room for scientific progress. Some theories aren’t as solid as you might think, and there are plenty of questions that have researchers &lt;a href="https://www.boredpanda.com/ocean-mysteries/" class=" staff-link"&gt;puzzled&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Internet users took to an online thread to share what they think are the biggest still-unanswered &lt;a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/AskReddit/comments/1pbfr7f/what_is_the_biggest_mystery_we_still_arent_close/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer nofollow" class=" staff-link"&gt;mysteries&lt;/a&gt; that we don’t seem to be close to fully solving yet. Read on to get your creative juices flowing and to think about something bigger than "what should I have for dinner?"&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p class="clear"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;img loading="lazy" alt="" class="alignnone image-size-full" src="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/cover_2d58f0e87bcebb07eafaf695663ba720.jpg"&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;div class="open-list-items clearfix "&gt;  &lt;p class="desktop-in-content-ad post-ads "&gt; &lt;span class="dfp-ad" data-source="primis"&gt; &lt;span id="desktop-widget-loaded"&gt;    &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;     &lt;div class="open-list-item open-list-block clearfix text-block "&gt; &lt;span id="list-text-3"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Though we don’t fully understand why people sleep, there are some solid, quality theories that scientists are working with.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For example, recent research suggests that the &lt;a href="https://www.health.harvard.edu/mind-and-mood/are-toxins-flushed-out-of-the-brain-during-sleep" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer nofollow" class=" staff-link"&gt;primary purpose&lt;/a&gt; of sleep for humans may be to remove toxic and metabolic waste from the brain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to one perspective article, if these toxins are allowed to build up, they &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/39941597/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer nofollow" class=" staff-link"&gt;might compromise&lt;/a&gt; brain functionality.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Meanwhile, researchers at the Washington University School of Medicine in St. Louis &lt;a href="https://medicine.washu.edu/news/neurons-help-flush-waste-out-of-brain-during-sleep/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer nofollow" class=" staff-link"&gt;found&lt;/a&gt; that during sleep, brain cells propel fluid into, through, and out of the brain, cleaning it of waste.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“These neurons are miniature pumps. Synchronized neural activity powers fluid flow and removal of debris from the brain. If we can build on this process, there is the possibility of delaying or even preventing neurological diseases, including Alzheimer’s and Parkinson’s disease, in which excess waste – such as metabolic waste and junk proteins – accumulate in the brain and lead to neurodegeneration,” explains neurologist Li-Feng Jiang-Xie, PhD, first author and postdoctoral research associate in the Department of Pathology &amp;amp; Immunology.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;div class="open-list-item open-list-block clearfix " data-submission-id="9744035"&gt;  &lt;p id="9744035" class="post-content-description text-open-list"&gt; &lt;img loading="lazy" class="image-size-full" src="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Max_Headroom_broadcast_signal_intrusion-692ff5452292b__700.jpg" alt="Eerie figure wearing sunglasses against a distorted background representing unsolved mysteries and unknown puzzles." title="Eerie figure wearing sunglasses against a distorted background representing unsolved mysteries and unknown puzzles."&gt; &lt;span class="bordered-description with-image"&gt;Tossing out one less existential, but who pirated the WGN signal with a Max Headroom skit in the 80s. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lots of theories, but no real evidence and no one has any idea who did it. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kudos to the people involved for actually keeping their mouths shut for 40 years. Makes me think it was one person that did it all on their own. What are the chances of more than one person keeping a lid on that?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;On the one hand, I want the guy(s) who did it to come out and admit it and how they did it. Statute of limitations has to be up right?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;But I get why they don’t. I’m sure the Feds would find some way to convict them of something if they came forward, statute of limitations be d****d.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="post-bottom-meta-links clearfix "&gt; &lt;span class="sources"&gt; &lt;a class="open-list-submission-source" href="https://www.reddit.com/r/AskReddit/comments/1pbfr7f/what_is_the_biggest_mystery_we_still_arent_close/nrqopwh/" target="_blank"&gt; non_clever_username &lt;/a&gt; &lt;span class="open-list-submission-source-separator"&gt;, &lt;/span&gt; &lt;a class="open-list-submission-source" href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Max_Headroom_signal_hijacking" target="_blank"&gt; Unknown &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="report"&gt; &lt;a class="open-list-submission-report" href="" data-href="/contact-us/?report-post=https://www.boredpanda.com/reddit-post-11366-8/"&gt;Report&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt;   &lt;/div&gt;   &lt;div class="open-list-item open-list-block clearfix " data-submission-id="9744048"&gt;  &lt;p id="9744048" class="post-content-description text-open-list"&gt; &lt;img loading="lazy" class="image-size-full" src="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/pexels-blaque-x-264516-932638-69300d73aa65a__700.jpg" alt="Underwater scene with light rays piercing through dark water, symbolizing mysteries we aren’t getting closer to solving" title="Underwater scene with light rays piercing through dark water, symbolizing mysteries we aren’t getting closer to solving"&gt; &lt;span class="bordered-description with-image"&gt;What kind of life lives in our oceans . Current scientific estimates say that we have only discovered 10-25% of marine species.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="post-bottom-meta-links clearfix "&gt; &lt;span class="sources"&gt; &lt;a class="open-list-submission-source" href="https://www.reddit.com/r/AskReddit/comments/1pbfr7f/what_is_the_biggest_mystery_we_still_arent_close/nrqie12/" target="_blank"&gt; Ok-Strawberry488 &lt;/a&gt; &lt;span class="open-list-submission-source-separator"&gt;, &lt;/span&gt; &lt;a class="open-list-submission-source" href="https://www.pexels.com/photo/underwater-photography-of-deep-sea-932638/" target="_blank"&gt; Blaque X &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="report"&gt; &lt;a class="open-list-submission-report" href="" data-href="/contact-us/?report-post=https://www.boredpanda.com/reddit-post-11366-21/"&gt;Report&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt;   &lt;/div&gt;  &lt;div class="open-list-item open-list-block clearfix text-block "&gt; &lt;span id="list-text-6"&gt;&lt;p&gt;“It is critical that the brain disposes of metabolic waste that can build up and contribute to neurodegenerative diseases. We knew that sleep is a time when the brain initiates a cleaning process to flush out waste and toxins it accumulates during wakefulness. But we didn’t know how that happens. These findings might be able to point us toward strategies and potential therapies to speed up the removal of damaging waste and to remove it before it can lead to dire consequences,” &lt;a href="https://medicine.washu.edu/news/neurons-help-flush-waste-out-of-brain-during-sleep/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer nofollow" class=" staff-link"&gt;notes&lt;/a&gt; Jonathan Kipnis, PhD, the senior author on the paper, the Alan A. and Edith L. Wolff Distinguished Professor of Pathology &amp;amp; Immunology, and a BJC Investigator.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to Kipnis, if you can enhance the cleaning process in the brain, it would be possible to sleep less and remain healthy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Not everyone has the benefit of eight hours of sleep each night, and loss of sleep has an impact on health.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;div class="open-list-item open-list-block clearfix " data-submission-id="9744094"&gt;  &lt;p id="9744094" class="post-content-description text-open-list"&gt; &lt;img loading="lazy" class="image-size-full" src="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/zachary-ferguson-ZedTs5qheOM-unsplash-6930068f98687__700.jpg" alt="Person wearing boots and jeans sitting by the water, reflecting on mysteries that remain unsolved and puzzling." title="Person wearing boots and jeans sitting by the water, reflecting on mysteries that remain unsolved and puzzling."&gt; &lt;span class="bordered-description with-image"&gt;Restless legs syndrome (RLS) is a condition that causes a very strong urge to move the legs. The urge to move usually is caused by an uncomfortable feeling in the legs. It typically happens in the evening or at night when sitting or lying down. Moving eases the discomfort for a short time.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="post-bottom-meta-links clearfix "&gt; &lt;span class="sources"&gt; &lt;a class="open-list-submission-source" href="https://www.reddit.com/r/AskReddit/comments/1pbfr7f/what_is_the_biggest_mystery_we_still_arent_close/nrqq5j1/" target="_blank"&gt; CletusMuckenfuss &lt;/a&gt; &lt;span class="open-list-submission-source-separator"&gt;, &lt;/span&gt; &lt;a class="open-list-submission-source" href="https://unsplash.com/photos/man-in-black-jacket-and-blue-denim-jeans-sitting-on-brown-wooden-log-during-daytime-ZedTs5qheOM" target="_blank"&gt; Zachary Ferguson &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="report"&gt; &lt;a class="open-list-submission-report" href="" data-href="/contact-us/?report-post=https://www.boredpanda.com/reddit-post-11366-67/"&gt;Report&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt;   &lt;/div&gt;  &lt;div class="open-list-item open-list-block clearfix " data-submission-id="9744032"&gt;  &lt;p id="9744032" class="post-content-description text-open-list"&gt; &lt;img loading="lazy" class="image-size-full" src="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/robina-weermeijer-3KGF9R_0oHs-unsplash-693000ebc7a48__700.jpg" alt="Model of the human brain showing detailed anatomy, illustrating one of the many mysteries we aren’t getting closer to solving." title="Model of the human brain showing detailed anatomy, illustrating one of the many mysteries we aren’t getting closer to solving."&gt; &lt;span class="bordered-description with-image"&gt;The brain. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;I have brain cancer, and when I was first diagnosed with it I asked how it happened and my doctor shrugged and told me that they don't really understand how brain cancers develop and that we are just stepping our toes in the door for treatment for it.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="post-bottom-meta-links clearfix "&gt; &lt;span class="sources"&gt; &lt;a class="open-list-submission-source" href="https://www.reddit.com/r/AskReddit/comments/1pbfr7f/what_is_the_biggest_mystery_we_still_arent_close/nrre45x/" target="_blank"&gt; Own_Construction2682 &lt;/a&gt; &lt;span class="open-list-submission-source-separator"&gt;, &lt;/span&gt; &lt;a class="open-list-submission-source" href="https://unsplash.com/photos/brown-brain-decor-in-selective-focus-photography-3KGF9R_0oHs" target="_blank"&gt; Robina Weermeijer &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="report"&gt; &lt;a class="open-list-submission-report" href="" data-href="/contact-us/?report-post=https://www.boredpanda.com/reddit-post-11366-5/"&gt;Report&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt;   &lt;/div&gt;  &lt;div class="open-list-item open-list-block clearfix " data-submission-id="9744038"&gt;  &lt;p id="9744038" class="post-content-description text-open-list"&gt; &lt;img loading="lazy" class="image-size-full" src="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Linear_A_cup-693002519d9ae-png__700.jpg" alt="Ancient undeciphered symbols and markings representing mysteries we aren’t getting any closer to solving." title="Ancient undeciphered symbols and markings representing mysteries we aren’t getting any closer to solving."&gt; &lt;span class="bordered-description with-image"&gt;We don’t seem to be making any headway in deciphering Linear A, the Minoan writing from. Which is kind of odd because there’s a rather big sample size and it’s in a pretty central location whose people and culture influenced a lot of our touchstones today, but there’s really been no progress to speak of.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="post-bottom-meta-links clearfix "&gt; &lt;span class="sources"&gt; &lt;a class="open-list-submission-source" href="https://www.reddit.com/r/AskReddit/comments/1pbfr7f/what_is_the_biggest_mystery_we_still_arent_close/nrqakt9/" target="_blank"&gt; emptycagenowcorroded &lt;/a&gt; &lt;span class="open-list-submission-source-separator"&gt;, &lt;/span&gt; &lt;a class="open-list-submission-source" href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Linear_A" target="_blank"&gt; Evans, Arthur, Sir &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="report"&gt; &lt;a class="open-list-submission-report" href="" data-href="/contact-us/?report-post=https://www.boredpanda.com/reddit-post-11366-11/"&gt;Report&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt;   &lt;/div&gt; &lt;div class="open-list-item open-list-block clearfix text-block "&gt; &lt;span id="list-text-9"&gt;&lt;p&gt;From your perspective, what are the biggest, most important &lt;a href="https://www.boredpanda.com/national-park-workers-rescue-officers-share-strange-stories/" class=" staff-link"&gt;mysteries&lt;/a&gt; that remain unanswered to this very day, dear Pandas? What theories do you personally think most people take for granted, even though there’s still room for research?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What do you do to stay up-to-date with &lt;a href="https://www.boredpanda.com/unique-historical-objects/" class=" staff-link"&gt;scientific&lt;/a&gt; breakthroughs? Let us know what you think in the comments below.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;div class="open-list-item open-list-block clearfix " data-submission-id="9744056"&gt;  &lt;p id="9744056" class="post-content-description text-open-list"&gt; &lt;img loading="lazy" class="image-size-full" src="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/jeremy-thomas-4dpAqfTbvKA-unsplash-6930149fe97ab__700.jpg" alt="Vast starry night sky showing cosmic mysteries and space phenomena beyond current human understanding." title="Vast starry night sky showing cosmic mysteries and space phenomena beyond current human understanding."&gt; &lt;span class="bordered-description with-image"&gt;What the universe, or multi-verse, is inside of. Like where is the end and if there is no end what is it all in? My brain can't handle this, no amount of theories can make me stop wondering.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="post-bottom-meta-links clearfix "&gt; &lt;span class="sources"&gt; &lt;a class="open-list-submission-source" href="https://www.reddit.com/r/AskReddit/comments/1pbfr7f/what_is_the_biggest_mystery_we_still_arent_close/nrq5ncl/" target="_blank"&gt; Edgeguy13 &lt;/a&gt; &lt;span class="open-list-submission-source-separator"&gt;, &lt;/span&gt; &lt;a class="open-list-submission-source" href="https://unsplash.com/photos/the-stars-and-galaxy-as-seen-from-rocky-mountain-national-park-4dpAqfTbvKA" target="_blank"&gt; Jeremy Thomas &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="report"&gt; &lt;a class="open-list-submission-report" href="" data-href="/contact-us/?report-post=https://www.boredpanda.com/reddit-post-11366-29/"&gt;Report&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt;   &lt;/div&gt;      &lt;div class="open-list-item open-list-block clearfix " data-submission-id="9744060"&gt;  &lt;p id="9744060" class="post-content-description text-open-list"&gt; &lt;img loading="lazy" class="image-size-full" src="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/VS-YouTube-ZombieParasiteCordycepsFungusTakesOverInsectsThroughMindControlNationalGeographic-218-69301049bf259__700.jpg" alt="Close-up of an insect on mossy surface, illustrating natural mysteries that remain unsolved in the environment." title="Close-up of an insect on mossy surface, illustrating natural mysteries that remain unsolved in the environment."&gt; &lt;span class="bordered-description with-image"&gt;How do parasites know how to control the behavior of their hosts? Particularly things like fungus, which don't appear to actually have minds of their own? &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Also, how does something evolve to learn how to do that?&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="post-bottom-meta-links clearfix "&gt; &lt;span class="sources"&gt; &lt;a class="open-list-submission-source" href="https://www.reddit.com/r/AskReddit/comments/1pbfr7f/what_is_the_biggest_mystery_we_still_arent_close/nrrvydw/" target="_blank"&gt; DeadSuperHero &lt;/a&gt; &lt;span class="open-list-submission-source-separator"&gt;, &lt;/span&gt; &lt;a class="open-list-submission-source" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vijGdWn5-h8" target="_blank"&gt; National Geographic &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="report"&gt; &lt;a class="open-list-submission-report" href="" data-href="/contact-us/?report-post=https://www.boredpanda.com/reddit-post-11366-33/"&gt;Report&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt;   &lt;/div&gt;    &lt;div class="open-list-item open-list-block clearfix " data-submission-id="9744114"&gt;  &lt;p id="9744114" class="post-content-description text-open-list"&gt; &lt;img loading="lazy" class="image-size-full" src="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/andrej-lisakov-2ENbeTLengk-unsplash-6930075f024d6__700.jpg" alt="Person sleeping peacefully wrapped in a blanket surrounded by pillows, representing mysteries that remain unsolved." title="Person sleeping peacefully wrapped in a blanket surrounded by pillows, representing mysteries that remain unsolved."&gt; &lt;span class="bordered-description with-image"&gt;What does sleep actually do, and why do we need it? On the surface, it seems obvious, but there seems to be a lack of general consensus on why it's necessary. Some species require very little sleep, some require a lot. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We can point to anecdotes regarding how different animals do it, and even the benefits that come from sufficient sleep.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We have some good ideas about what sleep does for the body, along with theories as to why this is a necessity. But in terms of a definitive answer, things seem kind of murky.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="post-bottom-meta-links clearfix "&gt; &lt;span class="sources"&gt; &lt;a class="open-list-submission-source" href="https://www.reddit.com/r/AskReddit/comments/1pbfr7f/what_is_the_biggest_mystery_we_still_arent_close/nrru3cx/" target="_blank"&gt; DeadSuperHero &lt;/a&gt; &lt;span class="open-list-submission-source-separator"&gt;, &lt;/span&gt; &lt;a class="open-list-submission-source" href="https://unsplash.com/photos/a-woman-sleeping-in-a-bed-with-a-blanket-and-pillows-2ENbeTLengk" target="_blank"&gt; Andrej Lišakov &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="report"&gt; &lt;a class="open-list-submission-report" href="" data-href="/contact-us/?report-post=https://www.boredpanda.com/reddit-post-11366-86/"&gt;Report&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt;   &lt;/div&gt;   &lt;div class="open-list-item open-list-block clearfix " data-submission-id="9744057"&gt;  &lt;p id="9744057" class="post-content-description text-open-list"&gt; &lt;img loading="lazy" class="image-size-full" src="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/pexels-nicola-barts-7925815-69300eea14392__700.jpg" alt="Thoughtful man in a blue shirt and red tie reflecting deeply on unsolved mysteries and complex questions." title="Thoughtful man in a blue shirt and red tie reflecting deeply on unsolved mysteries and complex questions."&gt; &lt;span class="bordered-description with-image"&gt;How to reliably prevent or stop hiccups. For such a universal experience, its not terribly well-understood since it happens so infrequently, unpredictably, and for (usually) such a short period of time.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="post-bottom-meta-links clearfix "&gt; &lt;span class="sources"&gt; &lt;a class="open-list-submission-source" href="https://www.reddit.com/r/AskReddit/comments/1pbfr7f/what_is_the_biggest_mystery_we_still_arent_close/nrrf5ti/" target="_blank"&gt; vonHindenburg &lt;/a&gt; &lt;span class="open-list-submission-source-separator"&gt;, &lt;/span&gt; &lt;a class="open-list-submission-source" href="https://www.pexels.com/photo/concerned-black-businessman-in-city-7925815/" target="_blank"&gt; Nicola Barts &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="report"&gt; &lt;a class="open-list-submission-report" href="" data-href="/contact-us/?report-post=https://www.boredpanda.com/reddit-post-11366-30/"&gt;Report&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt;   &lt;/div&gt;       &lt;div class="open-list-item open-list-block clearfix " data-submission-id="9744162"&gt;  &lt;p id="9744162" class="post-content-description text-open-list"&gt; &lt;span class="bordered-description"&gt;Intelligence is a concept we understand. Animals don't know what intelligence is, and yet they might or might not use it. What are some other concepts similar to intelligence that we have no idea exist and we have no way of knowing they exist. It's a big assumption that we can understand everything in the universe using intelligence.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="post-bottom-meta-links clearfix "&gt; &lt;span class="sources"&gt; &lt;a class="open-list-submission-source" href="https://www.reddit.com/r/AskReddit/comments/1pbfr7f/what_is_the_biggest_mystery_we_still_arent_close/nrrrgz7/" target="_blank"&gt; permacougar &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="report"&gt; &lt;a class="open-list-submission-report" href="" data-href="/contact-us/?report-post=https://www.boredpanda.com/reddit-post-11366-133/"&gt;Report&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt;   &lt;/div&gt;     &lt;div class="open-list-item open-list-block clearfix " data-submission-id="9744102"&gt;  &lt;p id="9744102" class="post-content-description text-open-list"&gt; &lt;img loading="lazy" class="image-size-full" src="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/wesley-tingey-4aSz0dNLBW8-unsplash-1-69301400cd4c9__700.jpg" alt="A mysterious UFO hovering over dark mountains at sunset, symbolizing unsolved mysteries and unexplained phenomena." title="A mysterious UFO hovering over dark mountains at sunset, symbolizing unsolved mysteries and unexplained phenomena."&gt; &lt;span class="bordered-description with-image"&gt;I think it's bizarre so many people in our government are saying aliens are real and people are just brushing it off as a nothing burger.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="post-bottom-meta-links clearfix "&gt; &lt;span class="sources"&gt; &lt;a class="open-list-submission-source" href="https://www.reddit.com/r/AskReddit/comments/1pbfr7f/what_is_the_biggest_mystery_we_still_arent_close/nrqeo57/" target="_blank"&gt; newtonreddits &lt;/a&gt; &lt;span class="open-list-submission-source-separator"&gt;, &lt;/span&gt; &lt;a class="open-list-submission-source" href="https://unsplash.com/photos/a-large-object-flying-through-the-air-at-sunset-4aSz0dNLBW8" target="_blank"&gt; Wesley Tingey &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="report"&gt; &lt;a class="open-list-submission-report" href="" data-href="/contact-us/?report-post=https://www.boredpanda.com/reddit-post-11366-75/"&gt;Report&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt;   &lt;/div&gt; &lt;div class="open-list-item open-list-block clearfix " data-submission-id="9744107"&gt;  &lt;p id="9744107" class="post-content-description text-open-list"&gt; &lt;img loading="lazy" class="image-size-full" src="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/alexander-mils-IHVCVi6zt9g-unsplash-6930172b8b112__700.jpg" alt="A glowing black hole in space with orbiting objects, illustrating mysterious cosmic phenomena people cannot solve." title="A glowing black hole in space with orbiting objects, illustrating mysterious cosmic phenomena people cannot solve."&gt; &lt;span class="bordered-description with-image"&gt;What really happens if you try to enter a black hole and what’s on the other side? We will likely never know.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="post-bottom-meta-links clearfix "&gt; &lt;span class="sources"&gt; &lt;a class="open-list-submission-source" href="https://www.reddit.com/r/AskReddit/comments/1pbfr7f/what_is_the_biggest_mystery_we_still_arent_close/nrrmjt7/" target="_blank"&gt; djazzie &lt;/a&gt; &lt;span class="open-list-submission-source-separator"&gt;, &lt;/span&gt; &lt;a class="open-list-submission-source" href="https://unsplash.com/photos/an-artists-impression-of-a-black-hole-in-space-IHVCVi6zt9g" target="_blank"&gt; Alexander Mils &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="report"&gt; &lt;a class="open-list-submission-report" href="" data-href="/contact-us/?report-post=https://www.boredpanda.com/reddit-post-11366-79/"&gt;Report&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt;   &lt;/div&gt;          &lt;div class="open-list-item open-list-block clearfix " data-submission-id="9744062"&gt;  &lt;p id="9744062" class="post-content-description text-open-list"&gt; &lt;img loading="lazy" class="image-size-full" src="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/55221958844-6930151a81764-png__700.jpg" alt="A smiling couple posing closely together, capturing a moment amidst unsolved mysteries people continue discussing." title="A smiling couple posing closely together, capturing a moment amidst unsolved mysteries people continue discussing."&gt; &lt;span class="bordered-description with-image"&gt;Not biggest on a universal or global scale, but locally near Philadelphia, a couple has been missing since 2005 and vanished without a trace. They were at a bar and after leaving were never seen again. Car missing, no activity on phones or credit cards. Just gone. A lot of speculation but so far no leads and it bugs me. If interested just google “missing South St couple Philadelphia”.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="post-bottom-meta-links clearfix "&gt; &lt;span class="sources"&gt; &lt;a class="open-list-submission-source" href="https://www.reddit.com/r/AskReddit/comments/1pbfr7f/what_is_the_biggest_mystery_we_still_arent_close/nrqrl6o/" target="_blank"&gt; lifeslidesdown &lt;/a&gt; &lt;span class="open-list-submission-source-separator"&gt;, &lt;/span&gt; &lt;a class="open-list-submission-source" href="https://edition.cnn.com/2025/04/06/us/petrone-imbo-missing-philadelphia-cec" target="_blank"&gt; CNN &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="report"&gt; &lt;a class="open-list-submission-report" href="" data-href="/contact-us/?report-post=https://www.boredpanda.com/reddit-post-11366-35/"&gt;Report&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt;   &lt;/div&gt; &lt;div class="open-list-item open-list-block clearfix " data-submission-id="9744075"&gt;  &lt;p id="9744075" class="post-content-description text-open-list"&gt; &lt;img loading="lazy" class="image-size-full" src="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/vitaly-gariev-GaUM9PSNcH4-unsplash-693016c3cf38b__700.jpg" alt="Person with blonde hair facing a chalkboard covered in complex equations representing unsolved mysteries and challenges in science." title="Person with blonde hair facing a chalkboard covered in complex equations representing unsolved mysteries and challenges in science."&gt; &lt;span class="bordered-description with-image"&gt;Prime numbers remain quite a mystery. I was going to say that they aren't close to finding patterns or ways for identifying the "next" prime number, but tbh I don't know if that's true. Apparently this summer it was &lt;a href="https://www.scientificamerican.com/article/mathematicians-hunting-prime-numbers-discover-infinite-new-pattern-for/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;published&lt;/a&gt; that mathmeticians developed a new method for *defining* prime numbers.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I'll leave this up as I think it fits the topic, but I'll let other correct me if we are closer than I thought.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="post-bottom-meta-links clearfix "&gt; &lt;span class="sources"&gt; &lt;a class="open-list-submission-source" href="https://www.reddit.com/r/AskReddit/comments/1pbfr7f/what_is_the_biggest_mystery_we_still_arent_close/nrq72xx/" target="_blank"&gt; animalmarshall &lt;/a&gt; &lt;span class="open-list-submission-source-separator"&gt;, &lt;/span&gt; &lt;a class="open-list-submission-source" href="https://unsplash.com/photos/woman-facing-a-blackboard-filled-with-equations-GaUM9PSNcH4" target="_blank"&gt; Vitaly Gariev &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="report"&gt; &lt;a class="open-list-submission-report" href="" data-href="/contact-us/?report-post=https://www.boredpanda.com/reddit-post-11366-48/"&gt;Report&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt;   &lt;/div&gt;    &lt;div class="open-list-item open-list-block clearfix " data-submission-id="9744087"&gt;  &lt;p id="9744087" class="post-content-description text-open-list"&gt; &lt;span class="bordered-description"&gt;One day my dog was running along the fence with the neighbors dog, which both of my dogs have done for years. I call him to come back inside and 1/3 of his ear was missing. It looked like someone had just stripped a piece off the edge for some beef jerky or something (he had Lab ears, if that helps you imagine haha)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;After freaking out for a second (and before I loaded him into the car to head to the ER vet), I looked all up and down the fence where they run, I tried to see if the neighbors dog had blood on or around his mouth - maybe she got Boo's ear when they were running. NOTHING. No ear strip, no blood, nothing along the path he runs. I looked for days too. Whenever the dogs were outside, I was outside looking for Boo Boo's ear and never found it.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;While, honestly, thank god. It would have probably made me puke to find his ear strip well after the fact, but I really would like to know what happened.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;That's my biggest mystery.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="post-bottom-meta-links clearfix "&gt; &lt;span class="sources"&gt; &lt;a class="open-list-submission-source" href="https://www.reddit.com/r/AskReddit/comments/1pbfr7f/what_is_the_biggest_mystery_we_still_arent_close/nrr7tsf/" target="_blank"&gt; 614meg &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="report"&gt; &lt;a class="open-list-submission-report" href="" data-href="/contact-us/?report-post=https://www.boredpanda.com/reddit-post-11366-60/"&gt;Report&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt;   &lt;/div&gt;   &lt;div class="open-list-item open-list-block clearfix " data-submission-id="9744104"&gt;  &lt;p id="9744104" class="post-content-description text-open-list"&gt; &lt;img loading="lazy" class="image-size-full" src="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/wojciech-rzepka-MI0igXg037A-unsplash-693016fd6ca88__700.jpg" alt="Ancient cemetery with weathered gravestones and a stone church tower, evoking mysteries we aren’t close to solving." title="Ancient cemetery with weathered gravestones and a stone church tower, evoking mysteries we aren’t close to solving."&gt; &lt;span class="bordered-description with-image"&gt;Who or what is behind our existence? Why are we something?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you are as logical as you think you are, why do you have emotions?&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="post-bottom-meta-links clearfix "&gt; &lt;span class="sources"&gt; &lt;a class="open-list-submission-source" href="https://www.reddit.com/r/AskReddit/comments/1pbfr7f/what_is_the_biggest_mystery_we_still_arent_close/nrs59su/" target="_blank"&gt; WindowNo6601 &lt;/a&gt; &lt;span class="open-list-submission-source-separator"&gt;, &lt;/span&gt; &lt;a class="open-list-submission-source" href="https://unsplash.com/photos/a-cemetery-with-a-tall-tower-in-the-background-MI0igXg037A" target="_blank"&gt; Wojciech Rzepka &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="report"&gt; &lt;a class="open-list-submission-report" href="" data-href="/contact-us/?report-post=https://www.boredpanda.com/reddit-post-11366-77/"&gt;Report&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt;   &lt;/div&gt; &lt;div class="open-list-item open-list-block clearfix " data-submission-id="9744131"&gt;  &lt;p id="9744131" class="post-content-description text-open-list"&gt; &lt;span class="bordered-description"&gt;Aliens. For decades we had several testimonies from people ranging from farmers to astronauts and the highest government officials. Yet the discussion always hits the wall with the simple question: where is the evidence? No matter who discusses the topic we never get over the issue of the lack of credible evidence. Reason tells me that it is impossible that we are the only living conscious beings on this ever expanding universe. But if visitors are always coming in and out, where is the actual proof and why do they not present themselves to us?!&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="post-bottom-meta-links clearfix "&gt; &lt;span class="sources"&gt; &lt;a class="open-list-submission-source" href="https://www.reddit.com/r/AskReddit/comments/1pbfr7f/what_is_the_biggest_mystery_we_still_arent_close/nrqdmzl/" target="_blank"&gt; Prime-119 &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="report"&gt; &lt;a class="open-list-submission-report" href="" data-href="/contact-us/?report-post=https://www.boredpanda.com/reddit-post-11366-103/"&gt;Report&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt;   &lt;/div&gt;   &lt;div class="open-list-item open-list-block clearfix " data-submission-id="9744134"&gt;  &lt;p id="9744134" class="post-content-description text-open-list"&gt; &lt;span class="bordered-description"&gt;Spontaneous Human Combustion&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ball lightning&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ancient iron alloys that do not rust.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="post-bottom-meta-links clearfix "&gt; &lt;span class="sources"&gt; &lt;a class="open-list-submission-source" href="https://www.reddit.com/r/AskReddit/comments/1pbfr7f/what_is_the_biggest_mystery_we_still_arent_close/nrrbc25/" target="_blank"&gt; Jo_of_Average &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="report"&gt; &lt;a class="open-list-submission-report" href="" data-href="/contact-us/?report-post=https://www.boredpanda.com/reddit-post-11366-106/"&gt;Report&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt;   &lt;/div&gt;  &lt;div class="open-list-item open-list-block clearfix " data-submission-id="9744068"&gt;  &lt;p id="9744068" class="post-content-description text-open-list"&gt; &lt;span class="bordered-description"&gt;Every six months I hear they’ve finally found Amelia Earharts plane. Do I care if they solve the mystery? Nope don’t gaf at all, but apparently lots of other people do .&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="post-bottom-meta-links clearfix "&gt; &lt;span class="sources"&gt; &lt;a class="open-list-submission-source" href="https://www.reddit.com/r/AskReddit/comments/1pbfr7f/what_is_the_biggest_mystery_we_still_arent_close/nrq6ckg/" target="_blank"&gt; SadExercises420 &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="report"&gt; &lt;a class="open-list-submission-report" href="" data-href="/contact-us/?report-post=https://www.boredpanda.com/reddit-post-11366-41/"&gt;Report&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt;   &lt;/div&gt;   &lt;div class="open-list-item open-list-block clearfix " data-submission-id="9744108"&gt;  &lt;p id="9744108" class="post-content-description text-open-list"&gt; &lt;span class="bordered-description"&gt;What’s really in Area 51, no guesses or theories, ‘ just the facts ma’am’.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="post-bottom-meta-links clearfix "&gt; &lt;span class="sources"&gt; &lt;a class="open-list-submission-source" href="https://www.reddit.com/r/AskReddit/comments/1pbfr7f/what_is_the_biggest_mystery_we_still_arent_close/nrqb68e/" target="_blank"&gt; h20poIo &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="report"&gt; &lt;a class="open-list-submission-report" href="" data-href="/contact-us/?report-post=https://www.boredpanda.com/reddit-post-11366-80/"&gt;Report&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt;   &lt;/div&gt; &lt;div class="open-list-item open-list-block clearfix " data-submission-id="9744124"&gt;  &lt;p id="9744124" class="post-content-description text-open-list"&gt; &lt;span class="bordered-description"&gt;How to cure cold so that our body doesnt shutdown for a few days.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="post-bottom-meta-links clearfix "&gt; &lt;span class="sources"&gt; &lt;a class="open-list-submission-source" href="https://www.reddit.com/r/AskReddit/comments/1pbfr7f/what_is_the_biggest_mystery_we_still_arent_close/nrqtiv8/" target="_blank"&gt; Not____007 &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="report"&gt; &lt;a class="open-list-submission-report" href="" data-href="/contact-us/?report-post=https://www.boredpanda.com/reddit-post-11366-96/"&gt;Report&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt;   &lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;   &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Bored Panda</author><pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 23:02:02 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMibEFVX3lxTE1yREJxZkoyY0V6cmtYWkpCVDM2UHFWS196ZEVEa1RXOEUxN191dEQxUTNSek1JalBQVzJzNHM0VXFpYnJlMDJ4RWZBVG5qcFdZZXl3TjRXU0J5UUtRSkRKUlc2cGFhM0RUNUEzNw</guid></item><item><title>青少年因“笑”而陷入困境，因为哥哥在取笑她的体重后被惊讶的“业力”击中-雅虎生活方式加拿大</title><link>https://ca.style.yahoo.com/teen-gets-trouble-laughing-brother-230000463.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="" data-article-body="true"&gt;&lt;h3 class="mb-4 text-lg font-bold"&gt;NEED TO KNOW&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul class="mb-4"&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;At just 17 years old, one woman had been constantly called “fat” by her family for years&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Her brother even went so far as to taunt her, saying she would die of diabetes&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Then one day, he received unexpected news that she called “karma"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Family dynamics can be complicated, especially when issues of body image and health are involved.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;One Reddit user recently shared that her family constantly calls her "fat," all while her older brother’s unhealthy habits have gone unchecked – until an unexpected twist made her feel like "karma" had finally caught up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The 17-year-old poster explained that her family, specifically her 21-year-old brother, J, consistently criticizes her weight.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;"For the longest while ever since I started puberty my family would not stop calling me fat," she wrote. "I'm 140 pounds and doctors say that's normal weight, but to my family its considered fat."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="relative mb-4"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="relative text-sm mt-1 pr-2.5"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Getty&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; Stock image of person weighing themselves.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;She noted that her older brother is easily "the most active participant in calling me overweight."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;"He always tell me that I'm going to die from heart disease or be diagnosed with diabetes because I 'eat too much,'” the user &lt;a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/AITAH/comments/1p2bzff/aitah_for_laughing_when_my_brother_was_diagnosed/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:wrote in her post;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;wrote in her post&lt;/a&gt;. However, she claimed that he "eats way more" than she does and rarely gets any exercise.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Still, her family insists "that 'he's a growing boy, so he must eat.' ”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Never miss a story — sign up for &lt;a href="https://people.com/people-news-daily-newsletter-sign-up-8692701" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:PEOPLE's free daily newsletter;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;PEOPLE's free daily newsletter&lt;/a&gt; to stay up-to-date on the best of what PEOPLE has to offer​​, from celebrity news to compelling human interest stories.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Over the years, the double standard extended to birthdays and meals. While she didn’t get cake, J did, and when she made dinner, she was told to cook extra so her brother could eat as much as he wanted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The unfair treatment didn’t end there. The poster was blamed for finishing household food, no matter how little she actually consumed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“A whole liter of juice? finished by me even if I took only one cup. Snacks? I finished them. Leftover dinner? Me. Everything is always finished by me no matter how much I try to prove that I didn't do it,” she explained.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Over time, she stopped arguing, knowing it was pointless to fight against a family set on blaming her.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;"Eventually I stopped putting up a fight because I knew it wasn't me and arguing with people who were dead set on believing you ate everything didn't get anywhere," she wrote.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The story took a surprising turn when J began feeling unwell and went to the doctor, explaining that he was "feeling sluggish and dehydrated." After testing, he was diagnosed with type 2 diabetes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“I watched as my mom and J stared at the lab results in utter shock and disbelief. J was so dumbfounded that I couldn't help but laugh,” the Reddit user revealed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;"J and our mom looked at me with a mixture of shame and rage. My mom grabbed me and had me get a blood test as well because apparently if J had it so did I, but when the lab showed that I was healthy, I laughed even harder this time," she continued.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;However, her mom then told their entire extended family that she "laughed at my unfortunate brother instead of feeling sorry for him and now I'm being lashed out at by everyone."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;So, she turned to Reddit to ask if she was in the wrong for laughing at his diagnosis or if she was justified, given his behavior toward her.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="relative mb-4"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="relative text-sm mt-1 pr-2.5"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Getty&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; Stock image of teenager at the doctor's office.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;In an edit, the user emphasized that her laughter didn’t mean she didn’t care about her brother’s diagnosis. She agreed that "diabetes is a serious condition," adding that she has been preparing her brother's meals since his diagnosis to ensure he is on the right track.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;"I make sure to give him stuff that won't raise his sugar and cause any further complications, just because I laughed at him and he has a history of being my biggest hater, doesn't mean that I don't love my brother, he is still my family at the end of the day," she wrote.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Still, her post sparked a mix of reactions online.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Some users felt her brother got karma for bullying her, while others argued that laughing at a serious health issue was inappropriate, highlighting the delicate balance of fairness in complicated family dynamics.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Read the original article on &lt;a href="https://people.com/teen-laughs-at-older-brothers-health-diagnosis-reddit-11859624" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:People;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;People&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Yahoo Lifestyle Canada</author><pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiggFBVV95cUxPckNnTWowWU1rUkJVVG9DM3JHVDI0d3FXTEFqY3Y5TUtUSzN6WE9EU0U5T25GX1M1RDlmejZPMlpYYXNCeWtYSjFiRFBZVlBZbW56VUZtaUpETmp5STZLYXA0MlVxSWVYdUlMMXg3WHlNTkdpa3FxbzR3X0dROEJrMDhn</guid></item><item><title>研究发现，笑气可以立即缓解抑郁症- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/laughing-gas-can-offer-immediate-relief-from-depression-study-finds</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;A review by researchers from the University of Birmingham and the University of Oxford in the UK has found that controlled doses of laughing gas (or &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Nitrous_oxide"&gt;nitrous oxide&lt;/a&gt;) really can provide quick-acting relief from  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/depression" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73097" data-postid="184148" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;depression&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The treatment seems to be viable over longer periods of time, with repeated doses, and can be effective in individuals with both &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/depression"&gt;major depressive disorder&lt;/a&gt; (MDD) and treatment-resistant depression (TRD) – some of the people who are hardest to treat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/women-have-twice-as-many-depression-genes-as-men-says-largest-of-its-kind-study"&gt;Women Have Twice as Many Depression Genes as Men, Says Largest-of-Its-Kind Study&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"This population has often lost hope of recovery, making the results of this study particularly exciting," &lt;a href="https://www.birmingham.ac.uk/news/2025/clinical-use-of-nitrous-oxide-could-help-treat-depression-major-study-shows"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; consultant psychiatrist Steven Marwaha, from the University of Birmingham.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"These findings highlight the urgent need for new treatments that can complement existing care pathways, and further evidence is needed to understand how this approach can best support people living with severe depression."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_184152" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-184152" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/12/NeuronDiagram.jpg" alt="Neuron diagram" class="wp-image-184152 size-full" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/12/NeuronDiagram.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/12/NeuronDiagram-600x622.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-184152" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Laughing gas (represented by the red circles) may work against depression by dampening signaling between neurons. (Gill et al., &lt;em&gt;eBioMedicine&lt;/em&gt;, 2025)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers evaluated seven  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/clinical-trials" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73032" data-postid="184148" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;clinical trials&lt;/a&gt; involving 247 participants in total, as well as four plans for future trials known as protocol papers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Across the trials, selected volunteers inhaled nitrous oxide at concentrations of either 50 percent or 25 percent, with the effects compared to volunteers who had inhaled a &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/what-is-a-placebo"&gt;form of placebo&lt;/a&gt; instead.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The higher of the two concentrations typically alleviated depression's symptoms better, but often came with more side effects, including nausea, headaches, and &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/depersonalization-disorder-what-we-know-about-mysterious-condition"&gt;feelings of dissociation&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers found that administering the gas helped reduce &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/brain-scans-identify-six-distinct-types-of-depression-and-anxiety"&gt;depressive symptoms&lt;/a&gt; in as little as two hours. Relief was relatively short-lived, with symptoms returning within the week unless the dose was repeated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"This study brings together the best possible evidence indicating that nitrous oxide has the potential to provide swift and clinically significant short-term improvements in patients with severe depression," &lt;a href="https://www.birmingham.ac.uk/news/2025/clinical-use-of-nitrous-oxide-could-help-treat-depression-major-study-shows"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; clinical psychologist Kiranpreet Gill, from the University of Birmingham.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/newsletter?utm_source=promo_generic_health"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-642x273.jpg" alt="Subscribe to ScienceAlert's free fact-checked newsletter" class="alignnone wp-image-182810 size-medium" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-642x273.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-768x326.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-600x255.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final.jpg 850w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While more in-depth analysis is required, the researchers suggest the treatment's effects may be related to the way nitrous oxide calms down the glutamatergic system – a key component of the nervous system &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.neuropharm.2011.07.036"&gt;already linked&lt;/a&gt; to depression.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Laughing gas is also known to &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1177/0271678x18789273"&gt;increase blood flow&lt;/a&gt;, which may help cycle gases, waste, and nutrients through the brain. Once scientists understand more about why this works, treatments may become tailored to individual patients.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What is certain is that new treatments are urgently needed. The new study highlights the increasing burden of depression, which is now the leading cause of disability worldwide, affecting &lt;a href="https://www.who.int/news-room/fact-sheets/detail/depression"&gt;more than 300 million people&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Our analyses show that nitrous oxide could form part of a new generation of rapid-acting treatments for depression," &lt;a href="https://www.birmingham.ac.uk/news/2025/clinical-use-of-nitrous-oxide-could-help-treat-depression-major-study-shows"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; Gill.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Importantly, it provides a foundation for future trials to investigate repeated and carefully managed dosing strategies that can further determine how best to use this treatment in clinical practice for patients who don't respond to conventional interventions."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The research has been published in &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.ebiom.2025.106023"&gt;&lt;em&gt;eBioMedicine&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 21:02:07 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMinAFBVV95cUxNN1ZjTVdEWlRmc0JMeFhUTExnQ0pyaE92QWhpcS1QTEY4ZTlESmI3MWxVUmhnbWVzSjhOcWF1WnFLa2JrWW50dmNMQk5EdkNSSTdJMjlqaUpIU1dFUHBRTW1fcWxfQnJmQkVmaDR1OFpHSjhvdXNXNlBrQkJxWnJ0TEZKWTFMc0lrZ3RqaTZCcUpLLWV4Y2NWejNWTDM</guid></item><item><title>特朗普敦促制定新的疫苗接种时间表。以下是其他国家/地区的做法。-《华盛顿邮报》</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/world/2025/12/06/trump-rfk-international-vaccine-schedule/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="4FAZEERLFRBOFJZ5INUIZJW2KY" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;International differences in childhood immunization schedules have entered the political spotlight.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="6IM7S6RGWVGGNCUBIFUV625LJA" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;President Donald Trump on Friday evening directed a review of international practices, hours after a key vaccine advisory panel &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/health/2025/12/05/acip-childhood-immunization-schedule-hepatitis-b/" target="_blank"&gt;lifted its recommendation&lt;/a&gt; that all U.S. newborns receive hepatitis B vaccines at birth.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 20:35:08 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikwFBVV95cUxQM0FQN1ZCWHJxSXJGbkFlZlBZZDNyZGE4U3lBLVdDZTZJbml1a3ZHenlMTnd1Z2c5TFM5TXBZaDlNVTFkTFRtRE1lWjFiZ3phMVBBTnltbUl2MnIzM0FRZmt6aWl2WWJyVEt1d1IyaS1SMmd4dlhGeWtWT0hmdEQ3SWNFdDdFMEZiRkg3X1RrRWlsN1U</guid></item><item><title>对抗侵袭性白血病的“显著”药物效果- statnews.com</title><link>https://www.statnews.com/2025/12/06/ash-meeting-syndax-drug-for-acute-myeloid-leukemia/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content the-content wp-block-post-content is-layout-flow wp-block-post-content-is-layout-flow"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This is the online version of ASH in 30 Seconds, STAT’s report from the American Society of Hematology meeting. Sign up for the email version&lt;a href="https://www.statnews.com/signup/ash-in-30-seconds/"&gt; here&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We hear most of the country is freezing. We wouldn’t know. We’re in Orlando, Fla. where the temps are in the low 80s. Over the next four days, STAT reporters Damian Garde, Katherine MacPhail and Adam Feuerstein will break a sweat to bring you news, analysis and on-the-ground insights from the annual meeting of the American Society of Hematology.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thanks for joining us. Let’s get started.&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;div class="restricted-content-breaker article" aria-labelledby="restricted-story-heading" aria-describedby="restricted-story-description" checked&gt;
			&lt;div class="restricted-content-breaker-bar"&gt;
				&lt;p class="restricted-text"&gt;STAT+ Exclusive Story&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p class="restricted-login"&gt;Already have an account? &lt;a href="/login/" data-stat-login data-stat-paywall-cta="breaker login cta"&gt;Log in&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; 
			&lt;/div&gt;
			&lt;img class="restricted-content-breaker-bg" src="/wp-content/themes/stat/images/stat-plus-breaker-bg.png" alt="STAT+"&gt;
			&lt;div class="restricted-content-breaker-wrapper"&gt;
				&lt;span class="stat-paywall-archive"&gt;
					&lt;a href="https://www.statnews.com/stat-plus/"&gt;
						&lt;img class="stat-plus-logo" src="/wp-content/themes/stat/images/stat-plus-logo-white.svg" alt="STAT+"&gt;
					&lt;/a&gt;
				&lt;/span&gt;
				&lt;h2 id="restricted-story-heading"&gt;This article is exclusive to STAT+ subscribers&lt;/h2&gt;
				&lt;h3 id="restricted-story-description"&gt;Unlock this article — plus daily coverage and analysis of the biotech sector — by subscribing to STAT+.&lt;/h3&gt;
				&lt;p class="restricted-content-breaker-wrapper-cta mobile"&gt;Already have an account? &lt;a href="/login/" data-stat-login data-stat-paywall-cta="breaker login cta mobile"&gt;Log in&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;div class="restricted-content-breaker-cards"&gt;
					&lt;div class="slider-container" aria-label="Subscription plan toggle"&gt;
						&lt;button type="button" class="individual" aria-pressed="false"&gt;Individual plans&lt;/button&gt;
						&lt;p class="switch" role="switch" tabindex="0" aria-checked="false"&gt;
							&lt;button class="slider"&gt;&lt;/button&gt;
						&lt;/p&gt;
						&lt;button type="button" class="group" aria-pressed="false"&gt;Group plans&lt;/button&gt;
					&lt;/div&gt;
							

		
						&lt;/div&gt;
				&lt;a href="https://www.statnews.com/stat-plus/" class="stat-button view-all" data-stat-paywall-cta="breaker view all plans" aria-label="View All Plans"&gt;View All Plans&lt;/a&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
		
		&lt;div class="restricted-message-breaker"&gt;
			&lt;div class="restricted-content-wrapper"&gt;
								
								&lt;div class="restricted-content-message"&gt;
					&lt;p class="restricted-content-text"&gt;
						To read the rest of this story subscribe to STAT+.					&lt;/p&gt;
					&lt;a href="https://www.statnews.com/stat-plus/" class="stat-button restricted-button" data-stat-paywall-cta="breaker subscribe cta 1"&gt;Subscribe&lt;/a&gt;
									&lt;/div&gt;
								
							&lt;/div&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;

		&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>statnews.com</author><pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 20:32:16 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikAFBVV95cUxOZ1AtRnRGeXB4WmpmVFZwcHZ6czc2UjlmVW05TFEzRU9FTnNia0V4QmpLWWpvT2JiTV9BNmIyelBjQzVGTUtaMDl6ZFZzOERwYlBjanZERVFmWUlMTU52MGRBU0lzcUdzUVpCNWxFNnpyRElwRUtCLTE3YXNtRDZLR3RVMVZCNlNqYTlnMFJBbEM</guid></item><item><title>我们询问了家庭专业人士，您应该在冬季将加湿器放在哪里，我们做错了-云杉</title><link>https://www.thespruce.com/where-to-put-a-humidifier-in-winter-11859537</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="sc-page_1-0" class="comp sc-page mntl-sc-page mntl-block structured-content" data-sc-sticky-offset="138" data-sc-ad-label-height="11" data-sc-ad-track-spacing="100" data-sc-min-track-height="250" data-sc-max-track-height="600" data-sc-breakpoint="50em" data-sc-load-immediate="5" data-sc-content-positions="[1, 1, 1, 1250, 1, 1, 1, 1]" data-bind-scroll-on-start="true"&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-block_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block lifestyle-sc-block-callout--summary lifestyle-sc-block-callout mntl-sc-block-callout mntl-block theme-summary lifestyle-sc-block-callout--border" data-tracking-id="mntl-sc-block-callout" data-tracking-container="true"&gt;&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block-callout-heading_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block-callout-heading mntl-text-block"&gt;Key Points&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;div id="mntl-sc-block-callout-body_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block-callout-body mntl-text-block"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Avoid placing humidifiers near vents, beds, or windows to maximize effectiveness.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Maintain humidity levels between 30% and 50% to prevent damage and ensure comfort.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Clean humidifiers weekly and use distilled water to minimize bacteria and mineral buildup.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_2-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block lifestyle-sc-block-html mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; If your home's dry air is starting to take a toll, a &lt;a href="https://www.thespruce.com/best-mist-humidifiers-4066052" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;good humidifier&lt;/a&gt; can turn things around pretty quickly. But during the coldest season, you might be wondering where the best spot is for your humidifier in winter, and if you should be using one at all.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_3-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block lifestyle-sc-block-adslot mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block u-no-article-width-restriction"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_4-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block lifestyle-sc-block-html mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; To understand the dos and don'ts of winter humidifier use and the best position for your handy appliance, we spoke with an expert for the best advice. Here's what they had to say about where to place your humidifier, plus a few tips on getting the settings just right.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_5-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block lifestyle-sc-block-adslot mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block u-no-article-width-restriction"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="mntl-sc-block_6-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block lifestyle-sc-block-callout--meetourexpert lifestyle-sc-block-callout mntl-sc-block-callout mntl-block theme-meetourexpert lifestyle-sc-block-callout--border" data-tracking-id="mntl-sc-block-callout" data-tracking-container="true"&gt;&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block-callout-heading_2-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block-callout-heading mntl-text-block"&gt;Meet the Expert&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;div id="mntl-sc-block-callout-body_2-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block-callout-body mntl-text-block"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.twobrosfoundationrepair.com/about" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1" rel="nofollow"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Aaron Lipman&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; is the owner of Two Brothers Foundation Repair and a home expert with over 20 years of experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://comfortunion.com/about-us/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="2" rel="nofollow"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Asif Bux&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; is the owner and service manager at Comfort Union, an HVAC service company based in Canada.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-where-to-put-a-humidifier-in-winter"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_7-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block lifestyle-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading lifestyle-headings"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Where to Put a Humidifier in Winter &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_8-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block lifestyle-sc-block-html mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; As a general rule of thumb, home expert Aaron Lipman says to keep it away from vents and at least three feet from your bed.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_9-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block lifestyle-sc-block-adslot mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block u-no-article-width-restriction"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_10-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block lifestyle-sc-block-html mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; "The airflow from vents can disrupt the mist and reduce its effectiveness," he says, and having it too close to your bed can lead to "over-exposure to moisture, which could irritate breathing during sleep."
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_11-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block lifestyle-sc-block-adslot mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block u-no-article-width-restriction"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_12-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block lifestyle-sc-block-html mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; The goal of running a humidifier is balancing the ideal conditions for your home with the ideal conditions for feeling comfortable yourself, so &lt;a href="https://www.thespruce.com/room-humidifier-shopping-1908137" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;it depends on what room&lt;/a&gt; you'd like it in.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_13-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block lifestyle-sc-block-adslot mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block u-no-article-width-restriction"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_14-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block lifestyle-sc-block-html mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Asif Bux, owner of Comfort Union HVAC service company, adds that you should also keep portable humidifiers away from windows, since &lt;a href="https://www.thespruce.com/condensation-on-windows-8742997" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;the humidity can condense&lt;/a&gt; on cold surfaces or get blown away unevenly by airflow.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_15-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block lifestyle-sc-block-adslot mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block u-no-article-width-restriction"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_16-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block lifestyle-sc-block-html mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; If you have wooden floors or antique wooden furniture, a humidifier can help with shrinkage and cracking that gets exacerbated by dry air, but Lipman says you'll want to have a tray or waterproof mat beneath it. This will stop any warping and keep spills or condensation from causing other forms of damage.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_17-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block lifestyle-sc-block-adslot mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block u-no-article-width-restriction"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_18-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block lifestyle-sc-block-html mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Want more cleaning and organizing tips? Sign up for our free &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.thespruce.com/the-spruce-daily-inline-8610447" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;daily newsletter&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt; for the latest hacks, expert advice, and more!&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_19-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block lifestyle-sc-block-adslot mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block u-no-article-width-restriction"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-what-humidifier-settings-should-you-use"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_20-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block lifestyle-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading lifestyle-headings"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; What Humidifier Settings Should You Use? &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure id="mntl-sc-block_21-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block lifestyle-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image figure-landscape figure-high-res"&gt; 
&lt;figcaption id="mntl-figure-caption_1-0" class="comp mntl-figure-caption text-utility-100 figure-article-caption"&gt; &lt;span class="figure-article-caption-owner"&gt;Credit: &lt;p&gt;Carol Yepes / Getty Images&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_22-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block lifestyle-sc-block-html mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; The ideal percentage range for a humidifier in winter is between 30% and 50%. Much of it will depend on the climate where you live, the kind of home or apartment you have, and what your needs are.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_23-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block lifestyle-sc-block-adslot mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block u-no-article-width-restriction"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_24-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block lifestyle-sc-block-html mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.thespruce.com/low-humidity-in-house-5219369" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Lower than this&lt;/a&gt; and you might damage wood features and structures like beams and harm drywall, Lipman says. Bux also adds that you'll be more likely to notice the dry air and there will be more static electricity, too.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_25-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block lifestyle-sc-block-adslot mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block u-no-article-width-restriction"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_26-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block lifestyle-sc-block-html mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; A higher percentage can lead to mold and mildew. Both experts recommend having a hygrometer to help you keep an eye on levels. A built-in humidifier, however, is capable of managing humidity levels on its own.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_27-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block lifestyle-sc-block-adslot mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block u-no-article-width-restriction"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_29-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block lifestyle-sc-block-adslot mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block u-no-article-width-restriction"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-should-you-run-a-humidifier-during-winter"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_30-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block lifestyle-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading lifestyle-headings"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Should You Run a Humidifier During Winter? &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_31-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block lifestyle-sc-block-html mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Yes, a humidifier can be a super useful tool to make your home (and sinuses) more comfortable and keep the interiors damage-free during winter.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_32-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block lifestyle-sc-block-adslot mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block u-no-article-width-restriction"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_33-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block lifestyle-sc-block-html mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; "Running a humidifier can alleviate these issues and make your home feel warmer, even at slightly lower temperatures—helping you save on energy bills," says Bux.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_34-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block lifestyle-sc-block-adslot mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block u-no-article-width-restriction"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_35-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block lifestyle-sc-block-html mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Lipman agrees that a humidifier is extremely helpful, but notes that it should be approached with caution, too.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_36-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block lifestyle-sc-block-adslot mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block u-no-article-width-restriction"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_37-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block lifestyle-sc-block-html mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; "Over-humidification can cause condensation on windows, seepage into walls, and invite mold growth," he says.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_38-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block lifestyle-sc-block-adslot mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block u-no-article-width-restriction"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_39-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block lifestyle-sc-block-html mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Keeping a watchful eye and ensuring you have the right settings is key for a seamless experience.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_40-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block lifestyle-sc-block-adslot mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block u-no-article-width-restriction"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-other-tips-for-running-your-humidifier"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_41-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block lifestyle-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading lifestyle-headings"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Other Tips for Running Your Humidifier &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_42-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block lifestyle-sc-block-html mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Now that you're aware of the best settings and placement for your humidifier, here are a few other pointers for keeping your humidifier running smoothly and boosting your air quality throughout winter:
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_43-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block lifestyle-sc-block-adslot mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block u-no-article-width-restriction"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_44-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block lifestyle-sc-block-html mntl-sc-block-html"&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Think about the room. &lt;/strong&gt;If you're shopping for a new humidifier, think about the size of the room it'll be in as you'll want to buy a humidifier with the right capacity.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Clean it regularly. &lt;/strong&gt;Lipman notes it's important to &lt;a href="https://www.thespruce.com/how-to-clean-a-humidifier-8746032" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;regularly clean your humidifier&lt;/a&gt; to cut down on bacteria buildup. Aim to do so every week.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Maintain cleanliness. &lt;/strong&gt;Bux says you should use distilled or filtered water in portable humidifiers "to reduce mineral buildup and white dust."&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Consider other air gadgets. &lt;/strong&gt;Think about getting an &lt;a href="https://www.thespruce.com/best-air-purifiers-4062977" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;air purifier&lt;/a&gt; for your home to work in tandem with a humidifier; these can clear out bacteria, viruses, mold, and dust, which often feel more prevalent during winter.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Anticipate maintenance on whole-house humidifiers. &lt;/strong&gt;If you have a whole-home humidifier, Bux recommends scheduling in annual maintenance with your technician to ensure everything is working properly. It's best to do so before the times of year when you'll need it most.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Spruce</author><pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 20:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiekFVX3lxTE0zT2kyaDhva29WOTRST21RTGdWb3lqV3p0M1ZOWElhcGxZZmFvTnlRaVppUjRUckpETF9IOUo1Tnp0eHBoVjF1WDZSSURqek0wNjBtMlVkNm5na2ZFOG93OXJqVkVEZjJkaWgyM0NIbWxNazI1Tk1PaGNB</guid></item><item><title>新研究确定了每天服用多种维生素的实际受益者- SciTechDaily</title><link>https://scitechdaily.com/new-research-identifies-who-actually-benefits-from-daily-multivitamins/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>SciTechDaily</author><pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 19:41:44 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMinAFBVV95cUxOQlh1U0FLU3loRzJMOHJYMzAyRGQzaWU1eXJWdmYySXpnMHZqOFgtclp6a3B2dHY4U09aeVVLNVlfTmJPM1BoNjQ2Rm4zaEx1TGNiX0xLT05RY0pQM1dZN2VnRmo3OW9hOFlPNUl5eVliRUFUVkY5QzV4bmwyUzNGenAyaTIwWGhMbzlaZU5BYXBxQkpNaHcxTVZuY1g</guid></item><item><title>7种富含镁的食物有助于改善您的睡眠和情绪- GQ</title><link>https://www.gq.com/story/7-magnesium-rich-foods-to-help-improve-your-sleep-and-your-mood-1</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="body__inner-container"&gt;&lt;p&gt;On top of supporting GABA production, Dryden says that magnesium helps convert the amino acid tryptophan into serotonin, which then gets converted into melatonin, a hormone that’s crucial for sleep because it signals to the body that it’s nighttime and helps regulate the body’s internal clock (known as circadian rhythm).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Even though magnesium doesn’t directly produce melatonin, it’s really important in helping that process get done and if we don’t get enough magnesium, that process might not happen as efficiently,” Dryden says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dryden says that research has shown that magnesium can help improve sleep efficiency, reducing the time it takes to fall asleep and decreasing the number of wake-up times throughout the night. A &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC8996025/"&gt;2021 study published in &lt;em&gt;Sleep&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; taking into account roughly 4,000 people backs this up, showing that participants who supplemented with magnesium experienced higher quality sleep than participants who didn’t supplement with magnesium.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;7 magnesium-rich foods worth adding to your diet&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;As mentioned earlier, it’s best to get magnesium through diet versus supplements because you’ll be consuming other important nutrients at the same time. The magnesium-rich foods included here all have other nutrients that either support sleep, mood, or both.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p role="heading" aria-level="3" class="heading-h3"&gt;1. Pumpkin seeds&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pumpkin seeds top both Pratt and Dryden’s lists for the best magnesium-rich foods for better mood and sleep. &lt;a href="https://ods.od.nih.gov/factsheets/Magnesium-HealthProfessional/"&gt;It has more magnesium than any other food&lt;/a&gt;, with 156 milligrams per serving, or 37% of the recommended daily value. “Pumpkin seeds also contain tryptophan, which is an amino acid that’s important for relaxation and sleep,” Dryden says. If you don’t plan on carving any pumpkins this fall, pumpkin seeds are easy to find at most grocery stores. They make a nice, crunchy topper for salads, oatmeal, or yogurt.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p role="heading" aria-level="3" class="heading-h3"&gt;2. Chia seeds&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another seed that’s high in magnesium is chia seeds. “Two tablespoons of chia seeds is going to give you a pretty decent amount of magnesium,” Dryden says. Besides magnesium, she says that these tiny seeds are also high in omega-3 fatty acids, which are important for brain function and decreasing inflammation—both important for avoiding depression and anxiety.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p role="heading" aria-level="3" class="heading-h3"&gt;3. Leafy greens&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One magnesium-rich food Kriegler recommends is leafy greens because it’s super versatile and high in many other important nutrients, including &lt;a href="https://www.gq.com/story/high-fiber-diet-2"&gt;fiber&lt;/a&gt;. You probably already know how important fiber is for gut health. Due to the strong connection between &lt;a href="https://www.gq.com/story/gut-health"&gt;gut health and brain health&lt;/a&gt;, a thriving microbiome is crucial for mood regulation. A &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/36692989/"&gt;2023 scientific article published in &lt;em&gt;Nutritional Neuroscience&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; highlights a connection between a high-fiber diet and a lower risk of depression.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>GQ</author><pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 18:39:05 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilAFBVV95cUxQRFM1ZU5WYy1vS2E3SEswNDVPbnB2Z2dzZ2xZLTBXN3VueW9vaFAxVEI1QXB4N3NNS2VBb3Q2Nl9QUVhkb3oxN242LW03cGdLQXM1eEJMekhoVEpFcU1jR256SXJKV2ZnQ1B6RDZNdTJfTVdtdUhGN2JzbHdMdHNyTlFMSmJpTzdaSEljZE5FRUdjanNn</guid></item><item><title>健康专家推荐的6种多吃水果以改善肾脏健康- EatingWell</title><link>https://www.eatingwell.com/best-fruits-for-kidney-health-11863363</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-page_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-page mntl-block structured-content" data-sc-sticky-offset="90" data-sc-ad-label-height="24" data-sc-ad-track-spacing="100" data-sc-min-track-height="250" data-sc-max-track-height="600" data-sc-breakpoint="50em" data-sc-load-immediate="4" data-sc-content-positions="[1, 1250, 1550, 1950, 2350, 2750, 3150, 3550, 3950]" data-bind-scroll-on-start="true"&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-block_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-callout--summary mntl-sc-block-universal-callout--tips mntl-sc-block-universal-callout theme-summary callout--bordered" data-text="Key Points" data-tracking-id="mntl-sc-block-callout" data-tracking-container="true"&gt;
&lt;div class="mntl-sc-block-universal-callout__body"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Research shows that eating more fruit is linked to a lower risk of kidney disease.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Red grapes, apples, berries, lemons and pineapple are lower in potassium for kidney health.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Simple strategies like fruit salads and smoothies make it easy to add these fruits to your daily routine.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_2-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Your kidneys work hard every day to filter waste and support overall health. These bean-shaped organs perform the crucial task of removing toxins, balancing fluids and maintaining the right levels of essential nutrients in your body.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="1"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_3-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_4-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; And the foods you eat can make a big difference when it comes to taking care of your kidneys. Fruits, in particular, offer a powerful combination of vitamins, minerals, antioxidants and fiber that help protect these vital organs. "A study looked at data from over 98,000 participants and found that eating more fruit was associated with a 6 to 8% lower risk of developing kidney disease," says &lt;a href="https://www.plantpoweredkidneys.com/meet-jen/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Jen Hernandez, RD&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="2"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_5-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_6-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; But not all fruits are created equal when it comes to kidney health. Here are the ones experts say offer the most benefit—and easy ways to enjoy them.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_7-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-1-red-grapes"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_8-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; 1. Red Grapes &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_9-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Red grapes pack a kidney-friendly punch thanks to a special plant compound. "Red grapes contain the phytochemical resveratrol, which supports kidney health," says &lt;a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/erin-hetrick-ms-rd-ldn-60710031/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Erin Hetrick, M.S., RD, LDN&lt;/a&gt;. Resveratrol is a powerful antioxidant that helps protect cells from damage and &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/80991/10-ways-to-reduce-inflammation/" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;reduce inflammation&lt;/a&gt; throughout the body, including in the kidneys.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="3"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; These bite-sized fruits are also low in potassium compared to many other fruits, making them a smart choice for kidney health. Enjoy them fresh as a snack, freeze them for a cool treat or toss them into salads for a burst of sweetness. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_10-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_12-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_14-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-2-apples"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_15-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; 2. Apples &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_16-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; An &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/health-benefits-of-apples-11810716" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;apple a day&lt;/a&gt; might do more than keep the doctor away—it could help your kidneys, too. "Apples have anti-inflammatory properties and soluble fiber, which can help lower blood cholesterol and glucose levels," says Hetrick.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="4"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; “Both of these benefits are vital for diabetic and hypertensive kidney disease,” says &lt;a href="https://sportsnephrology.com/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="2" rel="nofollow"&gt;Raeeda Gheewala, M.D&lt;/a&gt;. High blood pressure and diabetes are two of the leading causes of kidney disease, so managing these conditions through diet can have a protective effect on kidney function.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="5"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; The soluble fiber in apples also supports digestive health and helps you feel full longer. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_17-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-3-blueberries"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_18-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; 3. Blueberries &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_19-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; These tiny berries deliver a big impact when it comes to kidney protection. "Blueberries are high in anthocyanins and vitamin C, which offer strong antioxidant and anti-inflammatory benefits," says Gheewala. Anthocyanins are the compounds that give blueberries their deep blue color, and they work to combat oxidative stress and inflammation that can damage kidney cells over time. "Research has shown that people who consumed more fruits like berries and apples had a 16% lower risk of developing chronic kidney disease thanks to the flavonoids from these fruits," says Hernandez.&lt;span data-cite="6" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Whether fresh or frozen, blueberries are an easy addition to breakfast bowls, yogurt or smoothies.&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_20-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-4-lemons"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_21-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; 4. Lemons  &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_22-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; These tart citrus fruits offer unique benefits for kidney health, particularly when it comes to &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/best-foods-to-eat-to-prevent-kidney-stones-11705389" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;preventing kidney stones&lt;/a&gt;. "These citrus fruits provide citrate, which can reduce kidney stone formation and enhance hydration," says Gheewala. Citric acid may help inhibit the formation of calcium oxalate stones.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="7"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Plus, adding lemon to your water makes staying hydrated more enjoyable, and proper hydration is one of the most important things you can do for your kidneys. The &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/2052728/6-foods-with-more-vitamin-c-than-an-orange/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;vitamin C&lt;/a&gt; in lemons (and limes!) also provides antioxidant protection.&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_23-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-5-pineapple"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_24-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; 5. Pineapple &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_25-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; This tropical fruit brings both flavor and function to a kidney-friendly diet. "Pineapple is a kidney-friendly fruit that I often recommend. It's rich in vitamin C, manganese, dietary fiber and contains anti-inflammatory and antioxidant phytochemicals that support kidney health," says Hernandez. Pineapple also contains bromelain, an enzyme with anti-inflammatory properties.&lt;span data-cite="8" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Like red grapes, pineapple is lower in potassium than many other fruits, which can be important for people monitoring their potassium intake. Its natural sweetness makes it a satisfying option for dessert or snacks.&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_26-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-6-raspberries"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_27-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; 6. Raspberries &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_28-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Don't let their small size fool you—raspberries are fiber powerhouses. "They are considered one of the highest fiber fruits with 8 grams of fiber per 1 cup serving!&lt;span data-cite="9" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Fiber is important in regulating blood sugars and promoting regularity. Blood sugar stabilization is crucial in preserving kidney function for those patients with diabetes," says &lt;a href="https://www.michigankidney.com/about-us/dietitian/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1" rel="nofollow"&gt;Alex Evink, M.S., RD&lt;/a&gt;. Diabetes is a major risk factor for kidney disease, so keeping blood sugar levels stable through high-fiber foods like raspberries can help protect kidney function over time.&lt;span data-cite="10" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; These berries also provide vitamin C, manganese and antioxidants that fight inflammation. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_29-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-tips-to-enjoy-them"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_30-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Tips to Enjoy Them &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_31-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Ready to boost your kidney health with these fruits? Here are expert-approved ways to make them part of your daily routine:
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_32-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_33-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mix and match:&lt;/strong&gt; "A fruit salad or smoothie is a great way to incorporate a variety of fruits together to be a nutritionally dense superfood," says Hetrick. Combine several of the fruits above for maximum benefit.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Season wisely:&lt;/strong&gt; "Add lemon or lime juice to meals to enhance flavor instead of added salt," says Gheewala. This simple swap supports kidney health while adding brightness to everything from fish to vegetables.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Prep for success:&lt;/strong&gt; "Buy fresh fruit in season for the cheapest and best quality options. Wash with water as soon as you get home and chop, placing in clear containers front-and-center of your fridge so you always see it as a quick option when looking for a snack," says Hernandez.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bake with fruit:&lt;/strong&gt; "Add applesauce to muffins or baked goods," says Evink. This adds natural sweetness and moisture while reducing the need for added sugar and fat.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Stock the freezer:&lt;/strong&gt; "Don't forget that frozen fruit is picked at its peak ripeness and can frequently be a more affordable option that doesn't go bad like its fresh counterparts," says Hernandez. Frozen berries are perfect for smoothies and require zero prep work.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_34-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_36-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-when-to-talk-to-a-health-care-provider"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_37-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; When to Talk to a Health Care Provider &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_38-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; While these fruits offer benefits for kidney health, it's important to recognize that individual needs can vary, especially for people with existing kidney disease. "If someone has a more advanced stage of chronic kidney disease, they may need to limit potassium intake. Potassium is a standard lab test, and patients should speak to their physician about their levels," says Hetrick.&lt;span data-cite="11" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_39-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_40-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; "Anyone with CKD, high potassium, or on dialysis—or who takes blood pressure or potassium-altering medications—should consult a nephrologist or renal dietitian before major dietary changes," says Gheewala. A registered dietitian who specializes in kidney health can help you create a personalized eating plan that supports your specific needs while still including delicious, nourishing foods.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_41-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-our-expert-take"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_42-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Our Expert Take &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_43-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Your kidneys work around the clock to keep your body healthy, and the fruits you eat can support this vital function. Red grapes, apples, blueberries, lemons and limes, pineapple and raspberries all offer unique compounds—from resveratrol and fiber to antioxidants—that protect kidney health and reduce the risk of kidney disease. Research shows that people who eat more fruit have a lower risk of developing kidney problems, making these colorful foods a smart addition to your daily routine. Simple strategies like keeping washed fruit visible in your fridge, adding lemon juice to meals and choosing frozen options can make it easy to enjoy these kidney-friendly picks every day. Just remember that if you have existing kidney disease or take certain medications, working with a health care provider ensures your diet supports your individual needs.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>EatingWell</author><pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 18:07:44 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMic0FVX3lxTFAzcXdoaGhmenBRUjJGMWt6VnFRb1RFVTEzUG9ydloyTTk2dDI4TnMzeFF0X0FBM05jcTlWbG9jUG94akpHTUVLbTFyT1U3dVk2Qmd4Uk1wQ2N0cDJKblFuU3g3emFCX1NEcXNNWFNqeEtjek0</guid></item><item><title>最近的一项研究发现， 40岁以上的人需要认真对待2个新的痴呆风险因素- BuzzFeed</title><link>https://www.buzzfeed.com/jillianwilson/dementia-research-new-risk-factors-cholesterol-vision</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="subbuzz buzz-width--standard__subbuzz buzz-type--long__subbuzz subbuzz-text
  subbuzz-index-14
  
  
  
  
  " data-module="subbuzz-text"&gt;
  
  &lt;p id="139813421" class="subbuzz-anchor"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“The research is also showing that if you have two groups of individuals, someone who has comorbid metabolic diseases such as hypertension, high cholesterol, diabetes, versus somebody who doesn’t, and both of these individuals have dementia, the rates of progression of dementia in somebody who doesn’t have metabolic risk factors tend to be slower,” explained Fesharaki-Zadeh.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s never too late to make changes and corrections, he noted, whether you’re a young, seemingly healthy person, in your 80s or 90s, or someone who has already been diagnosed with dementia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Our brains are highly malleable, Fesharaki-Zadeh said. So if you decide to make healthy lifestyle changes at any point, your brain will respond and be healthier for it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This article originally appeared on&lt;/em&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/entry/dementia-research-new-risk-factors-goog_l_69209634e4b06c13afa4a363" target="_blank" data-skimlinks-tracking="7994329"&gt;&lt;em&gt;HuffPost.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BuzzFeed</author><pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 16:35:02 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilwFBVV95cUxNeDIwdm1OSXZtM1Nxdy05VEJ1TjBLSHVFd3lKV1lVZkQwZUxEZkpSbVBTcDBMWjRaeFJsb3BXLWdOX2ZlUXhzMVo5dmM1c1p2Tk83TzNaVi1OZEw0VHZKbzBPc09maW9Tc0tZTGhzby1aMW1uUGkyclI4c25BaldUSWxYOGg5NVVFcERxc2RkY0dTeUhsXzFv</guid></item><item><title>最近的一项研究发现， 40岁以上的人需要认真对待2个新的痴呆风险因素- BuzzFeed</title><link>https://www.buzzfeed.com/jillianwilson/dementia-research-new-risk-factors-cholesterol-vision?origin=web-hf</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="subbuzz buzz-width--standard__subbuzz buzz-type--long__subbuzz subbuzz-text
  subbuzz-index-14
  
  
  
  
  " data-module="subbuzz-text"&gt;
  
  &lt;p id="139813421" class="subbuzz-anchor"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“The research is also showing that if you have two groups of individuals, someone who has comorbid metabolic diseases such as hypertension, high cholesterol, diabetes, versus somebody who doesn’t, and both of these individuals have dementia, the rates of progression of dementia in somebody who doesn’t have metabolic risk factors tend to be slower,” explained Fesharaki-Zadeh.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s never too late to make changes and corrections, he noted, whether you’re a young, seemingly healthy person, in your 80s or 90s, or someone who has already been diagnosed with dementia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Our brains are highly malleable, Fesharaki-Zadeh said. So if you decide to make healthy lifestyle changes at any point, your brain will respond and be healthier for it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This article originally appeared on&lt;/em&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/entry/dementia-research-new-risk-factors-goog_l_69209634e4b06c13afa4a363" target="_blank" data-skimlinks-tracking="7994329"&gt;&lt;em&gt;HuffPost.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BuzzFeed</author><pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 16:35:02 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiqgFBVV95cUxPLUZmZnNGRFVMdWRnT0dmeUV3OVhONUkzdXVYSm5OQlB4UHROT3lsT3JfZm51LUlxWDNMaGNPdTlaV2Zhc1BJMEJQOHpyM09xYUs1NERRVW15VmFXQzhVQ1hnMDBZOXdNU05WUmI0TXlzWndadUNQU3MtYkJMUnBQbXdCbkVxYjlLUFk0OGFGS2QwbVEwdGpiSWpqMHdpSEJTd0NKcHRQZUZsQQ</guid></item><item><title>天然激素解锁隐藏的脂肪燃烧开关- ScienceDaily</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/12/251205054739.htm</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p id="first" class="lead"&gt;Studies in mice have shown that a hormone produced in the intestine can send signals to the brain and influence how much energy the body uses. This hormone, called FGF19 (fibroblast growth factor 19), activates processes that help the body spend more energy, use stored fat as fuel, and improve weight control and blood glucose levels in obese animals.&lt;/p&gt;

						&lt;div id="text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Researchers linked these effects to the action of FGF19 in the hypothalamus, a key brain region that receives information from the rest of the body and the environment to coordinate energy metabolism. They found that when FGF19 signals in the hypothalamus, it boosts the activity of thermogenic adipocytes (i.e., fat cells that burn energy to produce heat), which are specialized fat cells that help the body generate heat instead of storing calories.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;New Paths for Obesity and Diabetes Treatments&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Because of these findings, the scientists believe that FGF19 could inspire new medications for obesity, diabetes, and other metabolic conditions. The idea is to develop compounds that imitate the behavior of natural substances in the body, mimicking the action of endogenous compounds (i.e. those produced by the body itself).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This strategy resembles the way some of the latest diabetes and obesity drugs work. Ozempic, for example, contains semaglutide, an ingredient that activates receptors mimicking the hormone GLP-1. By doing so, it sends satiety signals to the brain and helps patients feel full with less food.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;According to the study, FGF19 did more than change appetite or fat storage. The hormone also lowered peripheral inflammation and improved the animals' tolerance to cold. When the researchers blocked the sympathetic nervous system, however, these benefits disappeared. In further experiments, they observed that exposure to cold increased the expression of FGF19 receptors in the hypothalamus. Because the hypothalamus is crucial for maintaining body temperature, these results suggest that FGF19 may help the body adapt by coordinating energy balance and thermoregulation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;FGF19, Thermogenesis, and Brain Control of Energy&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"FGF19 had already been linked to a reduction in food intake. Our work broke new ground by showing that it also plays an important role by acting on the hypothalamus and stimulating an increase in energy expenditure in white and brown adipose tissue. In other words, in addition to controlling appetite, it stimulates thermogenesis. So, in terms of therapy associated with obesity, it'd make a lot of sense," explains Professor Helena Cristina de Lima Barbosa, from the Obesity and Comorbidities Research Center (OCRC) at the State University of Campinas (UNICAMP).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="insertion_middle"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The OCRC is a Research, Innovation, and Dissemination Center (RIDC) of FAPESP, which also funded the project through grants to doctoral student Lucas Zangerolamo, the first author of the study, supervised by Barbosa.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The work has been described in detail in an article published in the American Journal of Physiology -- Endocrinology and Metabolism, where it was highlighted as a Top Article in May.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Global Obesity Crisis and Urgent Health Targets&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The World Atlas of Obesity 2025 warns that, if current trends continue, global health goals for this year will not be met. These targets include halting the rise in diabetes and obesity and cutting premature deaths from cardiovascular disease, chronic respiratory disease, and cancer by 25%, using 2010 as the reference year.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Atlas estimates that more than 1 billion people worldwide are currently living with obesity. If effective actions are not put in place, this number could surpass 1.5 billion by 2030. Obesity is already associated with about 1.6 million premature deaths each year from non-communicable diseases.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In Brazil, around 31% of the population has obesity. In addition, between 40% and 50% of adults do not reach the recommended levels of physical activity in terms of frequency or intensity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="insertion_bottom"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Where FGF19 Comes From and How It Works&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;FGF19, which is involved in the control of energy metabolism, is mainly produced in the small intestine. In the liver, it regulates the production of bile acids and also influences the synthesis of glucose and fats. While its primary roles in the liver have been widely explored in scientific literature, its effects in the brain have received much less attention.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"In the lab, we work with bile acids, which are also the subject of my master's degree, and they regulate the release of FGF-19. Our initial studies led us down this path," Zangerolamo told Agência FAPESP.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At eight weeks of age, the mice used in the study were randomly assigned to two groups. One group received a standard diet (control) and the other was fed a high-fat diet to induce obesity. The researchers then administered FGF19 directly into the brains of the obese animals. All mice were kept in carefully controlled conditions of temperature, lighting, and access to water.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the article, the scientists report that central FGF19 signaling improved energy homeostasis. It did this by boosting the activity of the sympathetic nervous system and stimulating thermogenesis in adipose tissue, leading the tissue to consume more energy in the form of heat.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"The brain plays an extremely important role in controlling the body's adiposity. At the same time as it receives information from peripheral tissues, it triggers commands. These commands, apparently using the sympathetic nervous system, seem to be an interesting way of thinking about energy expenditure," adds Barbosa.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Digging Deeper Into Brain Cells and FGF19 Receptors&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To better understand which brain cells respond to FGF19, the authors compiled and examined public scRNA-seq data from several studies of the hypothalamus. This method makes it possible to sequence RNA from individual cells, revealing which genes are active in each cell type. In total, the team evaluated transcription from more than 50,000 single cells to identify hypothalamic cell populations that express FGF19 receptors.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The researchers note that a key question now is how to encourage the body to produce more FGF19 on its own. They are also working to connect these findings with what is already known about the neural circuits that regulate eating behavior.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"We want to broaden this understanding. We're studying the hypothalamus to evaluate the inflammation commonly observed when a high-fat diet is administered and whether FGF19 plays a role in this area," says Zangerolamo, who did part of the work during an internship at the Joslin Diabetes Center at Harvard Medical School with Professor Yu-Hua Tseng, who is also an author of the article.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

					&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceDaily</author><pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 15:33:34 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMib0FVX3lxTE9TZlFGUUVHUUg4WUxUYkNFdUI1aTRkYmcwMzFFQUptcG1Sc0h4a0JUSEdNQTdqNllPdFZkOXhjYzBQcGJ6Vm94TDhEQVVqT0t6V1puTzY4bkY4V0R1LTBHTEd1RDZxcWZmWkFGeDJCRQ</guid></item><item><title>患有狂犬病的器官捐赠者移植后肾脏受者死亡-《纽约时报》</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/12/06/health/rabies-death-skunk-kidney-transplant.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The New York Times</author><pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 14:37:09 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiwFBVV95cUxNQzZrR3dBTGhlRzdHTlhETUxUYnlCNjlHY1RtSlZTcnJ1OFlXaVdKQTVjVk9oVld3TXRIUlhsMFBPMVBJSldxTHcwc2VmcC0wbFh3Z0JwY3VSVXd1bXY0ZTdKc2R3N2J3OGdBNU85N1pIM1FwT0VabndORjJDcHBuUnB1X0lyam82YUtB</guid></item><item><title>这种疾病无法治愈，它突然再次迅速蔓延- AOL.com</title><link>https://www.aol.com/disease-no-cure-suddenly-spreading-151215789.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="caas-body"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Measles cases are surging worldwide, with 11 million infections reported last year alone. The World Health Organization says the once-achievable goal of eliminating measles is now far from reach.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The WHO cites vaccination levels that are too low to protect many parts of the world. Health experts say 95% of people in a region must be vaccinated to achieve herd immunity and stop the spread.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Without sustained attention, hard-fought gains can easily be lost," the WHO said. "Where children are unvaccinated, outbreaks occur. Based on current trends of measles vaccination coverage and incidence, the WHO Strategic Advisory Group of Experts on Immunization (SAGE) concluded that measles elimination is under threat, as the disease resurged in numerous countries that achieved, or were close to achieving, elimination."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;RELATED STORY | &lt;/b&gt;&lt;a class="link rapid-noclick-resp" href="https://www.scrippsnews.com/health/more-than-150-unvaccinated-students-quarantined-in-south-carolina-measles-outbreak" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:More than 150 unvaccinated students quarantined in South Carolina measles outbreak;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas"&gt;&lt;b&gt;More than 150 unvaccinated students quarantined in South Carolina measles outbreak&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Health officials continue to advocate for the MMR vaccine as the most effective means to combat the deadly and highly contagious virus. The shots are reported to be 97% effective, preventing illness and further spread of the disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Children are routinely vaccinated for measles at 12 to 15 months and again at 4 to 6 years of age — before going to kindergarten — but children as young as 6 months old can receive the measles vaccine if they are at risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to the CDC, measles causes the following symptoms:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The World Health Organization says that herd immunity against measles can be reached when a community achieves a 95% vaccination rate. U.S. health officials estimate that 92.7% of kindergarten students were vaccinated last school year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Measles cases in the United States have surged to a 33-year high, with over 1,798 confirmed infections this year, according to data released Wednesday from the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The cases have resulted in the deaths of at least three people and have left 212 hospitalized. An alarming 92% of the cases were found in unvaccinated individuals, according to the &lt;a class="link rapid-noclick-resp" href="https://www.cdc.gov/measles/data-research/index.html" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Centers for Disease Control and Prevention.;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas"&gt;Centers for Disease Control and Prevention.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>AOL.com</author><pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 14:26:08 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMieEFVX3lxTE4ySnpwU0ZEOUVaRHQxZG5sZUlURWNrNjM1b2Q5QWY3bzFQdll2M2pGdmtURjJ1SjdwSTdOQ0x5OGFyUF9LeDRvNXJmYzlwN1VBZWtBNk1kNmVaaEVTOUlLT3dwV2pVb3dLOTJWQVh5YnB5eVdrV0NyVw</guid></item><item><title>研究发现，耳鸣会触发身体的“战斗或逃跑”反应- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/tinnitus-triggers-your-bodys-fight-or-flight-response-study-finds</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Chronic tinnitus may increase stress levels by keeping the body that much closer to a fight-or-flight response to sound, a new study suggests.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;By carefully studying the facial expressions of people with &lt;span&gt;and without tinnitus&lt;/span&gt;, scientists have found a pattern of altered involuntary facial movements and pupil dilation associated with distress and threat assessment in those with the condition.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Moreover, by cataloguing the facial movements of their tinnitus participants, the team of researchers, led by neuroscientist Daniel Polley of Mass General Brigham in the US, was even able to predict the severity of the ear-ringing condition.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Related: &lt;/b&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/tinnitus-is-somehow-linked-to-a-crucial-bodily-function"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Tinnitus Is Somehow Linked to a Crucial Bodily Function&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The results suggest that people with debilitating chronic tinnitus experience heightened vigilance and react to normal, everyday sounds as though they were threats.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"For the first time," &lt;a href="https://www.massgeneralbrigham.org/en/about/newsroom/press-releases/new-tinnitus-facial-eye-biomarkers-could-unlock-testing-treatments"&gt;Polley says&lt;/a&gt;, "we directly observed a signature of tinnitus severity. When we began this study, we didn't know if sounds would elicit facial movements; so, to discover that these movements not only occur, but can provide the most informative measure to date of tinnitus distress, is quite surprising."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chronic tinnitus is a condition in which a constant buzzing, clicking, or high-pitched ringing can be heard in one or both ears (but not by anyone else).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;No one knows what causes it, and it currently has no objective clinical biomarkers, since tinnitus is a purely subjective experience, like migraine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Imagine if  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/cancer" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73077" data-postid="183755" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;cancer&lt;/a&gt; severity were determined by giving patients a questionnaire – this is the state of affairs for some common neurological disorders like tinnitus," &lt;a href="https://www.massgeneralbrigham.org/en/about/newsroom/press-releases/new-tinnitus-facial-eye-biomarkers-could-unlock-testing-treatments"&gt;Polley says&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This makes it &lt;a href="https://www.mayoclinic.org/diseases-conditions/tinnitus/diagnosis-treatment/drc-20350162"&gt;difficult to diagnose&lt;/a&gt; and even more challenging to track over time. There is also no known cure, although some sufferers report symptom reductions or&lt;span&gt; better symptom management&lt;/span&gt; after trying &lt;a href="https://www.healthdirect.gov.au/tinnitus"&gt;sound therapy&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.health.harvard.edu/blog/what-is-cognitive-behavioral-therapy-202406053047"&gt;cognitive behavioral therapy&lt;/a&gt;, or &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1002/14651858.CD007330"&gt;tinnitus retraining therapy&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.health.harvard.edu/newsletter_article/tinnitus-ringing-in-the-ears-and-what-to-do-about-it"&gt;Almost everyone&lt;/a&gt; will experience tinnitus at some point in their lives, but for most people, it will be temporary.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chronic tinnitus is when the condition lasts for at least six months, and it affects more than &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1001/jamaneurol.2022.2189"&gt;120 million people around the world&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It's also notoriously &lt;a href="https://my.clevelandclinic.org/health/symptoms/14164-tinnitus"&gt;frustrating for patients&lt;/a&gt;, and treatment options are inconsistent, which can leave some people feeling dismissed or unsupported in clinical settings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In some cases, it's severe enough to disrupt sleep and interfere with daily activities, with &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0um3YAzHJzA"&gt;strong links to depression and anxiety&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Any clue that can help doctors understand the condition may bring us closer to knowing its causes, which could then help with the development of new, more effective treatments.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Human faces undergo a phenomenon known as &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Microexpression"&gt;microexpressions&lt;/a&gt;: vanishingly brief, involuntary twitches that can reveal strong emotions, for example.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Recently, scientists have also made headway in using facial cues to diagnose the severity of conditions that lack clear clinical biomarkers, such as &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/severe-melancholia-depression-can-be-diagnosed-by-facial-expression"&gt;severe depression&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Polley and his team adopted a similar approach for studying tinnitus. They recruited 97 study participants – 47 with tinnitus or sound sensitivity, and 50 without – and made them listen to a range of sounds from a &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.3758/s13428-018-1027-6"&gt;previously compiled database&lt;/a&gt; of emotionally evocative audio recordings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These sounds all have assigned associations, from positive sounds such as soft music and laughter, through more neutral sounds such as background chatter, rustling paper, and kitchen sounds, to unpleasant sounds such as &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.3758/s13428-021-01643-0"&gt;screeching metal&lt;/a&gt;, sirens, and alarms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/tinnitus-could-be-our-brains-way-of-coping-with-nerve-damage"&gt;Tinnitus Could Be Our Brain's Way of Coping With Nerve Damage&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While listening to these sounds, each participant had their facial expressions tracked, and their eyes recorded to look for signs of pupil dilation as the body shifts into threat assessment mode. Then, AI software was used to tease out tiny changes in facial expression that human eyes might miss.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The control group of tinnitus-free participants tended to show microexpressions consistent with the emotional association of each sound: a slight smile for pleasant sounds, and a slight frown for unpleasant sounds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, the tinnitus participants showed markedly reduced facial changes compared to the control group, regardless of how pleasant or unpleasant the sound was. Meanwhile, their pupils dilated extra wide for all sounds – again, no matter the category. The pupils of the control group dilated only for the most unpleasant, loudest sounds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Each of these markers individually – the lack of facial expression and the exaggerated pupil response – enabled the scientists to gauge not just &lt;i&gt;whether&lt;/i&gt; or not a participant had tinnitus, but how severely they were impacted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/newsletter?utm_source=promo_generic_health"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-642x273.jpg" alt="Subscribe to ScienceAlert's free fact-checked newsletter" class="alignnone wp-image-182810 size-medium" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-642x273.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-768x326.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-600x255.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final.jpg 850w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A popular idea in tinnitus research is that, in response to hearing loss, the brain &lt;a href="https://www.health.harvard.edu/newsletter_article/tinnitus-ringing-in-the-ears-and-what-to-do-about-it"&gt;'turns up' its auditory pathways to compensate&lt;/a&gt; (although not all cases of tinnitus are associated with hearing loss).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, this proposed mechanism cannot predict the severity of the condition, suggesting it may be only part of the overall picture.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chronic tinnitus is likely to be a complex condition, with a wide range of causes and presentations. The work of Polley and his team fills in some of the blanks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"These biomarkers get to the root of the distress," &lt;a href="https://www.massgeneralbrigham.org/en/about/newsroom/press-releases/new-tinnitus-facial-eye-biomarkers-could-unlock-testing-treatments"&gt;Polley says&lt;/a&gt;. "While imaging might show hyperactive brain regions in tinnitus patients, these biomarkers reveal body-wide threat evaluation systems that are operating outside of their normal range, leading to the distressful symptoms they experience."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The research was published in &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1126/scitranslmed.adp1934"&gt;&lt;i&gt;Science Translational Medicine&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 14:01:52 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimgFBVV95cUxQQXhHcV9xSnlhVVZnaU9TU0YtUlF3MnVweWZTQkhWc3c1dFY4SEhueUcwWFNORW16cUxweG5paDMzaHR2NjV6Ym1ZVTgtRDQ0a0s0OEdKUnY5V3ZqUTNGZDJpUHJTZ0F2WDFiNHl5OE5jZkxQWTh5TG9ERDhTbS00MXBRSERyWEdQUXpTUlkzcHBBMEY1UnAwMmRR</guid></item><item><title>服用维生素D时犯的头号错误- EatingWell</title><link>https://www.eatingwell.com/mistake-when-taking-vitamin-d-11861230</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-page_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-page mntl-block structured-content" data-sc-sticky-offset="90" data-sc-ad-label-height="24" data-sc-ad-track-spacing="100" data-sc-min-track-height="250" data-sc-max-track-height="600" data-sc-breakpoint="50em" data-sc-load-immediate="4" data-sc-content-positions="[1, 1250, 1550, 1950, 2350, 2750, 3150, 3550, 3950]" data-bind-scroll-on-start="true"&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-block_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-callout--summary mntl-sc-block-universal-callout--tips mntl-sc-block-universal-callout theme-summary callout--bordered" data-text="Key Points" data-tracking-id="mntl-sc-block-callout" data-tracking-container="true"&gt;
&lt;div class="mntl-sc-block-universal-callout__body"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;The biggest mistake you’re making is choosing the wrong form of vitamin D supplement. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Vitamin D3 is from animals, and it is the type you make from the sun, which is absorbed better.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Choose an independently-tested supplement or add fatty fish and fortified foods to your diet. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_2-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; You might be doing everything right—&lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/8034163/benefits-vitamin-d/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;taking a vitamin D supplement&lt;/a&gt;, drinking milk, eating salmon and soaking up midday rays. On the surface, it seems like you’ve got your &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/7950001/signs-you-might-have-a-vitamin-d-deficiency/" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;vitamin D bases covered&lt;/a&gt;. Yet almost 25% of people in the United States are running low. Vitamin D plays far more roles in the body than you may realize.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="1"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_3-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_4-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;br&gt;
“While its claim to fame is often associated with the role it plays in protecting bone health through helping the body absorb calcium, that’s not all you need vitamin D for,” says &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/author/elizabeth-shaw/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Elizabeth Shaw, M.S., RDN, CPT&lt;/a&gt;. “It’s also involved in communication in the body, muscle movement and immune health. In fact, you need vitamin D to help kick free radicals out of your body, like the common cold and flu, so you can stay healthy.”&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="2"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_5-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_6-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;br&gt;Even if you’re taking a vitamin D supplement like clockwork every day, you still might not be absorbing enough.  According to experts, the biggest mistake people are making is choosing the wrong form of vitamin D. So, which one should you be choosing? Here, we break down the differences between the two types of vitamin D and which one you should be reaching for. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_7-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-the-difference-between-vitamin-d2-and-d3"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_8-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; The Difference Between Vitamin D2 and D3 &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_9-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;br&gt;When you look at vitamin D supplements options, you may notice two forms available: vitamin D2 and vitamin D3. While both can help raise and maintain vitamin D levels, they come from different sources and your body utilizes them differently. Below we explore what sets the two apart. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_10-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_11-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Vitamin D2 &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_12-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Vitamin D2, also known by its scientific name ergocalciferol, comes primarily from plant-based sources. “Vitamin D2 is photosynthesized in plants, mushrooms and yeasts. In other words, mushrooms exposed to sunlight synthesize vitamin D2,” explains &lt;a href="https://www.lifeextension.com/wellness/authors/holli-ryan" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1" rel="nofollow"&gt;Holli Ryan, RD, LD&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="3"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_13-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_14-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Both D2 and D3 must undergo two steps to become biologically active: first, conversion in the liver, then again in the kidney. However, once activated, research shows that vitamin D3 is more effective at raising and maintaining 25(OH)D levels, which is your blood serum vitamin D status. Vitamin D2 has structural differences that reduce its ability to bind to vitamin D-binding protein, and it also breaks down more quickly. Its shorter half-life means it doesn’t stay in your system as long either. Ultimately, making it the less-than-desirable option.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="4"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_15-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_17-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_18-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Vitamin D3  &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_19-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Vitamin D3, also known as cholecalciferol, is found in animal-based foods such as salmon, tuna, herring, egg yolks, and cheese, as well as in fortified foods like dairy milk and orange juice.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="2"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; It’s also the form your body naturally produces when you get some rays. “Vitamin D3 is closer to the form your body naturally makes from sunlight, so it’s more efficient at supporting and maintaining vitamin D levels,” explains &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/bonnie-taub-dix-11796963" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Bonnie Taub-Dix, RDN&lt;/a&gt;.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_20-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_21-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Although the body can use both forms of vitamin D, studies show that vitamin D3 can raise blood levels of vitamin D higher and for longer than vitamin D2, says Shaw. In fact, guidelines indicate that vitamin D3 is approximately five times more potent at raising serum 25(OH)D concentrations, compared to D2.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="2"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_22-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_24-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-why-choosing-d3-matters"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_25-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Why Choosing D3 Matters &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_26-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; With nearly 5% of the population at risk of vitamin D deficiency and another 18% with insufficient levels, maintaining adequate levels is a widespread problem.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="2"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Vitamin D plays multiple critical roles in health, from &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/foods-for-bone-health-11745664" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;supporting strong bones&lt;/a&gt; to bolstering immune health to aiding with muscle movement. When levels run low, it may lead to weakened immunity, fatigue, or low mood. That’s why choosing the right form of vitamin D is so important. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_27-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-how-to-choose-the-right-vitamin-d-supplement"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_28-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; How to Choose the Right Vitamin D Supplement &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_29-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Here are a few expert-backed tips to &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/what-to-look-for-in-a-supplement-8645052" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;help guide you&lt;/a&gt; towards picking up the right vitamin D supplement.  
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_30-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_31-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Look for independently tested brands&lt;/strong&gt;: Start by choosing a supplement verified by a trusted independent testing organization. “Labels from testing organizations, like NSF certified or USP, mean you know what’s on the label is in the bottle,” says Shaw. This helps ensure you’re choosing a safe, high-quality option.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Choose D3:&lt;/strong&gt; Check that the supplement is in D3 form. “It should read ‘cholecalciferol’ if it has the D3 form,” Shaw points out.  &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Find vegan-friendly D3&lt;/strong&gt;: If you’re vegan, look for an algae-derived vitamin D3 supplement, since most D3 supplements are derived from lanolin (sheep’s wool), says Ryan. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pick a form you’ll take consistently: &lt;/strong&gt;Softgels and liquid drops are both good options;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;choose the form you’ll take most comfortably and consistently, advises Taub-Dix. And “check with your healthcare provider to determine what dose is right for you,” she adds.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pair it with fat in your diet: &lt;/strong&gt;Once you’ve found a tried and true supplement, don’t forget to pair it with fat. “Because vitamin D is fat-soluble, I always remind people to pair these foods with a source of healthy fat to support absorption,” says Shaw. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_32-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_34-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-other-ways-to-get-vitamin-d"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_35-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Other Ways to Get Vitamin D &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_36-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; In addition to choosing the right vitamin D supplement, your diet, beverage choices and scheduling in sunshine time can help you &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/get-vitamin-d-without-supplement-11806255" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;boost your vitamin D levels&lt;/a&gt; too. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_37-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_38-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dive into fatty fish&lt;/strong&gt;: Salmon, trout, sardines, herring and tuna are all &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/foods-with-more-vitamin-d-than-an-egg-8732396" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;natural sources of vitamin D&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Eat the whole egg&lt;/strong&gt;: The yolk contains several nutrients, including vitamin D.  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Try wild or UVB-treated mushrooms:&lt;/strong&gt; Wild mushrooms naturally contain vitamin D2 and UVB-treated varieties can contain high amounts of vitamin D too. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Drink milk: &lt;/strong&gt;Dairy milk is typically fortified with vitamin D. Plant-based milks may also be fortified - check the label.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Choose fortified cereals: &lt;/strong&gt;Many ready-to-eat breakfast cereals contain added vitamin D. Look for it on the nutrition facts panel.  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Grab a glass of OJ&lt;/strong&gt;: Drinking 100% fortified orange juice can give you not only vitamin D but also calcium. &lt;strong&gt;(2,5)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Schedule sunlight time:&lt;/strong&gt; While sunlight is a free and natural way to get vitamin D, several variables can make it challenging to rely on alone. Age, skin pigmentation, geographical location, sunscreen use, body fat percentage and the season all affect how much vitamin D your skin produces, says Ryan. “Exposing your skin to UVB rays from the sunlight for around 15 minutes daily without sunscreen can be helpful, but be sure to avoid excessive sun exposure without protecting your skin”.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_39-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_40-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Monitor your levels regularly with a blood test to ensure you are maintaining adequate vitamin D levels. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_41-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-our-expert-take"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_42-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Our Expert Take &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_43-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; The number one mistake people make when taking vitamin D is choosing the wrong form. Experts recommend selecting a vitamin D3 supplement over D2 for maximum benefit and absorption. Research states vitamin D3 is five times more potent than vitamin D2, and more effective at raising and maintaining blood vitamin D levels. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_44-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_45-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; When picking out a supplement, make sure it’s independently tested, contains the D3 form, and comes in either soft or drop form. Other ways to boost your vitamin D levels are by eating fatty fish, mushrooms or drinking fortified milk or orange juice. Aim for at least 15 minutes of sunlight exposure a day. And don’t forget to monitor your vitamin D levels annually, as vitamin D plays a role in whole-body health. 
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>EatingWell</author><pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMic0FVX3lxTFBBRTBiSGRYNF9ZV3dVb2tjUk9yNmlJYnR3MTlfU0t2d0xfTVVaTEU4Rk40S2gxdVVRVlNPRTNDTjVTNFI1U2NUY3RnT254VWJzb01pZ2t5ampGdE5YSXdVczZaTDVadjhHNGwwZzdWeU9WeTQ</guid></item><item><title>我已经在后脑勺里藏了一个石灰大小的洞30年了- HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffpost.com/entry/cancer-hole-head-neck-pain_n_68fd1945e4b011e80886928d</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;section class="entry__content-list js-entry-content js-cet-subunit"&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Isn’t it amazing how old trauma like this can still present itself all these years later?” Jade said as she tapped hair-thin needles into pressure points along my shoulder blades. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;What does she mean, old trauma? I didn’t ask about that.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;At 38, a neurologist told me I have degenerative disc disease in my cervical spine that is so bad it looked like I spent years wrangling a jackhammer on a construction site. As a suburban mom and college professor, what could I have possibly done in life to contribute to this condition? Carry a growing baby in the björn and a toddler on my hip as I ran in and out of Target? Lug my entire office in a tote bag from class to class across campus? It has never been clear. So it made sense that the acupuncturist assumed all of my neck pain radiated from the bulging discs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;What I brought up with Jade, though, was my tumor site. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“When I was in college,” I told her, “I had a malignant tumor removed from the base of my skull.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I had no idea,” Jade said with surprise. “Did you have physical therapy?” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“No, I didn’t. It was so long ago, and I was so young,” I explained. “The surgeon removed a chunk of my scalp and it wasn’t until 10 years later that I realized he had actually removed part of my occipital bone, too.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;She stood close behind me, giving me time and space to put two and two together.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Is it possible that I have simultaneous issues causing my pain and discomfort?” I asked. “Could my decades-old surgery have anything to do with the chronic throbs I always feel on both sides of my neck?”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jade sat me at the edge of the table and turned my head right, then down, then left as she ran the tip of her pointer finger along each side of my hanging head.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Blood rushed into my cheeks. I fumbled for an answer to her unexpected question. Hearing no audible objection from me, Jade tenderly parted my hair. Her thumbs pushed inside the lime-sized hole in my head, precisely tracing the suboccipital muscles to see where they had reattached themselves after my surgery.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure class="cli cli-image js-no-inject"&gt;&lt;p class="cli-image__spacer"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="cli-image__source-wrapper"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="cli-image__caption caption-cli"&gt;This is the photo that the author submitted to accompany her melanoma community profile. It was the first time she ever photographed her scar.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;div class="cli-image__credit" aria-label="Image Credit: Courtesy of Jennifer Young"&gt;&lt;p class="credit-container"&gt;&lt;span class="credit"&gt;Courtesy of Jennifer Young&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Who was the last person to ask to see my flawed scalp? I shifted on the table. It was probably my surgical oncologist. Who even knows that skin graft is there? My family, of course, but who else? My hairdresser? She is probably the only one. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Engrossed by the sea foam color sunlit on the wavy glass of the window, I sat transfixed. The soft spa sounds of lapping waves and sea birds chirping circulated in the room as I half listened to Jade speak about the physical trauma to my head and neck and the surgical scar that has now been part of my body for more than half my life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“It isn’t until we uncover old trauma like this and begin to treat it that we can truly heal,” she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;While Jade was clearly referring to my physical body, her words synonymously triggered thoughts about something else too — the scars she can’t see on the inside. It has finally dawned on me that, even after continuously interacting with the world and understanding how it has shaped me, I never truly realized that surviving cancer as a young adult could still have an enormous impact on my life decades later. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Is it possible for people to not realize how much previous traumas affect them? &lt;a href="https://www.thenationalcouncil.org/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Trauma-infographic.pdf" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="According to the National Council for Mental Wellbeing" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68fd1945e4b011e80886928d" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.thenationalcouncil.org/wp-content/uploads/2022/08/Trauma-infographic.pdf" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="0"&gt;According to the National Council for Mental Wellbeing&lt;/a&gt;, 70% of adults in the U.S. have experienced some type of traumatic event at least once in their lives. That’s 235.1 million people. Trauma, then, is more universal than we probably realize. And while some people do not remember traumatic or painful experiences from the past at all, many others work to understand the potential effects on their lives. But do these attempts to understand what they’ve been through automatically translate into true healing?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;In spite of these efforts, emotions and thoughts we ignore or push down can still manifest physically, sometimes as tension, fatigue, or even illness. In other words, “your body expresses what your mind suppresses,” says &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/loroxburgh/reel/C7znvUzSqP7/" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Lauren Roxburgh" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68fd1945e4b011e80886928d" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.instagram.com/loroxburgh/reel/C7znvUzSqP7/" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="1"&gt;Lauren Roxburgh&lt;/a&gt;, international body alignment expert and wellness educator dubbed The Body Whisperer. And while repressed memories may not be readily accessible, they can sometimes resurface later in life, often triggered by specific cues or situations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sitting in my acupuncturist’s office, I was suddenly aware that I had been holding that broken girl deep inside of me for too long. I felt ready to reconnect with her, to write her back into my story. As the mother of four children around the same age as when I was diagnosed with cancer, I see pieces of her in them. Each of them are navigating all the challenges that come with new adulthood — finding your own identity, learning to navigate new and old relationships, and developing emotional and financial independence. All of that was happening for me back then, too. How did I manage a cancer diagnosis on top of everything else? How could the 19-year-old me have juggled those balls and not have expected one to drop? &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure class="cli cli-image js-no-inject"&gt;&lt;p class="cli-image__spacer"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="cli-image__source-wrapper"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="cli-image__caption caption-cli"&gt;The author and her husband, age 19, just a few weeks before her biopsy.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;div class="cli-image__credit" aria-label="Image Credit: Courtesy of Jennifer Young"&gt;&lt;p class="credit-container"&gt;&lt;span class="credit"&gt;Courtesy of Jennifer Young&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;A rush of memories released as Jade carefully pushed the slender points of filiform into the narrows of my neck. I thought back to my 19-year-old self and realized she and I still have a lot in common. She had to borrow wisps of hair from behind her ears to bobby pin over the bald spot on the back of her head every time she twisted up her hair. I still do that. She had to carefully cover the pockmarks on her shoulders from the vaccine shots with just-long-enough capped sleeves. I do that, too. She always yanked at her swimsuit to cover the square skin graft scar on her left butt cheek. Guess what? It still shows.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;But how did it never occur to me until this moment that the emotional trauma I endured as a young adult was even bigger and brighter than every blemish on my body? And while I am grateful to now have nurturing practitioners to help ease my physical pain, I realized that every time I worked to cover up these imperfections so that no one can see them, I stashed those old painful feelings beneath metal hairpins and bathing suit bottoms at the same time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Desperate to put as much space as possible between my trauma and the rest of my life, I thought I had to erase that chapter entirely. How would it feel if instead I paid closer attention to the cues my body has been giving me and worked to acknowledge that heartbreak from long ago?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Although today many people are better at recognizing the emotional and psychological impacts of trauma like cancer has, I believe there are many others like me who never gave themselves that grace. Psychiatrist and author &lt;a href="https://www.besselvanderkolk.com/resources/the-body-keeps-the-score" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Bessel Van Der Kolk, M.D." data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68fd1945e4b011e80886928d" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.besselvanderkolk.com/resources/the-body-keeps-the-score" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="2"&gt;Bessel Van Der Kolk, M.D.&lt;/a&gt;, underscores this notion in his bestselling book “The Body Keeps the Score”: “... trauma almost invariably involves not being seen, not being mirrored, and not being taken into account.” Is releasing these trapped emotions the key to restoring balance and well-being? &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Now, it seems like a no-brainer that missing bone from the back of my head was one likely cause of upper body pain for all of these years. But having my very own ah-ha moment in the least expected time and place is not lost on me, and what Jade has been saying gets through: A textbook understanding of trauma is not enough. True healing will only come if I accept every scar and allow each version of myself to be seen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;My physical wounds healed long ago, of course, but I now understand that scars — both physical and emotional — are stories our bodies carry, even when we’d prefer them to stay untold. Old traumas heal, it seems, not when we hide our scars, but when we finally let them speak.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Since that moment at my acupuncturist’s office, I’ve started unpacking this chapter more intentionally — reflecting on it, writing about it, and having honest conversations I used to avoid. It’s helped. I even worked up the courage to submit a survivor profile to a melanoma community on Instagram — including a photo that showed the scar on the back of my head.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;I almost hit delete a dozen times! But I didn’t, and the multitude of likes and messages I received connected me to others whose lives had been touched by cancer — and, unexpectedly, it felt like that 19-year-old version of me was connected to them too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Healing isn’t about going back; it’s about bringing every part of myself forward. And for the first time in a long time, that feels possible.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure class="cli cli-image js-no-inject"&gt;&lt;p class="cli-image__spacer"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="cli-image__source-wrapper"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="cli-image__caption caption-cli"&gt;The author and her husband married after she reached five years in remission. They have four children.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;div class="cli-image__credit" aria-label="Image Credit: Courtesy of Jennifer Young"&gt;&lt;p class="credit-container"&gt;&lt;span class="credit"&gt;Courtesy of Jennifer Young&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Jennifer Young, a long-term melanoma survivor, is currently working on a coming-of-age memoir about love, illness, and the decades-long journey to reclaim who she was. She’s written for Coping Magazine, Business Insider, and Elephants and Tea, among others. A writing professor, she teaches students how to find their voice on the page and serves as faculty adviser for the Oncology Society. She lives in New York with her husband, their four children, and a 100-pound Golden Retriever who thinks he still fits in their laps. Visit&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="http://jenniferyoung.net/" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="jenniferyoung.net" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68fd1945e4b011e80886928d" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="http://jenniferyoung.net/" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="3"&gt;jenniferyoung.net&lt;/a&gt; or follow her on Instagram &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/jennifer_young_writer/?hl=en" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="@jennifer_young_writer" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68fd1945e4b011e80886928d" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.instagram.com/jennifer_young_writer/?hl=en" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="4"&gt;@jennifer_young_writer&lt;/a&gt; for more.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Do you have a compelling personal story you’d like to see published on HuffPost? Find out what we’re looking for &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/static/how-to-pitch-huffpost" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-internal-link" data-vars-item-name="here" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68fd1945e4b011e80886928d" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="/static/how-to-pitch-huffpost" data-vars-target-content-type="feed" data-vars-type="web_internal_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="5"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="mailto:pitch@huffpost.com" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="send us a pitch at pitch@huffpost.com." data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68fd1945e4b011e80886928d" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="mailto:pitch@huffpost.com" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="6"&gt;send us a pitch at pitch@huffpost.com.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>HuffPost</author><pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 13:58:22 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijAFBVV95cUxNRHFuMEU1dy1HUmhUQkU3c1JQTDhrUzhTS2FXTHl1LUJINmkxTTlUSzVxdUZrTEtwYmJIc0VMZWJwNm4wWlVSWUJXRGotVExQb2JPUXZXaWJ5QVhWUExxX1haYl8xY0E0OG0yWXJoZm1tVi10UnFtNGgyc0U5YnluVjlWcDdLZXREVXZCedIBkgFBVV95cUxORHNaMjZydVY5RDQ3MnZOd3c5czU4bi1uZUhZNE03dDZkWlZLR2lIYlJlZGxYOVBOTzdKeU4wLWJSakVDTFFZSHFOeW9reEs3NzFLLXJFeDNZZ0FmWEVtOUl0TEU4TWxlNWNydC1UNzBBTGhBbzNNUUpaQ1B3NEFMdk1GRnZkS0pmOXl5RVNlV0FHQQ</guid></item><item><title>高血压药物自愿召回： FDA -雅虎</title><link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/articles/high-blood-pressure-medication-voluntarily-130137494.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="" data-article-body="true"&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;A New Jersey drug maker has voluntarily recalled thousands of bottles of a combination high &lt;a href="https://thehill.com/homenews/nexstar_media_wire/5484940-american-heart-association-updates-blood-pressure-guidelines-for-2025-heres-whats-new/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:blood pressure;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;blood pressure&lt;/a&gt; medication over concerns the product could be cross-contaminated with another drug, the Federal Drug Administration said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The recall covers more than 11,100 bottles of bisoprolol fumarate and hydrochlorothiazide tablets under the brand name Ziac. Testing of reserve samples showed presence of ezetimibe, a drug used for high cholesterol, FDA &lt;a href="https://www.fda.gov/safety/industry-guidance-recalls/recalls-background-and-definitions" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:officials said in a report;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;officials said in a report&lt;/a&gt; published online.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The recall level for the drug is &lt;a href="https://www.fda.gov/safety/industry-guidance-recalls/recalls-background-and-definitions" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Class III;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Class III&lt;/a&gt;, meaning the use or exposure to the product is “not likely to cause adverse health consequences.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Glenmark Pharmaceuticals Inc., located in Elmwood Park, is recalling the pills, which are in 2.5 mg and 6.25 mg doses.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The FDA says packages affected are:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class="mb-4"&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;30-count bottles NDC 68462-878-30&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;100-count bottle NDC-68462-878-01&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;500-count bottles NDC68462-878-05&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The affected lot numbers were set to expire beginning in November 2025 through May 2026.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;i&gt;Copyright 2025 Nexstar Media, Inc. All rights reserved. This material may not be published, broadcast, rewritten, or redistributed.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;a href="https://thehill.com" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:For the latest news, weather, sports, and streaming video, head to The Hill.;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt; For the latest news, weather, sports, and streaming video, head to The Hill. &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Yahoo</author><pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 13:01:37 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimAFBVV95cUxPekU4QWdzdUJjVXJQcmFqd0RJMzZOUW9zdVdHbEMxNmlhMWh3UzJDcHZ2ZkpmM3g3X1BzaXlBVWNobVM3UmhHd29EM3ZMeWYxVktfaDF2Q1ppSFRna1NBQXJ5X3I2OUdXODBESGtNeEFYR0ZVS2ZnTzJEWjZGSEVkMVhfS3R2WTVCXzM3UXo2V291bUFFVnU2Wg</guid></item><item><title>自闭症令人困惑的表亲-黑客新闻</title><link>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=46172443</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Hacker News</author><pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 12:04:17 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiWEFVX3lxTE9VR3FHSUdVT2Y0Rl9TN0lqZTRkbE5hYVRvTTJUb21tV21WSWY2WUNyTW9DNjV5aThrdEdfVUw0Qk1WLXQydUFmX2pjQk9OajRRdWVobXpnQTY</guid></item><item><title>不，这不是焦虑或疲劳：心脏病医生揭示了你的身体最容易被忽视的迹象-经济时报</title><link>https://m.economictimes.com/magazines/panache/no-it-is-not-anxiety-or-fatigue-heart-doctor-reveals-the-most-overlooked-sign-that-your-body-is-under-stress/articleshow/125804780.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div data-brcount="15" class="artText"&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a fast-paced world where stress often hides behind exhaustion, irritability or anxious thoughts, a US based cardiologist is drawing attention to a simpler but widely ignored indicator. According to Dr Sanjay Bhojraj, the clearest sign that the body is under significant stress is unexpectedly waking up in the middle of the night.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; The interventional cardiologist and &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a ref="dofollow" data-ga-onclick="Inarticle articleshow link click#Magazines#href" href="/topic/functional-medicine" target="_blank"&gt;functional medicine&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; expert shared the insight through a recent video report on Instagram, urging people not to dismiss nighttime wakefulness as harmless.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-mid-newpos-mgid="mgid_125804780" id="div-mgid-mid-newpos-125804780"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Why Nighttime Awakenings Matter&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt; In the caption of his Instagram report, Dr Bhojraj stated, “One of the most overlooked signs of stress isn’t anxiety, irritability, or even fatigue, it is waking up in the middle of the night.” He explained that although many assume such brief disruptions are normal, they actually indicate that the nervous system is struggling to regulate itself.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="E_3" class="etoro"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; The body is designed to remain in a &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a ref="dofollow" data-ga-onclick="Inarticle articleshow link click#Magazines#href" href="/topic/parasympathetic-state-during-sleep" target="_blank"&gt;parasympathetic state during sleep&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, responsible for rest, repair and recovery. However, as highlighted in the Instagram report, stress hormones like cortisol can rise at inappropriate times due to factors such as unstable blood sugar, inflammation, emotional overload or irregular sleep timing. This hormonal spike can abruptly pull someone out of sleep between 1 and 3 AM.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote class="instagram-media" data-instgrm-captioned data-instgrm-permalink="https://www.instagram.com/reel/DR4-1M-EeR6/?utm_source=ig_embed&amp;amp;utm_campaign=loading" data-instgrm-version="14"&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt; &lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;h2&gt;A Metabolic Alarm, Not Just Poor Sleep&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt; Dr Bhojraj explained in the video transcript that normally &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a ref="dofollow" data-ga-onclick="Inarticle articleshow link click#Magazines#href" href="/topic/cortisol-levels" target="_blank"&gt;cortisol levels&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; should peak just before waking up in the morning. But if someone finds themselves awake suddenly in the night, it signals that the body is operating under stress. He described this reaction as a metabolic alarm signalling that the liver may be overworking, blood sugar levels may be dipping or the nervous system is overstimulated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-mid-vdoai="vdoai_125804780" id="div-vdoai-mid-125804780"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; “In functional medicine, these patterns matter. They tell us your body is carrying more stress than you realize, and it is trying to get your attention the only way it can,” he added in the Instagram caption.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-msid="125804780" class="masterclass_carousel"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-size="[[300, 250], [600, 250], [600, 300]]" data-adsslot="/7176/Economictimes/ET_News/ET_News_ROS/ET_News_ROS_MID_INTL_300" data-loc="100" id="div-gpt-ad-858478126-1-125804780" class="country_specAD"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; Dr Bhojraj emphasises that understanding the root patterns behind stress is key to preventing long term health consequences. His clinical approach integrates research in genomic medicine, advanced lipid testing and lifestyle tools such as breathwork, nutrition and sleep therapy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt; While many accept disrupted sleep as a minor inconvenience, Dr Bhojraj reminds that the body signals distress long before chronic stress develops into serious disease. Ignoring such signals allows stress to compound quietly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-size="[[300, 250], [600, 250], [600, 300]]" data-adsslot="/7176/Economictimes/ET_News/ET_News_ROS/ET_News_ROS_MID1_INTL_300" data-loc="2" id="div-gpt-ad-858478132-1-125804780" class="country_specAD2nd"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-size="[[300, 250], [600, 250], [600, 300]]" data-adsslot="/7176/Economictimes/ET_News/ET_News_ROS/ET_News_ROS_MID1_INTL_300" data-loc="5" id="div-gpt-ad-858478132-1-125804780" class="country_specAD2nd"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-size="[[300, 250], [600, 250], [600, 300]]" data-adsslot="/7176/Economictimes/ET_News/ET_News_ROS/ET_News_ROS_MID1_INTL_300" data-loc="3" id="div-gpt-ad-858478132-1-125804780" class="country_specAD2nd"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="inSideInd"&gt;&lt;div data-ga-action="Preference Banner InArticle Widget" data-ga-impression="Preference Banner InArticle Widget#Impressions | Preference Banner | Articleshow#url" class="Pbanner"&gt;&lt;div class="Pbannertext"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Add &lt;/p&gt;&lt;img alt="ET Logo" src="https://img.etimg.com/photo/123467569.cms"&gt;&lt;p&gt; as a Reliable and Trusted News Source&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Economic Times</author><pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 12:02:45 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijAJBVV95cUxOOFUwQ1I5WV85YjdZQ01kdm9CWVdYV2prNF9MVlNZamFmU3Z5Ny1USUV0dDEyem00dE14VUhGaXp3TXprNC1idzBUUUpsZlBxSXhUT2JFVHhJSDh6RmxHNzVoaU1vSVIwZVBteEVpWmpUU0UtU29TWkl5OFM0d3BaU05nMkxSOXZidmkxV3FqQV9fWGVNb1ZDYkljYm43YjZHT2NOVnpFVjc1cWhnVURITk1rT05wN1M4T25IVk5fMFlXNHFCb21tNzVVWVFSME1zR21iMDF5RUstYzk3am01RzBRaWxPdFZvdzh2cVhVQlp2Q3VweExEbjFtS2ZHcHhjQXRJbEhFN3U5d1Z60gGSAkFVX3lxTE5ZVy01TnNJd05sN0cyUFFaUEt5R2tMSnRoN21JdUpjWHpmYUd6QnZHbWNoUWE5Qk5aTnA0ZDcwMFNfOXVlMVhUYUVNT29FSHlQUjN0aVp6dWdfay1Db25pZm5adkVyYnBtcVhXa0JSZmV0aVhqc2pvMTdwUFBTNU5KM0hsVFNvU2lla21YNFhLc1hiY25ndU1Za3RqaEIyUjFhSnluRk1nMEJqTDcxZXVvLW9TdFVLc0haT01MR0k0cHF5S2hZSFdBQl9tdTk2Y214SE9sNGU1UVhXY0F4MnVEWE4tOWN5MG95ckdkcy0zVWxPaGFoX3Jtc1VwR1ZsMEVyczRVQnhRel9OaTdJOFBxVFE</guid></item><item><title>本月，医生警告“假日心脏综合症”以及其他心血管疾病。原因如下。- HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffpost.com/entry/holiday-heart-syndrome-signs-prevention-goog_l_6931b52fe4b0824b6df84e5e</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;section class="entry__content-list js-entry-content js-cet-subunit"&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;The holiday season is known to be a little (or a lot) extra. You may find that you drink more cocktails, eat more sweets or skip your daily walk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;While it’s of course OK to indulge in the treats of the season, doctors also warn that you should be mindful: The rich meals, increased alcohol consumption, heightened stress and disrupted routines of the holiday season are known to be hard on the heart, as proven by &lt;a href="https://newsroom.heart.org/news/heart-attack-deaths-more-likely-during-winter-holiday-season-than-any-other-time-of-year" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="the increase in heart attacks" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="6931b52fe4b0824b6df84e5e" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://newsroom.heart.org/news/heart-attack-deaths-more-likely-during-winter-holiday-season-than-any-other-time-of-year" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="0"&gt;the increase in heart attacks&lt;/a&gt; this time of year. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;This isn’t to say you can’t enjoy your holiday season and the food- and drink-based traditions that come along with it. Instead, you should think about celebrating responsibly and doing all that you can to protect your heart health and lower your stress throughout the final weeks of the year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Below, doctors share the overlooked cardiovascular dangers of the holiday season along with ways to enjoy this time safely.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Drinking too much alcohol can cause ‘holiday heart syndrome.’&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Holiday heart syndrome refers to a cardiac rhythm disturbance, an arrhythmia,” said &lt;a href="https://www.massgeneral.org/doctors/17312/ahmed-tawakol" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Dr. Ahmed Tawakol" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="6931b52fe4b0824b6df84e5e" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.massgeneral.org/doctors/17312/ahmed-tawakol" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="1"&gt;Dr. Ahmed Tawakol&lt;/a&gt;, the co-director of the Cardiovascular Imaging Research Center at Massachusetts General Hospital. It causes an irregular heart rhythm (also known as atrial fibrillation) sometimes in otherwise healthy people after excessive or binge drinking.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Binge drinking ― which is common around the holidays ― is known to cause this issue. (Binge drinking is defined as having four or more drinks for women and five or more drinks for men on a single occasion, according to Tawakol.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some people who experience holiday heart syndrome report a rapid or irregular heartbeat while others feel a sense of anxiety, Tawakol said. “And some people it can cause shortness of breath or chest pain, dizziness — certainly can cause some fatigue.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;While holiday heart syndrome can happen in anyone, and often happens to healthy people, those who are “already predisposed to heart disease, high blood pressure or sleep apnea may be at higher risk during these times of heavy drinking,” &lt;a href="https://uoflhealth.org/provider/mrinali-shetty-heart-care/" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Dr. Mrin Shetty" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="6931b52fe4b0824b6df84e5e" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://uoflhealth.org/provider/mrinali-shetty-heart-care/" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="2"&gt;Dr. Mrin Shetty&lt;/a&gt;, the director of the Women’s Heart Program at the University of Louisville, told HuffPost via email.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“&lt;span&gt;In some cases, holiday heart syndrome can resolve itself within 24 to 48 hours, but it’s important to understand that it can increase the risk of long-term heart issues, especially if these arrhythmias become more frequent or persist,” Shetty continued. Holiday heart syndrome &lt;a href="https://www.uab.edu/news/youcanuse/item/13914-holiday-heart-syndrome-what-is-it-how-can-you-prevent-it" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="can increase chances of" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="6931b52fe4b0824b6df84e5e" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.uab.edu/news/youcanuse/item/13914-holiday-heart-syndrome-what-is-it-how-can-you-prevent-it" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="3"&gt;can increase chances of&lt;/a&gt; strokes, heart attacks and blood clots.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“&lt;span&gt;The exact mechanism behind this phenomenon isn’t fully understood, but alcohol can affect the electrical signals in the heart,” Shetty explained. “Binge drinking leads to dehydration, electrolyte imbalances and stress on the heart, all of which can make the heart more susceptible to abnormal rhythms.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“&lt;span&gt;The phenomenon peaks around Christmas Day, the day after Christmas and New Years Day — hence the term: holiday heart,”&lt;/span&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/sarah-spelsberg-md-fawm-fewm-3201116b" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Dr. Sarah Spelsberg" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="6931b52fe4b0824b6df84e5e" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.linkedin.com/in/sarah-spelsberg-md-fawm-fewm-3201116b" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="4"&gt;Dr. Sarah Spelsberg&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;, an emergency medicine resident at UNC Health Southeastern in North Carolina, told HuffPost via email. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“We see it a lot in the emergency department,” Spelsberg added.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Stress also impacts your heart health during this season.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;While the &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/entertainment/topic/holidays" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-internal-link" data-vars-item-name="holidays" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="6931b52fe4b0824b6df84e5e" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="/entertainment/topic/holidays" data-vars-target-content-type="feed" data-vars-type="web_internal_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="5"&gt;holidays&lt;/a&gt; are a joyous time for many people, they are downright stressful for others as financial concerns, family issues, busy schedules and holiday travel all come front of mind.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“What’s interesting is that we see a surge in heart attacks around stressful periods,” Tawakol said. People are more likely to have heart attacks around earthquakes, sporting events, after elections and “we also see an increase in heart attacks around the holidays,” he noted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“Chronic stress can increase blood pressure, elevate heart rate and raise cortisol levels, all of which contribute to heart disease over time,” Shetty said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stress can also disrupt your sleep — and sleep is crucial for so many aspects of our health, including our heart health. Not sleeping well can increase your heart disease risk, said &lt;a href="https://providerdirectory.uabmedicine.org/provider/elizabeth-jackson/670012" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Dr. Elizabeth Jackson" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="6931b52fe4b0824b6df84e5e" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://providerdirectory.uabmedicine.org/provider/elizabeth-jackson/670012" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="6"&gt;Dr. Elizabeth Jackson&lt;/a&gt;, the director of the Cardiovascular Outcomes and Effectiveness Research Program at University of Alabama at Birmingham Medicine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;When you’re stressed, you may also not make time to exercise, which is detrimental to your cardiovascular health. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“We know when we’re stressed, we oftentimes don’t exercise as much, and becomes a bit of a vicious cycle ... even just going for a walk after dinner, every little bit can help you reduce that stress, improve your sleep habits and going out for a walk has great benefits for helping you maintain a healthy weight during the holiday times, to help you with blood pressure, with blood sugar control, if you have diabetes, [it’s] certainly good to keep active,” Jackson added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cold weather can cause heart problems, too.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“Cold weather itself can be a factor in the winter months. If not well protected, the cold can cause ... narrowing of the blood vessels, causing one’s heart rate and blood pressure to rise,” Shetty said. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;“This puts extra strain on the heart, which may not be tolerated by those with heart conditions such as angina or heart failure.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shoveling heavy snow can also cause heart problems in susceptible people, according to Tawakol.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;When it’s cold out, it’s important that you dress warmly to reduce strain on your heart, Spelsberg said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure class="cli cli-image js-no-inject"&gt;&lt;p class="cli-image__spacer"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="cli-image__source-wrapper"&gt;&lt;div class="cli-image__credit" aria-label="Image Credit: ljubaphoto via Getty Images"&gt;&lt;p class="credit-container"&gt;&lt;span class="credit"&gt;ljubaphoto via Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption class="cli-image__caption caption-cli"&gt;Drinking too much alcohol can cause heart issues such as irregular heartbeat. &lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;It’s important that you create a relaxing routine during the holiday season.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s clear that holiday &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/life/topic/stress" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-internal-link" data-vars-item-name="stress" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="6931b52fe4b0824b6df84e5e" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="/life/topic/stress" data-vars-target-content-type="feed" data-vars-type="web_internal_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="7"&gt;stress&lt;/a&gt; makes folks’ heart health worse. To deal with stress during the holidays (and all year), create a toolkit of all the things that help you feel less stressed, Jackson recommended. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Get your tool set all together so that when that stressful time comes, you can pull out the tools that work for you,” Jackson said. This could be meditation, breathing exercises, daily walks, music, puzzles, she noted, but you know what works best for you. If a cup of tea and your go-to comfort show is what you need to decompress, do that.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;And even if the stress of the holidays still gets under your skin, these stress-reducing activities still have benefit. Habits that help you cope, such as better sleep, exercise and mindfulness, have all been shown to make you less sensitive to the physical consequences of stress, therefore less at risk for heart issues, Tawakol said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Having a healthy heart during the holiday season (and all year round) is all about balance.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“To maintain heart health during the holidays, practice moderation by limiting alcohol and rich foods while balancing with healthier options,” Spelsberg said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;This doesn’t mean not having a cookie or a slice of pie, instead it means having some fruit with your dessert or a big salad along with a decadent meal. Think of what you can add to your plate for nourishment rather than subtracting foods.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most guidelines say women should have no more than one drink a day and men should have no more than two, Jackson added, “but even most days of the week, not having that drink is probably healthier for you.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Beyond your diet, commit to some exercise throughout the holiday season and be aware of heart attack symptoms, Spelsberg noted. If you notice chest pain, shortness of breath, dizziness or heart palpitations, don’t ignore them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“It’s important to get checked by a health care professional. Early intervention can make a significant difference in preventing long-term cardiac complications,” Shetty said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“&lt;span&gt;The holidays are a time for joy, and by taking a proactive approach to your heart health, you can enjoy them without compromising your well-being,” Shetty continued. “Remember, small changes and mindful habits can go a long way in protecting your heart, not just now, but for years to come.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>HuffPost</author><pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 12:00:18 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipAFBVV95cUxPSGNtaGlpdEszU1dkVk81Q1pfMzRKSXVzcTZJZVp3ZTZWeXoxUjYtbmt4eVZtdFVhWVNydm5JNzNOUmpUTGs2a2RsWHYwMG15UE9IcFQwbEl4LXFwdldhVlVMVHNFVVhNZk1ydDJqWmNSaE4tMzZDOHlyOWxtcWMtTVFfNUxHU1ZvS3czcU1UelRDeFpTRWJLdjkxYWlObnNyOFVocdIBqgFBVV95cUxOeTFaOFVQUDBnQlZtcWxqRFFLeVp1M2NENTM2TG9ZYzZnZTNEUEduYjQ5NVF1R3RxZ0ZobXBKbmZIdlJBWWVBdjY2WFBuZWpNRnpSNkVqOUtzN2pGMTJWWThiQ2VJWDBmWlZlcnVMOTJPdjg3WTZqbHpiRVJnUXNtU1g5dEsyM3JYeEp4NldJWWhxQWJMR05zUENNLWM0ZVR0R0tIaWFIdmlmZw</guid></item><item><title>运动营养师如何在没有超加工食品的情况下吃高蛋白饮食来促进锻炼并感到满意— Business Insider</title><link>https://www.businessinsider.com/nutritionist-eats-high-protein-diet-without-ultra-processed-foods-2025-12</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;section class="post-body-content post-story-body-content" data-component-type="post-body-content" data-load-strategy="exclude" data-track-content="" data-post-type="story" data-track-marfeel="post-body-content"&gt;
            
                &lt;p&gt;Grocery store shelves are stacked with convenient, protein-ified snacks, from bars to soda. But how much should you rely on them if you're trying to avoid ultra-processed foods?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For &lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.businessinsider.com/nutritionist-cut-upfs-shares-3-lessons-after-year-2024-12" data-track-click='{"element_name":"body_link","event":"tout_click","index":"bi_value_unassigned","product_field":"bi_value_unassigned"}' rel=""&gt;Rob Hobson&lt;/a&gt;, a sports nutritionist, the answer is simple: it's "very, very easy" to consume &lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.businessinsider.com/how-to-eat-enough-protein-without-skimping-on-fiber-2025-11" data-track-click='{"element_name":"body_link","event":"tout_click","index":"bi_value_unassigned","product_field":"bi_value_unassigned"}' rel=""&gt;enough protein&lt;/a&gt; without relying on UPFs, which are linked to obesity, type 2 diabetes, and cardiovascular disease when eaten in large amounts. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To support his daily hourlong workout routine, which combines endurance training on an assault bike and weightlifting, he aims to consume around &lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.businessinsider.com/protein-mistakes-health-issues-hit-your-goals-without-wasting-money-2025-4" data-track-click='{"element_name":"body_link","event":"tout_click","index":"bi_value_unassigned","product_field":"bi_value_unassigned"}' rel=""&gt;0.7g of protein&lt;/a&gt; per pound of body weight each day. Hobson said this is enough to build muscle, feel full, and fuel himself.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He used to turn to protein bars and shakes, which are typically ultra-processed, but &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="https://www.businessinsider.com/how-ultra-processed-foods-impact-your-body-calories-weight-gain-2025-1" data-track-click='{"element_name":"body_link","event":"tout_click","index":"bi_value_unassigned","product_field":"bi_value_unassigned"}' rel=""&gt;cut down on UPFs &lt;/a&gt;two years ago.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hobson shared how he hits his protein targets without eating UPFs, but stressed he is mindful of being overly restrictive. He does this by following the&lt;a target="_self" class="" href="https://www.businessinsider.com/dietitian-follows-80-20-rule-diet-protein-fiber-2025-11" data-track-click='{"element_name":"body_link","event":"tout_click","index":"bi_value_unassigned","product_field":"bi_value_unassigned"}' rel=""&gt; 80/20 rule&lt;/a&gt;: eating whole, unprocessed foods most of the time, and whatever he's craving for the remainder.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I still have a glass of wine. If I want a bit of chocolate, I will. If I want to have a pizza, I will," he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hobson added that it's important not to obsess over single nutrients, such as protein. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"If you do that, then chances are you are missing out on other stuff," he said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="f5b64409-1ca2-4daa-830e-f774a9a7db3e" data-toc-id="f5b64409-1ca2-4daa-830e-f774a9a7db3e"&gt;Eating oats with minimally processed protein powder for breakfast&lt;/h2&gt;
              &lt;figure class="figure image-figure-image   " data-type="img" data-e2e-name="image-figure-image" data-media-container="image" itemscope="" itemtype="https://schema.org/ImageObject"&gt;
              
              
                
              
              &lt;span class="image-source-caption "&gt;
                    &lt;figcaption class="image-caption headline-semibold" data-e2e-name="image-caption"&gt;
                      Hobson eats overnight oats with minimally processed protein powder for breakfast.
                      
              &lt;span class="image-source headline-regular" data-e2e-name="image-source" itemprop="creditText"&gt;
              
              Stefan Tomic/Getty Images
              
              &lt;/span&gt;
                    &lt;/figcaption&gt;
                  &lt;/span&gt;
              &lt;/figure&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;After he gets home from the gym, Hobson eats a bowl of overnight oats containing oats, milk, and a minimally processed protein powder. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It's whey protein that's been hydrolyzed, but it doesn't contain anything else," he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Oats contain some protein, but they are high in soluble fiber, which helps lower cholesterol, and insoluble fiber, which supports smooth digestion and feeds the beneficial microbes in the gut.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="17a93eee-f410-41ab-b7a5-e4668d9819c3" data-toc-id="17a93eee-f410-41ab-b7a5-e4668d9819c3"&gt;Adding beans to soup&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Beans are a cheap and convenient source of both protein and fiber. Just one cup of black beans, for example, contains around 15 grams of protein.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hobson adds them to his meals to up the protein count. "If I buy a ready-made soup, I will just chuck in half a can of beans," he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="36a10c12-5c7d-40a4-ac56-1feb6a2a0293" data-toc-id="36a10c12-5c7d-40a4-ac56-1feb6a2a0293"&gt;Keeping the kitchen stocked with easy protein&lt;/h2&gt;
              &lt;figure class="figure image-figure-image   " data-type="img" data-e2e-name="image-figure-image" data-media-container="image" itemscope="" itemtype="https://schema.org/ImageObject"&gt;
              
              
                
              
              &lt;span class="image-source-caption "&gt;
                    &lt;figcaption class="image-caption headline-semibold" data-e2e-name="image-caption"&gt;
                      Hobson keeps his fridge stocked with tofu and other protein sources.
                      
              &lt;span class="image-source headline-regular" data-e2e-name="image-source" itemprop="creditText"&gt;
              
              Tathiane Fernandes/Getty Images
              
              &lt;/span&gt;
                    &lt;/figcaption&gt;
                  &lt;/span&gt;
              &lt;/figure&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;Hobson always keeps his fridge stocked with protein sources, like canned tuna, tofu, and chicken, which he can quickly cook up and add to a stir-fry or stew. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I find it really easy just to use those foods," he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;His go-to is a source of protein with some pre-cooked rice from a bag, vegetables, and soy sauce.&lt;/p&gt;
            
            
            &lt;/section&gt;
            
            
            
            
            
            
    
    
    
    
      &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Business Insider</author><pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 11:40:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiqAFBVV95cUxQM05DZjVxV2RKMUxvV3R1aDdxekJpbHFqUUNHZHVSQm9pY19WaU1uQ0t2ZThoUnltS2dlejUxZ2E1TDF2MUtqLVhsM1daZUZKRVlvc3dyV1lYeTZYSnY4X3IxcmdsakFiOXJtemRfSlNHbnVoNFZTX0x6U2h4WEUyRC1GbnRkLXRsU2VnaVh1RTdsVEY1alRMRmZqZWZsLUNSTkpISVc3cjk</guid></item><item><title>在RFK Jr.的领导下，疾病预防控制中心为反疫苗运动提供了扩音器-《华盛顿邮报》</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/health/2025/12/06/cdc-acip-anti-vaccine-rhetoric/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="DZ4Y2POOUFDI5NZLOBMPXWXP4I" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;ATLANTA — For decades, the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention has fought attempts by the anti-vaccine movement to sow doubts in the safety and efficacy of the shots that marked a triumph of public health. This week, the agency instead provided a powerful platform for the cause.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 11:32:06 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihwFBVV95cUxOS28teDI1TzlTbW1UNG1RenBJQUoxT21naExIcnRyTFQxeDVEaHJCcExTd1l4Y21lam14Sm9VRFhnc0duOUJxUDk3ampyaGk3eFpoQWpjUDY4Y0hPekV5WlNia3BOM2xmRkRpMUlpcW1ENVlzQ2lPQUlmV09fWXJTMlQyem9GVnc</guid></item><item><title>医学谜团：下巴剧烈疼痛。然后她的脸在眼前开始“变形”。-《华盛顿邮报》</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/health/2025/12/06/medical-mysteries-jaw-popping/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text subtype-from-the-source" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="IYMR4BTAK5BEFNVXUYQH3RLYQQ" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;In the spring of her senior year at college, Annie Sedoric woke up with jaw pain. It was March 2020, and there was a lot to worry about at the start of the covid pandemic, so she tried to ignore the pain, even as it grew worse.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 11:32:04 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihgFBVV95cUxPWnJKUTBGdDB2TXdDa3hWZDBSdGt1aGZQU1N6UlhiU1BjZFdOZ1B4T3pTRTVsSkFidGU0VzBoZ3ZiS2ZIcGo4V0d2QWp0SjhjOS1BRGFmOTNVcGJPUnA0NEp5Q2dDcEFGVWNURFlCRHgzZm9TWjgwVlhMeEhXd0pDQm5HRjYydw</guid></item><item><title>忘记褪黑激素：从NASA启发的研究中诞生的时差疗法，更快地重置您的身体-印度国防评论</title><link>https://indiandefencereview.com/forget-melatonin-the-jet-lag-cure-born-from-nasa-inspired-research-that-resets-your-body-faster/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="dynamic-entry-content"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In an era of hypermobility, where business meetings in Berlin follow red-eyes from Boston and leisure travelers chase sunsets across hemispheres, &lt;strong&gt;jet lag remains a stubborn adversary&lt;/strong&gt;. Despite decades of research and a booming wellness industry promising quick fixes, the human body continues to resist the tyranny of time zone shifts.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Jet lag isn’t just a minor inconvenience—it’s a physiological &lt;strong&gt;tug-of-war&lt;/strong&gt; between your internal clock and the external world. The result? Days of &lt;strong&gt;fatigue&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;insomnia&lt;/strong&gt;,&lt;strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://indiandefencereview.com/this-popular-yogurt-should-be-avoided-according-to-this-expert/" target="_blank" data-type="post" data-id="70829" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;digestive issues&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;, and &lt;strong&gt;cognitive fog&lt;/strong&gt; that can derail even the most meticulously planned itinerary. And as global travel rebounds post-pandemic, the urgency to understand and mitigate jet lag has never been greater.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;What makes jet lag so insidious is its unpredictability. Two travelers on the same flight can experience vastly different symptoms. Age, chronotype, direction of travel, and even genetics play a role. Yet, the core conflict remains universal: our circadian rhythms, finely tuned to the &lt;strong&gt;24-hour cycle of light&lt;/strong&gt; and dark, don’t take kindly to abrupt changes.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Now, a growing body of research is shedding new light on how to outsmart this biological inertia. From strategic light exposure to pre-flight sleep adjustments, scientists are uncovering practical, evidence-based strategies that could finally offer weary travelers a fighting chance.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Resetting the Clock: Light as the Master Regulator&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The single most powerful tool in the jet lag arsenal? Light. Exposure to natural light is the primary cue that synchronizes our internal clocks with the external environment. Morning sunlight can help advance the circadian rhythm, making it easier to adjust to eastward travel, while evening light can delay it for westward shifts. The &lt;a href="https://www.sleepfoundation.org/jet-lag" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Sleep Foundation&lt;/a&gt; highlights light exposure as one of the most effective ways to reset your body clock.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-video is-provider-youtube wp-block-embed-youtube wp-embed-aspect-16-9 wp-has-aspect-ratio"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Apps like Timeshifter, developed with input from NASA scientists, use this principle to create personalized jet lag plans. They recommend when to seek or avoid light, &lt;a href="https://indiandefencereview.com/losing-attention-span-4-science-backed-habits-help-get-back/" target="_blank" data-type="post" data-id="92798" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;caffeine&lt;/a&gt;, and sleep based on your itinerary and sleep patterns. While not a cure-all, these tools represent a leap forward from the days of blindly popping melatonin and hoping for the best.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;For travelers without access to such apps, the rule of thumb is simple: get outside. Even 20–30 minutes of natural light exposure in the morning can accelerate adaptation, especially when paired with light exercise like walking.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Sleep Strategically, Not Spontaneously&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;One of the most common mistakes travelers make is trying to “power through” jet lag by staying awake until local bedtime. The intention is right, but the execution often backfires. Sleep deprivation can intensify symptoms and make it harder to adjust.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Experts recommend gradually shifting your &lt;a href="https://indiandefencereview.com/to-sleep-better-science-recommends-doing-this-1-2-hours-before-bed-and-its-surprisingly-simple/" target="_blank" data-type="post" data-id="87863" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;sleep schedule &lt;/a&gt;before departure. If you’re flying east, try going to bed and waking up an hour earlier each day for a few days before your flight. For westward travel, do the opposite. The &lt;a href="https://wwwnc.cdc.gov/travel/page/jet-lag" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Centers for Disease Control and Prevention (CDC)&lt;/a&gt; supports this approach as a proactive way to reduce jet lag.&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;div class="wp-block-image"&gt;
&lt;figure class="aligncenter size-full"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="" alt="Tourist With A Suitcase Sleeping At Boarding Gate Waiting For His Delayed Flight" class="wp-image-98134" data-lazy-srcset="https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/tourist-with-a-suitcase-sleeping-at-boarding-gate-waiting-for-his-delayed-flight.jpg 1000w, https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/tourist-with-a-suitcase-sleeping-at-boarding-gate-waiting-for-his-delayed-flight-380x253.jpg 380w, https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/tourist-with-a-suitcase-sleeping-at-boarding-gate-waiting-for-his-delayed-flight-520x346.jpg 520w" data-lazy-sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" data-lazy-src="https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/tourist-with-a-suitcase-sleeping-at-boarding-gate-waiting-for-his-delayed-flight.jpg"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/tourist-with-a-suitcase-sleeping-at-boarding-gate-waiting-for-his-delayed-flight.jpg" alt="Tourist With A Suitcase Sleeping At Boarding Gate Waiting For His Delayed Flight" class="wp-image-98134" srcset="https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/tourist-with-a-suitcase-sleeping-at-boarding-gate-waiting-for-his-delayed-flight.jpg 1000w, https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/tourist-with-a-suitcase-sleeping-at-boarding-gate-waiting-for-his-delayed-flight-380x253.jpg 380w, https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/tourist-with-a-suitcase-sleeping-at-boarding-gate-waiting-for-his-delayed-flight-520x346.jpg 520w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px"&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;figcaption class="wp-element-caption"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Tourist With A Suitcase Sleeping At Boarding Gate Waiting For His Delayed Flight. Credit: Shutterstock&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Avoiding naps during the first day at your destination can also help, though short, strategic naps (20–30 minutes) may be beneficial if timed correctly. The key is consistency—your body needs clear signals to recalibrate.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Hydration, Caffeine, and the Myth of the Midnight Meal&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Air travel is notoriously dehydrating, and dehydration can intensify jet lag symptoms. The Aerospace Medical Association recommends drinking at least eight ounces of water for every hour in the air. Alcohol and caffeine, while tempting, should be used sparingly. Caffeine can help with alertness but should be avoided within six hours of your intended bedtime.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Emerging research suggests that meal timing may influence circadian rhythms. A study in Cell Reports found that mice who ate during their active phase adjusted more quickly to time zone changes. While human studies are ongoing, some experts suggest aligning meals with local time upon arrival to help reset the body’s internal clock.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;From Wearables to Chronomedicine&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;As interest in circadian health grows, so too does the technology designed to support it. Wearables like the &lt;strong&gt;Oura Ring &lt;/strong&gt;and &lt;strong&gt;WHOOP strap&lt;/strong&gt; now track sleep stages and recovery metrics, offering insights into how travel affects the body. Meanwhile, pharmaceutical companies are exploring chronobiotic drugs—compounds that can shift circadian rhythms more precisely than melatonin.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The most promising frontier may lie in personalized medicine. Researchers are beginning to understand that circadian rhythms vary widely between individuals. Tailoring interventions to each person’s biological profile could redefine how we approach jet lag in the years ahead.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;That future may still be on the horizon. For now, the best defense against jet lag remains a blend of science and strategy: plan ahead, seek the sun, hydrate well, and respect your body’s need for rest.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Indian Defence Review</author><pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 11:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMixwFBVV95cUxOcldwcjJwSEFxMklWRHpRemJfZkE1Um9aX3pEMDdrenA5Z0VJbkEtRlExZUt6ZXAtaV9qdHFCRmRzU29rZFhhSWIyYTVVT2lacmw1UTZUZ0swOFRnMUc2dFlQcXhMSEU3ZHpXaTBERnR3RXhyM0J4Z2VLN2k4Q1ZFU0R3ei1CZTR5bzhqS242eXlQT1JJNmxEMUFnZW0ta1RZQnh2ajdtZ3p6T0J0dkZNMGI1RmI1X0Z1X2g0Y25fRlYxRGJkQ3RJ</guid></item><item><title>大麻使用者无法控制地抽搐，听起来很恶心-副</title><link>https://www.vice.com/en/article/cannabis-users-are-scromiting-and-its-as-gross-as-it-sounds/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content wp-block-post-content is-layout-flow wp-block-post-content-is-layout-flow"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A new study out of the University of Illinois Chicago confirms what ER doctors have been noticing for a while: cannabinoid hyperemesis syndrome (CHS, for short, “&lt;a href="https://www.vice.com/en/article/what-is-scromiting/"&gt;scromiting&lt;/a&gt;” for long) is very real, and getting more common. &lt;/p&gt;




&lt;p&gt;It should be noted, though, that we are nowhere near epidemic levels, as it remains quite rare and only affects cannabis power users.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="ai-viewports ai-viewport-3 ai-insert-19-35138887" data-insertion-position="prepend" data-selector=".ai-insert-19-35138887" data-insertion-no-dbg data-code="PGRpdiBjbGFzcz0nY29kZS1ibG9jayBjb2RlLWJsb2NrLTE5IGFpLWxpc3QtYmxvY2staXAnIHN0eWxlPSdtYXJnaW46IDhweCBhdXRvOyB0ZXh0LWFsaWduOiBjZW50ZXI7IGRpc3BsYXk6IGJsb2NrOyBjbGVhcjogYm90aDsnPgoKPGRpdiBjbGFzcz0nYWktZHluYW1pYyBhaS1pcC1kYXRhJyAgY291bnRyaWVzPSdERSwgS1InIGNvdW50cnktbGlzdD0nVycgZGF0YS1jb2RlPSdQR1JwZGlCamJHRnpjejBuYkc1bmRHUXRaSGx1WVcxcFl5MXBibUZ5ZEdsamJHVW5JSE4wZVd4bFBTSnRhVzR0YUdWcFoyaDBPak13TUhCNE95QmhiR2xuYmkxcGRHVnRjem9nWTJWdWRHVnlPeUJxZFhOMGFXWjVMV052Ym5SbGJuUTZJR05sYm5SbGNqc2daR2x6Y0d4aGVUb2dabXhsZURzaVBqd3ZaR2wyUGc9PSc+PC9kaXY+CjwvZGl2Pgo=" data-block="19"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;







&lt;p&gt;CHS is an unpleasant side effect of a person’s plan to chill out with their favorite cannabis product of choice. After years of heavy cannabis use, a small but growing number of people will suddenly find themselves experiencing waves of nausea, abdominal pain, and vomiting so violently that it’s accompanied by a terrifying scream, hence the nickname “Scromiting” — a screaming vomit.&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;p&gt;Episodes can last up to two days. Hot showers seem to be the only reliable form of short-term relief, and a lot of them. The only reliable long-term fix anyone has stumbled upon so far is the most obvious one: stop using all forms of cannabis, immediately.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="ai-viewports ai-viewport-3 ai-insert-19-49887112" data-insertion-position="prepend" data-selector=".ai-insert-19-49887112" data-insertion-no-dbg data-code="PGRpdiBjbGFzcz0nY29kZS1ibG9jayBjb2RlLWJsb2NrLTE5IGFpLWxpc3QtYmxvY2staXAnIHN0eWxlPSdtYXJnaW46IDhweCBhdXRvOyB0ZXh0LWFsaWduOiBjZW50ZXI7IGRpc3BsYXk6IGJsb2NrOyBjbGVhcjogYm90aDsnPgoKPGRpdiBjbGFzcz0nYWktZHluYW1pYyBhaS1pcC1kYXRhJyAgY291bnRyaWVzPSdERSwgS1InIGNvdW50cnktbGlzdD0nVycgZGF0YS1jb2RlPSdQR1JwZGlCamJHRnpjejBuYkc1bmRHUXRaSGx1WVcxcFl5MXBibUZ5ZEdsamJHVW5JSE4wZVd4bFBTSnRhVzR0YUdWcFoyaDBPak13TUhCNE95QmhiR2xuYmkxcGRHVnRjem9nWTJWdWRHVnlPeUJxZFhOMGFXWjVMV052Ym5SbGJuUTZJR05sYm5SbGNqc2daR2x6Y0d4aGVUb2dabXhsZURzaVBqd3ZaR2wyUGc9PSc+PC9kaXY+CjwvZGl2Pgo=" data-block="19"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;





&lt;p&gt;Publishing their research in &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jamanetworkopen/fullarticle/2841769" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;JAMA Network Open&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;, researchers reviewed a national database of emergency department visits between 2016 and 2022, using cases that included both cannabis use and cyclical vomiting syndrome as a proxy for CHS, since it only recently became its own official diagnosis. They counted around 100,000 suspected cases in that period. &lt;/p&gt;




&lt;p&gt;Rates were steady and low…and then 2020 hit, and suddenly CHS visits spiked across the country. Not sure what could’ve happened in 2020 that would’ve made everyone want to get out of their own heads for a couple of hours or maybe two straight years, but whatever it was, cases started dipping back down in 2022, though not quite back to the old levels.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="ai-viewports ai-viewport-3 ai-insert-19-74778749" data-insertion-position="prepend" data-selector=".ai-insert-19-74778749" data-insertion-no-dbg data-code="PGRpdiBjbGFzcz0nY29kZS1ibG9jayBjb2RlLWJsb2NrLTE5IGFpLWxpc3QtYmxvY2staXAnIHN0eWxlPSdtYXJnaW46IDhweCBhdXRvOyB0ZXh0LWFsaWduOiBjZW50ZXI7IGRpc3BsYXk6IGJsb2NrOyBjbGVhcjogYm90aDsnPgoKPGRpdiBjbGFzcz0nYWktZHluYW1pYyBhaS1pcC1kYXRhJyAgY291bnRyaWVzPSdERSwgS1InIGNvdW50cnktbGlzdD0nVycgZGF0YS1jb2RlPSdQR1JwZGlCamJHRnpjejBuYkc1bmRHUXRaSGx1WVcxcFl5MXBibUZ5ZEdsamJHVW5JSE4wZVd4bFBTSnRhVzR0YUdWcFoyaDBPak13TUhCNE95QmhiR2xuYmkxcGRHVnRjem9nWTJWdWRHVnlPeUJxZFhOMGFXWjVMV052Ym5SbGJuUTZJR05sYm5SbGNqc2daR2x6Y0d4aGVUb2dabXhsZURzaVBqd3ZaR2wyUGc9PSc+PC9kaXY+CjwvZGl2Pgo=" data-block="19"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;





&lt;p&gt;The good news is that CHS is treatable once it’s recognized. Unfortunately, it’s often not recognized at all, and its symptoms can be easily misconstrued as something else entirely, leading to a battery of unnecessary tests. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Hopefully, that era is now over, as CHS is officially included in the International Classification of Diseases. Let’s just hope medical professionals brush up on all the latest diseases.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="ai-viewports ai-viewport-3 ai-insert-19-83569286" data-insertion-position="prepend" data-selector=".ai-insert-19-83569286" data-insertion-no-dbg data-code="PGRpdiBjbGFzcz0nY29kZS1ibG9jayBjb2RlLWJsb2NrLTE5IGFpLWxpc3QtYmxvY2staXAnIHN0eWxlPSdtYXJnaW46IDhweCBhdXRvOyB0ZXh0LWFsaWduOiBjZW50ZXI7IGRpc3BsYXk6IGJsb2NrOyBjbGVhcjogYm90aDsnPgoKPGRpdiBjbGFzcz0nYWktZHluYW1pYyBhaS1pcC1kYXRhJyAgY291bnRyaWVzPSdERSwgS1InIGNvdW50cnktbGlzdD0nVycgZGF0YS1jb2RlPSdQR1JwZGlCamJHRnpjejBuYkc1bmRHUXRaSGx1WVcxcFl5MXBibUZ5ZEdsamJHVW5JSE4wZVd4bFBTSnRhVzR0YUdWcFoyaDBPak13TUhCNE95QmhiR2xuYmkxcGRHVnRjem9nWTJWdWRHVnlPeUJxZFhOMGFXWjVMV052Ym5SbGJuUTZJR05sYm5SbGNqc2daR2x6Y0d4aGVUb2dabXhsZURzaVBqd3ZaR2wyUGc9PSc+PC9kaXY+CjwvZGl2Pgo=" data-block="19"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;





&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;



&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>VICE</author><pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilwFBVV95cUxNY21aZ0RHR1d2cHkwOVNrX0Raejk4aTZxTmt3NFNzVUEtMTVReF9TQnZqbnQwLWJfbmEtUUNCYTFwUUlKdDREeURCSHhxNUlNM3FSd1RqWmFfaFVJSWJqTmhTeHduOTZxcVQzZk9hZFBsdGQwWld0N25zaWdhZlk3NU9RNUxOV2otSHI2RE55TDFrY0MwdWpV</guid></item><item><title>在将老鼠暴露于普通生活垃圾后，科学家们做出了令人不安的发现： “想想这如何等同于人类” -雅虎</title><link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/articles/scientists-disturbing-discovery-exposing-mice-090000195.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="" data-article-body="true"&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;A new study found that it took only weeks for microplastics to make their way into the brain tissues of mice, raising concerns about what that could mean for human health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="mb-4 text-lg font-bold"&gt;What's happening?&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;As &lt;a href="https://www.newsweek.com/warning-microplastics-escape-gut-infiltrate-brain-1890760" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:detailed;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;detailed&lt;/a&gt; by Newsweek, researchers exposed a set of mice to microplastics in drinking water, and they found that the tiny particles had migrated from their guts into liver, kidney, and brain tissues in as little as four weeks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;"We could detect microplastics in certain tissues after the exposure," University of New Mexico associate professor Eliseo Castillo, one of the &lt;a href="https://ehp.niehs.nih.gov/doi/10.1289/EHP13435" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:study's authors;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;study's authors&lt;/a&gt;, told the outlet. "That tells us it can cross the intestinal barrier and infiltrate into other tissues."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The findings, published in the journal &lt;a href="https://www.newsweek.com/warning-microplastics-escape-gut-infiltrate-brain-1890760" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Environmental Health Perspectives;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Environmental Health Perspectives&lt;/a&gt;, also &lt;a href="https://ehp.niehs.nih.gov/doi/10.1289/EHP13435#sec-4" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:revealed;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;revealed&lt;/a&gt; that researchers discovered "metabolic differences" in the colons, livers, and brains of the animals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="mb-4 text-lg font-bold"&gt;Why is this concerning?&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Mice typically live for only &lt;a href="https://www.britannica.com/animal/house-mouse" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:a few years;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;a few years&lt;/a&gt;, so the fact that differences were evident after such a short period of time set off alarm bells. According to &lt;a href="https://www.newsweek.com/warning-microplastics-escape-gut-infiltrate-brain-1890760" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Newsweek;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Newsweek&lt;/a&gt;, the lab mice were exposed to equivalent concentrations that humans experience in their drinking water on a daily basis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;"Think about how that equates to humans, if we're exposed from birth to old age," Castillo &lt;a href="https://www.newsweek.com/warning-microplastics-escape-gut-infiltrate-brain-1890760" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:told;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;told&lt;/a&gt; the news outlet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Researchers haven't drawn definite conclusions about the impacts of microplastics on our health, but they have been linked to a range of problems, including cancer, dementia, reproductive issues, and anxiety.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;These tiny particles, which are less than &lt;a href="https://www.ciel.org/breathing-plastic-the-health-impacts-of-invisible-plastics-in-the-air/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:five millimeters in length;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;five millimeters in length&lt;/a&gt;, have been found just about everywhere — even in the &lt;a href="https://www.ciel.org/breathing-plastic-the-health-impacts-of-invisible-plastics-in-the-air/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:air we breathe;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;air we breathe&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="mb-4 text-lg font-bold"&gt;What can be done about harmful microplastics?&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Researchers &lt;a href="https://ehp.niehs.nih.gov/doi/10.1289/EHP13435#sec-4" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:believe;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;believe&lt;/a&gt; that their latest findings could provide a roadmap to understanding the impact of exposure to mixed microplastics. In turn, this could lead to valuable insights to identify potential risks to our health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;"At the end of the day, the research we are trying to do aims to find out how this is impacting gut health," Castillo &lt;a href="https://www.newsweek.com/warning-microplastics-escape-gut-infiltrate-brain-1890760" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:told;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;told&lt;/a&gt; Newsweek. "If you don't have a healthy gut, it affects the brain, it affects the liver and so many other tissues. … that chronic exposure could lead to systemic effects."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Scientists are also developing ways to remove microplastics from drinking water.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;A team at Tarleton State University found that molecules in certain plants show promise as a solution, while researchers at the Indian Institute of Science created a hydrogel to &lt;a href="https://thecooldown.com/green-tech/revolutionary-material-microplastics-pollution-hydrogel/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:eliminate more than 90%;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;eliminate more than 90%&lt;/a&gt; of polyvinyl chloride and polypropylene particles.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Switching to &lt;a href="https://guide.thecooldown.com/step/explore-plastic-free-alternatives-for-everyday-products/r/recyyL53BQALKavvy" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:plastic-free alternatives;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;plastic-free alternatives&lt;/a&gt; for common household products can also help limit your exposure to toxins. This year, Tide released a laundry detergent that doesn't come in plastic packaging. &lt;a href="https://guide.thecooldown.com/step/ditch-plastic-food-containers/r/recNZY30UUD3R6VMx" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Silicone food storage containers;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Silicone food storage containers&lt;/a&gt; and metal razors are other options as well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Join our &lt;a href="https://www.thecooldown.com/tech-newsletter/?recFukzCNZuLraLb5" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:free newsletter;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;free newsletter&lt;/a&gt; for weekly updates on the coolest innovations &lt;strong&gt;improving our lives&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;saving our planet&lt;strong&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Yahoo</author><pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 09:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMinAFBVV95cUxPQUl5anBDRVZ6SFg2cXFSd0o4d2ZobmdMRWdYTmFEeHJhQ3NnVnJIbzBkakdRUWVoNUNLVGMtY0lkMU0waC1Sb3BmUHNzWlhDOEdKaXNBNi1tR2dwcGJsS3R0Q3FJT3lOQkdDc0pmUUxxblN1QjJ3U29qcTRuOVNWZ05PV29KTFdmNjJhcndTM2RqNzFZaFdTUFRuWHc</guid></item><item><title>克罗恩病： “我不想离开家” -英国广播公司</title><link>https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/c4gv309qx4wo</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article&gt;&lt;p data-component="headline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 hNbOGD"&gt;&lt;h1 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 idLnWK"&gt;'I don't want to leave the house because of Crohn's'&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 gtLOOD"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="hero-image" class="sc-5340b511-1 cMIbKV"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20251203-121739-f954f14c69-web-2.35.1-2/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 gUePlo hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/ffb7/live/f7af12c0-cf73-11f0-b355-05c29911d4af.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/ffb7/live/f7af12c0-cf73-11f0-b355-05c29911d4af.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/ffb7/live/f7af12c0-cf73-11f0-b355-05c29911d4af.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/ffb7/live/f7af12c0-cf73-11f0-b355-05c29911d4af.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/ffb7/live/f7af12c0-cf73-11f0-b355-05c29911d4af.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/ffb7/live/f7af12c0-cf73-11f0-b355-05c29911d4af.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/ffb7/live/f7af12c0-cf73-11f0-b355-05c29911d4af.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/ffb7/live/f7af12c0-cf73-11f0-b355-05c29911d4af.jpg.webp" loading="eager" alt="Collect/PA Real Life Two images side-by-side of Lucy Dare. On the left, she is shown as a young teenager, sat in bed with dark brown-red hair with a feeding tube in her nose. On the right, she is shown in her 20s, posing for a photo in a white top and dressed up with makeup, with blonde hair." class="sc-5340b511-0 hLdNfA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 jVqbAn"&gt;Collect/PA Real Life&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;Lucy Dare was diagnosed with Crohn's disease in 2019 after years of uncertainty, but has continued to face struggles&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;At the age of 12, Lucy Dare began to struggle with eating and excessive toilet use, but neither she nor her doctors knew what was going on.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Facing numerous difficulties throughout her teenage years, she was then misdiagnosed with an eating disorder, before it was finally confirmed in 2019 that she had Crohn's disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Now 21, Lucy says she is still struggling to hold down a job and manage everyday life, as she battles with the incurable condition.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"I don't want to leave the house because of the pain and the anxiety," she says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 gXrNRM"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 cMIbKV"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20251203-121739-f954f14c69-web-2.35.1-2/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 gUePlo hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/e1d4/live/01778a20-cf75-11f0-a892-01d657345866.png.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/e1d4/live/01778a20-cf75-11f0-a892-01d657345866.png.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/e1d4/live/01778a20-cf75-11f0-a892-01d657345866.png.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/e1d4/live/01778a20-cf75-11f0-a892-01d657345866.png.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/e1d4/live/01778a20-cf75-11f0-a892-01d657345866.png.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/e1d4/live/01778a20-cf75-11f0-a892-01d657345866.png.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/e1d4/live/01778a20-cf75-11f0-a892-01d657345866.png.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/e1d4/live/01778a20-cf75-11f0-a892-01d657345866.png.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Collect/PA Real Life Lucy Dare as a young teenager, sat at a dining table in front of a small plate of food, which she is picking up in her left hand. She is wearing a dressing gown and a pink headscarf." class="sc-5340b511-0 hLdNfA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 jVqbAn"&gt;Collect/PA Real Life&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;Lucy was originally misdiagnosed with an eating disorder before doctors found she had Crohn's disease&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The first signs of Lucy's condition included rectal bleeding, severe abdominal pain, weight loss, fatigue and using the toilet up to 15 times a day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;This caused her to lose weight, and at 13 years old, she weighed just 38kg (5st 13.8lb).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Combined with her need to use the toilet urgently after mealtimes, doctors began to assume she had anorexia or bulimia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;In 2019, Lucy spent five months being fed through a tube, as anything she ate was being voided from both ends of her body, before she was then admitted to an eating disorder inpatient unit in north London.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"Because I was such a low weight, and a young girl, they just assumed it was an eating disorder," she explains.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"They admitted me into an eating disorder unit, for six months to stay away from home.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"It was really horrible."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 gXrNRM"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 cMIbKV"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20251203-121739-f954f14c69-web-2.35.1-2/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 gUePlo hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/13b6/live/9420b4a0-cf75-11f0-a892-01d657345866.png.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/13b6/live/9420b4a0-cf75-11f0-a892-01d657345866.png.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/13b6/live/9420b4a0-cf75-11f0-a892-01d657345866.png.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/13b6/live/9420b4a0-cf75-11f0-a892-01d657345866.png.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/13b6/live/9420b4a0-cf75-11f0-a892-01d657345866.png.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/13b6/live/9420b4a0-cf75-11f0-a892-01d657345866.png.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/13b6/live/9420b4a0-cf75-11f0-a892-01d657345866.png.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/13b6/live/9420b4a0-cf75-11f0-a892-01d657345866.png.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Collect/PA Real Life Lucy Dare as an adult, taking a mirror selfie in a gym changing room. She is wearing a white sports bra and blue fitness shorts." class="sc-5340b511-0 hLdNfA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 jVqbAn"&gt;Collect/PA Real Life&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;Lucy has struggled to keep down a job due to Crohn's, but says fitness work has given her "clarity, control, and strength"&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;When her symptoms failed to improve after months in the unit, Lucy was finally referred for an endoscopy and colonoscopy, which revealed she had Crohn's disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;This, however, did not mark the end of her struggles.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Lucy later experienced a perforated bowel due to the disease, which left her vomiting faeces, and had to undergo life-saving surgery to remove 60cm (23.6in) of her small intestine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"The recovery was hard and long, just a long time of being uncomfortable and in pain," she says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Lucy is still struggling to find medication that works for her, and faces regular visits to A&amp;amp;E due to chronic pain and digestive symptoms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Crohn's disease has also made it difficult for Lucy to get work.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"I did have a job last year, but I lost it because I kept having time off all the time for Crohn's. So I haven't been able to work or anything," she says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"It's just been a lot of ups and downs."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;However, she has found the benefits of fitness in managing her condition.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"Fitness gives me clarity, control and a sense of strength that the illness often challenges," she says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 hNbOGD"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 gXmhTb"&gt;What is Crohn's disease?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Crohn's disease is a &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.nhs.uk/conditions/crohns-disease/" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;long-term condition where part of the gut becomes inflamed&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;It cannot currently be cured, but its symptoms can be managed through various treatments and medications.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Common symptoms include diarrhoea, blood or mucus in faeces, stomach pain, fatigue and loss of appetite.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Symptoms most commonly start in teenagers and young adults, but Crohn's can happen at any age.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BBC</author><pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 08:05:04 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiWkFVX3lxTE51VHVaSHhpQmxQUlg3QURfd01BUWNYdTZobFczd2h2UTN1dll0TlpsZTB4SUhpMFI4UllvS3ZMSktSdWoxNlRwcVdPbGI3cEN1dFdYN0U3bjc1UdIBX0FVX3lxTFBZTzY5MlBnSlUyNWY4UHhOQ0tNR0VMRkZGRk9zc3B5Y3BUTUJjUHpERzctMGlFTGpOVGtXM2FlQ3RfQ0xJYmNiazBmbmNseTh4WlZnQXVjeE1MZWlLLWZR</guid></item></channel></rss>