<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>GNews Health</title><link>https://news.google.com/</link><description></description><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>科学家发现辉瑞COVID刺戳与眼睛变化有关，增加角膜损伤风险-每日邮报 | Scientists discover Pfizer COVID jab linked to eye changes that raise corneal damage risk - Daily Mail</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiqgFBVV95cUxOeXBWRl85a3JuMWV6WWVzdjJ2dVBqSFR3UjBmaHd1ZmNiMmZfdWJ2TE85SmZCb0NhMUl3WUtBbFhZUjRjdkl1cGM3UjRvVVdVVXhZN2F5OEsxRG1KVXlncWFoYlQxMkI4OFdoMDFKOGxUMG01bG5jYi05cnk2NEhuVkx5WTM0Y3V2NURWc2RzaklUek1RZWRxNEhmWVFkeFFJM3VCZzlodC1qZ9IBrwFBVV95cUxPVDlmWUk3UHVBYjUwbEl3N2gxM2NDeGRsVFMzZHpNNUtvTFZ2OHJpcXdOYnVFM254OThJem9aR2dteG9sUG1OMk14ZE8zTy1ZSnFwSmhtSS1fUDExeTdNazhBQTluTjNidG1WNlpkSnVzYmt0U2dpWEFUZFAtcVE2a2E2Vi1jWXBuaGdMNF9lUmtDdDV6TmRYRXI3M2toc2c1bW9RWjdsUktwVU1nVGp3?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div itemprop="articleBody"&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Scientists have discovered that &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/pfizer/index.html" id="mol-83ca13b0-63e3-11f0-8403-ab410a00d31a" class=""&gt;Pfizer's&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/coronavirus/index.html" id="mol-dddd0710-6332-11f0-aaa3-89582d67f3b8" class=""&gt;COVID-19&lt;/a&gt; vaccine may increase the risk of eye damage, leading to vision loss. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The new study specifically examined how the vaccine affected patients' corneas, the &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/sciencetech/article-14839199/Man-blinded-Fourth-July-fireworks-grows-new-eye.html"&gt;clear front part of the eye&lt;/a&gt; that allows light to enter.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In 64 people, scientists in Turkey measured changes in the cornea's inner layer, called the endothelium, before taking the first Pfizer dose and two months after receiving the second.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Results revealed that taking both doses of the vaccine led to thicker corneas, fewer endothelial cells in the eye and more variation in size of these specialized cells that form the endothelium.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In the short term, these changes suggest the Pfizer vaccine may temporarily weaken the endothelium, even though patients didn't suffer clear vision problems during the study.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;For people with healthy eyes, these small changes likely won't affect vision right away.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;However, if scientists find that these changes last for years, they could lead to corneal swelling or blurry vision, especially in those with pre-existing eye problems or people who have had a cornea transplant.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;A thicker cornea and reduced cell density could contribute to eye conditions like corneal edema, bullous keratopathy, or corneal decompensation, which can all cause permanent vision loss in severe cases, especially if left untreated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Scientists have discovered a link between the Pfizer COVID-19 vaccine and thickening of the cornea, the clear front part of the eye (Stock Image)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The researchers warned in the study, published Wednesday in the journal &lt;a class="" rel="nofollow noreferrer noopener" target="_blank" href="https://www.tandfonline.com/doi/full/10.1080/09286586.2025.2522724"&gt;Ophthalmic Epidemiology&lt;/a&gt;: 'The endothelium should be closely monitored in those with a low endothelial count or who have had a corneal graft.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;An eye doctor can use a special microscope called specular microscopy to find out if someone has a low endothelial cell count.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;If you have blurry vision or eye discomfort, this test can also check if your cornea’s cells are healthy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;A low count can be the result of aging, eye diseases like Fuchs’ dystrophy, eye surgeries, injuries, or infections. These factors damage the cells that keep your cornea clear, and they don’t grow back. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Specifically, the team found that the Pfizer-BioNTech vaccine caused a patient's cornea to go from 528 to 542 micrometers in thickness, or roughly 0.0208 inches to 0.0213 inches. This is a roughly two-percent increase in micrometers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;A slightly thicker cornea isn't automatically harmful. The cornea can thicken temporarily due to inflammation, fluid buildup, or stress on the endothelium from minor illnesses or injuries to the eyes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;If it stays too thick for months or years, however, it could make the cornea less clear, potentially affecting vision.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The team did not recommend against vaccination and will still need to conduct long-term testing on patients to see if these changes continue to appear months and years after taking the shots. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;The Pfizer-BioNTech mRNA COVID-19 vaccine (pictured) has also been tied to rare inflammatory heart conditions&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The average number of endothelial cells, which keep the cornea clear by pumping out excess fluid, dropped from 2,597 to 2,378 cells per square millimeter in the study, a loss of about eight percent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Normal endothelial cell counts range from 2,000 to 3,000 cells per square millimeter in healthy adults, so 2,378 is still within a safe range for most people.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;However, for someone with a low cell count to start with, due to a previous eye surgery, infection, or disease, this loss could be riskier for their vision.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Researchers also discovered that these cells became less uniform after the vaccination, with their coefficient of variation - each cell's difference in size - increasing from 39 to 42.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;When cells die, nearby cells stretch to fill the gaps, leading to bigger differences in size.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;This could mean the endothelium is less healthy. If this trend continued for years, it could affect the cornea’s clarity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span&gt;After vaccination, the study found fewer cells kept their healthy six-sided shape, with the total dropping from 50 to 48 percent of the cells in the eye.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Healthy endothelial cells are usually shaped like hexagons, which allows them to fit together tightly, like a honeycomb.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Although the two-percent drop was not a direct sign of damage, it suggested to the team that the cells might be reacting to some sort of stress over those two months to three months.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Researchers said their results also showed evidence that the changes had a high likelihood of being directly linked to taking the vaccine, meaning it wasn't just a random anomaly in the testing.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span&gt;If the signs of stress and inflammation drop off shortly after receiving the Pfizer shot, the impact of these minor changes would not be overly harmful. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;A woman undergoes an eye exam. Scientists have found multiple signs of stress in the eye after taking the Pfizer COVID-19 shot (Stock Image)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span&gt;To find these results, the team studied 128 eyes, 64 pairs in total, before each person received their COVID vaccinations.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span&gt;They followed up with the group approximately 75 days after they got their second dose of the Pfizer-BioNTech vaccine.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span&gt;The team used a machine called Sirius corneal topography to measure the corneas' thickness and shape, and another device, the Tomey EM-4000 specular microscope, to take detailed pictures of the endothelial cells to check their number, size and shape.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Each participant also took a full eye exam, including tests for vision sharpness, eye pressure and scans of the eye’s front and back parts to ensure overall eye health.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span&gt;By comparing the measurements taken before vaccination to those after, the researchers could see if the Pfizer vaccine was influencing the health of the eyes.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span&gt;The new data on potentially harmful side-effects linked to Pfizer's COVID vaccine added to a growing list of concerns the Trump Administration has highlighted.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span&gt;In May, the US Food and Drug Administration (FDA) forced Pfizer and Moderna to use &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/health/article-14739333/trump-fda-covid-vaccine-pfizer-moderna-heart-damage.html"&gt;expanded warning labels&lt;/a&gt; about the risks of heart damage tied to COVID-19 vaccines.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The shots previously included warning labels about the rare chance of patients suffering myocarditis, inflammation of the heart muscle, and pericarditis, inflammation of the sac-like lining surrounding the heart.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The new labels expanded that warning to certain age groups, particularly men between the ages of 16 and 25.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Researchers found that this seemingly healthy group appeared to be at the highest risk of the rare complications.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
            

            
            
            
            
            &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Daily Mail</author><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 16:04:18 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiqgFBVV95cUxOeXBWRl85a3JuMWV6WWVzdjJ2dVBqSFR3UjBmaHd1ZmNiMmZfdWJ2TE85SmZCb0NhMUl3WUtBbFhZUjRjdkl1cGM3UjRvVVdVVXhZN2F5OEsxRG1KVXlncWFoYlQxMkI4OFdoMDFKOGxUMG01bG5jYi05cnk2NEhuVkx5WTM0Y3V2NURWc2RzaklUek1RZWRxNEhmWVFkeFFJM3VCZzlodC1qZ9IBrwFBVV95cUxPVDlmWUk3UHVBYjUwbEl3N2gxM2NDeGRsVFMzZHpNNUtvTFZ2OHJpcXdOYnVFM254OThJem9aR2dteG9sUG1OMk14ZE8zTy1ZSnFwSmhtSS1fUDExeTdNazhBQTluTjNidG1WNlpkSnVzYmt0U2dpWEFUZFAtcVE2a2E2Vi1jWXBuaGdMNF9lUmtDdDV6TmRYRXI3M2toc2c1bW9RWjdsUktwVU1nVGp3</guid></item><item><title>美国年轻人的胃肠道癌症激增- Gizmodo | Gastrointestinal Cancers Are Surging Among Younger Americans - Gizmodo</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMilgFBVV95cUxNeFVXMVdpRkhaTjBpM2c4VTJXWW9aY0tWOWNrdGx4WG1EOU52MEpkTEFxVW56MTU2TjJmUFJzSEFCR0o1REdQREZ4dTdEUFp2d3JwSFZwTnhHUzhqVWxzaWYyT2l2bjZBLXQ5OWhsdmVWQ2xKaWlCbk9pcVVjbDVkWm5hVzl1LXgwWHVvV2pYSDhidUFxVEE?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content prose dark:prose-invert lg:prose-lg lg:leading-[29px] font-serif max-w-none"&gt;
              
              
              &lt;p&gt;Young people appear to be increasingly vulnerable to gastrointestinal cancers, but researchers aren’t entirely sure what is driving the surge in disease.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;In a new study out this week, scientists led by the Dana-Farber Cancer Institute found that rates of early-onset GI cancers—those occurring in people younger than 50—are rising more rapidly than other types of cancer. In particular, colorectal cancer cases have significantly increased, while rates of other forms of the disease, like stomach cancer, are creeping up, too. While the paper doesn’t come to definitive conclusions as to why these conditions are becoming more common, the researchers point to risk factors like obesity, a poor diet, and sedentary behavior.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="not-prose my-8 -mx-4 xs:max-w-xs xs:mx-auto"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;“Colorectal cancer is the most common early-onset GI cancer worldwide, accounting for more than half of the cases, but it is not the only GI cancer that is rising in younger adults,” said senior study author Kimmie Ng, director of the Young-Onset Colorectal Cancer Center at Dana-Farber, in a &lt;a href="https://www.dana-farber.org/newsroom/news-releases/2025/global-rise-in-many-early-onset-gi-cancers-detailed-in-two-dana-farber-reviews-with-colorectal-cancer-leading-the-trend"&gt;statement.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;“Unfortunately, pancreatic, gastric, and esophageal cancers are also increasing in young people,” she added.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p class="not-prose"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Ng and her colleagues reviewed data collected from 100 studies, as well as past scientific reviews, and cancer-related guidelines. They also analyzed three publicly available cancer statistic databases.&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;p&gt;Since 2010, the incidence of early-onset GI cancers has been increasing globally, they found, but especially in high-income countries like the U.S. Between 2010 and 2019, the age-adjusted incidence rate in the U.S. increased by 2.16% annually—the greatest increase of any early-onset cancer during that time. In 2022, there were at least 25,000 Americans under 50 who developed GI cancer. The team’s findings were &lt;a href="https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jama/fullarticle/2836671"&gt;published&lt;/a&gt; Thursday in JAMA.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;An earlier, &lt;a href="https://academic.oup.com/bjs/article/112/7/znaf102/8191209?login=false#google_vignette"&gt;separate review of data&lt;/a&gt;—by some of the same authors—over a similar time period concluded that the rate of GI cancer has tripled in young people aged between 15 and 19, and almost doubled in those aged between 20 and 24.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;“The rising incidence of early-onset GI cancers is alarming and underscores the need for enhanced prevention strategies and early detection methods,” said Ng.&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;p&gt;As the rates of these cancers have risen, so have some of their risk factors, including rates of obesity and time spent sitting; ultraprocessed foods are also more common now, especially in Western diets. Still, the researchers estimate that as much as 30% of early-onset GI cancer may be linked to genetic mutations. Other scientists have argued that other issues, like &lt;a href="https://gizmodo.com/scientists-may-have-figured-out-why-young-people-are-getting-colorectal-cancer-more-often-2000594349"&gt;common stomach infections&lt;/a&gt;, could also be driving the increase in cancer rates.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p class="not-prose"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Even as the causes remain unclear, what is clear is that more work needs to be done to help catch these cancers early enough, before they become impossible to treat, the researchers said. In 2020, public health experts recommended routine screening for &lt;a href="https://gizmodo.com/45-is-the-new-50-when-it-comes-to-colorectal-cancer-scr-1845499824"&gt;colorectal cancer in people 45&lt;/a&gt; and up, but the researchers noted that a year later, fewer than 20% of people ages 45 to 49 went for a screening. Another outstanding question is whether early-onset GI cancers are different from those caught later in life, and if so, should they be treated differently.&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;p&gt;“We need to be thinking not only about the risk factors for these diseases but also how to screen, diagnose, and treat young people with these cancers,” said Ng.&lt;/p&gt;
                          &lt;/div&gt;

            &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Gizmodo</author><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 15:12:56 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilgFBVV95cUxNeFVXMVdpRkhaTjBpM2c4VTJXWW9aY0tWOWNrdGx4WG1EOU52MEpkTEFxVW56MTU2TjJmUFJzSEFCR0o1REdQREZ4dTdEUFp2d3JwSFZwTnhHUzhqVWxzaWYyT2l2bjZBLXQ5OWhsdmVWQ2xKaWlCbk9pcVVjbDVkWm5hVzl1LXgwWHVvV2pYSDhidUFxVEE</guid></item><item><title>胶原蛋白注射剂和补充剂真的是年轻肌肤的秘诀吗？ -《卫报》 | Are collagen shots and supplements really the secret to youthful skin? - The Guardian</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMipgFBVV95cUxNOW1IVnhUN2s2emFOQnRPQnZMdWxZblhwTlN3VUtjTzlJNUVjQzVYRmkwTng5cG1WUzBMMWJxaVhob216b1hidTVSNE9Wel9KRW5xMGVFbVNLLXpXbGZKVG1lenFnYW5CLWk1SDF4cDE4OGJtNkcyYW5uZUloM2xJRDBzZlF4dnVWOGZ4NEVva3QzTzZ4ZnRtUjVPeVpTaW50T0VxTWxn?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body-commercial-selector article-body-viewer-selector dcr-11jq3zt"&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-15rw6c2"&gt;F&lt;/span&gt;rom high-end aesthetics clinics to the middle aisle of Lidl, collagen is having a moment. Whether it’s in the form of fruity shots or powdered supplements, this structural protein is being touted as the secret to youthful skin and glossy hair.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;Celebrities are also singing the praises of a collagen-boosting procedure called NeoGen, with the actor &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/reel/DMHolloi7P5/?utm_source=ig_web_copy_link&amp;amp;igsh=MzRlODBiNWFlZA==" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;Leslie Ash&lt;/a&gt; claiming earlier this week that it had “taken 10 years off her”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="sign-in-gate"&gt;&lt;gu-island name="SignInGateSelector" priority="feature" deferuntil="visible" props='{"contentType":"Article","sectionId":"fashion","tags":[{"id":"fashion/skincare","type":"Keyword","title":"Skincare"},{"id":"science/medical-research","type":"Keyword","title":"Medical research"},{"id":"fashion/beauty","type":"Keyword","title":"Beauty"},{"id":"lifeandstyle/lifeandstyle","type":"Keyword","title":"Life and style"},{"id":"lifeandstyle/health-and-wellbeing","type":"Keyword","title":"Health &amp;amp; wellbeing"},{"id":"science/science","type":"Keyword","title":"Science"},{"id":"type/article","type":"Type","title":"Article"},{"id":"tone/features","type":"Tone","title":"Features"},{"id":"profile/linda-geddes","type":"Contributor","title":"Linda Geddes"},{"id":"publication/theguardian","type":"Publication","title":"The Guardian"},{"id":"theguardian/mainsection","type":"NewspaperBook","title":"Main section"},{"id":"theguardian/mainsection/uknews","type":"NewspaperBookSection","title":"UK news"},{"id":"tracking/commissioningdesk/uk-home-news","type":"Tracking","title":"UK Home News"}],"isPaidContent":false,"isPreview":false,"host":"https://www.theguardian.com","pageId":"fashion/2025/jul/18/do-collagen-shots-supplements-really-work-youthful-skin","idUrl":"https://profile.theguardian.com","contributionsServiceUrl":"https://contributions.guardianapis.com","editionId":"US"}'&gt;&lt;/gu-island&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;But amid the glowing endorsements and glossy marketing, a fundamental question remains: can anything else really boost collagen – and is it desirable to do so?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;Collagens are a group of proteins that provide structural support and mechanical strength to the gel-like extracellular matrix in skin, cartilage and other body tissues. There are various types, each comprising long chains of amino acids that wind together to form strong fibres called fibrils.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;Viewed under an electron microscope, these fibrils form a basket-like mesh in young, healthy skin. But as we age, the amount of collagen declines and its structure becomes more cross-linked and fragmented.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;“In younger skin, the fibres tend to be longer and more flexible, but in older skin, they’re shorter and more rigid, primarily as a result of UV damage,” said Prof John Connelly, who studies skin repair and regeneration at Queen Mary University of London.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;Collagen is not the only protein that keeps skin looking youthful. Elastin allows skin to stretch and spring back, while other structural proteins help to organise and stabilise collagen. Long sugar chains known as glycosaminoglycans – including the popular skincare ingredient hyaluronic acid – play a key role in hydrating&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;the tissue. Like collagen, these components degrade and change with age, contributing to sagging, reduced plumpness and wrinkles.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;Yet collagen continues to dominate the spotlight. Many skincare products list it as an ingredient but “these proteins are very large, so they don’t easily cross the skin barrier when applied topically”, said &lt;a href="https://www.kcl.ac.uk/people/tanya-shaw" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;Prof Tanya Shaw&lt;/a&gt;, a spokesperson for the British Skin Foundation and expert in wound healing at King’s College London. That said, collagen in creams may help draw moisture to the skin’s surface, providing a temporary plumping effect.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;Collagen drinks are the latest plot twist. Their aim is to supply the raw materials for fibroblasts, the skin cells responsible for collagen production. There was also evidence that fragments of extracellular matrix proteins might act as signals, stimulating fibroblasts to produce not just collagen but also elastin and hyaluronic acid, said Dr Jonathan Kentley, a consultant dermatologist at the Montrose clinic in London and Chelsea and Westminster hospital.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;Most collagen supplements use fragments derived from chicken, fish or pork, which are absorbed through the gut and transported to the skin via the bloodstream. However, many are probably broken down further during digestion and it is unclear whether other&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;dietary proteins would offer similar building blocks, according to Connelly and Shaw.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;Even if some fragments do reach the skin, they would be working in a damaged environment. “If you start to make new collagen, where does it go, and how does it interact with the existing collagen?” said &lt;a href="https://research.manchester.ac.uk/en/persons/michael.sherratt" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;Dr Mike Sherratt&lt;/a&gt;, a skin mechanics expert at the University of Manchester. Also, “if it gets into the bloodstream, it’s not only going to affect the skin, but presumably other organs and tissues as well”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;Animal studies offer some support for collagen supplements: radio-labelled collagen fragments have been shown to reach the skin and boost gene activity linked to collagen production in mice. “Mouse studies have also shown reduced wrinkle formation following UV exposure,” said Kentley.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;Some human trials have also reported improved hydration, elasticity, and fewer wrinkles after consuming fish collagen. But most of these were industry-funded and a recent &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0002934325002839#sec0015" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;meta-analysis&lt;/a&gt; of 23 studies found that only those receiving funding from companies showed significant effects. Kentley said: “When the studies were separated into high-quality and low-quality studies, the high-quality studies showed no skin benefits. So, these results must be interpreted with extreme caution.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;What about medical procedures such as NeoGen? It uses high-frequency radio waves to covert nitrogen gas into plasma (ionised gas), which delivers controlled heat to deeper layers of the skin. Animal studies suggest this controlled thermal damage alters collagen structure, causing skin tightening, and promotes the shedding of surface layers, improving tone and texture.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;“Small clinical studies on patients have also shown an improvement in skin tone and wrinkling,” said Kentley. “However, as this is a relatively new technology there is relatively little evidence other than a handful of small studies.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;Other procedures such as microneedling also induce tiny, controlled injuries to the skin, triggering a wound healing response, while injectable “biostimulators” – such as Sculptra – create a foreign body response that stimulates fibroblasts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;While all these procedures have some clinical evidence supporting their ability to stimulate new collagen, the quality is variable and no head-to-head trials have pitted these products and procedures against each other.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;Kentley said: “Given that aesthetic medicine is so highly personalised and each product or procedure will have its own benefits and risks, the best way to know what is right for you is by seeing a qualified physician who is not conflicted by the quest for profit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;“In terms of topical treatments, there are decades of evidence to support the use of tretinoin [a prescription-strength retinoid] to boost collagen production and reduce other signs of skin ageing such as pigmentation.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;Although celebrity endorsements and dramatic before-and-after pictures can be persuasive, it is also worth remembering that these procedures are not a permanent fix for skin ageing – they require continuing treatments, which can be costly. The most effective long-term strategy to protect and preserve your collagen is to minimise UV exposure from an early age, through consistent use of sunscreen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;Sherratt showed me a photo of him during &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2022/jul/19/britain-heatwave-1976-crisis-summer-heat" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;Britain’s 1976 heatwave&lt;/a&gt;, when he was nine. Unlike the proteins inside our cells that are regularly renewed, he said, type I collagen in the dermis had a half-life of about 15 years and elastin was thought to be meant to last a lifetime. “These proteins accumulate damage over time. So, it’s highly likely that some of the extracellular matrix proteins in my face and forearm still carry damage from that 1976 holiday.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;For those of us who did not faithfully apply sunscreen in our youth, it is worth being realistic about how much even the most advanced treatments can achieve. While they may temporarily firm and smooth the skin, the deeper biological damage has already taken place – and much of it may be irreversible.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Guardian</author><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 14:02:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipgFBVV95cUxNOW1IVnhUN2s2emFOQnRPQnZMdWxZblhwTlN3VUtjTzlJNUVjQzVYRmkwTng5cG1WUzBMMWJxaVhob216b1hidTVSNE9Wel9KRW5xMGVFbVNLLXpXbGZKVG1lenFnYW5CLWk1SDF4cDE4OGJtNkcyYW5uZUloM2xJRDBzZlF4dnVWOGZ4NEVva3QzTzZ4ZnRtUjVPeVpTaW50T0VxTWxn</guid></item><item><title>为什么美国人燃烧的卡路里比以往任何时候都多，但体重却不断增加-研究发现 | Why Americans Keep Gaining Weight Despite Burning More Calories Than Ever - Study Finds</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMingFBVV95cUxNM25MZjRSOExkYnM5V01MVTZxbm1SSUVqOUtYOFVJbjdHWl8yTmY3bll3R1d5VlltWGt3OGh4WGIzczIwZE9rZE5fN05KbE1xV2ZHRkxiaE9aNnhKa0JYSFczNUhBOXBtZDc2TU5PR2c5MkVwSVM2b3hUS0d0Mm9oWUZWS05mcE1ZNHVodmFyMTNPQndZYUhkY25uSGJKZw?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content"&gt;&lt;div class="post-featured-image"&gt;&lt;picture&gt;
&lt;source type="image/webp" data-lazy-srcset="https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Overweight-1200x675.jpeg.webp"&gt;&lt;/source&gt;
&lt;img src="" alt="Overweight man with belly popping out of shirt" data-lazy-src="https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Overweight-1200x675.jpeg"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;img src="https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/Overweight-1200x675.jpeg" alt="Overweight man with belly popping out of shirt"&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;
&lt;/picture&gt;
&lt;p class="post-featured-image-caption"&gt;(© Anastasia - stock.adobe.com)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-global-study-of-4-000-people-reveals-processed-food-not-lack-of-exercise-drives-obesity-epidemic"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Global study of 4,000+ people reveals processed food, not lack of exercise, drives obesity epidemic&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;div class="wp-block-group has-octonary-background-color has-background is-layout-constrained wp-block-group-is-layout-constrained"&gt;
&lt;h3 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-in-a-nutshell"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;In A Nutshell&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;



&lt;ul class="wp-block-list"&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A global study of 4,213 adults finds that people in wealthier countries actually burn &lt;em&gt;more&lt;/em&gt; daily calories than those in traditional lifestyles.&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;Obesity in developed nations is not driven by inactivity but by increased intake, especially of ultra-processed foods.&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;Physical activity levels did &lt;em&gt;not&lt;/em&gt; significantly decline with economic development, challenging common obesity assumptions.&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;The percentage of ultra-processed food in the diet was strongly linked to higher body fat, suggesting food quality—not movement—is the key issue.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DURHAM, N.C. —&lt;/strong&gt; Americans burn more calories daily than people living traditional lifestyles in developing countries. Yet we’re also significantly fatter. How can that be?&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;A Duke University study of 4,213 people spanning 34 populations worldwide — from Tanzanian hunter-gatherers to Norwegian office workers — shows that &lt;a href="https://studyfinds.org/tag/weight-gain/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;expanding waistlines&lt;/a&gt; have little to do with becoming less active. What we eat, not how much we move, is the real driver.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The research, published in the &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.pnas.org/doi/10.1073/pnas.2420902122" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Proceedings of the National Academy of Sciences&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;, found that “daily energy expenditures are greater in developed populations, and activity energy expenditures are not reduced in more industrialized populations.” This directly challenges the common assumption that declining physical activity is the main cause of &lt;a href="https://studyfinds.org/tag/obesity/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;obesity&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;As the authors write in the study’s significance section, these results “suggest that &lt;a href="https://studyfinds.org/category/food/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;dietary intake &lt;/a&gt;plays a far greater role than reduced expenditure in the elevated prevalence of obesity associated with economic development.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-developed-countries-actually-burn-more-daily-calories"&gt;Developed Countries Actually Burn More Daily Calories&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;To measure how many calories people actually burn each day, the researchers used a technique called “doubly labeled water,” which tracks how quickly the body processes certain harmless isotopes over 7 to 14 days. It’s considered the most accurate method available for measuring total energy expenditure in real-world settings.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Surprisingly, the study found that people in more economically developed countries &lt;a href="https://studyfinds.org/fitness-trackers-fitbit-calories-inaccurate/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;burned more&lt;/a&gt; calories per day than those in less developed ones. This wasn’t just because they were taller or heavier, though body size did explain part of the difference. Even after adjusting for weight and muscle mass, the difference in calories burned was modest, only about 6%.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The researchers also expected to see lower &lt;a href="https://studyfinds.org/effects-sitting-offset-by-30-minutes-exercise/"&gt;physical activity levels&lt;/a&gt; in wealthier nations, but that wasn’t the case. Across all 34 populations studied, people in industrialized societies were just as physically active as those in traditional or rural settings. There was “no significant change” in physical activity levels with economic development, meaning people across different lifestyles generally moved their bodies just as much.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;div class="wp-block-group has-octonary-background-color has-background is-layout-constrained wp-block-group-is-layout-constrained"&gt;
&lt;figure class="wp-block-image size-large"&gt;&lt;img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" src="" alt="Overweight or obese man exercising" class="wp-image-45215" data-lazy-srcset="https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2021/06/AdobeStock_296619733.jpeg 1200w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2021/06/AdobeStock_296619733-378x252.jpeg 378w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2021/06/AdobeStock_296619733-276x184.jpeg 276w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2021/06/AdobeStock_296619733-600x400.jpeg 600w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2021/06/AdobeStock_296619733-400x267.jpeg 400w" data-lazy-sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" data-lazy-src="https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2021/06/AdobeStock_296619733-1200x800.jpeg"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" src="https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2021/06/AdobeStock_296619733-1200x800.jpeg" alt="Overweight or obese man exercising" class="wp-image-45215" srcset="https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2021/06/AdobeStock_296619733.jpeg 1200w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2021/06/AdobeStock_296619733-378x252.jpeg 378w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2021/06/AdobeStock_296619733-276x184.jpeg 276w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2021/06/AdobeStock_296619733-600x400.jpeg 600w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2021/06/AdobeStock_296619733-400x267.jpeg 400w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px"&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;figcaption class="wp-element-caption"&gt;Despite people in wealthier countries getting more physical activity, researchers say it’s the constant consumption of ultra-processed foods that influenced weight gain. (© New Africa – stock.adobe.com)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;



&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-how-ultra-processed-foods-drive-weight-gain"&gt;How Ultra-Processed Foods Drive Weight Gain&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The real difference between countries wasn’t how much people moved. It was what they ate.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Among the 25 populations where dietary data were available, one trend stood out clearly: the more &lt;a href="https://studyfinds.org/tag/ultra-processed-food/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;ultra-processed foods&lt;/a&gt; people consumed, the more body fat they tended to carry. These foods — like &lt;a href="https://studyfinds.org/tag/sugary-drinks" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;sugary drinks&lt;/a&gt;, packaged snacks, and ready-to-eat meals — are industrially made and often contain long lists of ingredients.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;According to the researchers, one likely explanation is that these foods are easier to digest, which means the body absorbs more calories from them. Less energy is lost during digestion, and more gets stored. Some studies suggest these foods may also interfere with the body’s hunger signals, causing people to eat more than they need.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Even though people in wealthier countries were burning more calories, they were also eating more; and not just more food overall, but more food that seems to encourage &lt;a href="https://studyfinds.org/fat-around-muscles-deadlier/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;fat storage&lt;/a&gt;. Because participants in the study maintained a stable weight during the measurement period, the researchers were able to infer that calorie intake must have closely matched calorie expenditure at the time. That means the high calorie burn in developed countries is matched by equally high consumption, likely driven by food quality rather than quantity alone&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-what-this-means-for-fighting-obesity"&gt;What This Means for Fighting Obesity&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The researchers emphasize that physical activity is still vital for &lt;a href="https://studyfinds.org/category/wellness/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;overall health&lt;/a&gt;. It lowers the risk of &lt;a href="https://studyfinds.org/tag/heart-disease/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;heart disease&lt;/a&gt;, improves &lt;a href="https://studyfinds.org/tag/mental-health/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;mental well-being&lt;/a&gt;, and helps maintain a &lt;a href="https://studyfinds.org/tag/metabolism/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;healthy metabolism&lt;/a&gt;. But when it comes specifically to obesity, the biggest factor appears to be the kind of food people eat, not how much they move.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Interestingly, the study also found that much of the increase in body mass in wealthier countries came from muscle and lean tissue, not just fat. In other words, better access to nutrition helps support healthy growth, even as it contributes to weight gain. Still, body fat increased more than &lt;a href="https://studyfinds.org/tag/muscle-mass/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;muscle mass&lt;/a&gt;, pointing to a mismatch between calorie intake and the body’s needs.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;What stood out most was this: the differences in body fat between rich and poor countries were about 10 times greater than any differences linked to how many calories people burned. That’s a powerful argument for focusing on the food environment — what’s available, affordable, and marketed to people — rather than just telling individuals to exercise more.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;For decades, public health campaigns have leaned on the slogan “eat less, move more.” This study suggests it’s time to shift focus. The root of the &lt;a href="https://studyfinds.org/tag/obesity/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;obesity crisis&lt;/a&gt; may not be laziness, but the global rise of ultra-processed foods that are cheap, convenient, and engineered to be overeaten.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Disclaimer:&lt;/strong&gt; This study is observational and cross-sectional, meaning it cannot establish cause-and-effect relationships. While the data strongly support associations between economic development, ultra-processed food consumption, and obesity, the authors note that more research is needed to clarify the underlying physiological and environmental mechanisms. Additionally, dietary data were only available for a subset of populations. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;div class="wp-block-group has-quaternary-background-color has-background is-layout-constrained wp-block-group-is-layout-constrained"&gt;
&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-paper-summary"&gt;Paper Summary&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;h4 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-methodology"&gt;Methodology&lt;/h4&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Researchers analyzed data from 4,213 adults aged 18–60 across 34 populations representing different levels of economic development, from hunter-gatherers to industrialized societies. They used the doubly labeled water method, considered the gold standard for measuring energy expenditure, which tracks isotope depletion in body water over 7–14 days to calculate total daily calories burned. Body composition was measured using deuterium dilution to determine fat-free mass, fat mass, and body fat percentage. Economic development was categorized using the UN Human Development Index, which incorporates measures of wealth, education, and life expectancy. The study also examined dietary data from 25 populations, including the percentage of ultra-processed foods in people’s diets.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h4 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-results"&gt;Results&lt;/h4&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Body fat percentage and obesity rates increased significantly with economic development across all populations studied. However, total daily energy expenditure was actually higher in more developed countries, primarily due to larger body sizes. When adjusted for body size, energy expenditure decreased only modestly (6–11%) with development, and this small difference could explain only about one-tenth of the obesity differences between populations. Surprisingly, physical activity energy expenditure showed no significant decline with economic development. Among populations with dietary data, the percentage of ultra-processed foods in the diet was positively correlated with body fat percentage, demonstrating that dietary intake rather than reduced energy expenditure drives obesity in developed countries.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h4 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-limitations"&gt;Limitations&lt;/h4&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The study used cross-sectional data, making it impossible to establish causality in the relationships between economic development, diet, and obesity. Detailed dietary information was available for only 25 of the 34 populations studied. The research could not identify specific environmental, social, or physiological factors that promote increased calorie intake and absorption in developed settings. Some energy expenditure measurements used estimated rather than directly measured basal metabolic rates. The study also couldn’t resolve whether differences in food quality, quantity, digestibility, or other factors drive the dietary effects observed.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h4 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-funding-and-disclosures"&gt;Funding and Disclosures&lt;/h4&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The study was supported by multiple funding sources including the US National Science Foundation, Chinese Academy of Sciences, International Atomic Energy Agency, and various other research institutions. The Doubly Labeled Water Database used in the research is supported by the International Atomic Energy Agency. The authors declared no competing financial interests that could bias the research findings.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h4 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-publication-information"&gt;Publication Information&lt;/h4&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The paper “Energy expenditure and obesity across the economic spectrum” was published in the &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.pnas.org/doi/10.1073/pnas.2420902122" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Proceedings of the National Academy of Sciences&lt;/a&gt; (PNAS)&lt;/em&gt; on July 14, 2025. The research was conducted by an international consortium of scientists led by Amanda McGrosky (Elon University), Amy Luke (Loyola University), and Herman Pontzer (Duke University), among many other contributors from institutions worldwide. The study is available as an open-access publication under Creative Commons licensing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Study Finds</author><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 13:49:14 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMingFBVV95cUxNM25MZjRSOExkYnM5V01MVTZxbm1SSUVqOUtYOFVJbjdHWl8yTmY3bll3R1d5VlltWGt3OGh4WGIzczIwZE9rZE5fN05KbE1xV2ZHRkxiaE9aNnhKa0JYSFczNUhBOXBtZDc2TU5PR2c5MkVwSVM2b3hUS0d0Mm9oWUZWS05mcE1ZNHVodmFyMTNPQndZYUhkY25uSGJKZw</guid></item><item><title>亚利桑那州的一名居民刚刚死于瘟疫。关于这种疾病的须知事项- CNN | An Arizona resident has just died of the plague. What to know about this disease - CNN</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiigFBVV95cUxQcUVhMGZEbXZpbXB5R3NHd1FQdFYtVVlxVWV2Uy1DbHBaaF9talAtQUZrcnlvQURXaGpOZjVHNkJ0aHhPcVFZOWhfVFZMTHVSR0RHdE9nR1YwYVdkcjJqeGF6TEZYNjkyRXFaMjB4ZkJDbW1BNGtPSXVmQ1dyYWdKWUVyRlUwUDVpeVHSAY8BQVVfeXFMTjFEN291S2pUbGI5dFJMSFpHaURKMk5TcHNlNHZyTVFYNUNqMkE3TXV0QzlfNTRWa0llQWNPNnFyTl96UkgyMWE3b2J0akx3X3IxQ0lLQVhPN2JEUkJaTDMwdXB0OE5uamZFU3p2cEJuT3V1U3JyZ0NtLVFDZGEzZmVBY1JkdFp6SnRqNlR0VzQ?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article__content" data-editable="content" itemprop="articleBody" data-reorderable="content"&gt;
                  &lt;div data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/action-bar/instances/cmd6i2mf4000r26nseicf0baw@published" data-label-id-prefix="action-bar-start-of-article" class="action-bar" data-dynamic-breakpoint-placement='{"extraLarge":{"placement":".layout-article-elevate__left"}}' data-expand-conditions='{"follow":{"extraLarge":{"alwaysExpand":true}},"shareOptions":{"large":{"maxNumOfActions":1},"medium":{"maxNumOfActions":1},"extraLarge":{"withAction":"follow","maxNumOfActions":2}}}'&gt;
    &lt;p class="action-bar__overlay"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;div class="action-bar__action-sheet" tabindex="-1"&gt;
        
            &lt;div class="action-bar__action-sheet--action" data-title="share options"&gt;
                  &lt;div data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/social-share/instances/cmd6i2mf4000u26ns3fko5n5e@published" class="social-share_labelled-list"&gt;
    &lt;div class="social-share_labelled-list__share-links vossi-social-share_labelled-list" data-type="share-links"&gt;
        &lt;button class="social-share_labelled-list__share" data-url="https://www.facebook.com/dialog/share?app_id=80401312489&amp;amp;href=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.cnn.com%2F2025%2F07%2F18%2Fhealth%2Fpneumonic-plague-bacteria-infection-wellness&amp;amp;display=popup" data-type="facebook" aria-label="share with facebook" title="Share with Facebook"&gt;
                &lt;svg class="icon-facebook-circle" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 16 16" fill="none"&gt;
&lt;path d="M8.04139 1.33301C11.7458 1.33301 14.7488 4.33601 14.7488 8.04042C14.7488 11.3884 12.296 14.1632 9.08943 14.6663V9.97928H10.6523L10.9497 8.04042H9.08943V6.78225C9.08943 6.25182 9.34934 5.73475 10.1825 5.73475H11.0283V4.08409C11.0283 4.08409 10.2607 3.95309 9.52685 3.95309C7.99476 3.95309 6.99336 4.88165 6.99336 6.56269V8.04042H5.29031V9.97928H6.99336V14.6663C3.78677 14.1632 1.33398 11.3882 1.33398 8.04042C1.33398 4.33601 4.33699 1.33301 8.04139 1.33301Z" fill="#0C0C0C"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;
&lt;/svg&gt;

                &lt;span class="social-share_labelled-list__share-links--label"&gt;Facebook&lt;/span&gt;
        &lt;/button&gt;
        &lt;button class="social-share_labelled-list__share" data-url="https://twitter.com/intent/tweet?text=Check%20out%20this%20article%3A&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.cnn.com%2F2025%2F07%2F18%2Fhealth%2Fpneumonic-plague-bacteria-infection-wellness" data-type="x" aria-label="share with x" title="Share with X"&gt;
                &lt;svg class="icon-x-share" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 16 16" fill="none"&gt;
&lt;path fill-rule="evenodd" clip-rule="evenodd" d="M5.99386 8.11503L0 0.666992H4.74756L8.44753 5.27039L12.4004 0.687719H15.0151L9.71175 6.84331L16 14.667H11.2666L7.2603 9.6887L2.98317 14.6532H0.354296L5.99386 8.11503ZM11.9565 13.287L2.91105 2.04698H4.0571L13.0912 13.287H11.9565Z" fill="#0C0C0C"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;
&lt;/svg&gt;

                &lt;span class="social-share_labelled-list__share-links--label"&gt;Tweet&lt;/span&gt;
        &lt;/button&gt;
        &lt;a class="social-share_labelled-list__share" href="mailto:?subject=CNN%20content%20share&amp;amp;body=Check%20out%20this%20article%3A%0Ahttps%3A%2F%2Fwww.cnn.com%2F2025%2F07%2F18%2Fhealth%2Fpneumonic-plague-bacteria-infection-wellness" data-type="email" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" aria-label="share with email" title="Share with email"&gt;
                &lt;svg class="icon-email-share" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 24 24" fill="none"&gt;
&lt;path fill-rule="evenodd" clip-rule="evenodd" d="M2 6C2 4.89543 2.89543 4 4 4H20C21.1046 4 22 4.89543 22 6V18C22 19.1046 21.1046 20 20 20H4C2.89543 20 2 19.1046 2 18V6ZM4 6H20V9.11604L12 11.9396L4 9.11604V6ZM4 11.237V18H20V11.237L12.3328 13.943C12.1174 14.019 11.8825 14.019 11.6672 13.943L4 11.237Z" fill="#0C0C0C"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;
&lt;/svg&gt;

                &lt;span class="social-share_labelled-list__share-links--label"&gt;Email&lt;/span&gt;
        &lt;/a&gt;
        &lt;button class="social-share_labelled-list__share" data-url="https://www.cnn.com/2025/07/18/health/pneumonic-plague-bacteria-infection-wellness" data-type="copy" aria-label="copy link to clipboard" title="Copy link to clipboard"&gt;
                &lt;svg class="icon-hyperlink" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 16 16" fill="none"&gt;
&lt;path fill-rule="evenodd" clip-rule="evenodd" d="M5.64373 10.3574C5.38338 10.0971 5.38338 9.67496 5.64373 9.41461L9.88637 5.17197C10.1467 4.91162 10.5688 4.91162 10.8292 5.17197C11.0895 5.43232 11.0895 5.85443 10.8292 6.11478L6.58654 10.3574C6.32619 10.6178 5.90408 10.6178 5.64373 10.3574Z" fill="#0C0C0C"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;
&lt;path d="M4.22952 8.94321L5.64373 7.52899C5.90408 7.26865 5.90408 6.84654 5.64373 6.58619C5.38338 6.32584 4.96127 6.32584 4.70092 6.58619L3.28671 8.0004C1.98496 9.30215 1.98496 11.4127 3.28671 12.7144C4.58846 14.0162 6.69901 14.0162 8.00075 12.7144L9.41497 11.3002C9.67532 11.0399 9.67532 10.6178 9.41497 10.3574C9.15462 10.0971 8.73251 10.0971 8.47216 10.3574L7.05795 11.7716C6.2769 12.5527 5.01057 12.5527 4.22952 11.7716C3.44847 10.9906 3.44847 9.72426 4.22952 8.94321Z" fill="#0C0C0C"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;
&lt;path d="M8.94356 4.22916L7.52935 5.64338C7.269 5.90373 6.84689 5.90373 6.58654 5.64338C6.32619 5.38303 6.32619 4.96092 6.58654 4.70057L8.00075 3.28635C9.3025 1.98461 11.4131 1.98461 12.7148 3.28635C14.0165 4.5881 14.0165 6.69865 12.7148 8.0004L11.3006 9.41461C11.0402 9.67496 10.6181 9.67496 10.3578 9.41461C10.0974 9.15426 10.0974 8.73215 10.3578 8.4718L11.772 7.05759C12.553 6.27654 12.553 5.01021 11.772 4.22916C10.9909 3.44812 9.72461 3.44811 8.94356 4.22916Z" fill="#0C0C0C"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;
&lt;/svg&gt;

                &lt;span class="social-share_labelled-list__share-links--label"&gt;Link&lt;/span&gt;
        &lt;/button&gt;
        
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;button class="social-share_labelled-list__open" data-type="open" aria-label="open social share" title="Open social share"&gt;
        &lt;svg class="icon-ui-share-os" viewbox="0 0 24 24" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"&gt;&lt;path d="M19 12c.394 0 .714.32.714.714v8.572c0 .394-.32.714-.714.714H4.714A.715.715 0 014 21.286v-8.572a.715.715 0 011.429 0v7.857h12.857v-7.857c0-.394.32-.714.714-.714zm-7.664-9.79a.73.73 0 011.024 0l.076.075 4.916 4.854c.183.18.27.449.188.69a.734.734 0 01-1.216.314L12.57 4.5v11.786c0 .357-.357.714-.714.714s-.714-.359-.714-.714V4.5L7.372 8.143a.73.73 0 01-1.102-.091c-.21-.289-.149-.694.106-.946l4.884-4.821z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;

    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;button class="social-share_labelled-list__close" data-type="close" aria-label="close social share" title="Close social share"&gt;
        &lt;svg class="icon-ui-close" viewbox="0 0 24 24" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"&gt;&lt;path d="M19.787 18.758l-6.792-6.781 6.746-6.735a.728.728 0 00-1.028-1.03l-6.747 6.737-6.711-6.7a.728.728 0 00-1.028 1.03l6.71 6.698-6.723 6.712a.727.727 0 101.027 1.03l6.725-6.714 6.793 6.782a.725.725 0 001.028 0 .727.727 0 000-1.03"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;

    &lt;/button&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

            &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    
&lt;/div&gt;


    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmd6i2mf4000t26ns647d6oh2@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            &lt;a href="https://nam11.safelinks.protection.outlook.com/?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.coconino.az.gov%2FCivicAlerts.aspx%3FAID%3D3242%26fbclid%3DIwY2xjawLfXHRleHRuA2FlbQIxMABicmlkETFCd3hlUjY2M1ZGNURMRFdFAR5cdhAbD4Nab71-FQNNDDI_CXVgccQw2SMLR5OknCEoxkTUi1wDajEe0TzLvQ_aem_WYG09QZujnbgF13qssTFqQ&amp;amp;data=05%7C02%7CLee.Smith1%40wbdcontractor.com%7C56b895ea96eb4de6f08c08ddc4aa421b%7C0eb48825e8714459bc72d0ecd68f1f39%7C0%7C0%7C638882957727350616%7CUnknown%7CTWFpbGZsb3d8eyJFbXB0eU1hcGkiOnRydWUsIlYiOiIwLjAuMDAwMCIsIlAiOiJXaW4zMiIsIkFOIjoiTWFpbCIsIldUIjoyfQ%3D%3D%7C0%7C%7C%7C&amp;amp;sdata=XtnzWUVYRAIUUZuL2NXzTcBlX4K7rT%2FCs5m18Y5TbPM%3D&amp;amp;reserved=0" target="_blank"&gt;A person died from pneumonic plague&lt;/a&gt; in Arizona last week, the first death from the disease in this region in nearly two decades.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmd6ij16l000l3b6npdw4wbk2@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            This death might bring to mind the bubonic plague, the form of the plague that killed &lt;a href="https://nam11.safelinks.protection.outlook.com/?url=https%3A%2F%2Fmy.clevelandclinic.org%2Fhealth%2Fdiseases%2F21590-bubonic-plague&amp;amp;data=05%7C02%7CLee.Smith1%40wbdcontractor.com%7C56b895ea96eb4de6f08c08ddc4aa421b%7C0eb48825e8714459bc72d0ecd68f1f39%7C0%7C0%7C638882957727378234%7CUnknown%7CTWFpbGZsb3d8eyJFbXB0eU1hcGkiOnRydWUsIlYiOiIwLjAuMDAwMCIsIlAiOiJXaW4zMiIsIkFOIjoiTWFpbCIsIldUIjoyfQ%3D%3D%7C0%7C%7C%7C&amp;amp;sdata=Y83aweM5Rmp%2F3mKY68Q7OxFVrRcrd8%2BSu6v2nXC5L8I%3D&amp;amp;reserved=0" target="_blank"&gt;millions during the Middle Ages&lt;/a&gt;. This latest case is not the same form, and treatments have certainly advanced since that time. That said, I wanted to know what pneumonic plague is, how it’s spread and what its symptoms are. How is it diagnosed, and what treatments are available? What can people do to reduce the risk of contracting the disease? And how much should people be worried about plague?
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmd6ij16m000m3b6napsux1tk@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            To help with these questions, I spoke with CNN wellness expert Dr. Leana Wen. Wen is an emergency physician and clinical associate professor at George Washington University. She previously was Baltimore’s health commissioner.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmd6i2ntp00003b6npyq6r6u2@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            &lt;strong&gt;CNN:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;What is pneumonic plague?&lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmd6imbfp000t3b6n9wn9kr7a@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            &lt;strong&gt;Dr.&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Leana Wen: &lt;/strong&gt;Pneumonic plague is one of three types of plagues that are caused by the bacterium Yersinia pestis. The &lt;a href="https://nam11.safelinks.protection.outlook.com/?url=https%3A%2F%2Fmy.clevelandclinic.org%2Fhealth%2Fdiseases%2F17782-plague&amp;amp;data=05%7C02%7CLee.Smith1%40wbdcontractor.com%7C56b895ea96eb4de6f08c08ddc4aa421b%7C0eb48825e8714459bc72d0ecd68f1f39%7C0%7C0%7C638882957727398100%7CUnknown%7CTWFpbGZsb3d8eyJFbXB0eU1hcGkiOnRydWUsIlYiOiIwLjAuMDAwMCIsIlAiOiJXaW4zMiIsIkFOIjoiTWFpbCIsIldUIjoyfQ%3D%3D%7C0%7C%7C%7C&amp;amp;sdata=2eS3FL1Pz26EPW3LnYfIENdL%2FCkJwl1vgUkYjcPVL4Y%3D&amp;amp;reserved=0" target="_blank"&gt;type of plague&lt;/a&gt; someone has is classified based on where the bacteria are concentrated. Bubonic plague infects lymph nodes. Septicemic plague is when the bacteria cause a whole-body infection through the bloodstream, and pneumonic plague affects the lungs.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmd6im98l000r3b6norxbp95n@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            &lt;strong&gt;CNN: How does someone contract plague? Can it be spread from person to person?&lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmd6iorqt000y3b6nylafreuw@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            &lt;strong&gt;Wen:&lt;/strong&gt; It depends on the type of plague. Bubonic plague is typically caused by the bite of an infected &lt;a href="https://nam11.safelinks.protection.outlook.com/?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.cnn.com%2F2024%2F07%2F05%2Fhealth%2Fplague-human-risk-explainer%2Findex.html&amp;amp;data=05%7C02%7CLee.Smith1%40wbdcontractor.com%7C56b895ea96eb4de6f08c08ddc4aa421b%7C0eb48825e8714459bc72d0ecd68f1f39%7C0%7C0%7C638882957727415565%7CUnknown%7CTWFpbGZsb3d8eyJFbXB0eU1hcGkiOnRydWUsIlYiOiIwLjAuMDAwMCIsIlAiOiJXaW4zMiIsIkFOIjoiTWFpbCIsIldUIjoyfQ%3D%3D%7C0%7C%7C%7C&amp;amp;sdata=frtW1Y%2BLSAgysz6NOX%2B6kwGgdGKL9XWiAuZw8Dp2wHY%3D&amp;amp;reserved=0" target="_blank"&gt;rodent flea&lt;/a&gt;. It can progress to septicemic plague, which can also arise as a result of handling infected animals such as rats and cats. Cats and other animals can contract the plague through eating rodents or through the bite of fleas.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmd6iorqt000z3b6n907743m2@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Pneumonic plague develops when the bacteria spread to the lungs in someone who started out with bubonic or septicemic plague. It can also occur when the bacteria are directly transmitted through airborne droplets — if someone inhales droplets containing the Yersinia bacteria that are coughed by an infected person or animal. This is the only form of the plague that can be spread from person to person.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmd6iorqt00103b6n43epic39@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            &lt;strong&gt;CNN: What are the symptoms of the three types of plague?&lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmd6iorqt00113b6ndnzqb6bd@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            &lt;strong&gt;Wen:&lt;/strong&gt; People infected with all three forms develop common infectious symptoms including fever, headache, chills and weakness. Those with bubonic plague have one or more swollen and painful lymph nodes, also called buboes. In septicemic plague, the seeding of bacteria to other parts of the body can cause multi-organ failure and total body shock. Pneumonic plague is characterized by a rapidly progressing pneumonia with symptoms of shortness of breath, cough and chest pain.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmd6iopin000w3b6nl52uli48@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            &lt;strong&gt;CNN: Is plague common?&lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmd6iq4hg00163b6nxvenq5tu@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            &lt;strong&gt;Wen&lt;/strong&gt;: No. There are an average of seven human plague cases reported each year in the United States, according to &lt;a href="https://nam11.safelinks.protection.outlook.com/?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.cdc.gov%2Fplague%2Fmaps-statistics%2Findex.html&amp;amp;data=05%7C02%7CLee.Smith1%40wbdcontractor.com%7C56b895ea96eb4de6f08c08ddc4aa421b%7C0eb48825e8714459bc72d0ecd68f1f39%7C0%7C0%7C638882957727432616%7CUnknown%7CTWFpbGZsb3d8eyJFbXB0eU1hcGkiOnRydWUsIlYiOiIwLjAuMDAwMCIsIlAiOiJXaW4zMiIsIkFOIjoiTWFpbCIsIldUIjoyfQ%3D%3D%7C0%7C%7C%7C&amp;amp;sdata=lUAyKPCfdhkNm%2BSBR64JW9rp7OEoygODS51Ex3WqavU%3D&amp;amp;reserved=0" target="_blank"&gt;the US Centers for Disease Control and Prevention&lt;/a&gt;. Over 80% of cases are bubonic plague. Most human cases have occurred in &lt;a href="https://nam11.safelinks.protection.outlook.com/?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.cdc.gov%2Fplague%2Fmaps-statistics%2Findex.html&amp;amp;data=05%7C02%7CLee.Smith1%40wbdcontractor.com%7C56b895ea96eb4de6f08c08ddc4aa421b%7C0eb48825e8714459bc72d0ecd68f1f39%7C0%7C0%7C638882957727449679%7CUnknown%7CTWFpbGZsb3d8eyJFbXB0eU1hcGkiOnRydWUsIlYiOiIwLjAuMDAwMCIsIlAiOiJXaW4zMiIsIkFOIjoiTWFpbCIsIldUIjoyfQ%3D%3D%7C0%7C%7C%7C&amp;amp;sdata=6y2PY6Ue%2FfU8OP5%2BIoRkfUBTpBALRWx1mdNGx6jNC0I%3D&amp;amp;reserved=0" target="_blank"&gt;two regions&lt;/a&gt;: northern Arizona, northern New Mexico and southern Colorado; and California, southern Oregon and far western Nevada.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmd6iq28c00143b6ntllzs4dw@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Plague has also been reported in various parts of the world. According to the &lt;a href="https://nam11.safelinks.protection.outlook.com/?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.who.int%2Fhealth-topics%2Fplague%23tab%3Dtab_1&amp;amp;data=05%7C02%7CLee.Smith1%40wbdcontractor.com%7C56b895ea96eb4de6f08c08ddc4aa421b%7C0eb48825e8714459bc72d0ecd68f1f39%7C0%7C0%7C638882957727466741%7CUnknown%7CTWFpbGZsb3d8eyJFbXB0eU1hcGkiOnRydWUsIlYiOiIwLjAuMDAwMCIsIlAiOiJXaW4zMiIsIkFOIjoiTWFpbCIsIldUIjoyfQ%3D%3D%7C0%7C%7C%7C&amp;amp;sdata=LSH4l1A0vGpU7gmy6h8gzz9Jniujac82wllUWKbinIo%3D&amp;amp;reserved=0" target="_blank"&gt;World Health Organization&lt;/a&gt;, most human cases since the 1990s have occurred on the African continent. The three countries where plague is the most endemic are the Democratic Republic of Congo, Madagascar and the South American country of Peru.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmd6irnq2001b3b6nwagqfb70@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            &lt;strong&gt;CNN: How worried should people be about pneumonic plague, if it would be transmitted person to person?&lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmd6irnq2001c3b6nx6vov4vb@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            &lt;strong&gt;Wen:&lt;/strong&gt; In Arizona, there was only one person diagnosed with pneumonic plague. There have not been reports of other infected individuals. Health experts there reiterate that the “&lt;a href="https://nam11.safelinks.protection.outlook.com/?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.coconino.az.gov%2FCivicAlerts.aspx%3FAID%3D3242%26fbclid%3DIwY2xjawLfXHRleHRuA2FlbQIxMABicmlkETFCd3hlUjY2M1ZGNURMRFdFAR5cdhAbD4Nab71-FQNNDDI_CXVgccQw2SMLR5OknCEoxkTUi1wDajEe0TzLvQ_aem_WYG09QZujnbgF13qssTFqQ&amp;amp;data=05%7C02%7CLee.Smith1%40wbdcontractor.com%7C56b895ea96eb4de6f08c08ddc4aa421b%7C0eb48825e8714459bc72d0ecd68f1f39%7C0%7C0%7C638882957727484367%7CUnknown%7CTWFpbGZsb3d8eyJFbXB0eU1hcGkiOnRydWUsIlYiOiIwLjAuMDAwMCIsIlAiOiJXaW4zMiIsIkFOIjoiTWFpbCIsIldUIjoyfQ%3D%3D%7C0%7C%7C%7C&amp;amp;sdata=FsvN9Y0uLVNIY%2Bv3XZuzAB5GMvZD3x8JzE1svHR2pVg%3D&amp;amp;reserved=0" target="_blank"&gt;risk to the public of exposure to plague remains low&lt;/a&gt;.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmd6irnq2001d3b6ngqa2pgx3@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            &lt;strong&gt;CNN: How is plague diagnosed?&lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmd6irnq2001e3b6n8yxonyz9@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            &lt;strong&gt;Wen:&lt;/strong&gt; Diagnosis is made through &lt;a href="https://nam11.safelinks.protection.outlook.com/?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.cdc.gov%2Fplague%2Fdiagnosis-testing%2Findex.html&amp;amp;data=05%7C02%7CLee.Smith1%40wbdcontractor.com%7C56b895ea96eb4de6f08c08ddc4aa421b%7C0eb48825e8714459bc72d0ecd68f1f39%7C0%7C0%7C638882957727500966%7CUnknown%7CTWFpbGZsb3d8eyJFbXB0eU1hcGkiOnRydWUsIlYiOiIwLjAuMDAwMCIsIlAiOiJXaW4zMiIsIkFOIjoiTWFpbCIsIldUIjoyfQ%3D%3D%7C0%7C%7C%7C&amp;amp;sdata=CU67jJ2X12561wJkHcjOLSQ2gP2oiF1q26AGhxci8ug%3D&amp;amp;reserved=0" target="_blank"&gt;laboratory testing&lt;/a&gt; of blood, sputum and parts of a swollen lymph node. Because the disease progresses very quickly and effective antibiotic therapies exist, prompt recognition is crucial. In cases where there is a high level of suspicion, antibiotics are often started in advance of confirmatory testing.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmd6irnq2001f3b6nm66zfhny@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            &lt;strong&gt;CNN: What treatments are available?&lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmd6irnq2001g3b6n2mgbzcp8@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            &lt;strong&gt;Wen: &lt;/strong&gt;The good news is that there are accessible and effective therapies. &lt;a href="https://nam11.safelinks.protection.outlook.com/?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.mayoclinic.org%2Fdiseases-conditions%2Fplague%2Fdiagnosis-treatment%2Fdrc-20351297&amp;amp;data=05%7C02%7CLee.Smith1%40wbdcontractor.com%7C56b895ea96eb4de6f08c08ddc4aa421b%7C0eb48825e8714459bc72d0ecd68f1f39%7C0%7C0%7C638882957727517243%7CUnknown%7CTWFpbGZsb3d8eyJFbXB0eU1hcGkiOnRydWUsIlYiOiIwLjAuMDAwMCIsIlAiOiJXaW4zMiIsIkFOIjoiTWFpbCIsIldUIjoyfQ%3D%3D%7C0%7C%7C%7C&amp;amp;sdata=QVMHrl3nfPnhMZpKWXBs5wlgDVeyrgTjElBLq%2Fb5cTs%3D&amp;amp;reserved=0" target="_blank"&gt;Several antibiotics&lt;/a&gt; are effective against Yersinia pestis. In the US, &lt;a href="https://nam11.safelinks.protection.outlook.com/?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.cdc.gov%2Fplague%2Fhcp%2Fclinical-care%2Findex.html&amp;amp;data=05%7C02%7CLee.Smith1%40wbdcontractor.com%7C56b895ea96eb4de6f08c08ddc4aa421b%7C0eb48825e8714459bc72d0ecd68f1f39%7C0%7C0%7C638882957727536263%7CUnknown%7CTWFpbGZsb3d8eyJFbXB0eU1hcGkiOnRydWUsIlYiOiIwLjAuMDAwMCIsIlAiOiJXaW4zMiIsIkFOIjoiTWFpbCIsIldUIjoyfQ%3D%3D%7C0%7C%7C%7C&amp;amp;sdata=i0I6kQBfjqzGcXYJtZAkAo6i1%2Bcv8Z3ykNxWw5rMXic%3D&amp;amp;reserved=0" target="_blank"&gt;gentamicin and fluoroquinolones&lt;/a&gt; are first-line treatments.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmd6irnq2001h3b6n9rqzkupy@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            It’s crucial that antibiotic therapies are promptly started. If left untreated, the case fatality rate can be as high as &lt;a href="https://nam11.safelinks.protection.outlook.com/?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.who.int%2Fhealth-topics%2Fplague%23tab%3Dtab_1&amp;amp;data=05%7C02%7CLee.Smith1%40wbdcontractor.com%7C56b895ea96eb4de6f08c08ddc4aa421b%7C0eb48825e8714459bc72d0ecd68f1f39%7C0%7C0%7C638882957727553049%7CUnknown%7CTWFpbGZsb3d8eyJFbXB0eU1hcGkiOnRydWUsIlYiOiIwLjAuMDAwMCIsIlAiOiJXaW4zMiIsIkFOIjoiTWFpbCIsIldUIjoyfQ%3D%3D%7C0%7C%7C%7C&amp;amp;sdata=zmieQ6bYbzFrFqdA174bHsgWlcxlGRZdBgEf91saC0o%3D&amp;amp;reserved=0" target="_blank"&gt;30% to 100%.&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmd6irnq2001i3b6n2atfbp1r@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            &lt;strong&gt;CNN: Is there a vaccine against plague?&lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmd6irnq2001j3b6nqcrkbjly@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            &lt;strong&gt;Wen: &lt;/strong&gt;A vaccine against plague &lt;a href="https://nam11.safelinks.protection.outlook.com/?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.cdc.gov%2Fmmwr%2Fpreview%2Fmmwrhtml%2F00041848.htm&amp;amp;data=05%7C02%7CLee.Smith1%40wbdcontractor.com%7C56b895ea96eb4de6f08c08ddc4aa421b%7C0eb48825e8714459bc72d0ecd68f1f39%7C0%7C0%7C638882957727571268%7CUnknown%7CTWFpbGZsb3d8eyJFbXB0eU1hcGkiOnRydWUsIlYiOiIwLjAuMDAwMCIsIlAiOiJXaW4zMiIsIkFOIjoiTWFpbCIsIldUIjoyfQ%3D%3D%7C0%7C%7C%7C&amp;amp;sdata=M6K1rgO8rh7LseOC1SQ16a5vpiK3BnWx3oLEYyrR6ZA%3D&amp;amp;reserved=0" target="_blank"&gt;had been authorized&lt;/a&gt; for individuals at high risk of exposure, but this vaccine is &lt;a href="https://nam11.safelinks.protection.outlook.com/?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.cdc.gov%2Fplague%2Fprevention%2Findex.html&amp;amp;data=05%7C02%7CLee.Smith1%40wbdcontractor.com%7C56b895ea96eb4de6f08c08ddc4aa421b%7C0eb48825e8714459bc72d0ecd68f1f39%7C0%7C0%7C638882957727588497%7CUnknown%7CTWFpbGZsb3d8eyJFbXB0eU1hcGkiOnRydWUsIlYiOiIwLjAuMDAwMCIsIlAiOiJXaW4zMiIsIkFOIjoiTWFpbCIsIldUIjoyfQ%3D%3D%7C0%7C%7C%7C&amp;amp;sdata=hgGg2JXF2BgeX%2Bw%2FU7CR2m8oR1ctRMINZWqMsrblqPc%3D&amp;amp;reserved=0" target="_blank"&gt;no longer available&lt;/a&gt; in the United States, in part due to how rare this disease has become. Some &lt;a href="https://nam11.safelinks.protection.outlook.com/?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.nature.com%2Farticles%2Fs41541-024-00958-1&amp;amp;data=05%7C02%7CLee.Smith1%40wbdcontractor.com%7C56b895ea96eb4de6f08c08ddc4aa421b%7C0eb48825e8714459bc72d0ecd68f1f39%7C0%7C0%7C638882957727604820%7CUnknown%7CTWFpbGZsb3d8eyJFbXB0eU1hcGkiOnRydWUsIlYiOiIwLjAuMDAwMCIsIlAiOiJXaW4zMiIsIkFOIjoiTWFpbCIsIldUIjoyfQ%3D%3D%7C0%7C%7C%7C&amp;amp;sdata=lnGo%2FQi4DNWslDhi2gg0tPxz4cy6jnoihaqjBPpMthQ%3D&amp;amp;reserved=0" target="_blank"&gt;potential vaccine candidates&lt;/a&gt; are under development.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmd6irnq2001k3b6nmb0rbpvq@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            &lt;strong&gt;CNN: What can people do to reduce the risk of contracting the plague?&lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmd6irnq2001l3b6neyzo2ik5@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            &lt;strong&gt;Wen:&lt;/strong&gt; Most Americans do not live in areas where plague can be found. For those in Western US states where plague has occurred, there are &lt;a href="https://nam11.safelinks.protection.outlook.com/?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.coconino.az.gov%2FCivicAlerts.aspx%3FAID%3D3242%26fbclid%3DIwY2xjawLfXHRleHRuA2FlbQIxMABicmlkETFCd3hlUjY2M1ZGNURMRFdFAR5cdhAbD4Nab71-FQNNDDI_CXVgccQw2SMLR5OknCEoxkTUi1wDajEe0TzLvQ_aem_WYG09QZujnbgF13qssTFqQ&amp;amp;data=05%7C02%7CLee.Smith1%40wbdcontractor.com%7C56b895ea96eb4de6f08c08ddc4aa421b%7C0eb48825e8714459bc72d0ecd68f1f39%7C0%7C0%7C638882957727620660%7CUnknown%7CTWFpbGZsb3d8eyJFbXB0eU1hcGkiOnRydWUsIlYiOiIwLjAuMDAwMCIsIlAiOiJXaW4zMiIsIkFOIjoiTWFpbCIsIldUIjoyfQ%3D%3D%7C0%7C%7C%7C&amp;amp;sdata=2f%2BipoOjDDGfhrUOB2Y0XQJ4V5mx4g2QvV3fkTY5KEI%3D&amp;amp;reserved=0" target="_blank"&gt;several actions&lt;/a&gt; they can take to reduce their potential exposure.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmd6irnq2001m3b6nh9fpncjg@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            First, avoid contact with wild animals. Do not handle wild rodents. Do not touch sick or dead animals.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmd6irnq2001n3b6nplcoduve@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Second, because most cases are associated with rodents, people should prevent rodent infestation by storing pet food in rodent-proof containers and removing brush and trash around homes.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmd6irnq2001o3b6n5wz990i4@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Third, avoid fleabites. Wear long sleeves and use insect repellent containing DEET if you are hiking, camping or working outdoors. Keep fleas away from household pets by using veterinarian-approved flea control products.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmd6irnq2001p3b6nmtk0tvv8@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Fourth, keep pets out of areas known to be inhabited by wild rodents. Be on the outlook for illnesses in domestic animals, especially indoor-outdoor cats, and seek prompt veterinary care.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmd6irnq2001q3b6njo0zl5rc@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            All of this said, I think it’s important to be reminded of how uncommon plague is. People who live in areas where plague has been found should take preventive measures, and clinicians should ask about travel history to these areas. Most Americans, though, do not need to be concerned about plague based on this single recent case in Arizona.
    &lt;/p&gt;

              &lt;/div&gt;
                &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>CNN</author><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 11:02:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiigFBVV95cUxQcUVhMGZEbXZpbXB5R3NHd1FQdFYtVVlxVWV2Uy1DbHBaaF9talAtQUZrcnlvQURXaGpOZjVHNkJ0aHhPcVFZOWhfVFZMTHVSR0RHdE9nR1YwYVdkcjJqeGF6TEZYNjkyRXFaMjB4ZkJDbW1BNGtPSXVmQ1dyYWdKWUVyRlUwUDVpeVHSAY8BQVVfeXFMTjFEN291S2pUbGI5dFJMSFpHaURKMk5TcHNlNHZyTVFYNUNqMkE3TXV0QzlfNTRWa0llQWNPNnFyTl96UkgyMWE3b2J0akx3X3IxQ0lLQVhPN2JEUkJaTDMwdXB0OE5uamZFU3p2cEJuT3V1U3JyZ0NtLVFDZGEzZmVBY1JkdFp6SnRqNlR0VzQ</guid></item><item><title>当心“夏季长球” -切割 | Beware ‘Summer Long Balls’ - The Cut</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMigAFBVV95cUxOM25JSGlnejBzeEt1Z25zQXJiODlUY25VYUJXdnJfd1R1bHIxVDdfU0UyYzVtS2duVHFtQWo0dHhrRmNRaWhIM2s1TXQ1T21zWU12ZFlyczRLdmpLUkozQ1pUajNwdENheXB5dkZhZE9jZGtrQjRlclhzaUl2Mm9Leg?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="wwwthecut-zephr-anchor" class="article-content inset" data-editable="content"&gt;
      
        &lt;p class="clay-paragraph" data-editable="text" data-uri="www.thecut.com/_components/clay-paragraph/instances/cmd65k8m8000f3b782zu7hvkb@published" data-word-count="60"&gt;It’s a difficult time to be a man. They’re&lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2025/05/13/upshot/boys-falling-behind-data.html"&gt; falling behind women academically&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://generations.org/tabs/none/podcasts/41186"&gt;making less money &lt;/a&gt;than their dads and grandfathers, and are so desperate for kinship and community that they’ve started &lt;a href="https://www.npr.org/2025/01/23/nx-s1-5260230/stick-nation-sticktok"&gt;posting sticks on Instagram and asking each other to rank them&lt;/a&gt;. It’s tough out there, and now that the weather is heating up, it’s about to get tougher.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="clay-paragraph" data-editable="text" data-uri="www.thecut.com/_components/clay-paragraph/instances/cmd64z9rn000g3b78l9gjnv2c@published" data-word-count="83"&gt;A man told me something a few years ago that haunts me to this day: every summer, his balls get bigger. Not to the extent that he has to purchase &lt;a href="https://www.thecut.com/2013/12/underwear-company-to-men-get-on-womens-level.html"&gt;new underwear &lt;/a&gt;or anything, but enough to make a noticeable difference when he wears trunks or loose boxers. Every June or so, like clockwork, his “summer long balls” come in. It’s one of the harbingers of summer, sort of like a collie shedding its top coat or &lt;a href="https://www.thecut.com/article/why-are-people-mad-sabrina-carpenter-album-cover.html"&gt;Sabrina Carpenter releasing a new single.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="clay-paragraph" data-editable="text" data-uri="www.thecut.com/_components/clay-paragraph/instances/cmd64z9tm000h3b789q50rbiv@published" data-word-count="73"&gt;This guy says he doesn’t have strong feelings about his Summer Long Balls. “It’s not something I either like or dislike,” he said. “It is simply a reality.” But I don’t think he’s being entirely truthful. I’ve gone to the beach with him, and on at least one occasion, he had to find a Target en route and duck into the bathroom to self-adjust because his balls had gotten twisted in his trunks.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="clay-paragraph" data-editable="text" data-uri="www.thecut.com/_components/clay-paragraph/instances/cmd64z9vc000i3b785l79gygw@published" data-word-count="83"&gt;I had to know if this condition was specific to this one man, or if it was something that all men struggled with but  just didn’t talk about publicly. When I asked around my social circle, about half the men I polled didn’t know what the hell I was talking about. Others, however, acutely felt the pain of summer long balls. “It sucks,” one person told me. “I wish I could wear sluttier shorts in the summer. But I can’t do so comfortably.”&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="clay-paragraph" data-editable="text" data-uri="www.thecut.com/_components/clay-paragraph/instances/cmd64z9x1000j3b78e8ewmcrm@published" data-word-count="77"&gt;Another told me he experiences a variation on summer long balls in which sweat causes the skin from his scrotum to stick to his leg, creating what he dubs a “bat wing” effect. “You have to make sure no one sees you grab your crotch to rearrange if you’re in public,” he says. I even heard about a guy whose testicles were so distended they hit the toilet water when he sat down in a public restroom.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="clay-paragraph" data-editable="text" data-uri="www.thecut.com/_components/clay-paragraph/instances/cmd64z9ys000k3b78427bcsa9@published" data-word-count="53"&gt;Some pointed out the similarity to “&lt;a href="https://melmagazine.com/en-us/story/summer-penis-is-real-and-its-spectacular"&gt;summer penis&lt;/a&gt;,” the term coined by MEL Magazine’s Tracy Moore in 2018 to describe the way some men’s genitals appear to swell during the summer. This phenomenon, Moore writes, is caused by vasodilation, or the dilation of blood vessels to allow for increased flow to erectile tissue.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="clay-paragraph" data-editable="text" data-uri="www.thecut.com/_components/clay-paragraph/instances/cmd64za0l000l3b78j1t58rqt@published" data-word-count="99"&gt;But this is not the case for summer long balls, according to New Jersey urologist Anika Ackerman, which instead result from body self-regulating in warmer climates, so the testicles are at optimal temperature for sperm production. “When it’s a cold environment, the testicles move towards the body, and the scrotum tenses up,” Ackerman explained. (Think: &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nsH4aClj-ZY"&gt;George Costanza’s shrinkage incident&lt;/a&gt;.) “The opposite is true in a warm environment. The scrotum relaxes and the testicles move away from the body.” It’s not so much that men’s testicles become bigger in the heat; it’s that they travel further away from the body.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="clay-paragraph" data-editable="text" data-uri="www.thecut.com/_components/clay-paragraph/instances/cmd64za2f000m3b78dgn7lwk3@published" data-word-count="119"&gt;Still, the question remained: why do some men clearly experience summer long balls, while others don’t? And approximately what percentage of the male population is at risk, so to speak? I called Yaniv Larish, a urologist and surgeon at Fifth Avenue Urology, to see if he had any &lt;a href="http://theories.he"&gt;theories.&lt;/a&gt; He suspects that a good proportion of summer long ball cases are actually men with varicoceles, or enlarged veins within the scrotum. (Which is basically like varicose veins, but for your ballsack.) “When you have a varicocele, the blood is not moving around efficiently, so instead of circulating around the testicle and pulling the heat away, it’s pooling up and actually insulating the testicle at an elevated temperature,” he says.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="clay-paragraph" data-editable="text" data-uri="www.thecut.com/_components/clay-paragraph/instances/cmd64za8a000n3b783ao58qj5@published" data-word-count="82"&gt;About 15 percent of the male population has a varicocele in either one or both testicles. They’re often undiagnosed, because “men are way less educated about their bodies than women are,” Lavish says Varicoceles are usually harmless, but in some cases they can be linked to decreased fertility, in which case they are treated with minor surgery. “What you’re describing as summer long balls is, I suspect, really the varicocele becoming more pronounced as a result of the elevated temperature,” Larish says.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="clay-paragraph" data-editable="text" data-uri="www.thecut.com/_components/clay-paragraph/instances/cmd64zaah000o3b78frnp4x3b@published" data-word-count="95"&gt;If a man in your life is struggling with summer long balls, there are a few things he can do to alleviate his discomfort. Wearing tight underwear, for instance, can offer scrotal support; it’s also helpful to spend as much time in the air-conditioned indoors as possible, as hotter environments aren’t great for testicular health overall. Ackerman also told me about a product called &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/Vasectomy-Ice-Pack-Underwear-Inserts/dp/B09SQH4J81?tag=thecutonsite-20&amp;amp;ascsubtag=__c20718aam__cmd64qiqz00000if9xx84wbm1__________________" rel="sponsored,nofollow" data-track-type="product-link"&gt;“Nutsicles”&lt;/a&gt; — essentially, an ice pack for the testicles — that could possibly help, though it is intended primarily for men who have had vastectomies and not Summer Long Ball sufferers.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="clay-paragraph" data-editable="text" data-uri="www.thecut.com/_components/clay-paragraph/instances/cmd64zac5000p3b78o48swvqv@published" data-word-count="98"&gt;While there is no hard-and-fast cure for Summer Long Balls, the good news is that it’s temporary. Once the temperature goes down, so, too, will the circumference of a man’s balls. Men can also take solace in the fact that summer long balls can provide, if nothing else, a new opportunity for creative expression. “Actually, I think they’re kind of awesome,” a friend told me. “When they’re hanging way the heck down you can really grab a handful of them and twist them around, or pull them up to do a bullfrog.” Who says men don’t have hobbies?&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;aside data-uri="www.thecut.com/_components/newsletter-flex-text/instances/cmd64qist000j0if9l0n6uwof@published" class="newsletter-flex-text initially-hidden opacity-zero" data-track-id="thecut" data-track-type="newsletter-signup"&gt;
  &lt;div class="wrapper-style"&gt;


    &lt;div data-editable="settings"&gt;
      &lt;div class="text-form-wrapper"&gt;
        &lt;div class="text"&gt;
          &lt;h3 class="title"&gt;Stay in touch.&lt;/h3&gt;
          &lt;p class="description"&gt;Get the Cut newsletter delivered daily&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;

        
        
      &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;p class="newsletter-flex-text-divider"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;div class="terms-and-policy-wrapper initially-hidden"&gt;
        
        &lt;button class="terms-button" role="button"&gt;Vox Media, LLC Terms and Privacy Notice&lt;/button&gt;
        &lt;p class="expanded-terms " aria-hidden="true"&gt;By submitting your email, you agree to our &lt;a href="https://nymag.com/newyork/terms/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;Terms&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://nymag.com/newyork/privacy/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;Privacy Notice&lt;/a&gt; and to receive email correspondence from us.&lt;/p&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/aside&gt;

  


    &lt;/div&gt;

      &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Cut</author><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 11:00:35 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigAFBVV95cUxOM25JSGlnejBzeEt1Z25zQXJiODlUY25VYUJXdnJfd1R1bHIxVDdfU0UyYzVtS2duVHFtQWo0dHhrRmNRaWhIM2s1TXQ1T21zWU12ZFlyczRLdmpLUkozQ1pUajNwdENheXB5dkZhZE9jZGtrQjRlclhzaUl2Mm9Leg</guid></item><item><title>您的Joyspan是老龄化的关键-《纽约时报》 | Your Joyspan is the Key to Aging Well - The New York Times</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMigwFBVV95cUxNUFdzR1kzcTJDb3pBUE9rSy02UU9Gam1hWXZTMGd3LTNuM3VvVWViY0NJN2ZTd3RmWlFHcl9DNTRUTzhNYi1YdDI1NzE2WEpod1g3V1pOeFZwMEp1ejZSRlRERTJaWjdMdS1BZGgxRUNfdzdjdXVfdEZ2TzNZZU8yU2ljNA?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The New York Times</author><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 09:03:38 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigwFBVV95cUxNUFdzR1kzcTJDb3pBUE9rSy02UU9Gam1hWXZTMGd3LTNuM3VvVWViY0NJN2ZTd3RmWlFHcl9DNTRUTzhNYi1YdDI1NzE2WEpod1g3V1pOeFZwMEp1ejZSRlRERTJaWjdMdS1BZGgxRUNfdzdjdXVfdEZ2TzNZZU8yU2ljNA</guid></item><item><title>费城卫生部门警告蚊子传播的西尼罗河病毒- Inquirer.com | Philadelphia health department warns of mosquito-borne West Nile virus - Inquirer.com</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMijgFBVV95cUxOQ3g5Z2VxMWxndHkyMnA1Vkk2VUgxQXZyRHVGM2t5clVPUUlBOTdUSDVzRFRneFkyMzdJX0VfTUpVRlBtd1RzRTlUaE5DdV9TRHY3Y090RUNKcHZKb1hZdjV6MG5aQmhGZUVvLU1leFB5aG83Q0I1WlVSOXJzMWhWN2ZZcDVvRXRGSDJjNG9R?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="article-body" class="article-body-light "&gt;&lt;p class="inq-p text-primary  "&gt;Philadelphia health officials are cautioning residents to protect themselves against West Nile virus after detecting the disease in mosquitoes near &lt;a class="relative z-1 text-blue-mid hover:shadow-lightmode" data-link-type="article-body" href="https://www.visitphilly.com/things-to-do/attractions/pennypack-park/" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://www.visitphilly.com/things-to-do/attractions/pennypack-park/"&gt;Pennypack Park&lt;/a&gt; in the city’s Northeast section.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="lazyload-placeholder"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="inq-p text-primary  "&gt;The city’s &lt;a class="relative z-1 text-blue-mid hover:shadow-lightmode" data-link-type="article-body" href="https://www.phila.gov/departments/department-of-public-health/" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://www.phila.gov/departments/department-of-public-health/"&gt;Department of Public Health&lt;/a&gt; routinely conducts surveillance&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;for the virus. Recent testing results detected the season’s first infected mosquitoes in &lt;a class="relative z-1 text-blue-mid hover:shadow-lightmode" data-link-type="article-body" href="https://www.inquirer.com/topic/northeast-philadelphia"&gt;Northeast Philadelphia&lt;/a&gt;, prompting &lt;a class="relative z-1 text-blue-mid hover:shadow-lightmode" data-link-type="article-body" href="https://hip.phila.gov/document/5536/PDPH-HAN-WNVArboviruses-07.07.2025.pdf/" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://hip.phila.gov/document/5536/PDPH-HAN-WNVArboviruses-07.07.2025.pdf/"&gt;a July 7 city health advisory&lt;/a&gt; to area medical providers warning of an increased risk to residents of contracting West Nile.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="lazyload-placeholder"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="lazyload-placeholder"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="inq-p text-primary  "&gt;Health officials instructed medical providers to look out for virus symptoms in patients — and test them for West Nile when appropriate — from now through October’s end or until the first frost. Patients with unexplained neurological symptoms, including brain and spinal cord inflammation, must be tested.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="lazyload-placeholder"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="inq-p text-primary  "&gt;Suspected and confirmed cases should be reported immediately to the city’s health department.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="lazyload-placeholder"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="inq-p text-primary  "&gt;Doctors and nurses are also encouraged to discuss mosquito bite prevention with patients, especially those who work or spend time outdoors and those traveling to subtropical and tropical areas, where mosquito-borne illnesses are prevalent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="lazyload-placeholder"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="inq-p type-interstitial text-primary"&gt;&lt;b&gt;» READ MORE: &lt;a data-link-type="interstitial" href="https://www.inquirer.com/health/west-nile-virus-philadelphia-2024-symptoms-kids-dogs-spraying-20240827.html" class="no-underline text-blue-mid hover:shadow-lightmode"&gt;READ MORE: What to know about West Nile virus, including can dogs get it?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="lazyload-placeholder"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="lazyload-placeholder"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="lazyload-placeholder"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="inq-p text-primary  "&gt;The &lt;a class="relative z-1 text-blue-mid hover:shadow-lightmode" data-link-type="article-body" href="https://www.inquirer.com/health/west-nile-virus-philadelphia-2024-symptoms-kids-dogs-spraying-20240827.html" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://www.inquirer.com/health/west-nile-virus-philadelphia-2024-symptoms-kids-dogs-spraying-20240827.html"&gt;majority of people&lt;/a&gt; bitten by a West Nile-infected mosquito don’t get the virus, and most don’t experience any symptoms. Fewer than 1% will develop severe disease, according to Emily Kehoe, the city’s vectorborne disease surveillance coordinator.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="lazyload-placeholder"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="inq-p text-primary  "&gt;In rare cases, however, people can become extremely ill. About one out of 10 people die from a severe case, Kehoe said in an email Thursday to The Inquirer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="lazyload-placeholder"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="inq-p text-primary  "&gt;The virus can cause encephalitis or meningitis, which result in swelling of brain and of the membranes around the brain and spinal cord. Older adults and those with weakened immune systems are at higher risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="lazyload-placeholder"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="inq-p text-primary  "&gt;About 20% of people will develop a flulike illness with a fever, according to the &lt;a class="relative z-1 text-blue-mid hover:shadow-lightmode" data-link-type="article-body" href="https://www.cdc.gov/west-nile-virus/symptoms-diagnosis-treatment/index.html" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://www.cdc.gov/west-nile-virus/symptoms-diagnosis-treatment/index.html"&gt;Centers for Disease Control and Prevention&lt;/a&gt;. Other symptoms include rash, diarrhea, vomiting, headache, fatigue, joint pain, and body aches.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="lazyload-placeholder"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="lazyload-placeholder"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="lazyload-placeholder"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="inq-p text-primary  "&gt;There is no vaccine and no specific treatment. Rest, fluids, and pain medication can help&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;relieve symptoms. Most people fully recover.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="lazyload-placeholder"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="inq-p text-primary  "&gt;Each year, from 2020 to 2024 in Philadelphia, &lt;a class="relative z-1 text-blue-mid hover:shadow-lightmode" data-link-type="article-body" href="https://www.inquirer.com/health/west-nile-virus-philadelphia-health-department-20240821.html" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://www.inquirer.com/health/west-nile-virus-philadelphia-health-department-20240821.html"&gt;four to nine people were diagnosed&lt;/a&gt; with West Nile virus that caused neurological complications. During each of those years, at least one case was fatal. As of Thursday, there were no confirmed cases of West Nile virus among Philadelphia residents this year, according to Kehoe.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="lazyload-placeholder"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=" relative w-fit mt-6 mb-0 font-inquirer-headline text-primary"&gt;&lt;h3 class="block font-semibold mt-8 mb-4 text-5 leading-5 sm:text-8 sm:leading-8 lg:text-9 lg:leading-9"&gt;Beware of other viruses spread by mosquitoes or ticks&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="lazyload-placeholder"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="inq-p text-primary  "&gt;Viruses spread by mosquitoes or ticks to people are known as “arboviral infections.” They include West Nile, &lt;a class="relative z-1 text-blue-mid hover:shadow-lightmode" data-link-type="article-body" href="https://www.cdc.gov/powassan/about/index.html" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://www.cdc.gov/powassan/about/index.html"&gt;Powassan virus&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a class="relative z-1 text-blue-mid hover:shadow-lightmode" data-link-type="article-body" href="https://my.clevelandclinic.org/health/diseases/25082-jamestown-canyon-virus" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://my.clevelandclinic.org/health/diseases/25082-jamestown-canyon-virus"&gt;Jamestown Canyon&lt;/a&gt; virus.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="lazyload-placeholder"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="inq-p text-primary  "&gt;The health department first detected Powassan in black-legged ticks in Philadelphia in fall 2019. Mosquitoes infected with Jamestown Canyon virus were identified in Pennsylvania beginning in 2023.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="lazyload-placeholder"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="lazyload-placeholder"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="lazyload-placeholder"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="inq-p text-primary  "&gt;But arboviral infections are rare in the Philadelphia region.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="lazyload-placeholder"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="inq-p text-primary  "&gt;Each year, mosquitoes infected with West Nile virus are detected in parks citywide. Pennypack Park includes about 1,600 acres of woodlands, meadows and wetlands in the city’s &lt;a class="relative z-1 text-blue-mid hover:shadow-lightmode" data-link-type="article-body" href="https://www.inquirer.com/topic/holme-circle"&gt;Holme Circle&lt;/a&gt; neighborhood in Northeast Philadelphia. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="lazyload-placeholder"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="inq-p text-primary  "&gt;As additional mosquito samples — collected from other parts of the city — are tested for West Nile virus, the health department anticipates more positive results in coming weeks, Kehoe said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="lazyload-placeholder"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="inq-p text-primary  "&gt;The health department advises residents to take these steps to protect themselves from mosquito and tick-borne diseases:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="lazyload-placeholder"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="my-6"&gt;&lt;ol class="ml-5  list-disc my-6"&gt;&lt;li class="ml-5 mb-3 "&gt;&lt;p class="inq-p text-primary "&gt;Use bug repellent with &lt;a class="relative z-1 text-blue-mid hover:shadow-lightmode" href="https://www.epa.gov/insect-repellents/deet" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://www.epa.gov/insect-repellents/deet"&gt;DEET&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a class="relative z-1 text-blue-mid hover:shadow-lightmode" href="https://npic.orst.edu/factsheets/PicaridinGen.html" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://npic.orst.edu/factsheets/PicaridinGen.html"&gt;picaridin&lt;/a&gt;, or oil of lemon eucalyptus while outdoors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="ml-5 mb-3 "&gt;&lt;p class="inq-p text-primary "&gt;Wear long-sleeved shirts and long pants.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="ml-5 mb-3 "&gt;&lt;p class="inq-p text-primary "&gt;Use well-fitted screens on windows and doors to keep out mosquitoes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="ml-5 mb-3 "&gt;&lt;p class="inq-p text-primary "&gt;Regularly empty standing water outside the home. Drill holes in the bottom of trash cans and turn over plastic kiddie pools at day’s end.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="ml-5 mb-3 "&gt;&lt;p class="inq-p text-primary "&gt;Report mosquito problems to the city health department’s Mosquito Complaint hotline at 215-685-9000. Dead birds, which can carry West Nile and bird flu, should be reported to the state Game Commission at 833-742-9453.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="lazyload-placeholder"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Inquirer.com</author><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 09:00:01 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijgFBVV95cUxOQ3g5Z2VxMWxndHkyMnA1Vkk2VUgxQXZyRHVGM2t5clVPUUlBOTdUSDVzRFRneFkyMzdJX0VfTUpVRlBtd1RzRTlUaE5DdV9TRHY3Y090RUNKcHZKb1hZdjV6MG5aQmhGZUVvLU1leFB5aG83Q0I1WlVSOXJzMWhWN2ZZcDVvRXRGSDJjNG9R</guid></item><item><title>科学家警告：流行的糖替代品与脑细胞损伤有关- SciTechDaily | Scientists Warn: Popular Sugar Substitute Linked to Brain Cell Damage - SciTechDaily</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMimgFBVV95cUxNcjRJZTdQR3Q0Sjk0TTAyMG82bklUUTJiNzFiOUNOVURWVGQteTdmdmlFbGxkRWQ1ODVUQUk1ZVBGYjdoSHpjQW02UVFEYTkyVndOV3NtVWs5cHRzTHFQU2VpeXdSNlRiYk5wRVNSWkRIXzUxV21CT0N2Q3M4ZWsxRTZZQUlTR3pHQXBCRDFaSWxCSkRDcm9GRWN3?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>SciTechDaily</author><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 08:16:08 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimgFBVV95cUxNcjRJZTdQR3Q0Sjk0TTAyMG82bklUUTJiNzFiOUNOVURWVGQteTdmdmlFbGxkRWQ1ODVUQUk1ZVBGYjdoSHpjQW02UVFEYTkyVndOV3NtVWs5cHRzTHFQU2VpeXdSNlRiYk5wRVNSWkRIXzUxV21CT0N2Q3M4ZWsxRTZZQUlTR3pHQXBCRDFaSWxCSkRDcm9GRWN3</guid></item><item><title>阿尔茨海默病：原因、早期症状和可能有助于预防的11种生活方式改变-印度时报 | Alzheimer’s disease: Causes, early symptoms, and 11 lifestyle changes that could help prevent it - Times of India</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMinAJBVV95cUxQOFlUYjNLeTRzM0lmMHdtWTByRk5keWlaT19HZ195RTdGNGFuNUV0WFE0bEI5aTNYOVdFdmpsUmgteG1ISWFkVUdJaUIwek16Q2E1NWF0UlREek1QdWtaM1UwUWkxZ3F2ZG5GMGc1Y0tWZHo3eldrdnVmYXpkdVFrUjA2bU5sdFE1cXJuZkUzSUktZnBtdDBBYjZET08xMXNnZGxaWGJmM3FCbFQ4cXFONmVUTTRRR2V1X01vS3hYYjdUT0lBQ09IUUxfSllIVkpzc2U1OXVXMmh0WXZFRnVDVENnYk0wWFRrYmtJUDE4NGFWYVg5cGZKY1QzLVpteEhON002ZlVBb0kxUndjNGZlZWkxYjVIQzJ4dkx4cA?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alzheimer’s disease is the most common form of dementia, a progressive brain disorder that slowly erodes memory, thinking skills, and the ability to carry out everyday tasks. It affects not only individuals but also deeply impacts caregivers and families, often creating emotional, financial, and logistical challenges over time. In its early stages, it might look like simple forgetfulness. But over time, it can take away even the most basic abilities, like recognising loved ones or getting dressed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="3"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most symptoms begin after age 65, but the condition starts developing in the brain years, sometimes even decades, before that. As life expectancy rises, so does the number of people affected. Over 6 &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC9502739/" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;million &lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;older adults in the U.S. live with Alzheimer’s, and that number is expected to grow dramatically. This makes prevention even more important. Growing research shows that our lifestyle choices; what we eat, how we sleep, and how we move, can make a real difference in protecting brain health long before symptoms appear.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="9"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="10"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What causes Alzheimer’s disease? Key risk factors to know&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="11"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alzheimer’s disease doesn’t have a single known cause. Instead, it likely develops from a combination of genetic, environmental, and lifestyle factors that damage the brain over time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="13"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="14"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Age is the biggest risk factor. According to the &lt;a href="https://www.nia.nih.gov/health/alzheimers-causes-and-risk-factors/what-causes-alzheimers-disease" data-type="tilCustomLink"&gt;National Institute on Aging&lt;/a&gt;, the risk of Alzheimer’s doubles every five years after age 65. Ageing is linked to the buildup of abnormal proteins like beta-amyloid plaques and tangles in the brain.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Genetics and family history also play a role. People with a parent or sibling with Alzheimer’s are at higher risk. In particular, carrying the APOE ε4 gene variant has been linked to late-onset Alzheimer’s, but it doesn’t guarantee you’ll develop the disease.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Traumatic brain injury (TBI), especially repeated or severe head injuries, may trigger long-term brain changes that increase Alzheimer’s risk later in life.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Heart and vascular health matters, too. High blood pressure, cholesterol, diabetes, and heart disease can all impair blood flow to the brain, accelerating damage. Managing these conditions may reduce dementia risk.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Mental health is another factor. Chronic stress and depression have been linked to changes in brain structure and function, especially in memory-related areas.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Smoking and toxin exposure can raise the risk by increasing oxidative stress and inflammation in the brain. Quitting smoking at any age can help lower this risk.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="15"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Other contributing factors include low education levels, social isolation, and unhealthy lifestyle habits like poor diet or inactivity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="18"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Having these risk factors doesn’t mean you’ll develop Alzheimer’s, but they can increase your chances. Many of them, especially lifestyle-related ones, are preventable or manageable through early action.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="20"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="21"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Recognising the symptoms of Alzheimer’s disease&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="22"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;While occasional forgetfulness is a normal part of ageing, Alzheimer’s disease involves ongoing cognitive and behavioural decline that interferes with daily life. These changes typically worsen over time as brain cells are progressively damaged.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="25"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to the &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.alz.org/alzheimers-dementia/10_signs" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;Alzheimer’s Association&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; and the &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.nia.nih.gov/health/alzheimers-symptoms-and-diagnosis/what-are-signs-alzheimers-disease" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;National Institute on Aging&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, early signs include:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="31"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="32"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Memory loss that disrupts daily routines, such as forgetting recent conversations or appointments.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Difficulty completing familiar tasks, like using appliances or managing bills.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Problem-solving challenges, including trouble planning or following steps.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Language issues, such as struggling to find the right words or follow conversations.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Disorientation, with confusion about time or location.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Poor judgment, including neglecting hygiene or falling for scams.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Mood and personality changes, such as irritability, anxiety, or social withdrawal.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="33"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;These symptoms don’t always indicate Alzheimer’s; they can result from other conditions like depression or medication side effects. A medical diagnosis is key.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="35"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;In later stages, people may lose the ability to communicate, walk, or care for themselves. Research shows that early detection and intervention can improve quality of life and slow disease progression. If signs appear, consult a healthcare professional promptly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="38"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="39"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;11 lifestyle changes that could help prevent Alzheimer’s&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="40"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="42"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alzheimer’s often begins to develop decades before symptoms appear. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.thelancet.com/journals/lancet/article/PIIS0140-6736(24)01296-0/abstract" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;Research &lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;now shows that up to 45% of dementia cases could be delayed or prevented by addressing modifiable lifestyle factors throughout life. Here’s how targeting key areas can help protect your brain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="46"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="47"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Improve blood flow&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="48"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Healthy blood flow supplies the brain with oxygen and nutrients. Studies show that reduced cerebral blood flow is linked to Alzheimer’s and mild cognitive impairment. Promising evidence from &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.utsouthwestern.edu/newsroom/articles/year-2020/exercise-improves-memory-boosts-blood-flow-to-brain.html?" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;UT Southwestern&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; demonstrated that older adults with memory issues who engaged in one year of regular aerobic exercise experienced a nearly 47% increase in blood flow to memory-related brain regions and improved cognition.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="53"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="54"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Stay mentally active as you age&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="55"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Building what’s known as “cognitive reserve” helps delay dementia symptoms by strengthening neural networks through lifelong learning and activity. Research from Alzheimer’s Research UK shows that engaging in new, mentally challenging activities throughout life lowers the risk of dementia by up to 30%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="57"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="58"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Reduce inflammation&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="59"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chronic inflammation is a known factor in neurodegeneration. Diseases like gum inflammation contribute to increased dementia risk. A nutrient-rich, anti-inflammatory lifestyle, focused on whole foods, regular exercise, stress control, and good oral hygiene, helps protect the brain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="63"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="64"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Recognize genetic risk but take action&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="65"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Carrying the APOE-ε4 gene increases Alzheimer’s risk, but lifestyle still matters. The &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.thelancet.com/journals/lancet/article/PIIS0140-6736(24)01296-0/abstract" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;Lancet Commission&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; reports that even those with high genetic risk can significantly reduce dementia risk through healthy habits.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="69"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="70"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Avoid head trauma&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="71"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Head injuries can increase the risk of dementia later in life. Simple preventive steps, like wearing helmets during sports, using seat belts, and avoiding risky behaviors like texting while driving, can help protect brain health long term.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="75"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="76"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Minimize exposure to toxins&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="77"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chronic exposure to environmental toxins such as heavy metals, air pollution, alcohol, and certain medications affects cognitive health. Reducing exposure, eating detox-supportive foods, staying hydrated, and using tools like saunas can help reduce toxic burden.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="80"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="81"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Prioritize mental health&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="82"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Depression, stress, and anxiety are associated with brain changes and increased dementia risk. Approaches such as therapy, mindfulness, journaling, or meditation can support mental wellbeing and protect cognition.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="84"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="85"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Support immunity&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="86"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chronic illnesses that impair immunity (e.g., infections, autoimmune diseases) can accelerate brain aging. Ensuring good vitamin D levels, a balanced diet, and routine healthcare helps strengthen immune defenses that support brain health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="89"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="90"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Balance hormones&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="91"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hormones like thyroid, estrogen, and testosterone affect memory and mood. Age-related hormone declines can influence cognition. Regular hormone screenings allow early detection and intervention.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="93"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="94"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Avoid “diabesity”&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="95"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Combining obesity and type 2 diabetes, “diabesity” is strongly linked to dementia. Losing weight, managing blood sugar, and lowering systemic inflammation are key to reducing cognitive decline risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="97"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="98"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Ensure quality sleep&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="99"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sleep clears beta-amyloid and supports cognitive processing at night. Even one night of sleep deprivation can raise amyloid levels by 5%, while chronic poor sleep disrupts the toxin-cleaning “glymphatic” system and elevates Alzheimer’s risk. For optimal brain health, aim for 7–8 hours of restorative sleep nightly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="101"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Also Read: &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/curry-leaves-10-powerful-health-benefits-medicinal-uses-and-how-to-consume-them/articleshow/122575062.cms" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;Curry Leaves: 10 powerful health benefits, medicinal uses and how to consume them&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="104"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="105"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 04:07:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMinAJBVV95cUxQOFlUYjNLeTRzM0lmMHdtWTByRk5keWlaT19HZ195RTdGNGFuNUV0WFE0bEI5aTNYOVdFdmpsUmgteG1ISWFkVUdJaUIwek16Q2E1NWF0UlREek1QdWtaM1UwUWkxZ3F2ZG5GMGc1Y0tWZHo3eldrdnVmYXpkdVFrUjA2bU5sdFE1cXJuZkUzSUktZnBtdDBBYjZET08xMXNnZGxaWGJmM3FCbFQ4cXFONmVUTTRRR2V1X01vS3hYYjdUT0lBQ09IUUxfSllIVkpzc2U1OXVXMmh0WXZFRnVDVENnYk0wWFRrYmtJUDE4NGFWYVg5cGZKY1QzLVpteEhON002ZlVBb0kxUndjNGZlZWkxYjVIQzJ4dkx4cA</guid></item><item><title>科罗拉多男子为在严重的西尼罗河病毒病例中生存而战- KUSA.com | Colorado man fights to survive severe case of West Nile Virus - KUSA.com</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiuwFBVV95cUxPTXlIaXVVcHNHUF9Fc1U3enVaUTF2NG1CT0ZXOVQ1dVZ6Ym9Ub3FDQmRXSXdhNnR2V0JVTl8xVG5DcW1DYkJLN3BsdWxhbjZsSnNGNUx0R29veFhLa0hqM3dRVjJ2TEZtOWpkWjJCNWZldnhtWUZTdjMxZTFSd0QwbTZ4RFhEWjY2VTd3LUE5T1JjUlhqYnU4T1JRUUZMemZVTG9iNC1vR01MTzJtbDV6RDFjTlN4eDZhd2Fr?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Access Denied&lt;/h1&gt;
 
You don't have permission to access "http://www.9news.com/article/news/health/colorado-man-two-case-west-nile-virus/73-ab73f9f7-b130-4dbb-8854-534ac3fcae2a" on this server.&lt;p&gt;
Reference #18.340c3417.1752843876.1405db33
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;https://errors.edgesuite.net/18.340c3417.1752843876.1405db33&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/body&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>KUSA.com</author><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 04:06:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiuwFBVV95cUxPTXlIaXVVcHNHUF9Fc1U3enVaUTF2NG1CT0ZXOVQ1dVZ6Ym9Ub3FDQmRXSXdhNnR2V0JVTl8xVG5DcW1DYkJLN3BsdWxhbjZsSnNGNUx0R29veFhLa0hqM3dRVjJ2TEZtOWpkWjJCNWZldnhtWUZTdjMxZTFSd0QwbTZ4RFhEWjY2VTd3LUE5T1JjUlhqYnU4T1JRUUZMemZVTG9iNC1vR01MTzJtbDV6RDFjTlN4eDZhd2Fr</guid></item><item><title>研究指出自闭症亚型，为更个性化的护理敞开大门-残疾勺 | Study Pinpoints Autism Subtypes, Opening Door To More Personalized Care - Disability Scoop</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMivAFBVV95cUxNX1ZyZlVVSF9Ub2JraldXOEM3ZjB4ZDF4bWVYdGhKWS1HWldlWjc4WGJJNU1ydGZjZTAtNzVWaEk4VWo3SXRsQXVVeFIzRHgzQWRsUXowOXhZYmg3MGNxbjNNbFczN3Rkcl9GTWU4RkhvTnpHU3dnWVl4WXFjR25WUVA0dFc2alE5UXNZcF9CUVM0Vlh5OS0tZDJTWFljYWJBRl9DMnNIaTNjYlloRUtWYy1Lc3F2SV9FeUZ3Tg?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="pigeon-remove" data-pn="0"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are at least four distinct subtypes of autism, a new study finds, helping to explain the various trajectories of individuals on the spectrum and offering a path toward more targeted treatments.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Researchers grouped over 5,000 children ages 4 to 18 with autism based on more than 230 traits like social interactions, repetitive behaviors and developmental milestones to arrive at the classifications. Then, they assessed the children’s genetic profiles to uncover patterns characteristic of the different groups.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“These findings are powerful because the classes represent different clinical presentations and outcomes, and critically we were able to connect them to distinct underlying biology,” said Aviya Litman of Princeton University, a co-lead author of the &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41588-025-02224-z" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;study&lt;/a&gt; published this month in the journal Nature Genetics.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;div class="ad"&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Advertisement - Continue Reading Below&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p id="div-gpt-ad-1439298927391-2" class="ad-container"&gt;
      
    &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
  



&lt;p&gt;More than a third of children with autism in the study were in what the researchers dubbed the “Social and Behavioral Challenges” group. These children display core autism traits like social difficulty and repetitive behaviors and often have co-occurring conditions like attention deficit hyperactivity disorder, but tend to reach developmental milestones on schedule.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The “Moderate Challenges” group, which included about 34% of kids studied, experience a similar trajectory, but with milder presentations and no co-occurring psychiatric conditions. A third group known as “Mixed ASD with Developmental Delay” accounted for the roughly 19% of kids studied who exhibited delayed walking, talking and other developmental milestones, but without signs of anxiety, depression or disruptive behaviors.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;A final group described as “Broadly Affected” had more extreme and wide-ranging challenges including developmental delays, social and communication difficulties, repetitive behaviors and co-occurring psychiatric conditions. About 10% of kids with autism fell into this category.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The study found clear genetic patterns to explain the different presentations. The Broadly Affected group had the highest proportion of problematic de novo mutations, those that are not passed down from either parent, the findings show. By contrast, individuals in the Mixed ASD with Developmental Delay group were more likely to have rare inherited genetic variants.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Notably, in the Social and Behavioral Challenges group, researchers found mutations in genes that typically activate later in childhood, which could explain why children in this group are often diagnosed at older ages.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“This study shows us that autism isn’t a single condition with a single cause,” said Dr. Andy Shih, chief science officer at Autism Speaks. “It’s a spectrum made up of many different experiences, challenges and underlying biology. By understanding those differences, we can work toward better care that is matched to each person’s unique needs.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;While the study identified four autism subtypes, the researchers said there could be more and that unlocking this information may have significant implications for families.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“Understanding genetic causes for more individuals with autism could lead to more targeted developmental monitoring, precision treatment and tailored support and accommodations at school or work,” said Jennifer Foss-Feig, a coauthor of the study and a clinical psychologist at the Icahn School of Medicine at Mount Sinai who also serves as vice president and senior scientific officer at the Simons Foundation Autism Research Initiative. “It could tell families, when their children with autism are still young, something more about what symptoms they might — or might not — experience, what to look out for over the course of a lifespan, which treatments to pursue and how to plan for their future.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Disability Scoop</author><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 03:39:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMivAFBVV95cUxNX1ZyZlVVSF9Ub2JraldXOEM3ZjB4ZDF4bWVYdGhKWS1HWldlWjc4WGJJNU1ydGZjZTAtNzVWaEk4VWo3SXRsQXVVeFIzRHgzQWRsUXowOXhZYmg3MGNxbjNNbFczN3Rkcl9GTWU4RkhvTnpHU3dnWVl4WXFjR25WUVA0dFc2alE5UXNZcF9CUVM0Vlh5OS0tZDJTWFljYWJBRl9DMnNIaTNjYlloRUtWYy1Lc3F2SV9FeUZ3Tg</guid></item><item><title>日式散步、蛋白质提示和野火烟雾：健康与幸福的一周-《华盛顿邮报》 | Japanese walking, protein tips and wildfire smoke: The week in Well+Being - The Washington Post</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMilgFBVV95cUxOajhBVlBjU3NLRTBNY21yZlZwaEh3VWVTUV9MS24yd05nOXRrSzZqQUpjSFBUSVZ2OUxYWk0tdWF2VTFUbURqb2EzRW45NjZFZ2thQzBkMG5NNmpfNnVKdndjQUtFU29scDl1RVV1am1vdzB0SXBna05IT1Exa2lxQTZJLXI2RFVpa2ZsMlozUTBCd3hpd1E?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="meteredContent grid-center"&gt;&lt;div class="teaser-content"&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="UGQCTEK54VG6ZJMDUHNQ4TH7XI" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;&lt;i&gt;You’re reading our weekly Well+Being newsletter. &lt;/i&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/newsletters/well-being/?method=SURL&amp;amp;location=ART&amp;amp;itid=lk_inline_manual_2&amp;amp;itid=lk_inline_manual_2&amp;amp;itid=lk_inline_manual_2&amp;amp;itid=lk_inline_manual_2&amp;amp;itid=lk_inline_manual_2&amp;amp;itid=lk_inline_manual_2" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;i&gt;Sign up here&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;i&gt; to get it delivered to your inbox every Thursday.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="M265R3MXQVEFLA342IC4J2ZXYY" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Have you taken a walk today? Here at Well + Being, we’re excited about a “new” walking technique that’s actually been around for decades. And it’s worth rediscovering. As you know, exercise is so important for health and longevity, but it’s not always convenient or easy to schedule. That’s why we love to hear about workouts that maximize the benefits — better mood, sleep, muscle strength and blood pressure, anyone?— and doesn’t take &lt;i&gt;that&lt;/i&gt; long. This one, called “Japanese walking” can be done in just 30 minutes a day. And as an added bonus, summer can be the perfect time to take a walk in nature (which has its own mental health benefits) while also hitting your exercise goals. We’ve even scheduled a &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/wellness/2025/07/22/japanese-walking-questions-answers/" target="_blank"&gt;Live Chat on Tuesday at noon Eastern&lt;/a&gt; to answer your questions about how to use walking to get in shape. Please join us! But before that …&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-subscribe-cta" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-header" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;h2 id="GBRUOROFKBGXHJ7M6XROR3MGOQ" class="wpds-c-XIGbK wpds-c-XIGbK-iivLrAs-css headingStyleOverrides" data-apitype="header" data-contentid="GBRUOROFKBGXHJ7M6XROR3MGOQ" data-testid="article-header"&gt;This week’s must-reads:&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-list" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;ul class="PJLV font--article-body font-copy gray-darkest mt-0 mr-lg ml-lg mb-md list" data-contentid="6VOS4GDES5ACNFDGLCSBNZVCDU" data-apitype="list"&gt;&lt;li class="wpds-c-gtqFlz"&gt;&lt;span&gt;5 things doctors want you to know &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/wellness/2025/07/15/glp1-ozempic-nutrition-muscle-loss/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;b&gt;before you take a GLP-1&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="wpds-c-gtqFlz"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Do you use a fan to sleep? Here’s &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/wellness/2025/07/16/fans-sleep-circulation-white-noise/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;b&gt;why it works&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;b&gt;.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="wpds-c-gtqFlz"&gt;&lt;span&gt;I’m a pulmonologist. This is how I protect myself from &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/wellness/2025/07/15/how-lung-expert-protects-wildfire-smoke/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;b&gt;wildfire smoke&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;b&gt;.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="wpds-c-gtqFlz"&gt;&lt;span&gt;What causes obesity? A &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/wellness/2025/07/16/obesity-cause-diet-exercise/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;b&gt;major new study&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt; is upending common wisdom.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="wpds-c-gtqFlz"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Airplanes are loud and may &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/wellness/2025/07/14/loud-airplanes-damage-hearing/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;b&gt;damage your hearing&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. Here’s what helps.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="wpds-c-gtqFlz"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Is &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/wellness/2024/09/20/sparkling-water-hydration/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;b&gt;sparkling water&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt; as hydrating as plain water?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="wpds-c-gtqFlz"&gt;&lt;span&gt;What scientists think about new &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/technology/2025/07/16/orchid-polygenic-screening-embryos-fertility/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;b&gt;genetic prediction services&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt; for embryos&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-header" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;h2 id="FMNF5AUKEZBTLM6ME3KU4QOSPE" class="wpds-c-XIGbK wpds-c-XIGbK-iivLrAs-css headingStyleOverrides" data-apitype="header" data-contentid="FMNF5AUKEZBTLM6ME3KU4QOSPE" data-testid="article-header"&gt;How ‘Japanese walking’ may help you get in shape: Join our Live Chat!&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="RCVUR2BUPNEZRNAXLHNM2JN6SY" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;As one of the most accessible exercise options, walking is suitable for most people. One particular technique, known as interval walking training (IWT) or “Japanese walking,” is getting renewed attention after going viral on TikTok.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="ORKFK5FQYRH4FNN7F6XGKASSSQ" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;In a 2007 study, volunteers did three minutes of fast walking followed by three minutes at a slower pace, for 30 minutes per day at least four days per week. “One of the most surprising findings was that IWT markedly increased physical fitness and decreased blood pressure after the 5-month intervention whereas these improvements were not observed in the moderate-intensity continuous walking group,” Shizue Masuki, a researcher on the team and professor at Shinshu University Graduate School of Medicine in Matsumoto, told our reporter, Alexandra Frost.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-topic-follow-interstitial" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-header" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;h2 id="QD6CIJTJLNBUXMPBUEGLPULFHY" class="wpds-c-XIGbK wpds-c-XIGbK-iivLrAs-css headingStyleOverrides" data-apitype="header" data-contentid="QD6CIJTJLNBUXMPBUEGLPULFHY" data-testid="article-header"&gt;You might be fooling yourself about peanut butter&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="TOA62XB73VFNRLIZ3SWLXK35GE" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Optimizing your protein intake can be tricky. It’s not just &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/wellness/2023/05/24/protein-weight-loss-muscle-facts/" target="_blank"&gt;how much protein&lt;/a&gt; you eat that matters, but when you eat it, and the foods that you get it from. You may even have higher protein needs than you think depending on your overall health, your age, your activity levels and other factors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="RXY3DJDFUZG33NU46LVFUVT2MQ" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Nutrition reporter Anahad O’Connor spoke to experts and analyzed studies to identify the most common protein pitfalls. For example, you have probably heard that peanut butter has a lot of protein. But in reality, it’s a better source of fat than protein, said Jose Antonio, a professor of health and human performance at Nova Southeastern University in Florida. “The fat is good for you. But don’t fool yourself into thinking that you’re getting a lot of high-quality protein.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="YELXDYSLY5GE7IOUBO54HS23KM" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;To find out more about the mistakes that people make when it comes to eating protein, &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/wellness/2025/07/16/protein-how-much-do-i-need/" target="_blank"&gt;read our story here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-header" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;h2 id="GQU2LZM3U5BLHBP4ISI3JZU52I" class="wpds-c-XIGbK wpds-c-XIGbK-iivLrAs-css headingStyleOverrides" data-apitype="header" data-contentid="GQU2LZM3U5BLHBP4ISI3JZU52I" data-testid="article-header"&gt;What I eat in a day to boost my gut health&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="7GISK2JFOJDPXFRCUDOHSFGQ5E" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;&lt;i&gt;Our Ask a Doctor columnist is Trisha S. Pasricha, a physician at Beth Israel Deaconess Medical Center and an instructor in medicine at Harvard Medical School.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="HYABXFMUQFA4PIA5NGUIQKKHKE" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;&lt;b&gt;You talk a lot about how important it is to eat a high-fiber diet but that most Americans don’t meet their daily recommended fiber goals. What do you personally do to reach that goal?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="JEOLOOJO5FGRDI2VX6PODY7UZY" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Many of my patients automatically picture a “&lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/wellness/2025/04/14/im-gastroenterologist-here-are-8-tips-improve-your-gut-health/" target="_blank"&gt;high-fiber diet&lt;/a&gt;” as a life of &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/wellness/2023/11/20/kale-digestion-upset-stomach/" target="_blank"&gt;kale&lt;/a&gt; salads and never seeing a slice of white toast again.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="YMIFHRZJKZCU7DIUHDZXNJMN7Y" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;That’s not true — or at least it doesn’t have to be. As a gastroenterologist and busy mom, I operate on three big principles with my meals: They have to be easy to pull off (spending two hours prepping Instagram-worthy bento box lunches isn’t who I am), and I have to actually like my food. The easiest way to form &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/wellness/2023/12/21/habit-formation-practice-tips-brain/" target="_blank"&gt;healthier habits&lt;/a&gt; is to minimize the barriers to achieving them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="G43DA7PY6ZASRG5SBX7ZXOG2JQ" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Read her &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/wellness/2025/07/14/high-fiber-meal-plan/" target="_blank"&gt;full response&lt;/a&gt; here. And use our &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/wellness/2025/03/20/ask-a-doctor-health-question-form/" target="_blank"&gt;Ask a Doctor form&lt;/a&gt; to submit a question, and we may answer it in a future column.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-header" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;h2 id="RG3IALIZQ5CVPA6HFQQEAI2AUQ" class="wpds-c-XIGbK wpds-c-XIGbK-iivLrAs-css headingStyleOverrides" data-apitype="header" data-contentid="RG3IALIZQ5CVPA6HFQQEAI2AUQ" data-testid="article-header"&gt;Find your joy snack!&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="JB52TC5RYZF23FQB7FIYUGVIAY" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Here are a few things that brought us joy this week.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-list" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;ul class="PJLV font--article-body font-copy gray-darkest mt-0 mr-lg ml-lg mb-md list" data-contentid="JUHE2PFK5VCORDH6DDFZCOHNM4" data-apitype="list"&gt;&lt;li class="wpds-c-gtqFlz"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Why you should &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/travel/tips/duffel-bag-travel-hack/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;b&gt;ditch your roller bag&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="wpds-c-gtqFlz"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Eight decades later, a&lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/lifestyle/2025/07/15/holocaust-liberation-wwii-military-uscshoahfoundation/" target="_blank"&gt; &lt;b&gt;Holocaust survivor&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt; reunites with his liberator&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="wpds-c-gtqFlz"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Why &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/home/2025/07/23/tatami-mat-sleep-solution/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;b&gt;your next bed&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt; might be a 200-year-old Japanese design&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="wpds-c-gtqFlz"&gt;&lt;span&gt;A recipe for &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/recipes/colorful-summer-rolls-dipping-sauce/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;b&gt;colorful summer rolls&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt; with dipping sauce&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="wpds-c-gtqFlz"&gt;&lt;span&gt;A massive &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/lifestyle/2025/07/16/mars-meteorite-record-sale-sothebys-auction/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;b&gt;rock from Mars&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt; landed on Earth. It sold for a record $5.3M.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="wpds-c-gtqFlz"&gt;&lt;span&gt;This woman helped create a new tool that helps women&lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/lifestyle/2025/07/16/breast-cancer-detection-tool-uconn-engineering/" target="_blank"&gt; &lt;b&gt;look for breast tumors&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="wpds-c-gtqFlz"&gt;&lt;span&gt;A &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/lifestyle/2025/07/11/canada-ireland-message-bottle-brad-anita-squires/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;b&gt;love note in a bottle&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt; is found years later, an ocean away&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="ON44CMII5VBFDDOX62YPXL6MSA" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;&lt;i&gt;Let’s keep the conversation going. We want to hear from you! Email us at &lt;/i&gt;&lt;a href="mailto:wellbeing@washpost.com" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;i&gt;wellbeing@washpost.com&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;i&gt;.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="WIQWERRFMJA2JGV4QTR7TJNDBM" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;&lt;i&gt;Want to know more about “joy” snacks? Reporter and former neuroscientist &lt;/i&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/wellness/2022/11/17/feel-happier-joy-flourishing/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;i&gt;Richard Sima explains&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;i&gt; what they are and how they can make you feel happier. You can also &lt;/i&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/wellness/2023/02/24/joy-snacks-comic/?itid=lk_inline_manual_10" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;i&gt;read his advice as a comic&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;i&gt;.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 03:31:34 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilgFBVV95cUxOajhBVlBjU3NLRTBNY21yZlZwaEh3VWVTUV9MS24yd05nOXRrSzZqQUpjSFBUSVZ2OUxYWk0tdWF2VTFUbURqb2EzRW45NjZFZ2thQzBkMG5NNmpfNnVKdndjQUtFU29scDl1RVV1am1vdzB0SXBna05IT1Exa2lxQTZJLXI2RFVpa2ZsMlozUTBCd3hpd1E</guid></item><item><title>专家说，麻疹可以抹去免疫系统的记忆- ScienceAlert | Measles Can Erase Your Immune System's Memory, Expert Says - ScienceAlert</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMijgFBVV95cUxNeHNUc1psVmN1RzZaRmhkb080VEE2RExRY2xrZzBtbDc4VDdIRk9sNDExTldtVmpVUTF3ajVxVEJhT241eDVIT2xmWTNMRDBZMjlqNWRmcGxQdnFhRnpzN1czbHRIdnc0aXJ1MHJ3dzlvcWhyUlZGT3pVS2VxR25WaEhlRHB3VENZc0gwU1FR?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Blindness,  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/pneumonia" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73057" data-postid="168358" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;pneumonia&lt;/a&gt;, severe diarrhoea and even death – measles  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/virus" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73053" data-postid="168358" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;virus&lt;/a&gt; infections, especially in children, can have devastating consequences.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fortunately, we have a safe and effective defence. Measles vaccines are estimated to have averted more than &lt;a href="https://www.who.int/news-room/fact-sheets/detail/measles"&gt;60 million deaths&lt;/a&gt; between 2000 and 2023.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yet despite this success, measles cases are &lt;a href="https://www.who.int/data/gho/data/indicators/indicator-details/GHO/measles---number-of-reported-cases"&gt;rising sharply&lt;/a&gt; in the UK and around the world. This global surge is the result of several factors, from &lt;a href="https://www.unicef.org/press-releases/european-region-reports-highest-number-measles-cases-more-25-years-unicef-whoeurope"&gt;vaccine hesitancy to missed immunisation campaigns&lt;/a&gt;, leaving many children unprotected and vulnerable.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But there's more at stake than just measles itself. Emerging research suggests that the measles vaccination may offer surprising additional health benefits. Children who receive the vaccine have been shown to have a significantly &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/12690020/"&gt;lower risk of infections&lt;/a&gt; from diseases unrelated to measles.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/measles-devastates-your-body-in-a-variety-of-ways-heres-whats-at-risk?utm_source=SA_article&amp;amp;utm_campaign=related_link"&gt;Measles Devastates Your Body in a Variety of Ways. Here's What's at Risk.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One explanation for this broader benefit is the idea of "measles amnesia." This refers to the ability of the measles virus to erase parts of the body's immune memory.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Our immune system contains various cells that protect us from infections. Some produce  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/antibody" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73081" data-postid="168358" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;antibodies&lt;/a&gt; that neutralise  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/virus" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73053" data-postid="168358" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;viruses&lt;/a&gt;, while others detect and destroy infected cells. Immune memory allows the body to "remember" past infections and mount faster responses in the future.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32891958/"&gt;measles infection may reduce&lt;/a&gt; the number and diversity of these memory cells – leaving children vulnerable to a wide range of diseases they had previously developed immunity to. In other words, the virus doesn't just make children ill in the short term, it may also undo years of immune protection.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_168367" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-168367" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/07/measles_amnesia_vaccine_642.jpg" alt="white blood cells under a microscope" class="wp-image-168367 size-full" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/07/measles_amnesia_vaccine_642.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/07/measles_amnesia_vaccine_642-444x415.jpg 444w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/07/measles_amnesia_vaccine_642-600x561.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-168367" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Immune cells under a microscope. (jarun011/Getty Images)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;In one study, researchers found that between &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/31672891/"&gt;11% and 73% of antibodies&lt;/a&gt; targeting other diseases were lost after a measles infection in unvaccinated children. This immune depletion was not observed in children who had received the vaccine, suggesting that vaccination protects against this damaging effect.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This broad loss of immune protection may explain why measles outbreaks are often followed by spikes in other infectious diseases. Ongoing studies are exploring the impact of measles amnesia in regions such as &lt;a href="https://journals.plos.org/plosone/article?id=10.1371/journal.pone.0314828"&gt;West Africa&lt;/a&gt;, where measles and other infections remain widespread.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;A vaccine that does more?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another theory for the vaccine's broader benefit is known as the "non-specific effect". Unlike measles amnesia, which explains how the virus weakens immunity, the non-specific effect suggests that the measles vaccine actively strengthens the immune system against a wide range of pathogens.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Recent research has shown that measles vaccination may &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/38290093/"&gt;enhance the function&lt;/a&gt; of certain immune cells, making them more effective at fighting off other diseases. Some scientists believe this effect, rather than protection against amnesia alone, could be the primary reason why vaccinated children have better overall health outcomes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The measles vaccine is a &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/27737834/"&gt;live attenuated vaccine&lt;/a&gt;, which means it uses a weakened version of the virus to stimulate a strong immune response. Live vaccines, including the BCG vaccine for tuberculosis, are known to provide &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/27737834/"&gt;broad immune training effects&lt;/a&gt;, which may explain this non-specific protection.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Forgotten the dangers&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the 1960s, before widespread vaccination, measles caused around &lt;a href="https://www.who.int/news-room/fact-sheets/detail/measles"&gt;2.6 million deaths per year&lt;/a&gt;. It's hard to imagine today, but that's partly the problem.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As measles became rare, &lt;a href="https://www.who.int/news-room/fact-sheets/detail/measles"&gt;society began to forget&lt;/a&gt; how serious it is. We forgot how contagious it is (one infected person can spread the virus to up to 90% of nearby unvaccinated people) and we forgot how effective vaccination is (&lt;a href="https://www.who.int/teams/immunization-vaccines-and-biologicals/policies/position-papers/measles"&gt;two doses&lt;/a&gt; provide more than 90% long-term protection).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_168371" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-168371" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/07/measles_amnesia_rash_642.jpg" alt="measles rash" class="wp-image-168371 size-full" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/07/measles_amnesia_rash_642.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/07/measles_amnesia_rash_642-444x415.jpg 444w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/07/measles_amnesia_rash_642-600x561.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-168371" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Measles is more than an itchy rash. (Bilanol/Getty Images/Canva)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;And in some circles, this fading memory has been replaced by something more dangerous: mistrust. Misinformation, vaccine myths, and anti-vaccine rhetoric are spreading, just like the virus itself.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So, whether the additional protection offered by the vaccine is due to prevention of immune amnesia, a non-specific immune boost, or both, the takeaway is the same: Vaccinate children against measles. Because when we protect them from measles, we may also be protecting them from so much more.&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://counter.theconversation.com/content/261136/count.gif?distributor=republish-lightbox-basic" alt="The Conversation" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" loading="lazy"&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/profiles/antony-black-2393330"&gt;Antony Black&lt;/a&gt;, Lecturer, Life Sciences, &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/institutions/university-of-westminster-916"&gt;University of Westminster&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This article is republished from &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com"&gt;The Conversation&lt;/a&gt; under a Creative Commons license. Read the &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/measles-isnt-just-dangerous-it-may-erase-your-immune-system-261136"&gt;original article&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 02:15:48 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijgFBVV95cUxNeHNUc1psVmN1RzZaRmhkb080VEE2RExRY2xrZzBtbDc4VDdIRk9sNDExTldtVmpVUTF3ajVxVEJhT241eDVIT2xmWTNMRDBZMjlqNWRmcGxQdnFhRnpzN1czbHRIdnc0aXJ1MHJ3dzlvcWhyUlZGT3pVS2VxR25WaEhlRHB3VENZc0gwU1FR</guid></item><item><title>根据营养师的说法，您应该多吃但可能不会吃的令人惊讶的抗炎食物- EatingWell | The Surprising Anti-Inflammatory Food You Should Be Eating More Of but Probably Aren’t, According to Dietitians - EatingWell</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMilAFBVV95cUxOb1hueU1JcVhjTmh6dEpMc3FnSC0yQ0plRS1TMnNxYWZaaVo2ZWwybzRzZ1p0RTduUEZrUWQwb3ItRDdNa1hEdkh1YjVjNnJmVE5oOEVsdUwxODdpVkg2YUtmUk85VFJKQ0pldWlmTFUzN3ZEWGxRclN6T2FmbWxGdnQ4OW9pYUpZWldPWTNuMzNqSWEx?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-page_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-page mntl-block structured-content" data-sc-sticky-offset="90" data-sc-ad-label-height="24" data-sc-ad-track-spacing="100" data-sc-min-track-height="250" data-sc-max-track-height="600" data-sc-breakpoint="50em" data-sc-load-immediate="4" data-sc-content-positions="[1, 1250, 1550, 1950, 2350, 2750, 3150, 3550, 3950]" data-bind-scroll-on-start="true"&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-block_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-callout mntl-sc-block-universal-callout theme-generic" data-tracking-id="mntl-sc-block-callout" data-tracking-container="true"&gt;
&lt;div class="mntl-sc-block-universal-callout__body"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fatty fish like salmon and sardines are underrated anti-inflammatory foods that support overall health.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Rich in omega-3s like EPA and DHA, fish can help lower inflammation and protect the heart and brain.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Whether fresh, canned, or frozen, adding more fatty fish to your meals is simple—and worth the benefits.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_2-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; When you think of &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/anti-inflammatory-foods-to-stock-up-on-this-spring-11696622" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;anti-inflammatory foods&lt;/a&gt;, fatty fish like salmon, sardines and mackerel might not be the first to come to mind—but registered dietitians agree that they should be. Rich in omega-3 fatty acids, fatty fish may help reduce chronic inflammation and lower the risk of chronic diseases, like heart disease, type 2 diabetes, Alzheimer’s disease and cancer.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="1"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; “Including more fatty fish in your diet may support overall health and reduce your risk of these inflammation-related conditions,” says &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/author/lauren-manaker/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;Lauren Manaker, M.S., RDN&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="2"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="3"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_3-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_4-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Read on to learn why fatty fish like &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/8040993/is-salmon-good-for-you/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;salmon&lt;/a&gt;, sardines, mackerel, herring and anchovies are anti-inflammatory foods that you should be eating more of, plus tips for incorporating fish into your diet.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_5-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-how-can-fatty-fish-help-with-inflammation"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_6-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; How Can Fatty Fish Help with Inflammation?  &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_7-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Fatty fish like salmon, tuna, mackerel, &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/8059288/are-canned-sardines-healthy/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;sardines&lt;/a&gt; and anchovies are an excellent source of &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/8035578/omega-3-supplements-benefits/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;omega-3 fatty acids&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="4"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; More specifically, they’re rich in the long-chain omega-3 fatty acids eicosapentaenoic acid (EPA) and docosahexaenoic acid (DHA), which have anti-inflammatory effects.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="5"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; “These essential fatty acids play a critical role in reducing inflammation in the body,” Manaker says. “They work by decreasing the production of inflammatory molecules and compounds, which can help manage &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/what-is-inflammation-8766645" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="3"&gt;chronic inflammation&lt;/a&gt; linked to conditions like heart disease.”&lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_8-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_9-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; One study found that consuming two to three portions of fish per week reduced the risk of cardiovascular disease and cardiovascular disease outcomes by 8% and 10%, respectively. It also found that daily fish intake reduced the risk of heart disease by up to 30%.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="8"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_10-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_11-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; You can think of these anti-inflammatory properties as a protective barrier that helps defend the body against cellular damage. “Consuming more fatty fish [may also] help ensure our organs are protected from external and internal threats, such as pollutants,” says &lt;a href="https://tracynutrition.com/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Tracy Lockwood Beckerman, M.S., RD&lt;/a&gt;. These essential fatty acids are also important for supporting heart, &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/8026789/best-nutrient-for-brain-health-as-you-age/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;brain&lt;/a&gt; and skin health, adds &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/eastcoasthealth" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="3"&gt;Maddie Pasquariello, M.S., RD&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="6"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="7"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_12-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_13-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Because the body can’t produce them on its own, it’s essential to consume &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/foods-with-as-many-omega-3s-as-salmon-11681920" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;omega-3s through food&lt;/a&gt;. There’s no official recommendation for how much EPA and DHA to consume daily. However, the American Heart Association recommends eating 3 ounces of fish—preferably oily fish—at least twice a week.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="9"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_14-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_16-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-other-reasons-to-eat-fatty-fish"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_17-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; Other Reasons to Eat Fatty Fish &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_18-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Beyond their anti-inflammatory benefits, fatty fish are also a great source of &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/4-anti-inflammatory-proteins-you-should-be-eating-11679932" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;protein&lt;/a&gt;, which helps with muscle repair, growth and immune functioning. They also contain a variety of micronutrients that are essential for overall health. “Fatty fish are a source of vitamins and minerals such as vitamin D, a nutrient crucial for bone health and immune support, and selenium, an antioxidant that protects cells from damage,” says Manaker.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_19-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-tips-for-eating-more-fatty-fish"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_20-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; Tips for Eating More Fatty Fish &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_21-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Add Sardines or Anchovies to Salads, Snacks and Appetizers: &lt;/strong&gt;“I love using anchovies in Caesar dressing or on top of salads, and sardines are delicious on toast as an appetizer or snack,” Pasquariello says. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Start with a Milder Fish:&lt;/strong&gt; “Salmon and tuna are some of the easiest fish to cook, requiring just a quick sear or bake in the oven,” Pasquariello says. “I love pairing salmon with a Dijon mustard glaze or simple lemon and olive oil dressing, or cooking tuna with a quick sear on each side and topping it with sesame seeds and soy sauce.” &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/underrated-fish-you-should-be-eating-more-of-11727002" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Trout&lt;/a&gt; is another mild fish that’s quick to prepare. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Enjoy in Smaller Amounts: &lt;/strong&gt;If you don’t &lt;em&gt;love&lt;/em&gt; the taste of fish but still want to give it a try, consider a dish where fish plays more of a supporting role rather than the central focus. “You can add fish to dishes like pasta along with other ingredients to dilute the taste while still reaping the benefits,” Manaker says. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Eat More Canned Fish:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/8058717/reasons-to-eat-canned-fish-according-to-a-dietitian/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;Canned fish&lt;/a&gt;, like salmon or sardines, offer a convenient and cost-effective way to add more fish to your diet. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-sc-block-adslot-inline"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Stock Your Freezer with Frozen Fish: &lt;/strong&gt;Keep frozen fish on hand for nights when you’re too busy to make it to the grocery store. “Frozen options provide the same beneficial antioxidants and anti-inflammatory properties as fresh fish and might even have a less-pronounced fishy smell during cooking,” Beckerman says. Plus, you can &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/cooking-salmon-from-frozen-8759544" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="3"&gt;cook salmon directly from frozen&lt;/a&gt;—no thawing required. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_22-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_24-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-our-expert-take"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_25-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; Our Expert Take &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_26-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Fatty fish are rich in omega-3 fatty acids and are an excellent addition to an &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/what-is-an-anti-inflammatory-diet-8764103" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;anti-inflammatory diet&lt;/a&gt;. If you’re not eating fatty fish like tuna, mackerel, sardines and salmon regularly, now is a great time to start. And remember, eating fish doesn’t have to be complicated or expensive. Try adding fresh or canned fish to scrambled eggs, salads, toast, stir-fries or pasta dishes. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_27-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_28-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; “Start by incorporating it into meals you already enjoy—think salmon on a salad, mackerel spread on whole-grain crackers or tuna in a wrap,” Manaker says. “Aim for about two servings of lower-mercury fatty fish per week.”&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>EatingWell</author><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilAFBVV95cUxOb1hueU1JcVhjTmh6dEpMc3FnSC0yQ0plRS1TMnNxYWZaaVo2ZWwybzRzZ1p0RTduUEZrUWQwb3ItRDdNa1hEdkh1YjVjNnJmVE5oOEVsdUwxODdpVkg2YUtmUk85VFJKQ0pldWlmTFUzN3ZEWGxRclN6T2FmbWxGdnQ4OW9pYUpZWldPWTNuMzNqSWEx</guid></item><item><title>“我们是一个生病的社区” ：加拉廷县的药物滥用恶化- KBZK新闻 | “We Are a Sick Community”: Gallatin County’s substance abuse worsens - KBZK News</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiowFBVV95cUxQY2pHd2hZa0JPc085YTI1QkpiUFhpelRwdGE0eVZLNXFLcXRMRW1KdkVMUk5LZElTRmhMUzZxaG1RdVB2eUx2Vnk4N2xzTUJtMC1jMndRVHNTVDRtYndMTktfV0JfeDZ5Ukk0eHVwOTJhZFFGRDFhMnlCSi01aHRaVHVWUmhqbTJwX2c4Mm9jQlIyUW9FcFBQWHBwRjlJVmo1NnJN?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="RichTextArticleBody-body"&gt;&lt;p&gt;BOZEMAN — Gallatin County recently grabbed national attention after a CDC report labeled it the “drunkest county in America.” But while the headline may sound lighthearted to some, the reality unfolding behind the scenes paints a far more serious picture.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr. Jessie Holton, a veteran, former law enforcement officer, and now a licensed addiction counselor at Cedar Creek Integrated Health, knows the reality all too well. He’s been sober for 14 and a half years and now helps others navigate the same fight.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;WATCH: Gallatin County Grapples with Reputation as 'Drunkest County in America'&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="VideoEnhancement" data-video-disable-history&gt;
    
        &lt;p class="VideoEnhancement-title"&gt;Gallatin County, Montana Grapples with Reputation as 'Drunkest County in America'&lt;/p&gt;
    
    
    
        
    
    
&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It’s a far worse problem than I think people realize,” Holton said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As first reported in January, the CDC found that 26.8 percent of Gallatin County residents drink excessively, giving it the highest rate of heavy drinking in the nation. Holton says that numbers don’t just reflect lifestyle; they reflect culture.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="Figure" itemscope itemtype="http://schema.org/ImageObject"&gt;
    
        &lt;div class="Figure-container"&gt;
            &lt;img src="https://ewscripps.brightspotcdn.com/dims4/default/faf88d0/2147483647/strip/true/crop/3410x1912+0+0/resize/1280x718!/quality/90/?url=http%3A%2F%2Fewscripps-brightspot.s3.amazonaws.com%2F18%2Fc4%2F74db7af74b468aec514544eda415%2Fscreenshot-2025-07-17-at-4-37-47-pm.png" alt="Drive Sober Sign" srcset="https://ewscripps.brightspotcdn.com/dims4/default/faf88d0/2147483647/strip/true/crop/3410x1912+0+0/resize/1280x718!/quality/90/?url=http%3A%2F%2Fewscripps-brightspot.s3.amazonaws.com%2F18%2Fc4%2F74db7af74b468aec514544eda415%2Fscreenshot-2025-07-17-at-4-37-47-pm.png 1x,https://ewscripps.brightspotcdn.com/dims4/default/95e1f69/2147483647/strip/true/crop/3410x1912+0+0/resize/2560x1436!/quality/90/?url=http%3A%2F%2Fewscripps-brightspot.s3.amazonaws.com%2F18%2Fc4%2F74db7af74b468aec514544eda415%2Fscreenshot-2025-07-17-at-4-37-47-pm.png 2x"&gt;&lt;p class="Figure-credit" itemprop="author"&gt;MTN News &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    
    
        &lt;figcaption class="Figure-caption" itemprop="caption"&gt;MTN News &lt;/figcaption&gt;
    
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“How many breweries do we have? How many coffee shops do we have? We are a culture, a community that is thriving off of chemical dependency,” Holton says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Holton says that while Gallatin Valley offers mountain views, outdoor recreation, and a high quality of life, he says that comes at a steep price for many. Also known as a paradise paradox.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The minute we create a culture that uses chemical dependency as a coping mechanism, you’ve already created the disease,” Holton said. “Now, when we have people that are affected by it, you have to help them and treat them, and we have to change the culture. The area we live in is beautiful, but we are a sick community. We really are.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And the numbers back him up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to the Montana Department of Public Health and Human Services,alcohol-related deaths have nearly doubled over the past decade, rising from 1,563 deaths between 2009 and 2013 to 2,941 between 2019 and 2023.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In 2023 alone, hospitals across the state billed over $220 million for alcohol-related hospitalizations and emergency department visits. And in 2024, 66.7 percent of Montanans in treatment for substance use disorders reported alcohol as their primary substance of misuse.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bozeman Police Chief Jim Veltkamp says the numbers are felt daily by first responders.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I can tell you when patrol officers are out on patrol, most calls they go to involve alcohol in some way, shape, or form,” Veltkamp said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He added that one troubling sign of alcohol misuse is the high level of tolerance officers often encounter.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“We routinely see people at a very high alcohol concentration who seem to be functioning pretty decently — and that is an indication that it’s very common for them to be consuming very large amounts of alcoholic beverages,” he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr. Holton says that reflects a broader change in the substances people are using — and how strong those substances have become.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The substances we are using are getting higher in concentration,” Holton said. “You are going to end up with a quicker dependency, you’re going to have more health problems, and more criminal justice interactions.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He says 90 percent of the clients at Cedar Creek have had some involvement with the criminal justice system, and while the clinic runs intensive outpatient &lt;br&gt;programs, resources are stretched thin.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;With the closure of facilities like the Hope House in Bozeman and federal funding freezes looming, Holton says his staff is already seeing the impact.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“We are starting to see the influx of clients coming in and the people that need help,” he said. “We are in need of more funding because it doesn't exist.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Despite the challenges, Holton says he and his team remain committed to the work because, without them, many people would have nowhere to turn.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“They are long days. But it is what we have to do in this community to be able to make it viable. If not, our doors would be closed. And then what do we have?”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Resources: &lt;a class="Link" href="https://dphhs.mt.gov/BHDD/SubstanceAbuse/index"&gt;&lt;u&gt;https://dphhs.mt.gov/BHDD/SubstanceAbuse/index&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a class="Link" href="https://www.cedarcreekintegratedhealth.org/"&gt;&lt;u&gt;https://www.cedarcreekintegratedhealth.org/&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>KBZK News</author><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 23:32:59 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiowFBVV95cUxQY2pHd2hZa0JPc085YTI1QkpiUFhpelRwdGE0eVZLNXFLcXRMRW1KdkVMUk5LZElTRmhMUzZxaG1RdVB2eUx2Vnk4N2xzTUJtMC1jMndRVHNTVDRtYndMTktfV0JfeDZ5Ukk0eHVwOTJhZFFGRDFhMnlCSi01aHRaVHVWUmhqbTJwX2c4Mm9jQlIyUW9FcFBQWHBwRjlJVmo1NnJN</guid></item><item><title>在社区最黑暗的一天之后， Tyler's Tee-Off仍然是光明的灯塔- theCHIVE | Tyler’s Tee-Off continues to be a beacon of light after community’s darkest day - theCHIVE</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMi-AFBVV95cUxQeHQzVGg2M08yY2tsN1JCWXNZRUhpX0pORE52SWFSZnFPWHhydDRzOHJReUpteThWYnhKd3RLbm1Gb1o0blVZVkE5ZnEtemRLaTVuZVh1X0xVeEJDOEZZc3BRMEQ4SE0ySlhhMUZGaEJaOTN3YVpPdFY1c214Znp4T0gzSFk4OFVpcjlMd1NLUUg4RDlFWHl4bVdKaldvTlNqb0w3S0ZhbUlvR29Kckx3b0JOSGFHYjdfd0RUX3dpY2Rady1hRzNqcWhoazJBLVhUZ0tqcVdrUFRtdndxdEVyaEVCVERXM1lYMXoxY1ZtZ2I2RzdkZ3d5RQ?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="modal-content"&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;You are now leaving theCHIVE.com, click continue to proceed&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;a href="#" class="continue-btn" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;
            Continue
        &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>theCHIVE</author><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 21:48:27 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi-AFBVV95cUxQeHQzVGg2M08yY2tsN1JCWXNZRUhpX0pORE52SWFSZnFPWHhydDRzOHJReUpteThWYnhKd3RLbm1Gb1o0blVZVkE5ZnEtemRLaTVuZVh1X0xVeEJDOEZZc3BRMEQ4SE0ySlhhMUZGaEJaOTN3YVpPdFY1c214Znp4T0gzSFk4OFVpcjlMd1NLUUg4RDlFWHl4bVdKaldvTlNqb0w3S0ZhbUlvR29Kckx3b0JOSGFHYjdfd0RUX3dpY2Rady1hRzNqcWhoazJBLVhUZ0tqcVdrUFRtdndxdEVyaEVCVERXM1lYMXoxY1ZtZ2I2RzdkZ3d5RQ</guid></item><item><title>专家警告佛罗里达州的危险食肉细菌- WPLG Local 10 | Experts warn against dangerous flesh-eating bacteria in Florida - WPLG Local 10</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMirwFBVV95cUxQbDRMVTFWc0VlbV9UTy1fY3ZjMC1HLWUzM3FrVGxjOW5SVDV2VW02S0hWcG9XTHdJd3lkc1l4eUFfS01VUFpKeUNDQy1GblVPOUdDMWN6YTNzRlJWQWlEV1BYc0lWODkxRU5kVk9kS1JHaEVaWnFFZVh3UmlVWHlOMUVqdDRXSXNrQUpRNkZZOTRWQW9xN3dtcDVhQ0RSMW00NnpvTFR5WWNFU2JVN2tr?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article class="b-article-body"&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;PEMBROKE PINES, Fla.  — Flesh-eating bacteria has killed four people in Florida, including one person in Broward County, according to the Florida Department of Health. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="c-media-item"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="c-media-item__fig-caption"&gt;&lt;span class="c-media-item__title"&gt;Warning comes from experts regarding flesh-eating bacteria in Florida &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;Several years ago, relatives of William Pledger says he was in the bay off Pensacola Beach watching an air show. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.local10.com/espanol/2025/07/17/expertos-advierten-sobre-peligrosa-bacteria-come-carne-en-florida/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer" title="https://www.local10.com/espanol/2025/07/17/expertos-advierten-sobre-peligrosa-bacteria-come-carne-en-florida/"&gt;Leer en español&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;Five days later, his leg, which had a small cut on it, started getting sore.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;Then things took a turn for the worse as he was diagnosed with vibrio vulnificus which stems from bacteria found in warm coastal water that can cause severe, life threatening infections.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;That portion of Pledger’s leg had to be amputated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;Local 10 News spoke to another man who cut a toe on a barnacle in Longboat Key 13 years ago.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;After suffering severe pain, he was put into the intensive care unit for 10 days and still has the scars.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;Vibrio vulnificus is rare, but it’s on the rise with warmer temperatures. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;Health experts say symptoms include vomiting, diarrhea, abdominal pain, skin breakdown and blistering.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;They also say to avoid warm saltwater or brackish water if you have a weakened immune system or have open cuts or wounds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph b-article-body__copyright"&gt;Copyright 2025 by WPLG Local10.com - All rights reserved.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>WPLG Local 10</author><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 21:42:06 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMirwFBVV95cUxQbDRMVTFWc0VlbV9UTy1fY3ZjMC1HLWUzM3FrVGxjOW5SVDV2VW02S0hWcG9XTHdJd3lkc1l4eUFfS01VUFpKeUNDQy1GblVPOUdDMWN6YTNzRlJWQWlEV1BYc0lWODkxRU5kVk9kS1JHaEVaWnFFZVh3UmlVWHlOMUVqdDRXSXNrQUpRNkZZOTRWQW9xN3dtcDVhQ0RSMW00NnpvTFR5WWNFU2JVN2tr</guid></item><item><title>开创性的新方法可以以98 ％的准确率在症状出现前检测出帕金森氏症的年份-每日邮报 | Groundbreaking new method can detect Parkinson's years before symptoms with 98% accuracy - Daily Mail</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMinAFBVV95cUxPa2hxRnIzRXF0WGtjX3RnZkEzM3BURVN5dlJyRnNFcElpSkVjbktBUGVRc2Q5c0pOS1ljZm5IVjBqZTU5a2JlYXBfazhZWk5VeGpHdFdGaWxybHpZLUc4RTNwY3lmX1JNSlhSZFZXaWc3c05SVUdudDRIcHVfM00wVmZRUGJHeTRVejBSMkRqV29yRktncW4yMHZteUXSAaIBQVVfeXFMT1pTU09ybDU1OFlJT0V4eUlfT2JZd1RPQjl0UUxDYzhsUWNnRkhobjh3blV1RFU3WnM0X3BOQzNpX29xbGQtTGlZVHdhMGs5anlEOW9IZXMwdjRwT3dDVEVPaXZHMVpqWUhmdUo5YnNFR1JtSGtBSXNjZjUwZGxDSS1seHhCcTREOVRSd3pTM3dqTjZueTJtcWlsQjBEd0U5cExR?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div itemprop="articleBody"&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;font&gt;&lt;font&gt;&lt;font&gt;&lt;font&gt;Your dog may be able to tell if you develop Parkinson's disease years before any symptom, a new study suggests.&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;font&gt;&lt;font&gt;&lt;font&gt;&lt;font&gt;Parkinson's disease is a progressive neurological disorder that primarily affects movement,&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/health/article-14731127/change-vision-sign-Parkinsons-depth-perception-punam-krishan.html"&gt;&lt;font&gt;&lt;font&gt;&lt;font&gt;&lt;font&gt; causing symptoms like tremors, stiffness&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;font&gt;&lt;font&gt;&lt;font&gt;&lt;font&gt; and slow movement. &lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;font&gt;&lt;font&gt;&lt;font&gt;&lt;font&gt;Currently, this incurable disease can't be diagnosed with a definitive test and most patients do not know they have the condition until symptoms begin.&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;font&gt;&lt;font&gt;&lt;font&gt;&lt;font&gt;However, now researchers from University of Bristol, UK have found that dogs can smell the signs of Parkinson's disease (PD) through skin swabs with 98 percent accuracy well before any other test. &lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;font&gt;&lt;font&gt;&lt;font&gt;&lt;font&gt;Lead author Dr Nicola Rooney, Associate Professor at Bristol Veterinary School &lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;a class="" rel="nofollow noreferrer noopener" target="_blank" href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/07/250716000846.htm"&gt;&lt;font&gt;&lt;font&gt;&lt;font&gt;&lt;font&gt;said&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;font&gt;&lt;font&gt;&lt;font&gt;&lt;font&gt;: 'Identifying diagnostic biomarkers of PD, particularly those that may predict development or help diagnose disease earlier is the subject of much ongoing research. &lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;font&gt;&lt;font&gt;&lt;font&gt;&lt;font&gt;'I believe that dogs could help us to develop a quick non-invasive and cost-effective method to identify patients with Parkinson's disease.'&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;font&gt;&lt;font&gt;&lt;font&gt;&lt;font&gt;As of 2025, over 1million Americans suffer from the neurological disorder and a new person is diagnosed with every six minutes, according to American Parkinson Disease Association. &lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;font&gt;&lt;font&gt;&lt;font&gt;&lt;font&gt;Despite mostly affecting older adults aged 65 and above, about 10 percent of people are diagnosed prior to age 40 with young-onset Parkinson's. &lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;&lt;p class="clear"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;&lt;font&gt;&lt;font&gt;&lt;font&gt;&lt;font&gt;Actor Michael J Fox was diagnosed with Parkinson's disease at just 29 years old while former NFL player Brett Favre was diagnosed in January 2024&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;font&gt;&lt;font&gt;&lt;font&gt;&lt;font&gt;During early stages of Parkinson's disease, the neurons in the brain responsible for producing a chemical called dopamine begin to slowly break down or die. &lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;font&gt;&lt;font&gt;&lt;font&gt;&lt;font&gt;Dopamine acts as a messenger between the parts of the brain and nervous system that help control and coordinate body movements. &lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;font&gt;&lt;font&gt;&lt;font&gt;&lt;font&gt;The lack of dopamine causes the primary symptoms of the disease to begin appearing including tremors, drooling, cramped or small handwriting, trouble swallowing and a loss of smell. &lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;font&gt;&lt;font&gt;&lt;font&gt;&lt;font&gt;Over time, as the neurons continue to die, the patients also begins to experience a slowness in movement, muscle stiffness, balance problems and begin to show signs of depression. &lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;font&gt;&lt;font&gt;&lt;font&gt;&lt;font&gt;Ultimately, those suffering from Parkinson's may be unable to stand or walk independently and require a wheelchair or are bedridden. They may also require around-the-clock care. &lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;font&gt;&lt;font&gt;&lt;font&gt;&lt;font&gt;Medication can help manage symptoms, but their effectiveness may decrease over time, requiring adjustments to treatment plans. &lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;font&gt;&lt;font&gt;&lt;font&gt;&lt;font&gt;In this study, published in &lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;a class="" rel="noreferrer noopener" target="_blank" href="http://dx.doi.org/10.1177/1877718X251342485"&gt;&lt;font&gt;&lt;font&gt;&lt;font&gt;&lt;font&gt;The Journal of Parkinson's Disease&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;font&gt;&lt;font&gt;&lt;font&gt;&lt;font&gt;, the British researchers trained two dogs, a golden retriever and black labrador.&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;font&gt;&lt;font&gt;&lt;font&gt;&lt;font&gt;Both animals were given over 200 odor samples to learn how to recognize the difference in smell between skin oil (sebum) samples from individuals with Parkinson's and those without for weeks. &lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;&lt;font&gt;&lt;font&gt;&lt;font&gt;&lt;font&gt;Researchers have found that dogs can smell the signs of Parkinson's disease (stock image)&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;font&gt;&lt;font&gt;&lt;font&gt;&lt;font&gt;The dogs were rewarded when they correctly identified a positive sample or accurately ignored a negative one.&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;font&gt;&lt;font&gt;&lt;font&gt;&lt;font&gt;In a double-blind trial, where neither the handlers nor researchers knew which samples were which, the dogs were able to recognize nearly all Parkinson's-infected swabs.&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;font&gt;&lt;font&gt;&lt;font&gt;&lt;font&gt;Moreover, they were also able to detect Parkinson's in swabs from people with multiple health conditions.&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;font&gt;&lt;font&gt;&lt;font&gt;&lt;font&gt;As a result, the researchers concluded that the disease has a unique scent signature, and dogs could help identify it through subtle changes in the sebum produced by individuals with the disease. &lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;font&gt;&lt;font&gt;&lt;font&gt;&lt;font&gt;This could pioneer a faster, non-invasive way to detect the disease years earlier than current methods allow, experts claimed. &lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;font&gt;&lt;font&gt;&lt;font&gt;&lt;font&gt;Claire Guest, CEO of Medical Detection Dogs, the company that collaborated with the scientists, said: 'We are extremely proud to say that once again, dogs can very accurately detect disease.&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    
    
    &lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;font&gt;&lt;font&gt;&lt;font&gt;&lt;font&gt;'There is currently no early test for Parkinson's disease and symptoms may start up to 20 years before they become visible and persistent leading to a confirmed diagnosis.&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;font&gt;&lt;font&gt;&lt;font&gt;&lt;font&gt;'Timely diagnosis is key as subsequent treatment could slow down the progression of the disease and reduce the intensity of symptoms.'&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;font&gt;&lt;font&gt;&lt;font&gt;&lt;font&gt;Previous research has shown that Parkinson's disease affects the production and composition of sebum in the skin which can lead to an altered odor. &lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;font&gt;&lt;font&gt;&lt;font&gt;&lt;font&gt;Since dogs have a highly developed sense of smell, far superior to humans, they are able to detect these subtle differences in scent and identify signs of the disease earlier than any other evaluation. &lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
            

            
            
            
            
            &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Daily Mail</author><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 21:25:52 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMinAFBVV95cUxPa2hxRnIzRXF0WGtjX3RnZkEzM3BURVN5dlJyRnNFcElpSkVjbktBUGVRc2Q5c0pOS1ljZm5IVjBqZTU5a2JlYXBfazhZWk5VeGpHdFdGaWxybHpZLUc4RTNwY3lmX1JNSlhSZFZXaWc3c05SVUdudDRIcHVfM00wVmZRUGJHeTRVejBSMkRqV29yRktncW4yMHZteUXSAaIBQVVfeXFMT1pTU09ybDU1OFlJT0V4eUlfT2JZd1RPQjl0UUxDYzhsUWNnRkhobjh3blV1RFU3WnM0X3BOQzNpX29xbGQtTGlZVHdhMGs5anlEOW9IZXMwdjRwT3dDVEVPaXZHMVpqWUhmdUo5YnNFR1JtSGtBSXNjZjUwZGxDSS1seHhCcTREOVRSd3pTM3dqTjZueTJtcWlsQjBEd0U5cExR</guid></item><item><title>如果您是素食主义者但仍然疲惫不堪，您可能做错了这7件事- VegOut | If you're a vegan but still tired, you're probably doing these 7 things wrong - VegOut</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMitAFBVV95cUxNLW4xQnhZenpOSEVFWEtfamM0LTk1U3ZBYm8zTXZZRHpENnd3ajFaM1I0b0k3STNpTWtjcngxRF8wa2lrSnVtYlNjcHE4TTRXR0p3OHpGczVGT3NVdU5WQWhpYXNSNGRYRFVlOW0zS19HcXZHY3owR19jeVU0cm9UaVBRNmN1X1BMS05uOEhqblo4Z29hS2VQTmV3S1FyOHJ4Y1RPTUlEY0FwZzlrRF8xU1R3NlQ?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="markdown prose dark:prose-invert w-full break-words light"&gt;
&lt;p data-start="83" data-end="416"&gt;Crafting a plant-powered menu is one thing; turning that menu into all-day energy is another.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="83" data-end="416"&gt;I’ve met plenty of vegans (myself included) who checked every ethical box yet still felt like an extra on &lt;em data-start="285" data-end="303"&gt;The Walking Dead&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="83" data-end="416"&gt;If that’s you, chances are you’re tripping over one—or several—of the seven missteps below.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="83" data-end="416"&gt;Let’s fix them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 data-start="423" data-end="451"&gt;1. Under-eating calories&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p data-start="453" data-end="826"&gt;“Many new vegans find themselves constantly snacking or feeling fatigued… you’re just not eating enough calories or protein or fat or some combination thereof,” notes dietitian Sapna Vora in an interview with &lt;a href="https://plantbasednews.org/lifestyle/food/mistakes-new-vegans-make"&gt;&lt;em data-start="662" data-end="680"&gt;Plant Based News.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="828" data-end="1064"&gt;Plant foods are champions of nutrient density but lightweights in calorie density. Swapping a chicken-and-rice bowl (600 kcal) for a kale-and-quinoa bowl (350 kcal) looks heroic on Instagram—until your blood sugar free-falls by 3 p.m.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="1066" data-end="1400"&gt;My own wake-up call came during a photo-shoot week in Portland. I stuffed myself with smoothie bowls, felt “full,” then spent the afternoons yawning behind the lens.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="1066" data-end="1400"&gt;A calorie tracker revealed I’d been undershooting my needs by 600 kcal a day. Once I added an extra scoop of peanut butter and a fistful of walnuts, the slump vanished.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="1402" data-end="1418"&gt;&lt;strong data-start="1402" data-end="1416"&gt;Quick fix:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul data-start="1419" data-end="1663"&gt;
&lt;li data-start="1419" data-end="1578"&gt;
&lt;p data-start="1421" data-end="1578"&gt;Anchor every meal with a calorie-dense core: oats + nut butter at breakfast, hummus + whole-grain pita at lunch, or tofu curry with coconut milk at dinner.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li data-start="1579" data-end="1663"&gt;
&lt;p data-start="1581" data-end="1663"&gt;Don’t fear healthy fats; one tablespoon of olive oil adds 120 effortless calories.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 data-start="1670" data-end="1697"&gt;2. Skipping vitamin B12&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p data-start="1699" data-end="2074"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.vegansociety.com/resources/nutrition-and-health/nutrients/vitamin-b12/what-every-vegan-should-know-about-vitamin-b12"&gt;The Vegan Society&lt;/a&gt; puts it bluntly: “To get the full benefit of a vegan diet, vegans should either eat fortified foods two or three times a day or take a B12 supplement.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="2076" data-end="2323"&gt;B12 keeps your red-blood-cell factory humming; stall that assembly line and oxygen delivery plummets—hello, chronic fatigue. Because plants don’t make B12, relying on kombucha “trace amounts” is like banking on rainfall to fill your swimming pool.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="2325" data-end="2341"&gt;&lt;strong data-start="2325" data-end="2339"&gt;Quick fix:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul data-start="2342" data-end="2554"&gt;
&lt;li data-start="2342" data-end="2459"&gt;
&lt;p data-start="2344" data-end="2459"&gt;Pick one: 2–3 servings of B12-fortified foods daily &lt;strong data-start="2396" data-end="2402"&gt;or&lt;/strong&gt; a 250–500 µg chewable supplement several times a week.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li data-start="2460" data-end="2554"&gt;
&lt;p data-start="2462" data-end="2554"&gt;Check labels: some plant milks contain as little as 0.4 µg per cup—far below the 2.4 µg RDA.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 data-start="2561" data-end="2584"&gt;3. Overlooking iron&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p data-start="2586" data-end="2875"&gt;&lt;a href="https://nutritionsource.hsph.harvard.edu/iron/"&gt;Harvard’s Nutrition Source&lt;/a&gt; reminds us that iron-deficiency anemia is “the most common nutritional deficiency worldwide, causing extreme fatigue and lightheadedness.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="2877" data-end="3219"&gt;Non-heme iron (the plant kind) absorbs at roughly 10 % the rate of heme iron. Translation: that heroic spinach salad needs a strategy. I learned this the hard way after a routine blood panel flagged low ferritin.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="2877" data-end="3219"&gt;A squeeze of lemon over my lentils and a daily Brazil-nut-and-raisin trail mix nudged levels back into range within three months.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="3221" data-end="3237"&gt;&lt;strong data-start="3221" data-end="3235"&gt;Quick fix:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul data-start="3238" data-end="3524"&gt;
&lt;li data-start="3238" data-end="3341"&gt;
&lt;p data-start="3240" data-end="3341"&gt;Pair iron-rich beans, lentils, or tofu with vitamin C sidekicks—citrus, bell peppers, strawberries.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li data-start="3342" data-end="3429"&gt;
&lt;p data-start="3344" data-end="3429"&gt;Keep coffee and tea an hour away from iron-focused meals; tannins block absorption.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li data-start="3430" data-end="3524"&gt;
&lt;p data-start="3432" data-end="3524"&gt;Consider a gentle iron bisglycinate supplement if bloodwork—and your doctor—say you need it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 data-start="3531" data-end="3563"&gt;4. Living on processed carbs&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p data-start="3565" data-end="3836"&gt;Vegan convenience foods rescue road-trips but sabotage steady energy. On a recent Japan swing, I subsisted on konbini (convenience-store) white-bread sandwiches and soy lattes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="3565" data-end="3836"&gt;Delicious? Absolutely. Sustaining? Not so much. By day three my brain felt like mushy edamame.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="3838" data-end="4073"&gt;Ultra-processed carbs spike glucose, trigger insulin crashes, and leave you hunting for the next wrapper. Whole-grain, fiber-rich staples release energy slowly and deliver minerals the body converts into ATP (think quinoa’s magnesium).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="4075" data-end="4091"&gt;&lt;strong data-start="4075" data-end="4089"&gt;Quick fix:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul data-start="4092" data-end="4375"&gt;
&lt;li data-start="4092" data-end="4196"&gt;
&lt;p data-start="4094" data-end="4196"&gt;Build a “half-plate” habit: fill 50 % of your plate with vegetables or fruit before adding starches.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li data-start="4197" data-end="4299"&gt;
&lt;p data-start="4199" data-end="4299"&gt;Swap refined grains for intact ones—bulgur instead of couscous, steel-cut oats instead of instant.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li data-start="4300" data-end="4375"&gt;
&lt;p data-start="4302" data-end="4375"&gt;Batch-cook beans; they’re the slow-burn logs in your metabolic fireplace.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 data-start="4382" data-end="4408"&gt;5. Forgetting omega-3s&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p data-start="4410" data-end="4642"&gt;I’ve mentioned this before, but brain fog often masquerades as tiredness. Short-chain ALA (from flax or chia) must convert to long-chain DHA/EPA—an inefficient process. Low DHA can dull mental sharpness and deepen perceived fatigue.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="4644" data-end="4660"&gt;&lt;strong data-start="4644" data-end="4658"&gt;Quick fix:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul data-start="4661" data-end="4902"&gt;
&lt;li data-start="4661" data-end="4736"&gt;
&lt;p data-start="4663" data-end="4736"&gt;Grind two tablespoons of flaxseed daily and sprinkle it over breakfast.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li data-start="4737" data-end="4827"&gt;
&lt;p data-start="4739" data-end="4827"&gt;Consider an algae-derived DHA/EPA supplement (250–500 mg combined) a few times a week.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li data-start="4828" data-end="4902"&gt;
&lt;p data-start="4830" data-end="4902"&gt;Balance your omega-6 intake by moderating sunflower, corn, and soy oils.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 data-start="4909" data-end="4939"&gt;6. Burning the candle late&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p data-start="4941" data-end="5153"&gt;Diet isn’t the only drain. During a recent album review marathon (music blogging roots die hard) I stretched editing sessions past midnight. Even with immaculate macros, five-hour sleep windows trashed my energy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="5155" data-end="5292"&gt;Chronic sleep debt disrupts hunger hormones, pushing you toward sugary fixes, and tanks mitochondrial efficiency—the body’s battery pack.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="5294" data-end="5310"&gt;&lt;strong data-start="5294" data-end="5308"&gt;Quick fix:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul data-start="5311" data-end="5548"&gt;
&lt;li data-start="5311" data-end="5404"&gt;
&lt;p data-start="5313" data-end="5404"&gt;Guard a non-negotiable eight-hour sleep window—yes, even during &lt;em data-start="5377" data-end="5394"&gt;Stranger Things&lt;/em&gt; binges.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li data-start="5405" data-end="5472"&gt;
&lt;p data-start="5407" data-end="5472"&gt;Dim screens 90 minutes before bed; blue light delays melatonin.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li data-start="5473" data-end="5548"&gt;
&lt;p data-start="5475" data-end="5548"&gt;Trial magnesium glycinate (200–400 mg) if muscle tension keeps you wired.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 data-start="5555" data-end="5582"&gt;7. Flying blind on data&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p data-start="5584" data-end="5831"&gt;Guesswork is a poor coach. Without periodic check-ins—blood tests, food logs, even a basic mood tracker—you’re steering blindfolded. I book a comprehensive panel every six months; seeing my B12 or ferritin trendlines keeps me accountable and calm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="5833" data-end="5849"&gt;&lt;strong data-start="5833" data-end="5847"&gt;Quick fix:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul data-start="5850" data-end="6144"&gt;
&lt;li data-start="5850" data-end="5961"&gt;
&lt;p data-start="5852" data-end="5961"&gt;Schedule an annual (or biannual) panel covering B12, ferritin, vitamin D, thyroid panel, and omega-3 index.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li data-start="5962" data-end="6059"&gt;
&lt;p data-start="5964" data-end="6059"&gt;Use a simple app to log meals for a week each quarter; patterns (good and bad) jump out fast.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li data-start="6060" data-end="6144"&gt;
&lt;p data-start="6062" data-end="6144"&gt;Treat supplements as—wait for it—supplements, not excuses for a sugar-fueled diet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 data-start="6151" data-end="6167"&gt;&lt;strong data-start="6151" data-end="6167"&gt;The takeaway&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p data-start="6169" data-end="6451"&gt;Fatigue isn’t inevitable on a vegan path; it’s a sign something’s out of tune.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="6169" data-end="6451"&gt;Feed your calories, respect your micronutrients, curb the ultra-processed creep, and honor sleep.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="6169" data-end="6451"&gt;Tweak these seven levers and that perpetual yawn can become the steady hum of plant-powered momentum.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>VegOut</author><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 21:02:14 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMitAFBVV95cUxNLW4xQnhZenpOSEVFWEtfamM0LTk1U3ZBYm8zTXZZRHpENnd3ajFaM1I0b0k3STNpTWtjcngxRF8wa2lrSnVtYlNjcHE4TTRXR0p3OHpGczVGT3NVdU5WQWhpYXNSNGRYRFVlOW0zS19HcXZHY3owR19jeVU0cm9UaVBRNmN1X1BMS05uOEhqblo4Z29hS2VQTmV3S1FyOHJ4Y1RPTUlEY0FwZzlrRF8xU1R3NlQ</guid></item><item><title>自闭症的迹象可以编码在你走路的方式-黑客新闻 | Signs of autism could be encoded in the way you walk - Hacker News</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiWEFVX3lxTE9xeklOMy1adl94aDVhTWVOQU5lTTBLNkJEdEVaX1pNR0RvLVh0c3RoRHdCVkVWMnpTVlNsSG0tVlNvbVVTVUlwdWdEaHhEX1FtakluRHhBRFQ?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Hacker News</author><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 20:51:08 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiWEFVX3lxTE9xeklOMy1adl94aDVhTWVOQU5lTTBLNkJEdEVaX1pNR0RvLVh0c3RoRHdCVkVWMnpTVlNsSG0tVlNvbVVTVUlwdWdEaHhEX1FtakluRHhBRFQ</guid></item><item><title>阿姨的英雄事迹拯救了侄子的生命-桑达斯基登记处 | Aunt's heroics save nephew's life - Sandusky Register</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMifkFVX3lxTFB1UWY4ZzNOb2tPNFJpSzlBVUJTNWdsQ2U2dUM4eUVONk1YLW1ZU3BYVnptUUVHYkYzQk5QcVltYXI5elAwYlQ2a1ZEd0lJa3ZoYVVOS0kwTllUZmlEZU0xM2FRUDV4VW9OWXRzcVZuSWlybHp5MWN2T0dmTFFydw?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="tText n"&gt;&lt;p&gt;
            Your session was unable to be renewed and will be expiring in &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span id="tTimer"&gt;0&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; seconds. 
            Click &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span id="tRenew"&gt;here&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; to attempt to renew your session.

            &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="tStatus"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
         &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Sandusky Register</author><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 20:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMifkFVX3lxTFB1UWY4ZzNOb2tPNFJpSzlBVUJTNWdsQ2U2dUM4eUVONk1YLW1ZU3BYVnptUUVHYkYzQk5QcVltYXI5elAwYlQ2a1ZEd0lJa3ZoYVVOS0kwTllUZmlEZU0xM2FRUDV4VW9OWXRzcVZuSWlybHp5MWN2T0dmTFFydw</guid></item><item><title>38岁的男子，头部疼痛后被诊断出患有致命脑癌，存活率严峻-每日邮报 | Man, 38, diagnosed with deadly brain cancer with grim survival rate after suffering painful sensation in head - Daily Mail</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMivAFBVV95cUxPcGYyaC1IdmEtZ0lUWVNTTnhBME92UmhxZ0VrcFNyZ3hCSFlpMGI4SEV2enNFSkhiaERCVlJCakl0YjczWndhZkVvNHpSMWphVTNIckFBMWV6TXJtWXpDMWt3b1FjN0NoUUVXaDlFajFicVRnV21ZMzhERUxDMVRJczBXdkNZRktlRUd6N3dTUzJFTGRMLWNaa1pRSWFwdVQ2WEI4a3hRT2tZUFFsS1FDV29ZVTdfelJ1RDlmb9IBwgFBVV95cUxPa2h5ZFFwcDhVY3BCV3Q1ckpZRmZDcTdxbTNfVXI0ZWQxVlhCZ01saHFsR1BDaVRyREFjWmxmMDZwdkRRWXVUSEtlV1NZY0NqektxMnBzVzhHcDhzOVhxRmNCNG5RQ05EbHlBV3BwOVhmUGVuSkl0RHBvXzhTajN0b0NrRXdWazEtd3A0TTR2a19QbW9DS1JtaEVNcUZrQjZWN2ZhMXV5SnNJbm5vZ0lEZlNMcGNva2ZHd2YzeGp0QlhwQQ?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div itemprop="articleBody"&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Branden Newman had been suffering from migraines since he was just 13 years old.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Normally, he would take an over-the-counter painkiller and the pain in his head would disappear within 24 hours.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But in late April, the &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/texas/index.html" id="mol-b4d11a90-6333-11f0-ba8e-3b04051855cf"&gt;Texas&lt;/a&gt; native suffered a six-day migraine that left him unable to eat and constantly feeling dizzy, nauseous and sensitive to light.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;It was then that the now 38-year-old was taken to the emergency room, where scans revealed a large 'mass' in his head that had wrapped around one of his vital blood vessels.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Doctors diagnosed him &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/health/article-14888545/New-dad-dying-brain-cancer-days-son-birthday-glioblastoma.html"&gt;with glioblastoma&lt;/a&gt;, one of the most aggressive and deadly types of brain &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/cancer/index.html" id="mol-b8227300-6334-11f0-ba8e-3b04051855cf" class=""&gt;cancer&lt;/a&gt; which most patients do not survive for longer than 18 months.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Revealing his symptoms to &lt;a class="" rel="noreferrer noopener" target="_blank" href="https://www.today.com/health/men-s-health/glioblastoma-symptoms-migraine-rcna218836"&gt;TODAY&lt;/a&gt;, he said: 'I had a headache for six days straight. I wasn't eating. I was sleeping a lot and just not myself. I was just out of it.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Just six days after the diagnosis, he was rushed through for major surgery where doctors cut out part of his skull to remove 90 percent of the tumor.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But during the surgery, one of his major blood vessels spasmed, causing a stroke and now leaving him struggling to move anything on the left side of his body.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Branden Newman is pictured above with his wife Joanna. He was diagnosed with glioblastoma in May this year&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    
    
    &lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Glioblastomas can be diagnosed at any age and are particularly difficult to treat because the tumors can grow tentacles deep into the brain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;About 12,000 people are diagnosed with the disease every year, and only five percent of them survive longer than five years, estimates suggest.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Cases are rising, experts say, including a slight uptick among those under 40 years old, but physicians are stumped as to the cause. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Newman went to his primary care doctor, and then the emergency room after his wife Joanna, who works in a physician's office, recommended that he got checked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Branden had a migraine for six days,' she told local news station &lt;a class="" rel="nofollow noreferrer noopener" target="_blank" href="https://www.kcentv.com/article/news/local/overcome-this-salado-couples-love-story-becomes-battle-against-rare-brain-cancer/500-b3daed9d-9b07-45fe-9783-54ee8de855ad"&gt;KCENTV&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'He's always had migraines, but this one was different because it lasted so long and he was nauseous and the light really bothered him.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Revealing the moment she found out the diagnosis, she said: 'My boss came and got me out of the [operating room] and told me that they found a mass on Branden and I lost it.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;He was diagnosed with a 'mass' on May 2, and underwent a craniotomy to remove it on May 8, a surgery where doctors cut open the skull to access the brain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;To treat the cancer, doctors opened his skull and removed 90 percent of the tumor from his brain. The above photo is from after the surgery&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;He has endured radiation for six weeks followed by weekly chemotherapy for six months to eliminate the tumor cells, and is now undergoing daily chemotherapy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Newman is also taking perampanel, an anti-seizure medication that can have anti-tumor effects, and gabapentin, also an anti-seizure drug that has been linked to improved survival among people with the disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Doctors said that during the surgery, they tried to remove the tumor from around his middle cerebral artery,&lt;span&gt; one of the three major arteries that supply blood to the brain.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But during the procedure, the blood vessel spasmed, causing a stroke and damage to the brain tissue.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;He was initially unable to move his left side after waking up from surgery but has now recovered enough movement to walk again. He is still having trouble with his left arm.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Newman revealed his diagnosis amid Glioblastoma Awareness Day on July 16, which aims to make more people aware of the disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Warning signs of the disease include a persistent headache, vomiting, loss of appetite, double vision and changes in mood and personality.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Doctors say the overwhelming majority of headaches do not represent tumors, but those who are concerned should speak to their primary care providers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;The pair, from Texas, are childhood sweethearts having met in 2000 when Branden was 13 years old and she was just 11 years old&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Newman and his wife were childhood sweethearts, having met when he was 13 and she was just 11 years old while on a camping trip. The pair dated in high school and married in 2007.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But shortly after the wedding, the pair faced a crisis when Newman's wife was unexpectedly diagnosed with a non-cancerous spinal cord tumor that left her struggling to walk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Newman stuck by her and supported her through the surgery and the recovery. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;His wife said: 'Branden stuck by me through all of that, even at such a young age and facing life with potentially having your wife in a wheelchair.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'He took great care of me all the way through. I am so grateful. He's such a good man.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;She is now looking after Newman and helping to support him while he battles his diagnosis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The pair has also launched a fundraiser to help cover hospital and emergency bills triggered by battling the disease. It has already raised $140,000 out of its $35,000 goal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Daily Mail</author><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 19:38:53 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMivAFBVV95cUxPcGYyaC1IdmEtZ0lUWVNTTnhBME92UmhxZ0VrcFNyZ3hCSFlpMGI4SEV2enNFSkhiaERCVlJCakl0YjczWndhZkVvNHpSMWphVTNIckFBMWV6TXJtWXpDMWt3b1FjN0NoUUVXaDlFajFicVRnV21ZMzhERUxDMVRJczBXdkNZRktlRUd6N3dTUzJFTGRMLWNaa1pRSWFwdVQ2WEI4a3hRT2tZUFFsS1FDV29ZVTdfelJ1RDlmb9IBwgFBVV95cUxPa2h5ZFFwcDhVY3BCV3Q1ckpZRmZDcTdxbTNfVXI0ZWQxVlhCZ01saHFsR1BDaVRyREFjWmxmMDZwdkRRWXVUSEtlV1NZY0NqektxMnBzVzhHcDhzOVhxRmNCNG5RQ05EbHlBV3BwOVhmUGVuSkl0RHBvXzhTajN0b0NrRXdWazEtd3A0TTR2a19QbW9DS1JtaEVNcUZrQjZWN2ZhMXV5SnNJbm5vZ0lEZlNMcGNva2ZHd2YzeGp0QlhwQQ</guid></item><item><title>美国卫生官员表示，美国浪费了数十万支运往非洲的疫苗--Politico | US has wasted hundreds of thousands of vaccines meant for Africa, health officials there say - Politico</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMi2AFBVV95cUxQckJVTTI4Wks0dk1fT3NyWldodGJKV1oxVDB1aWVJS3dLWUVSZTlTQU8xVndOUmdZcUFXVmVtWUptRkFVT2I3NG9MYV9XVGZxcmJ2MmtiN29UM00zOElFdF9KZmswZjBEYW43Nk1xY09sSGtVdHFYNDhhUkVFQWtTYmFUMURIdWo1X1k3Q0I3YUJ5N0htREZGVC1zR0hGODlzWEFxbFl4SGNhN0R5UzNSblp0c3NJcnN2QUhwSllhOHNiaTZBWnJlQ3hCaWRXdTdwRlhYeUlNWDg?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Politico</author><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 19:38:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi2AFBVV95cUxQckJVTTI4Wks0dk1fT3NyWldodGJKV1oxVDB1aWVJS3dLWUVSZTlTQU8xVndOUmdZcUFXVmVtWUptRkFVT2I3NG9MYV9XVGZxcmJ2MmtiN29UM00zOElFdF9KZmswZjBEYW43Nk1xY09sSGtVdHFYNDhhUkVFQWtTYmFUMURIdWo1X1k3Q0I3YUJ5N0htREZGVC1zR0hGODlzWEFxbFl4SGNhN0R5UzNSblp0c3NJcnN2QUhwSllhOHNiaTZBWnJlQ3hCaWRXdTdwRlhYeUlNWDg</guid></item><item><title>大多数美国孕妇，幼儿的父母不打算接受所有推荐的儿童疫苗- CIDRAP | Most US pregnant women, parents of young kids don't plan to accept all recommended kids' vaccines - CIDRAP</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiwwFBVV95cUxPdW9nd1MybFJOY1prTTRyQmxNVTFsdGVkVTJJdkNIb0NYU0pqZno1ZnpadFJ4bGxseGZVSXV4bHhiWUtyX0NLampFX0h5ZDZGc3A4WngybVhqZTJTMUlFRG5lNDloZFdfLUR4WThBY0VZek90Q3RPeU81Vk5MQVVDc3ZNRmM0d3JPMm12T29sYUV3NUFzdlVPa2xhb09nNGRLLUxmQ3JRNTZsRGx5U0F6LXFNZ3BwNFNHSWVQQ0Jrd1hFQ2c?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="clearfix text-formatted field field--name-field-body field--type-text-long field--label-hidden field__item"&gt;&lt;figure role="group" class="caption caption-img align-left"&gt;
&lt;img alt="brain headache" src="/sites/default/files/iStock-680834894.jpg" loading="lazy"&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;kitzcorner/iStock&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Almost 20% of people who were hospitalized for COVID-19 infections early in the pandemic still had signs of impairment with brain function 2 years after infection, finds a new study in &lt;em&gt;Scientific Reports&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41598-025-96608-0"&gt;&lt;u&gt;The study&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; population came from Portugal, in a region hit hard by the first wave of the COVID-19 pandemic. Based on hospital admission episodes and SARS-CoV-2 infection status from March 2020 to February 2021, the authors identified four groups: group 1 (101) hospitalized for COVID-19 infections, group 2 (87) hospitalized but uninfected with COVID-19, group 3 (252) infected but not requiring hospitalization, and group 4 (258) uninfected and not hospitalized for any reason.&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cognitive assessments were conducted in two parts 2 years after infection, a general screening using the Montreal Cognitive Assessment and a subsequent neuropsychological assessment conducted by one of four psychologists if the score of the general screening was low. Overall, verbal memory, visual memory, executive functions, language, and information processing speed and attention were evaluated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ICU stay tied to increased cognitive impairment&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;The authors found that the prevalence of cognitive impairment at 2 years was 19.1%, 6.8%, 10.7%, and 3.2%, in groups 1, 2, 3, and 4, respectively. Notably, hospitalized patients (groups 1 and 2) more often had three or more impaired cognitive domains than the non-hospitalized participants (54.6% vs 19.4%).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cognitive impairment was more than five times higher in group 1 (adjusted odds ratio, 5.39, 95% confidence interval, 1.54 to 18.92) than in group 2. Higher odds of cognitive impairment were linked to older age (58 years and older), a history of clinical anxiety, and lower levels of education.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Intensive care unit admission and hospitalization for 15 or more days was also associated with cognitive impairment.&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Infection with SARS-CoV-2 during the first year of the pandemic was associated with three to five times higher odds of cognitive impairment 2 years after infection&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Infection with SARS-CoV-2 during the first year of the pandemic was associated with three to five times higher odds of cognitive impairment 2 years after infection," the authors concluded. "Survivors of the disease may require special attention from clinical doctors to diagnose and treat cognitive impairment."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
      
  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>CIDRAP</author><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 19:31:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiwwFBVV95cUxPdW9nd1MybFJOY1prTTRyQmxNVTFsdGVkVTJJdkNIb0NYU0pqZno1ZnpadFJ4bGxseGZVSXV4bHhiWUtyX0NLampFX0h5ZDZGc3A4WngybVhqZTJTMUlFRG5lNDloZFdfLUR4WThBY0VZek90Q3RPeU81Vk5MQVVDc3ZNRmM0d3JPMm12T29sYUV3NUFzdlVPa2xhb09nNGRLLUxmQ3JRNTZsRGx5U0F6LXFNZ3BwNFNHSWVQQ0Jrd1hFQ2c</guid></item><item><title>亚当斯县2人感染西尼罗河病毒- KUSA.com | 2 people in Adams County infected with West Nile Virus - KUSA.com</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiugFBVV95cUxNWTJxaWY1YVlmMGt0amlXV1pkN3V2OXFUWm81QnVKdDE4bXcwb19RM3pHNFQ2MVVNRjlsQ1FCOEdGVkJnWmljSGhIU3F5dGJ0dHAtLVVYeU9SeFFyTHhVckVuX0t5aDlWTk9rX2RkX1ZaaXVacF9SY2M3YlZ6NG9ZbmdZa2tiN2ZwZ1Rwd0Q4RVVhQUx3TnJzc0FBRTVwcHZLVi0yT1dOY1VnZU5YaXc4MC0ydUZrRmFDLXc?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Access Denied&lt;/h1&gt;
 
You don't have permission to access "http://www.9news.com/article/news/local/adams-county-colorado-west-nile-virus/73-fb73f48f-6eb7-481b-a22d-0c615012df3e" on this server.&lt;p&gt;
Reference #18.4c472317.1752791755.6220383
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;https://errors.edgesuite.net/18.4c472317.1752791755.6220383&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/body&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>KUSA.com</author><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 18:20:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiugFBVV95cUxNWTJxaWY1YVlmMGt0amlXV1pkN3V2OXFUWm81QnVKdDE4bXcwb19RM3pHNFQ2MVVNRjlsQ1FCOEdGVkJnWmljSGhIU3F5dGJ0dHAtLVVYeU9SeFFyTHhVckVuX0t5aDlWTk9rX2RkX1ZaaXVacF9SY2M3YlZ6NG9ZbmdZa2tiN2ZwZ1Rwd0Q4RVVhQUx3TnJzc0FBRTVwcHZLVi0yT1dOY1VnZU5YaXc4MC0ydUZrRmFDLXc</guid></item><item><title>每年造成11万人死亡的致命疾病在可怕的突变中迅速对抗生素产生抗药性-每日邮报 | Deadly illness that kills 110,000 a year rapidly becoming resistant to antibiotics in terrifying mutation - Daily Mail</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMixgFBVV95cUxNNENyVEU4NnJuR0htRlRJVzBqWlNadC1ZX2VQemFKYW1kTjNYQVJHQ2tWY2FZZ1d2cDBxdWMtcTE3ZGxiT2JrRVdmcmY4bDZXVTQybFJCUnEwa01uSXY1cHVFU0kwTE9iYzdSaFowWUlyZjhTbldiNzZOMHNjYWZEckQ3dVQ0TEozOGhzeFdvMUpFS2lTY3FLR2g1eFBrZGF3OHpCdmR6TGVTQVdfV2ZWbUlwcXFQLXhyWjZPTlBNbEdJaE8zLWfSAcsBQVVfeXFMTXdqX1VGbXlSd1pGRWVMcENXNmlGRkFwclBtYXQ2SzlNNVVpRXdYWjA2ZVBJZDhIcko4WVpGdzJBcWhyaXFQVEpJTDhyWVVzN1VNbUFGZ2U3V254N0xlVDlGV1BfZlpxcVZCel80X3NRdGt1NjA0SURVby15NUo0VGxkcDBwNE9EbFVvaWhILWJzRnVpVF9rcUs2UGI3UHlDQS1tdE5FMXVsRWRKSXFxWVkyVHQyREdQMURIN0Z3VEpUR1Z3ZnlmTkhUMzQ?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div itemprop="articleBody"&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;An ancient killer has become all the more dangerous with time, mutating often to better sidestep medications.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The bacterium &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/health/article-14797275/Victorian-bleeding-disease-typhoid-bacteria-deadly.html"&gt;that causes typhoid fever&lt;/a&gt;, Salmonella enterica serovar Typhi (S Typhi), has evolved to resist common antibiotics.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In 2022, a group of researchers from around the world identified more than 4,000 strains obtained from blood samples from over 70 countries as extensively drug-resistant (XDR) Typhi. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Drug-resistant strains have spread from country to country around 200 times since 1990. People infected &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/news/article-7471039/Toddler-diagnosed-case-drug-resistant-typhoid-trip-Pakistan.html"&gt;with resistant typhoid&lt;/a&gt; carry it to new countries, while the global food trade spreads resistant bacteria to dense cities with poor sanitation accelerates the spread.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Researchers warned that the most commonly used antibiotics, including Ampicillin, Chloramphenicol, and Azithromycin, may not save patients’ lives like they used to. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Approximately 5,700 Americans become ill each year, and 620 are hospitalized. Deaths from typhoid fever in the US are very infrequent. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Dr Jason Andrews, a specialist in infectious diseases at Stanford University and lead author of the report, said the breakneck pace at which S. Typhi is spreading ‘is a real cause for concern.’&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Typhoid fever sickens 11million people every year, causing fever, abdominal pain, and, if left untreated, intestinal bleeding and &lt;a target="_self" href="/health/sepsis/index.html" id="mol-d4cb4440-632b-11f0-970a-09a9b27031ec"&gt;sepsis&lt;/a&gt;. It kills about 100,000 people annually.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Our study found resistant typhoid crossed borders 197 times since 1990 - mostly within South Asia, and spreading to Africa and beyond&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Around one in five people who are not treated for typhoid will die.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;When the genes of a strain of bacteria mutate to resist antibiotics, doctors have far fewer treatment options when patients present with typhoid symptoms. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Researchers analyzed the genetics of over 7,600 samples of S. Typhi, including 3,489 samples from individuals with typhoid in Bangladesh, India, Nepal, and Pakistan from 2014 to 2019.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;They also looked at 4,169 older samples from more than 70 countries, some dating back to 1905. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;They pored over the bacteria’s genetic blueprint to identify genes that can change the bacterial protein that antibiotics usually attack. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;This causes the bacteria to make enzymes that break down the drug, eject antibiotics before they work, or use alternative biochemical pathways.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The team warned that typhoid-causing bacteria are mutating so rapidly that modern medicine can’t keep up, stating that by the time scientists decide to use vaccines based on today's resistance data, it may already be too late.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;South Asia is a hotspot where resistance continues to develop and then spreads globally. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Approximately 5,700 Americans become ill each year, and 620 are hospitalized. Deaths from typhoid fever in the US are very infrequent (stock image)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Since 1990, strains resistant to the antibiotic class quinolones have evolved independently at least 94 times, with 97 percent of these cases originating in South Asia, specifically in countries such as India, Pakistan, Bangladesh and Nepal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;What began as localized resistance, affecting 85 percent of Bangladeshi typhoid cases by the early 2000s, &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/news/article-5618227/First-known-epidemic-drug-resistant-typhoid-spreading-Pakistan.html"&gt;exploded across the region&lt;/a&gt;, surpassing a 95 percent prevalence in India, Pakistan, and Nepal within a decade.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The pattern repeats with newer drugs. Azithromycin resistance has emerged seven times since 2003, with Bangladeshi strains steadily proliferating since 2013, while resistance to last-line antibiotics cephalosporins now looms as the next frontier in the escalating crisis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;While these strains most often occur within South Asia and spread from there to Southeast Asia, East Africa, and Southern Africa, they have also been reported in the US, UK and Canada. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Dr Andrew said: ‘The fact resistant strains of S. Typhi have spread internationally so many times also underscores the need to view typhoid control, and antibiotic resistance more generally, as a global rather than local problem.’&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The research was published in &lt;a class="" rel="nofollow noreferrer noopener" target="_blank" href="https://www.thelancet.com/journals/lanmic/article/PIIS2666-5247(22)00093-3/fulltext"&gt;The Lancet Microbe&lt;/a&gt; journal.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Typhoid is rare in the US, and cases typically arise after a person has traveled internationally. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;It primarily affects people in areas with poor sanitation, and children under five are more susceptible. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In 2018, a Massachusetts daycare center temporarily closed after a child &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/article-5715271/Child-diagnosed-typhoid-fever-Massachusetts-daycare.html"&gt;was diagnosed with typhoid&lt;/a&gt;, likely contracted during recent international travel.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Typhoid fever spreads through fecal-oral transmission, meaning people ingest the bacteria Salmonella Typhi from food, water, or surfaces that have come in contact with fecal matter, such as eating food handled by someone with typhoid who didn’t wash their hands after using the bathroom.&lt;/p&gt;
    
    
    &lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The study has some gaps that need to be considered. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Researchers lacked sufficient genetic data from key regions, particularly parts of Africa and Oceania, where typhoid is prevalent. Without more samples from these areas, it is more difficult to track how and when resistant strains spread.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Even in countries with better monitoring, most samples are collected from just a few locations, which may not accurately reflect what is happening elsewhere.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;And since only a small fraction of typhoid cases get genetically tested, the true scale of antibiotic resistance and global spread is probably even worse than the numbers show.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Researchers said THIS highlights the need ‘to expand genomic surveillance to provide a more comprehensive window into the emergence, expansion, and spread of antibiotic-resistant organisms.’&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Daily Mail</author><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 18:08:42 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMixgFBVV95cUxNNENyVEU4NnJuR0htRlRJVzBqWlNadC1ZX2VQemFKYW1kTjNYQVJHQ2tWY2FZZ1d2cDBxdWMtcTE3ZGxiT2JrRVdmcmY4bDZXVTQybFJCUnEwa01uSXY1cHVFU0kwTE9iYzdSaFowWUlyZjhTbldiNzZOMHNjYWZEckQ3dVQ0TEozOGhzeFdvMUpFS2lTY3FLR2g1eFBrZGF3OHpCdmR6TGVTQVdfV2ZWbUlwcXFQLXhyWjZPTlBNbEdJaE8zLWfSAcsBQVVfeXFMTXdqX1VGbXlSd1pGRWVMcENXNmlGRkFwclBtYXQ2SzlNNVVpRXdYWjA2ZVBJZDhIcko4WVpGdzJBcWhyaXFQVEpJTDhyWVVzN1VNbUFGZ2U3V254N0xlVDlGV1BfZlpxcVZCel80X3NRdGt1NjA0SURVby15NUo0VGxkcDBwNE9EbFVvaWhILWJzRnVpVF9rcUs2UGI3UHlDQS1tdE5FMXVsRWRKSXFxWVkyVHQyREdQMURIN0Z3VEpUR1Z3ZnlmTkhUMzQ</guid></item><item><title>使用David Baker的新人工智能技术，无法治疗的“无序”蛋白质变得可以吸毒- STAT | Undruggable ‘disordered’ proteins become druggable with new AI techniques from David Baker - STAT</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMimwFBVV95cUxON2l2X01jNmVDb3pmNGVNN3JNTWtVQW43VS1rY0xtZ3hYaXV1Qkc2YW1vZzA2TWdRMHY3cG5kM2xLQ3h6clhwU0w0NGtTT1RkU25JUU5VTmJkN01jVC1mWjY0WXZ0clRGMC1ObmtPVTdMbWNIWTRKTEliems3N3h1a3N2QkkzbTM3RmhyeFV2WFBnTWtlWFo1LVpmbw?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content the-content wp-block-post-content is-layout-flow wp-block-post-content-is-layout-flow"&gt;&lt;p&gt;For decades, structural biologists shoved what looked like shoddy data in the back of their closets, embarrassed. While attempting to gather the structures of proteins, they would sometimes find that all or at least a portion of the protein would just not show up correctly in the data. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Joel Sussman, a former head of the Protein Data Bank, remembers when he found his first intrinsically disordered protein, though it wasn’t called that at the time. He showed it to a collaborator. “‘Oh, Joel, you’re not a very good biochemist. Obviously, it has a structure and you’re confused,’” he recalled her saying.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Most proteins fold into shapes with distinct elements: the ordered spiral of an alpha-helix, like a piece of cavatappi pasta; or beta sheets, like a slice of a lasagna — squiggly lines of pasta amino acids held parallel to each other with cheesy and saucy hydrogen bonds. A central tenet of structural biology is that a protein’s structure dictates its function. But &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S003169972411616X" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;around the same time&lt;/a&gt; that the world was preparing for Y2K, structural biologists finally began admitting that — just as Sussman and other scientists had seen — not all proteins have a permanent shape. A surprisingly large amount of important proteins (in fact, over &lt;a href="https://pubs.acs.org/doi/10.1021/cr400713r" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;half of all proteins in eukaryotes&lt;/a&gt;, it’s estimated) have strands of wiggly “spaghetti” in them. &lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;div class="restricted-content-breaker article" aria-labelledby="restricted-story-heading" aria-describedby="restricted-story-description" checked&gt;
			&lt;div class="restricted-content-breaker-bar"&gt;
				&lt;p class="restricted-text"&gt;STAT+ Exclusive Story&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p class="restricted-login"&gt;Already have an account? &lt;a href="/login/" data-stat-login data-stat-paywall-cta="breaker login cta"&gt;Log in&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; 
			&lt;/div&gt;
			&lt;img class="restricted-content-breaker-bg" src="/wp-content/themes/stat/images/stat-plus-breaker-bg.png" alt="STAT+"&gt;
			&lt;div class="restricted-content-breaker-wrapper"&gt;
				&lt;span class="stat-paywall-archive"&gt;
					&lt;a href="https://www.statnews.com/stat-plus/"&gt;
						&lt;img class="stat-plus-logo" src="/wp-content/themes/stat/images/stat-plus-logo-white.svg" alt="STAT+"&gt;
					&lt;/a&gt;
				&lt;/span&gt;
				&lt;h2 id="restricted-story-heading"&gt;This article is exclusive to STAT+ subscribers&lt;/h2&gt;
				&lt;h3 id="restricted-story-description"&gt;Unlock this article — plus in-depth analysis, newsletters, premium events, and news alerts.&lt;/h3&gt;
				&lt;p class="restricted-content-breaker-wrapper-cta mobile"&gt;Already have an account? &lt;a href="/login/" data-stat-login data-stat-paywall-cta="breaker login cta mobile"&gt;Log in&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;div class="restricted-content-breaker-cards"&gt;
					&lt;div class="slider-container" aria-label="Subscription plan toggle"&gt;
						&lt;button type="button" class="individual" aria-pressed="false"&gt;Individual plans&lt;/button&gt;
						&lt;p class="switch" role="switch" tabindex="0" aria-checked="false"&gt;
							&lt;button class="slider"&gt;&lt;/button&gt;
						&lt;/p&gt;
						&lt;button type="button" class="group" aria-pressed="false"&gt;Group plans&lt;/button&gt;
					&lt;/div&gt;
							

		
						&lt;/div&gt;
				&lt;a href="https://www.statnews.com/stat-plus/" class="stat-button view-all" data-stat-paywall-cta="breaker view all plans" aria-label="View All Plans"&gt;View All Plans&lt;/a&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
		
		&lt;div class="restricted-message-breaker"&gt;
			&lt;div class="restricted-content-wrapper"&gt;
								
								&lt;div class="restricted-content-message"&gt;
					&lt;p class="restricted-content-text"&gt;
						To read the rest of this story subscribe to STAT+.					&lt;/p&gt;
					&lt;a href="https://www.statnews.com/stat-plus/" class="stat-button restricted-button" data-stat-paywall-cta="breaker subscribe cta 1"&gt;Subscribe&lt;/a&gt;
									&lt;/div&gt;
								
							&lt;/div&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;

		&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>STAT</author><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 18:04:27 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimwFBVV95cUxON2l2X01jNmVDb3pmNGVNN3JNTWtVQW43VS1rY0xtZ3hYaXV1Qkc2YW1vZzA2TWdRMHY3cG5kM2xLQ3h6clhwU0w0NGtTT1RkU25JUU5VTmJkN01jVC1mWjY0WXZ0clRGMC1ObmtPVTdMbWNIWTRKTEliems3N3h1a3N2QkkzbTM3RmhyeFV2WFBnTWtlWFo1LVpmbw</guid></item><item><title>每日小剂量的流行补充剂可以降低痴呆症的风险-每日邮报 | Just a small daily dose of a popular supplement slashes dementia risk - Daily Mail</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMipgFBVV95cUxNR2wybHFXVktRbFFjQl9DUnhZWER0Z1g1R09LWUFob2ktUnptVmp5ZVpZZWNRQkdEa01wUjhBbmN6ZEN1ZlRwLVFvMktPdkF2VnBoMFVjc1NhMkcwVGZoSkZFTndhWXdfeTY4LUJURENlUU04RzRZZWE4akFxb2U4ZzZqelFQVG9oYkFkdmNqUmdQVmZaS09fNXFjejRGeTh4ZnEybDVn0gGrAUFVX3lxTE1ZaENRYllhcW9Wb1dzYXFqZkVQYUZRZU0wUU5BSVFjVU5MR0FaWkhnR3I5N0dVaDNxMnJiT0o0TXlOMVJqYTVGbkowaG1BN0IxSjB0ZWxvWnF0WkF5VVBUSGJrVktLY1FKSTQxYTREZ01RblpJc01XeVpFdUpCR0F4Tmt4QW1HWV9GWExCcGNKamhuaDRnR09RT1M4azZ2ZGNYalFjUWdrdlNvMA?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div itemprop="articleBody"&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;A severe lack of vitamin D could dramatically raise your chances of developing dementia and Alzheimer’s disease, according to a groundbreaking new study.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Researchers analyzed data from 16 major studies involving thousands of people and found that those with low vitamin D levels faced a significantly increased risk of cognitive decline.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/health/article-14806857/I-diagnosed-Alzheimers-overused-medical-procedure-caused-dementia.html"&gt;The study revealed that people &lt;/a&gt;with levels below 20 ng/ml, which is recommended by doctors were about 33 percent more likely to develop dementia or Alzheimer’s. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But those with even lower levels, under 10 ng/ml, had an even greater risk, nearly 50 percent higher for dementia and 51 percent higher for Alzheimer’s.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Scientists think that low vitamin D might affect the brain by disturbing calcium balance in nerve cells, which can cause brain aging and damage. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Vitamin D helps the brain by removing harmful proteins linked to Alzheimer’s, regulating calcium in nerve cells, and protecting brain cells from damage. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Experts say the findings highlight the importance of maintaining healthy vitamin D levels, especially in older adults, who are most vulnerable to both deficiency and cognitive disorders.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;While the research doesn’t prove that vitamin D supplements will prevent dementia, it strongly suggests that avoiding deficiency could be a crucial step in protecting your brain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;&lt;p class="clear"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;A Vitamin D deficiency (between 10 to 20ng/ml) can increase the risk of developing dementia and Alzheimer's disease by about 50 percent (stock image)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Researchers conducted a meta-analysis, combining data from 16 previous studies, including 12 long-term cohort studies and 4 cross-sectional studies. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The goal was to better understand how vitamin D levels affect the likelihood of cognitive decline. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Alzheimer's disease is one of the most common forms of dementia and mostly affects adults over the age of 65.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span&gt;It is believed to be caused by the development of toxic amyloid and beta proteins in the brain, which can accumulate in the brain and damage cells responsible for memory.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Amyloid protein molecules stick together in brain cells, forming clumps called plaques. While tau proteins twist together in fiber-like strands called tangles. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The plaques and tangles block the ability of the brain's neurons to send electrical and chemical signals back and forth. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Over time, this disruption causes permanent damage in the brain that leads to Alzheimer's disease and dementia, causing patients to lose their ability to speak, care for themselves or even respond to the world around them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span&gt;About 7million people in the US 65 and older live with the condition and over 100,00 die from it annually. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;&lt;p class="clear"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Leading health experts recommend taking 5,000 IU of vitamin D3 - priced at 20 cents per capsule or $17.99 for 90 - every day&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span&gt;The Alzheimer's Association estimates that by 2050, nearly 13 million Americans will be living with the disease.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;While there is no clear cause of the Alzheimer's disease, experts believe it can develop due to genetic mutations and lifestyle choices, such as physical inactivity, unhealthy diet and social isolation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Additional studies have also shown that Vitamin D &lt;span&gt;provides protection to the brain cells, regulates nerve growth as well as genes important for brain function.  &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Typically, the body makes vitamin D from direct sunlight on the skin or absorbs it from foods such as milk, egg yolks, beef liver, mushrooms and fatty fishes like salmon and mackerel.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Experts suggest that having a vitamin D level of 20 nanograms/ milliliter (mg/ml) in the blood or higher is adequate for good bone health and anything below 20ng/ml is considered a deficiency.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But despite the critical role it plays, nearly 40 percent of adults are Vitamin D deficient, meaning they are more likely to develop conditions such as osteoporosis (fragile bones), heart problems and Type 2 diabetes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Additionally, it also aids the function of neurotransmitters such as dopamine and serotonin, which play vital roles in overall mood, cognition and behavior. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Therefore, a deficiency can damage the cell and nerve growth process in the brain which can cause a decline in cognitive abilities, including executive functions like paying attention and processing information. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Brain cell and nerve damage can also contribute to problems in the hippocampus, a brain region crucial for memory formation, which in turn can impair communication between brain regions as well as the brain and rest of the body. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Taking regular Vitamin D supplements can help protect brain cells,contribute to brain development and maintain cognitive function&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Vitamin D deficiency can manifest in symptoms similar to depression, such as low mood, fatigue and loss of interest in activities - all of which are major contributors to the development of dementia. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;However, taking regular vitamin D supplements can help maintain healthy levels of the vitamin in the body which can help protection brain cells, contribute to brain development and maintain cognitive function. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Vitamin D supplements can also help reduce oxidative stress in the brain, described as an imbalance between free radicals and antioxidants in the body that leads to cell damage and various neurological conditions. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Furthermore, Vitamin D has anti-inflammatory properties that can help slow down cognitive decline in older adults. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Apart from capsules, Vitamin D levels in the blood can also be increased by eating consuming foods such as fatty fish and milk while also spending more time in the sun. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
            

            
            
            
            
            &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Daily Mail</author><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 17:38:58 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipgFBVV95cUxNR2wybHFXVktRbFFjQl9DUnhZWER0Z1g1R09LWUFob2ktUnptVmp5ZVpZZWNRQkdEa01wUjhBbmN6ZEN1ZlRwLVFvMktPdkF2VnBoMFVjc1NhMkcwVGZoSkZFTndhWXdfeTY4LUJURENlUU04RzRZZWE4akFxb2U4ZzZqelFQVG9oYkFkdmNqUmdQVmZaS09fNXFjejRGeTh4ZnEybDVn0gGrAUFVX3lxTE1ZaENRYllhcW9Wb1dzYXFqZkVQYUZRZU0wUU5BSVFjVU5MR0FaWkhnR3I5N0dVaDNxMnJiT0o0TXlOMVJqYTVGbkowaG1BN0IxSjB0ZWxvWnF0WkF5VVBUSGJrVktLY1FKSTQxYTREZ01RblpJc01XeVpFdUpCR0F4Tmt4QW1HWV9GWExCcGNKamhuaDRnR09RT1M4azZ2ZGNYalFjUWdrdlNvMA</guid></item></channel></rss>