<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>GNews Health</title><link>https://news.google.com/</link><description></description><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>削减如何动摇了艾滋病毒/艾滋病护理的核心，并将意味着未来还有数百万的感染者-卫报</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/global-development/2025/dec/01/global-health-hiv-aids-funding-cuts-infections-prevention</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body-commercial-selector article-body-viewer-selector dcr-hdpgoq"&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;In Mozambique, a teenage rape victim sought care at a health clinic only to find it closed. In Zimbabwe, Aids-related deaths have risen for the first time in five years. In Ethiopia and the &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/congo" data-link-name="in body link" data-component="auto-linked-tag"&gt;Democratic Republic of the Congo&lt;/a&gt; (DRC), patients with suspected HIV went undiagnosed due to test-kit stocks running out.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Stories of the devastating impact of US, British and wider European aid cuts on the fight against HIV – particularly in sub-Saharan &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/africa" data-link-name="in body link" data-component="auto-linked-tag"&gt;Africa&lt;/a&gt; – continue to mount as 2025 comes to an end, and are set out in a series of reports released in the past week.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="sign-in-gate"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The Trump administration &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2025/jan/24/foreign-aid-israel-egypt" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;abruptly cut all overseas aid spending&lt;/a&gt; in January, with only piecemeal restorations to funding since then. Other countries, &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/global-development/2025/jul/22/uks-aid-cuts-will-hit-childrens-education-and-raise-risk-of-death" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;including the UK&lt;/a&gt;, have announced their own cuts. It has been &lt;a href="https://www.who.int/news/item/03-11-2025-who-issues-guidance-to-address-drastic-global-health-financing-cuts" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;estimated that external health assistance&lt;/a&gt; over 2025 will be between 30% and 40% lower than it was in 2023.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="3c19269b-cb35-4d23-8355-90d0eebafd79" data-spacefinder-role="inline" data-spacefinder-type="model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.ImageBlockElement" class="dcr-173mewl"&gt;&lt;figcaption data-spacefinder-role="inline" class="dcr-fd61eq"&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-1inf02i"&gt;&lt;svg viewbox="0 0 18 13"&gt;&lt;path d="M18 3.5v8l-1.5 1.5h-15l-1.5-1.5v-8l1.5-1.5h3.5l2-2h4l2 2h3.5l1.5 1.5zm-9 7.5c1.9 0 3.5-1.6 3.5-3.5s-1.6-3.5-3.5-3.5-3.5 1.6-3.5 3.5 1.6 3.5 3.5 3.5z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-1qvd3m6"&gt;A Congolese HIV patient in Lualaba receiving only a month’s worth of medication instead of enough for 90 days, after USAID’s cuts.&lt;/span&gt; Photograph: Arlette Bashizi/Washington Post/Getty&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Winnie Byanyima, USAID’s executive director, said: “The complex ecosystem that sustains HIV services in dozens of low- and middle-income countries was shaken to its core.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Without swift action to get services back on track, UNAids has predicted there will be 3.3m more new HIV infections by 2030 than expected. And while there are signs of recovery, including new domestic funding in some countries, access remains far from universal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The &lt;a href="https://www.unaids.org/sites/default/files/2025-11/2025-WAD-report_en.pdf" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;UN agency’s report&lt;/a&gt; finds that services working to prevent HIV infections were particularly likely to be donor-funded and are among the hardest hit – with resources limited, treatment for existing patients has been prioritised. In Burundi, for example, the number of people receiving preventive HIV medicines fell by 64%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="b086f89a-a502-4bd2-ab9b-35aeaa2d4fec" data-spacefinder-role="supporting" data-spacefinder-type="model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.ImageBlockElement" class="dcr-a2pvoh"&gt;&lt;figcaption data-spacefinder-role="inline" class="dcr-9ktzqp"&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-1inf02i"&gt;&lt;svg viewbox="0 0 18 13"&gt;&lt;path d="M18 3.5v8l-1.5 1.5h-15l-1.5-1.5v-8l1.5-1.5h3.5l2-2h4l2 2h3.5l1.5 1.5zm-9 7.5c1.9 0 3.5-1.6 3.5-3.5s-1.6-3.5-3.5-3.5-3.5 1.6-3.5 3.5 1.6 3.5 3.5 3.5z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-1qvd3m6"&gt;USAID’s Winnie Byanyima. ‘What we need now is political courage,’ she said. &lt;/span&gt; Photograph: Fabrice Coffrini/AFP/Getty Images&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;A separate series of &lt;a href="https://frontlineaids.org/world-aids-day-2025" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;country-level reports from the British charity Frontline Aids&lt;/a&gt;, covering Angola, Kenya, Malawi, Mozambique, Nigeria, Tanzania, Uganda and Zimbabwe, highlights similar issues.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The full figures will take time to collate, but in some places there are already signs that new HIV cases, or Aids-related deaths, are rising after years of heading downwards.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Many of the gains in the fight against HIV in recent years have come via the recognition that some groups of people are at higher risk of infection – known as “key populations”. They include men who have sex with men, people who inject drugs, sex workers, transgender people, and prison inmates.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;In each case, offering services specifically designed around those groups’ needs has borne fruit – for example, LGBTQ+ friendly walk-in clinics can mean access to care for people who are stay away from public clinics due to the stigma around HIV.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Many of those clinics and other outreach services have closed, along with swathes of community-led organisations, previously reliant on donor funding. One member of the LGBTQ+ community in Uganda, quoted in the Frontline Aids country report, said the loss of safe spaces had left them “isolated and exposed […] the mental strain is overwhelming”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="c1de7999-c66f-4654-9501-2d20cb1fc0db" data-spacefinder-role="inline" data-spacefinder-type="model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.ImageBlockElement" class="dcr-173mewl"&gt;&lt;figcaption data-spacefinder-role="inline" class="dcr-fd61eq"&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-1inf02i"&gt;&lt;svg viewbox="0 0 18 13"&gt;&lt;path d="M18 3.5v8l-1.5 1.5h-15l-1.5-1.5v-8l1.5-1.5h3.5l2-2h4l2 2h3.5l1.5 1.5zm-9 7.5c1.9 0 3.5-1.6 3.5-3.5s-1.6-3.5-3.5-3.5-3.5 1.6-3.5 3.5 1.6 3.5 3.5 3.5z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-1qvd3m6"&gt;An HIV clinic in Kampala. The loss of community-led organisations in Uganda due to aid cuts has left many LGBTQ+ patients feeling ‘isolated and exposed’. &lt;/span&gt; Photograph: Hajarah Nalwadda/Getty&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;In sub-Saharan Africa, teenage girls and young women are disproportionately affected by HIV, but programmes designed specifically for them are another common casualty of the cuts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;In &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/kenya" data-link-name="in body link" data-component="auto-linked-tag"&gt;Kenya&lt;/a&gt;, activists report that people who can do so are hiding the fact they belong to a key population so as to access care in public clinics safely. They fear this will mean a loss of information on where and how the virus is spreading.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;John Plastow, executive director at Frontline Aids, said: “We are already seeing progress slip backwards.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="9bafebfe-e82f-4c1c-b604-0cb64013b32d" data-spacefinder-role="richLink" data-spacefinder-type="model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.RichLinkBlockElement" class="dcr-47fhrn"&gt;&lt;gu-island name="RichLinkComponent" priority="feature" deferuntil="idle" props='{"richLinkIndex":17,"element":{"_type":"model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.RichLinkBlockElement","prefix":"Related: ","text":"Control of HIV, TB and malaria at risk after global health fund donations fall","elementId":"9bafebfe-e82f-4c1c-b604-0cb64013b32d","role":"richLink","url":"https://www.theguardian.com/global-development/2025/nov/22/control-of-hiv-tb-and-malaria-at-risk-after-global-health-fund-donations-fall"},"ajaxUrl":"https://api.nextgen.guardianapps.co.uk","format":{"design":6,"display":0,"theme":0}}'&gt;&lt;/gu-island&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;But Plastow also saw the potential for a reset of health policies. “In several countries,” he said, “we are seeing the first signs of governments and communities working together to build more sustainable, homegrown HIV responses.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;UNAids also pointed to signs of hope, with countries including Nigeria, Uganda, Côte d’Ivoire, South Africa and Tanzania all pledging to increase domestic investment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;And, they said, innovations such as &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/society/2025/sep/24/hiv-prevention-jab-pre-exposure-prophylaxis-prep-lenacapavir-120-poorer-countries-2027" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;new long-acting injectable drugs&lt;/a&gt; to prevent infection were “gaining momentum”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“We know what works – we have the science, tools and proven strategies,” said Byanyima. “What we need now is political courage: investing in communities, in prevention, in innovation and in protecting human rights as the path to end Aids.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Guardian</author><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMitwFBVV95cUxNTE0xMDFiYTQtZDFndWhVdTR2eTZoTjN6YmN4cUJQYlNBLXNNeGowVUdOckZva00zM1NhN3hvZnQwTDVDeTdPSDc0ZnpycTMxNEpxeGE5RjhMckNvVDBiaUtJMHNmWjNEd0dXTmJzTUZGVFJULUxBV2NOTU5yRVQwRXBOelF3TzRZX0VUV3FnTXhKU2dlZlAwRk9kbm85X2N4S1ExbUttZktYRDdfRnpPSy0xbUJsaWc</guid></item><item><title>将大脑的防御转变为阿尔茨海默氏症的保护者- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/switch-turns-brains-defenses-into-protectors-against-alzheimers</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Specific immune cells in the brain may play a crucial role in preventing the onset of &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/alzheimer-s-disease"&gt;Alzheimer's disease&lt;/a&gt;, according to a new study – a discovery that could lead to new therapies that try to coax cells into this protective state.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.cell.2018.05.003"&gt;Earlier studies&lt;/a&gt; have shown that immune cells in the brain called &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Microglia"&gt;microglia&lt;/a&gt; can effectively tackle the symptoms of  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/go/IaO" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73015" data-postid="183250" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;Alzheimer's&lt;/a&gt;, but also make them worse through inflammation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Here, an international team of scientists took a detailed look at how microglia switch between those two helpful and harmful modes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Using mouse models of Alzheimer's, Icahn School of Medicine neuroscientist Pinar Ayata and colleagues found that when microglia get close to the &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/supplement-for-high-blood-pressure-clears-signs-of-alzheimers-in-mice"&gt;amyloid-beta protein&lt;/a&gt; clumps, a tell-tale sign of the disease, they enter a special state of neuroprotection.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/alzheimers-may-not-actually-be-a-brain-disease-reveals-expert"&gt;Alzheimer's May Not Actually Be a Brain Disease, Reveals Expert&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Microglia are not simply destructive responders in Alzheimer's disease – they can become the brain's protectors," &lt;a href="https://www.mountsinai.org/about/newsroom/2025/protective-microglia-subtype-offers-potential-new-therapeutic-pathway-in-alzheimers-disease"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; neuroscientist Anne Schaefer, from the Icahn School of Medicine in New York.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"This finding extends our earlier observations on the remarkable plasticity of microglia states and their important roles in diverse brain functions."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_183253" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-183253" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/MicrogliaScan.jpg" alt="Microglia in mouse brains" class="wp-image-183253 size-full" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/MicrogliaScan.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/MicrogliaScan-600x505.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-183253" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Microglia (green) responding to amyloid-beta plaques (blue) in the mouse brain. (Ayata et al., &lt;em&gt;Nature&lt;/em&gt;, 2025)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;There seem to be two crucial characteristics of this microglia subtype: The cells have lower levels of a protein previously &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1038/nn.4587"&gt;linked to Alzheimer's&lt;/a&gt;, called PU.1, and a greater expression of a protein called CD28, &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1146/annurev.immunol.14.1.233"&gt;a crucial participant&lt;/a&gt; in the wider immune system.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Microglia with this combination were better able to slow down the build-up of amyloid-beta protein clumps in mouse brains, while also limiting aggregations of tau – another potentially toxic protein &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/sky-high-levels-of-alzheimers-protein-found-in-newborns"&gt;associated with Alzheimer's&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers also stopped CD28 production in mice, finding that harmful, inflammation-causing microglia became more abundant, and that amyloid-beta plaques became more common.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This all fits with &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1038/nn.4587"&gt;earlier studies&lt;/a&gt; that have found the onset of Alzheimer's tends to happen later in life among individuals with a genetic disposition towards lower PU.1 expression in specific cells, compared to the general average.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"These results provide a mechanistic explanation for why lower PU.1 levels are linked to reduced Alzheimer's disease risk," &lt;a href="https://www.mpg.de/25641673/protective-brain-immune-cell-state-discovered"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; geneticist Alison Goate, from the Icahn School of Medicine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This seems to be a natural defense against &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/these-4-distinct-patterns-may-signal-alzheimers-according-to-science"&gt;Alzheimer's in the brain&lt;/a&gt;, but one which clearly isn't powerful enough to fully stop the disease from progressing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers are hopeful that future therapies might be able to increase the levels of this microglia subtype – though we need to make sure microglia work the same way in humans first.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/newsletter?utm_source=promo_generic_health"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-642x273.jpg" alt="Subscribe to ScienceAlert's free fact-checked newsletter" class="alignnone wp-image-182810 size-medium" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-642x273.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-768x326.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-600x255.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final.jpg 850w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alzheimer's is an &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/one-of-our-biggest-hopes-for-alzheimers-treatment-doesnt-seem-to-work"&gt;incredibly complex&lt;/a&gt; disease, involving &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/theres-one-critical-thing-you-can-do-to-keep-alzheimers-symptoms-at-bay"&gt;a host of&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/exercise-at-one-stage-of-life-may-cut-dementia-risk-by-up-to-45"&gt;risk factors&lt;/a&gt;, and so an &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/new-alzheimers-treatment-clears-plaques-from-brains-of-mice-within-hours"&gt;effective treatment&lt;/a&gt; will probably need to take aim at several targets at once. One mechanism researchers might consider for future studies is converting microglia into this neuroprotective mode.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The research also adds to our understanding of how Alzheimer's fits in with the immune system as a whole. The modified microglia identified in this study, in mouse brains, act in a similar way to&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/newly-discovered-t-cells-could-rid-late-stage-cancer-patients-of-tumors"&gt; T cells&lt;/a&gt; that roam around the rest of the nervous system.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"This discovery comes at a time when regulatory T cells have achieved major recognition as master regulators of immunity, highlighting a shared logic of immune regulation across cell types," &lt;a href="https://www.mountsinai.org/about/newsroom/2025/protective-microglia-subtype-offers-potential-new-therapeutic-pathway-in-alzheimers-disease"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; &lt;span&gt;epigeneticist Alexander Tarakhovsky&lt;/span&gt;, from the Rockefeller University in the US.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It also paves the way for immunotherapeutic strategies for Alzheimer's disease."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The research has been published in &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1038/s41586-025-09662-z"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Nature&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 03:42:08 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilwFBVV95cUxQTnc4QVN2d000NXZGTWRVYi1kM19wemJPV0xSUEk4VmRENjJJcnM3Mjk4dlIxUHJRaE9oQzRhc2hocm13X0lsOFMwcmZHaXVaNEdReGpvWVRtbGxRLTE5Zmg4cWN5cm52dF8xbEZRVTkxNFcwY1ZROVpZUkxPaEtMN0tlSVNoM19EVWV0X3JpUkg5MWNnUG1V</guid></item><item><title>“当我弟弟被诊断出患有糖尿病时，我是笑的混蛋吗？” -无聊的熊猫</title><link>https://www.boredpanda.com/brother-diagnosis-diabetes/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;  &lt;p&gt;For whatever reason, there seems to be that one family member who always seems to get away with everything. And then, there’s the sibling who gets blamed for literally everything, from finishing the last juice in the fridge to accidentally existing while the other &lt;a href="https://www.boredpanda.com/relationships/family/" target="_blank" class=" staff-link" rel="noopener "&gt;family&lt;/a&gt; member devours an entire cake.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Today’s Original Poster (OP) was always blamed for everything, and was often mocked for being “fat”. In fact, her older brother had a habit of reminding her that her “overeating” would cause her to have an illness. However, she ended up having the last laugh after a visit to the hospital.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;More info: &lt;a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/AITAH/comments/1p2bzff/aitah_for_laughing_when_my_brother_was_diagnosed/" target="_blank" class=" staff-link" rel="noopener nofollow"&gt;Reddit&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Sometimes life serves up moments so perfectly ironic that all you can do is laugh, and it has nothing to do with cruelty or insensitivity&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Teen boy eating pizza on bed with pizza box open, highlighting weight and diabetes themes in family dynamics.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="attachment-link-container shareable-image-block" id="brother-diagnosis-diabetes-4" data-href="http://www.boredpanda.com/brother-diagnosis-diabetes/?image_id=brother-diagnosis-diabetes-4.jpg"&gt;&lt;a class="web-share-button list-item-share new-share-experiment" data-location="single-post-image" data-title="Am I The Jerk For Laughing When My Brother Was Diagnosed With Diabetes?" data-share-url="https://www.boredpanda.com/brother-diagnosis-diabetes/?media_id=brother-diagnosis-diabetes-4" data-image="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/brother-diagnosis-diabetes-4.jpg"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;svg class="svg-icon icon-share-icon" role="img" viewbox="0 0 16 16"&gt;&lt;path d="M0 15C0 10.8824 5.22292 10.0588 8.79817 10.0588V14.1765L15.7006 8.23061C15.7941 8.15345 15.8695 8.05559 15.9213 7.94441C15.9731 7.83323 16 7.71155 16 7.58824C16 7.46492 15.9731 7.34314 15.9213 7.23196C15.8695 7.12078 15.7941 7.02302 15.7006 6.94586L8.79817 1V5.11765C2.3995 5.11765 0 9.76235 0 15Z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-9705617" src="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/brother-diagnosis-diabetes-4.jpg" alt="Teen boy eating pizza on bed with pizza box open, highlighting weight and diabetes themes in family dynamics." title="Teen boy eating pizza on bed with pizza box open, highlighting weight and diabetes themes in family dynamics." loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="post-tablet-ad-within-content post-ads"&gt;&lt;span class="dfp-ad" data-source="primis"&gt;&lt;span id="desktop-widget-loaded"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Image credits: &lt;a href="https://www.freepik.com/premium-photo/portrait-young-man-sitting-home-bed-eating-pizza-from-box-holding-piece-pizza_10140880.htm#from_element=cross_selling__photo" target="_blank" class=" staff-link" rel="noopener nofollow"&gt;user21473825 / Freepik (not the actual photo)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;The author was consistently blamed by her family for finishing food and was mocked for being “fat”, while her older brother ate freely without consequence&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Text excerpt discussing a brother mocking sister over weight and the brother later being diagnosed with diabetes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="attachment-link-container shareable-image-block" id="author_fa71c35dc4b7f0c4c8abffb40038a062" data-href="http://www.boredpanda.com/brother-diagnosis-diabetes/?image_id=author_fa71c35dc4b7f0c4c8abffb40038a062.jpg"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/author_fa71c35dc4b7f0c4c8abffb40038a062.jpg" alt="Text excerpt discussing a brother mocking sister over weight and the brother later being diagnosed with diabetes." title="Text excerpt discussing a brother mocking sister over weight and the brother later being diagnosed with diabetes." loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sibling mocks overweight sister for years, only to face diabetes, highlighting irony and health consequences.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="attachment-link-container shareable-image-block" id="a-3.pn" data-href="http://www.boredpanda.com/brother-diagnosis-diabetes/?image_id=a-3.png"&gt;&lt;a class="web-share-button list-item-share new-share-experiment" data-location="single-post-image" data-title="Am I The Jerk For Laughing When My Brother Was Diagnosed With Diabetes?" data-share-url="https://www.boredpanda.com/brother-diagnosis-diabetes/?media_id=a-3.pn" data-image="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/a-3.png"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;svg class="svg-icon icon-share-icon" role="img" viewbox="0 0 16 16"&gt;&lt;path d="M0 15C0 10.8824 5.22292 10.0588 8.79817 10.0588V14.1765L15.7006 8.23061C15.7941 8.15345 15.8695 8.05559 15.9213 7.94441C15.9731 7.83323 16 7.71155 16 7.58824C16 7.46492 15.9731 7.34314 15.9213 7.23196C15.8695 7.12078 15.7941 7.02302 15.7006 6.94586L8.79817 1V5.11765C2.3995 5.11765 0 9.76235 0 15Z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-9706142" src="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/a-3.png" alt="Sibling mocks overweight sister for years, only to face diabetes, highlighting irony and health consequences." title="Sibling mocks overweight sister for years, only to face diabetes, highlighting irony and health consequences." loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Text about a sibling relationship where the brother mocks sister over weight while she reacts to his diabetes diagnosis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="attachment-link-container shareable-image-block" id="author_952cfec09d85bb2e69bbbbf0f56f500e" data-href="http://www.boredpanda.com/brother-diagnosis-diabetes/?image_id=author_952cfec09d85bb2e69bbbbf0f56f500e.jpg"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/author_952cfec09d85bb2e69bbbbf0f56f500e.jpg" alt="Text about a sibling relationship where the brother mocks sister over weight while she reacts to his diabetes diagnosis." title="Text about a sibling relationship where the brother mocks sister over weight while she reacts to his diabetes diagnosis." loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Image credits:&lt;a class="author-name whitespace-nowrap text-neutral-content visited:text-neutral-content-weak focus-visible:-outline-offset-1 a cursor-pointer no-visited no-underline hover:no-underline staff-link" href="https://www.reddit.com/r/AITAH/comments/1p2bzff/aitah_for_laughing_when_my_brother_was_diagnosed/" target="_blank" aria-label="Author: Express-Letter4548" aria-haspopup="dialog" aria-expanded="false" rel="noopener nofollow"&gt;Express-Letter4548&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Young woman smiling at her phone while eating breakfast, reflecting on bro mocking sis over weight and diabetes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="attachment-link-container shareable-image-block" id="brother-diagnosis-diabetes-2" data-href="http://www.boredpanda.com/brother-diagnosis-diabetes/?image_id=brother-diagnosis-diabetes-2.jpg"&gt;&lt;a class="web-share-button list-item-share new-share-experiment" data-location="single-post-image" data-title="Am I The Jerk For Laughing When My Brother Was Diagnosed With Diabetes?" data-share-url="https://www.boredpanda.com/brother-diagnosis-diabetes/?media_id=brother-diagnosis-diabetes-2" data-image="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/brother-diagnosis-diabetes-2.jpg"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;svg class="svg-icon icon-share-icon" role="img" viewbox="0 0 16 16"&gt;&lt;path d="M0 15C0 10.8824 5.22292 10.0588 8.79817 10.0588V14.1765L15.7006 8.23061C15.7941 8.15345 15.8695 8.05559 15.9213 7.94441C15.9731 7.83323 16 7.71155 16 7.58824C16 7.46492 15.9731 7.34314 15.9213 7.23196C15.8695 7.12078 15.7941 7.02302 15.7006 6.94586L8.79817 1V5.11765C2.3995 5.11765 0 9.76235 0 15Z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-9705619" src="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/brother-diagnosis-diabetes-2.jpg" alt="Young woman smiling at her phone while eating breakfast, reflecting on bro mocking sis over weight and diabetes." title="Young woman smiling at her phone while eating breakfast, reflecting on bro mocking sis over weight and diabetes." loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Image credits:&lt;a href="https://www.freepik.com/free-photo/plus-size-person-doing-indoor-house-activities_38878994.htm#fromView=search&amp;amp;page=1&amp;amp;position=4&amp;amp;uuid=2868445d-7ebb-41f3-853e-38327e5f2c01&amp;amp;query=teen+overweight+girl++eating+home+" target="_blank" class=" staff-link" rel="noopener nofollow"&gt; pikisuperstar / Freepik  (not the actual photo)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="post-desktop-ad-within-content post-ads margin-left"&gt;&lt;span class="dfp-ad"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="pg-ad-label"&gt;ADVERTISEMENT&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p id="boredpandacom_desktop_post_2" align="center" data-freestar-ad="__728x90"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h3&gt;She noted that she often went through school and daily life eating very little, yet remained the scapegoat for missing snacks, leftovers, and household items&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Text excerpt discussing blame for finishing household items, relating to bro mocking sis over weight and diabetes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="attachment-link-container shareable-image-block" id="author_327595dac3c27c4b98a480273dbef4dd" data-href="http://www.boredpanda.com/brother-diagnosis-diabetes/?image_id=author_327595dac3c27c4b98a480273dbef4dd.jpg"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/author_327595dac3c27c4b98a480273dbef4dd.jpg" alt="Text excerpt discussing blame for finishing household items, relating to bro mocking sis over weight and diabetes." title="Text excerpt discussing blame for finishing household items, relating to bro mocking sis over weight and diabetes." loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Text on a white background reads a humorous confession about always finishing leftover dinner despite attempts to deny it, related to weight and diabetes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="attachment-link-container shareable-image-block" id="author_86117b619b0939dbbd2e62e03d969707" data-href="http://www.boredpanda.com/brother-diagnosis-diabetes/?image_id=author_86117b619b0939dbbd2e62e03d969707.jpg"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/author_86117b619b0939dbbd2e62e03d969707.jpg" alt="Text on a white background reads a humorous confession about always finishing leftover dinner despite attempts to deny it, related to weight and diabetes." title="Text on a white background reads a humorous confession about always finishing leftover dinner despite attempts to deny it, related to weight and diabetes." loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sibling mocks over weight stopped as brother faces diabetes diagnosis, highlighting family irony and health struggles.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="attachment-link-container shareable-image-block" id="author_c62b86c88c3946d1dd06cd50b28f79e7" data-href="http://www.boredpanda.com/brother-diagnosis-diabetes/?image_id=author_c62b86c88c3946d1dd06cd50b28f79e7.jpg"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/author_c62b86c88c3946d1dd06cd50b28f79e7.jpg" alt="Sibling mocks over weight stopped as brother faces diabetes diagnosis, highlighting family irony and health struggles." title="Sibling mocks over weight stopped as brother faces diabetes diagnosis, highlighting family irony and health struggles." loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Brother mocks sister’s weight for years until he is diagnosed with type 2 diabetes, surprising the whole family.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="attachment-link-container shareable-image-block" id="author_9bf686f1f2360b3578fd98f0398075b3" data-href="http://www.boredpanda.com/brother-diagnosis-diabetes/?image_id=author_9bf686f1f2360b3578fd98f0398075b3.jpg"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/author_9bf686f1f2360b3578fd98f0398075b3.jpg" alt="Brother mocks sister’s weight for years until he is diagnosed with type 2 diabetes, surprising the whole family." title="Brother mocks sister’s weight for years until he is diagnosed with type 2 diabetes, surprising the whole family." loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="post-desktop-ad-within-content post-ads margin-left"&gt;&lt;span class="dfp-ad"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="pg-ad-label"&gt;ADVERTISEMENT&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p id="boredpandacom_desktop_post_3" align="center" data-freestar-ad="__728x90"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Text excerpt showing a person's reaction of laughing while others express shame and rage over weight and health issues.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="attachment-link-container shareable-image-block" id="author_862ea5f099ac1fd38fa164947b41a56e" data-href="http://www.boredpanda.com/brother-diagnosis-diabetes/?image_id=author_862ea5f099ac1fd38fa164947b41a56e.jpg"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/author_862ea5f099ac1fd38fa164947b41a56e.jpg" alt="Text excerpt showing a person's reaction of laughing while others express shame and rage over weight and health issues." title="Text excerpt showing a person's reaction of laughing while others express shame and rage over weight and health issues." loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Image credits:&lt;a class="author-name whitespace-nowrap text-neutral-content visited:text-neutral-content-weak focus-visible:-outline-offset-1 a cursor-pointer no-visited no-underline hover:no-underline staff-link" href="https://www.reddit.com/r/AITAH/comments/1p2bzff/aitah_for_laughing_when_my_brother_was_diagnosed/" target="_blank" aria-label="Author: Express-Letter4548" aria-haspopup="dialog" aria-expanded="false" rel="noopener nofollow"&gt;Express-Letter4548&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Blood samples in test tubes on a lab table with a medical professional drawing blood from a patient's arm, diabetes testing context.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="attachment-link-container shareable-image-block" id="brother-diagnosis-diabetes-3" data-href="http://www.boredpanda.com/brother-diagnosis-diabetes/?image_id=brother-diagnosis-diabetes-3.jpg"&gt;&lt;a class="web-share-button list-item-share new-share-experiment" data-location="single-post-image" data-title="Am I The Jerk For Laughing When My Brother Was Diagnosed With Diabetes?" data-share-url="https://www.boredpanda.com/brother-diagnosis-diabetes/?media_id=brother-diagnosis-diabetes-3" data-image="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/brother-diagnosis-diabetes-3.jpg"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;svg class="svg-icon icon-share-icon" role="img" viewbox="0 0 16 16"&gt;&lt;path d="M0 15C0 10.8824 5.22292 10.0588 8.79817 10.0588V14.1765L15.7006 8.23061C15.7941 8.15345 15.8695 8.05559 15.9213 7.94441C15.9731 7.83323 16 7.71155 16 7.58824C16 7.46492 15.9731 7.34314 15.9213 7.23196C15.8695 7.12078 15.7941 7.02302 15.7006 6.94586L8.79817 1V5.11765C2.3995 5.11765 0 9.76235 0 15Z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-9705626" src="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/brother-diagnosis-diabetes-3.jpg" alt="Blood samples in test tubes on a lab table with a medical professional drawing blood from a patient's arm, diabetes testing context." title="Blood samples in test tubes on a lab table with a medical professional drawing blood from a patient's arm, diabetes testing context." loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Image credits:&lt;a href="https://www.freepik.com/free-photo/man-woman-wearing-doctor-uniform-having-blood-analysis-clinic_42512884.htm#fromView=search&amp;amp;page=1&amp;amp;position=46&amp;amp;uuid=41e032ac-f056-4795-b567-a7bb5ab6c851&amp;amp;query=blood+test" target="_blank" class=" staff-link" rel="noopener nofollow"&gt; krakenimages.com / Freepik (not the actual photo)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;One day, her brother began to feel unwell, and after a visit to the doctor, he was diagnosed with type 2 diabetes, shocking both him and their mother&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Text excerpt about a brother mocked for weight who later develops diabetes, highlighting family and health issues.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="attachment-link-container shareable-image-block" id="author_efb4227c2e9b3620eca14721e63d8466" data-href="http://www.boredpanda.com/brother-diagnosis-diabetes/?image_id=author_efb4227c2e9b3620eca14721e63d8466.jpg"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/author_efb4227c2e9b3620eca14721e63d8466.jpg" alt="Text excerpt about a brother mocked for weight who later develops diabetes, highlighting family and health issues." title="Text excerpt about a brother mocked for weight who later develops diabetes, highlighting family and health issues." loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Text discussing a sibling mocking over weight and the brother developing diabetes, highlighting karma and serious health issues.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="attachment-link-container shareable-image-block" id="a7c4beb8-2786-4cfa-ab1b-aff3b01e2375.pn" data-href="http://www.boredpanda.com/brother-diagnosis-diabetes/?image_id=a7c4beb8-2786-4cfa-ab1b-aff3b01e2375.png"&gt;&lt;a class="web-share-button list-item-share new-share-experiment" data-location="single-post-image" data-title="Am I The Jerk For Laughing When My Brother Was Diagnosed With Diabetes?" data-share-url="https://www.boredpanda.com/brother-diagnosis-diabetes/?media_id=a7c4beb8-2786-4cfa-ab1b-aff3b01e2375.pn" data-image="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/a7c4beb8-2786-4cfa-ab1b-aff3b01e2375.png"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;svg class="svg-icon icon-share-icon" role="img" viewbox="0 0 16 16"&gt;&lt;path d="M0 15C0 10.8824 5.22292 10.0588 8.79817 10.0588V14.1765L15.7006 8.23061C15.7941 8.15345 15.8695 8.05559 15.9213 7.94441C15.9731 7.83323 16 7.71155 16 7.58824C16 7.46492 15.9731 7.34314 15.9213 7.23196C15.8695 7.12078 15.7941 7.02302 15.7006 6.94586L8.79817 1V5.11765C2.3995 5.11765 0 9.76235 0 15Z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-9705972" src="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/a7c4beb8-2786-4cfa-ab1b-aff3b01e2375.png" alt="Text discussing a sibling mocking over weight and the brother developing diabetes, highlighting karma and serious health issues." title="Text discussing a sibling mocking over weight and the brother developing diabetes, highlighting karma and serious health issues." loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="post-desktop-ad-within-content post-ads margin-left"&gt;&lt;span class="dfp-ad"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="pg-ad-label"&gt;ADVERTISEMENT&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p id="boredpandacom_desktop_post_4" align="center" data-freestar-ad="__728x90"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sister cares for brother with diabetes after years of weight-related teasing, showing love despite his past mockery.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="attachment-link-container shareable-image-block" id="author_50f58926ff939665ac6339316c238852" data-href="http://www.boredpanda.com/brother-diagnosis-diabetes/?image_id=author_50f58926ff939665ac6339316c238852.jpg"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/author_50f58926ff939665ac6339316c238852.jpg" alt="Sister cares for brother with diabetes after years of weight-related teasing, showing love despite his past mockery." title="Sister cares for brother with diabetes after years of weight-related teasing, showing love despite his past mockery." loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Text discussing concerns about eating one meal a day and inability to eat breakfast or lunch without feeling nauseous or headaches.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="attachment-link-container shareable-image-block" id="author_5960815bc63834d976b6e003b45b5f27" data-href="http://www.boredpanda.com/brother-diagnosis-diabetes/?image_id=author_5960815bc63834d976b6e003b45b5f27.jpg"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/author_5960815bc63834d976b6e003b45b5f27.jpg" alt="Text discussing concerns about eating one meal a day and inability to eat breakfast or lunch without feeling nauseous or headaches." title="Text discussing concerns about eating one meal a day and inability to eat breakfast or lunch without feeling nauseous or headaches." loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Image credits:&lt;a class="author-name whitespace-nowrap text-neutral-content visited:text-neutral-content-weak focus-visible:-outline-offset-1 a cursor-pointer no-visited no-underline hover:no-underline staff-link" href="https://www.reddit.com/r/AITAH/comments/1p2bzff/aitah_for_laughing_when_my_brother_was_diagnosed/" target="_blank" aria-label="Author: Express-Letter4548" aria-haspopup="dialog" aria-expanded="false" rel="noopener nofollow"&gt;Express-Letter4548&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;She laughed at the irony of the situation, and after confirming she was healthy, she laughed even harder which annoyed her mother&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Growing up, the OP lived in a &lt;a href="https://www.boredpanda.com/art/home-design/" target="_blank" class=" staff-link" rel="noopener "&gt;home&lt;/a&gt; where her body was constantly under scrutiny. At 140 pounds which was well within a normal range for her age, she was repeatedly called “fat”, especially by her older brother who ironically ate far more and moved far less. This same brother would call her “overweight” and warn her that she was going to develop a heart disease with the way she ate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While she received no &lt;a href="https://www.boredpanda.com/worst-thing-happened-on-birthday/" target="_blank" class=" staff-link" rel="noopener "&gt;birthday&lt;/a&gt; treats, and often went without lunch or breakfast, her brother got bottomless servings justified by the fact that he was just “a growing boy”. Every time food went missing, from juice to leftovers, she was instantly blamed. It didn’t matter if she was at school all day or simply hadn’t touched it, her family was convinced she was the culprit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Eventually, she stopped defending herself and would remain quiet, but one day, her brother told their mother he felt sluggish and dehydrated and he was taken to the &lt;a href="https://www.boredpanda.com/lifestyle/health/" target="_blank" class=" staff-link" rel="noopener "&gt;hospital&lt;/a&gt;. A doctor ordered bloodwork, and the results came back with her brother diagnosed with Type 2 diabetes. The shock was so intense, but the OP couldn’t help laughing at the irony.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Their mother, furious that she dared to laugh, dragged her to get blood tests too, but her result came out and she was completely healthy. The OP laughed harder this time which made her &lt;a href="https://www.boredpanda.com/ex-gifted-kid-traceable-airpods/" target="_blank" class=" staff-link" rel="noopener "&gt;mother&lt;/a&gt; even more furious, leading her to tell the extended family about how she laughed at her “unfortunate” brother. Now, the whole family was lashing out at her which left her wondering if she was wrong for laughing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="post-desktop-ad-within-content post-ads margin-left"&gt;&lt;span class="dfp-ad"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="pg-ad-label"&gt;ADVERTISEMENT&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p id="boredpandacom_desktop_post_infinite_0" align="center" data-freestar-ad="__728x90"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Teen boy in a medical exam room looking at doctor preparing a syringe, representing diabetes and weight health concerns.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="attachment-link-container shareable-image-block" id="brother-diagnosis-diabetes-1" data-href="http://www.boredpanda.com/brother-diagnosis-diabetes/?image_id=brother-diagnosis-diabetes-1.jpg"&gt;&lt;a class="web-share-button list-item-share new-share-experiment" data-location="single-post-image" data-title="Am I The Jerk For Laughing When My Brother Was Diagnosed With Diabetes?" data-share-url="https://www.boredpanda.com/brother-diagnosis-diabetes/?media_id=brother-diagnosis-diabetes-1" data-image="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/brother-diagnosis-diabetes-1.jpg"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;svg class="svg-icon icon-share-icon" role="img" viewbox="0 0 16 16"&gt;&lt;path d="M0 15C0 10.8824 5.22292 10.0588 8.79817 10.0588V14.1765L15.7006 8.23061C15.7941 8.15345 15.8695 8.05559 15.9213 7.94441C15.9731 7.83323 16 7.71155 16 7.58824C16 7.46492 15.9731 7.34314 15.9213 7.23196C15.8695 7.12078 15.7941 7.02302 15.7006 6.94586L8.79817 1V5.11765C2.3995 5.11765 0 9.76235 0 15Z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-9705628" src="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/brother-diagnosis-diabetes-1.jpg" alt="Teen boy in a medical exam room looking at doctor preparing a syringe, representing diabetes and weight health concerns." title="Teen boy in a medical exam room looking at doctor preparing a syringe, representing diabetes and weight health concerns." loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Image credits: &lt;a href="https://www.freepik.com/free-photo/coronavirus-sample-procedure_10623631.htm#fromView=search&amp;amp;page=1&amp;amp;position=0&amp;amp;uuid=ad6e0faa-7944-43ff-ab80-9a9537449a06&amp;amp;query=teen+boy+doctor+appointment" target="_blank" class=" staff-link" rel="noopener nofollow"&gt;freepik / Freepik (not the actual photo)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In situations like the one described in the OP’s case, the family dynamics reflect patterns of scapegoating. According to &lt;a href="https://www.choosingtherapy.com/family-scapegoat/" target="_blank" class=" staff-link" rel="noopener nofollow"&gt;Choosing Therapy&lt;/a&gt;, family scapegoating occurs when one person is unfairly blamed for the family’s problems, absorbing criticism and frustration that really belong to the household as a whole or another family member.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Other members project their guilt, insecurity, or unresolved emotional issues onto the scapegoated individual, often using manipulative tactics like &lt;a href="https://www.boredpanda.com/exhausting-relationship-fb-pics/" target="_blank" class=" staff-link" rel="noopener "&gt;gaslighting&lt;/a&gt; or triangulation to reinforce the blame and further isolate the target.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These dynamics are often worsened by sibling favoritism. As the &lt;a href="https://www.bbc.com/future/article/20230809-the-lifelong-effects-of-the-favourite-child" target="_blank" class=" staff-link" rel="noopener nofollow"&gt;BBC&lt;/a&gt; explains, when one child is consistently favored, the others can feel overlooked, jealous, or inadequate, potentially leading to anxiety or low self-esteem. Meanwhile, the favored child may face pressure or develop a sense of entitlement, straining family bonds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Compounding these issues is a family culture that emphasizes blame over communication. Life coach &lt;a href="https://www.melissalloyd.org/unraveling-family-dysfunction-the-role-of-poor-communication/" target="_blank" class=" staff-link" rel="noopener nofollow"&gt;Melissa Lloyd&lt;/a&gt; notes that families operating this way often fall into cycles of conflict and emotional distance as frequent victim-blaming, sarcastic assumptions, and top-down authority stifle open dialogue and prevent healthy problem-solving.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Netizens were firmly on the OP’s side, emphasizing that she wasn’t wrong for laughing and pointing out the clear irony of the situation. They agreed that her laughter wasn’t cruelty but a reaction to the poetic justice on display. They encouraged her to protect her mental and physical health, warning that her environment could become increasingly toxic.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What do you think about this situation? Do you think laughing in a moment of irony makes someone a jerk, or was it justified here? We would love to know your thoughts!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Netizens insisted the author’s laughter was at the irony and that she wasn’t wrong for that given the way she had always been treated by her family&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Online discussion about sibling mocking over weight and karma as brother develops diabetes, showing ironic consequences and family dynamics.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="post-desktop-ad-within-content post-ads margin-left"&gt;&lt;span class="dfp-ad"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="pg-ad-label"&gt;ADVERTISEMENT&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p id="boredpandacom_desktop_post_infinite_1" align="center" data-freestar-ad="__728x90"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Reddit user comments mocking brother’s food habits and diabetes as sister laughs at his weight-related health issues.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Reddit comment advising to move out and avoid toxic family amid weight and diabetes struggles shared between siblings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Reddit comment highlighting karma as a result of sibling mocking over weight and subsequent diabetes diagnosis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Comment on forum discussing brother mocking sister over weight, with karma and diabetes irony mentioned.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="post-desktop-ad-within-content post-ads margin-left"&gt;&lt;span class="dfp-ad"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="pg-ad-label"&gt;ADVERTISEMENT&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p id="boredpandacom_desktop_post_infinite_2" align="center" data-freestar-ad="__728x90"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Commenter’s perspective on sibling mockery over weight and diabetes, highlighting irony and family conflict.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Screenshot of a Reddit comment expressing concern about skipping meals, related to a story about sibling weight and diabetes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Screenshot of a social media comment about a brother mocking sister’s weight and the brother developing diabetes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Comment on a forum about sibling mocking related to weight and diabetes, advising to laugh it off to avoid blame.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="post-desktop-ad-within-content post-ads margin-left"&gt;&lt;span class="dfp-ad"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="pg-ad-label"&gt;ADVERTISEMENT&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p id="boredpandacom_desktop_post_infinite_3" align="center" data-freestar-ad="__728x90"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Screenshot of an online comment discussing a brother mocking his sister's weight before developing diabetes himself.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Screenshot of a social media comment about food and weight, related to bro mocking sis and diabetes topic.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;div id="postPoll-9705084" class="post-poll poll-wrapper single-post" data-poll-viewed="false" data-post-id="9705084" data-main-post-id="" data-poll-id="19597"&gt; &lt;input class="post-9705084-poll-value" type="hidden" value="eyJwb2xsSWQiOjE5NTk3LCJwb3N0SWQiOjk3MDUwODQsImhpZGVDb21tZW50cyI6ZmFsc2UsInF1ZXN0aW9ucyI6W3siaWQiOjE5NTk3LCJwb2xsSWQiOjE5NTk3LCJ0ZXh0IjoiSG93IGRvIHlvdSBmZWVsIGFib3V0IE9QIGxhdWdoaW5nIHdoZW4gaGVyIGJyb3RoZXIgd2FzIGRpYWdub3NlZCB3aXRoIGRpYWJldGVzPyIsIm9yZGVyIjpudWxsLCJhbnN3ZXJzIjpbeyJpZCI6NzQxMDcsInF1ZXN0aW9uSWQiOjE5NTk3LCJ0ZXh0IjoiSXQgd2FzIGp1c3RpZmllZCBkdWUgdG8gdGhlIGlyb255Iiwidm90ZXMiOjZ9LHsiaWQiOjc0MTA4LCJxdWVzdGlvbklkIjoxOTU5NywidGV4dCI6Ikl0IHdhcyBpbnNlbnNpdGl2ZSBhbmQgbWVhbiIsInZvdGVzIjowfSx7ImlkIjo3NDEwOSwicXVlc3Rpb25JZCI6MTk1OTcsInRleHQiOiJJdCB3YXMgdW5kZXJzdGFuZGFibGUgYnV0IGF3a3dhcmQiLCJ2b3RlcyI6MX0seyJpZCI6NzQxMTAsInF1ZXN0aW9uSWQiOjE5NTk3LCJ0ZXh0IjoiSXQgc2hvdWxkbid0IGhhdmUgaGFwcGVuZWQiLCJ2b3RlcyI6MH1dfV0sInBvc3RUaXRsZSI6bnVsbCwicG9zdFVybCI6Imh0dHBzOlwvXC93d3cuYm9yZWRwYW5kYS5jb21cL2Jyb3RoZXItZGlhZ25vc2lzLWRpYWJldGVzXC8ifQ=="&gt; &lt;div data-bind="if: isInitialised()"&gt;    &lt;div data-bind="if: !isLoading() &amp;amp;&amp;amp; isShowingResults"&gt; &lt;div class="poll-content"&gt; &lt;h3 class="answered-content-title"&gt;Thanks! Check out the results:&lt;/h3&gt; &lt;h3 class="answered-content-question" data-bind="text: currentQuestionText()"&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;  &lt;p class="total-votes" data-bind="visible: totalVotes() &amp;gt; 10 &amp;amp;&amp;amp; isShowingResults &amp;amp;&amp;amp; totalVotesDisplayMode !== 0"&gt; &lt;span class="text"&gt;Total votes · &lt;/span&gt; &lt;span data-bind="text: totalVotesFormatted"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;  &lt;div class="subscribe-to-newsletter-block-wrapper"&gt; &lt;p class="badge"&gt;Newsletter&lt;/p&gt; &lt;div class="subscribe-to-newsletter-block"&gt; &lt;p class="left"&gt; &lt;h3 class="title"&gt;Subscribe to Access &lt;br&gt; Exclusive Polls&lt;/h3&gt; &lt;/p&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;  &lt;div class="disclaimer"&gt; &lt;p&gt;By entering your email and clicking Subscribe, you're agreeing to let us send you customized marketing messages about us and our advertising partners. You are also agreeing to our &lt;a href="https://www.boredpanda.com/privacy-policy/"&gt;Privacy Policy&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div data-bind="if: newsletterSubscribed" class="thank-you"&gt; &lt;div class="wrapper"&gt;  &lt;p class="right"&gt;Thank you! You've successfully subscribed to newsletters!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;     &lt;p class="clearfix"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Bored Panda</author><pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 03:35:09 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiZEFVX3lxTE5IOWlfTlBpWGJPMlhMVUhPMFRWbWdUYlFLYzc1c0FfbzJzVkVFTmpsVVVKYUlRRERSaHRGM1pMN1BGN0s5Yk1oc2JYSVNScC05TUVUNXNycGFiLUFJdzUyLXhkMGM</guid></item><item><title>心脏病风险较高的南印度人：突破性的基因研究揭示-德干先驱报</title><link>https://www.deccanherald.com/india/south-indians-more-prone-to-heart-disease-study-3815339</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="story-content-7ca60d47-9f3d-4741-a559-7236d133ead0" class="story-cards taboola-read-more-container"&gt;&lt;p class="wW6Na"&gt;Published 30 November 2025, 23:22 IST&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Deccan Herald</author><pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 23:22:11 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilAFBVV95cUxOT0hoeU5lT3dOUmNwYnlROHdDRy1wXzZacGc3SWcwVG45dTg0amQxVXd0X1p5VDFCNlRhRllpeTdJLWtickFCd2l3VDE5SzNpcW1ERUN6eDFTd1VxdnNMRmhmWGI5dVZfZUZrTElzMHY1RHBsTU1sYkJTV1F4MExVRFc0b25ZUm92RjY3bEV0Mlg0ZlJ6</guid></item><item><title>健康编辑与年轻人疾病激增的癌症斗争-每日邮报</title><link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-15310871/health-editor-cancer-surge-young-people-signs.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div itemprop="articleBody"&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The panic hit first. Then came the embarrassment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;After all, I had spent years giving health advice to colleagues, friends and family, convinced I was an expert in so many areas of medicine. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Yet there I was, at my desk as Health Editor at the Daily Mail in &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/new_york/index.html" id="mol-454e28a0-c942-11f0-9d74-9506a24b12fb"&gt;New York City&lt;/a&gt;, being told that I had &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/cancer/index.html" id="mol-4546d5a0-c942-11f0-9d74-9506a24b12fb"&gt;cancer&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;It was especially hard to take because being healthy had become so much a part of my identity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;I trained in martial arts, worked out religiously, tracked everything I ate and, if I'm honest, bragged constantly about it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Friends came to me for health advice: &lt;span class="mol-style-italic"&gt;Should I eat this? Will that give me cancer? What supplements do you take? How do I get abs?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In fact, my unusual eating habits were a running office joke: six boiled eggs for lunch, yoghurt parfaits mixed in giant baking bowls, and my infamous popcorn that would stink out the newsroom every afternoon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;So getting diagnosed with cancer at 29, when I was seemingly in perfect health, felt not only deeply unfair, but a little like some kind of cosmic payback for being so confident in my own good health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;To my utter shock, I was diagnosed with testicular cancer at 29 (author pictured)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;A forced smile barely hides my nerves as I prepare for my first CT scans, which will reveal if the cancer has spread &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;That said, however, the diagnosis didn't come entirely out of nowhere. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The day before, after putting it off for months, I'd finally had an ultrasound on an almond-sized lump in my left testicle.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The scan was meant to take 30 minutes, but dragged on for an hour and a half. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The technician muttered about 'poor visibility' and 'protocol' requiring clear images of every region.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Now I realize what was really happening: she was taking as many images as possible, knowing - or strongly suspecting - it was cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;I didn't get out until 3pm, and assumed I'd hear back in a few days.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But the next morning, at 9.03am exactly, my phone lit up. Most offices open at 9am, I thought, so clearly this was urgent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;I shot out of my chair and raced across the newsroom floor as the person on the phone told me to find a private room and turn my camera on. The doctor needed to speak to me urgently.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;I propped my phone up in front of me and sat awkwardly as the doctor connected and said, 'I'm so sorry - we're fairly confident you've got cancer.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;I trained in martial arts (pictured in my uniform) and worked out multiple times a week - being fit and healthy had become part of my identity &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Pictured: I wear a sheepish look as I wait to hear what stage the cancer has reached&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;As she delivered the hammer blow, I felt utterly numb. I was listening to every word, but they weren't registering. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;It was as if she was describing someone else, maybe one of the hundreds of patients I'd written about, but not me.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Then she added, 'There's good news… and bad news.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The bad news: they were confident it was cancer. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But the doctor told me that if you had to pick a cancer, this is one of the most treatable forms (which didn't feel very reassuring at the time).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But she was right. Testicular cancer has a five-year survival rate above 95 percent - and it doesn't take a health journalist to know how good that is.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The overall five-year survival rate for all cancers is roughly 69 percent, but many types which are increasingly common in young people are far deadlier, such as pancreatic (12 percent) and liver (21 percent).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Testicular cancer is uniquely treatable for a few reasons. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;First, the tumors are extraordinarily sensitive to chemotherapy, which can melt away cancer cells even if the disease has spread to other parts of the body. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;And it usually strikes men in their 20s or 30s, whose bodies handle aggressive treatment well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;In my mind I had prepared to do chemotherapy - after all, the doctor told me there was a 40 percent chance of the disease returning&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Pictured: The joy on my face after learning the cancer was contained to the testicle and I didn't need to have chemo&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Removing the testicle is also fairly straightforward - you're in and out of hospital in hours. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;And because lumps appear early, surgeons often remove the entirety of the cancer, reducing the risk of spread.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Still, I was told I needed surgery immediately.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;After hanging up with my doctor, I was struck by a blizzard of emotions. Looking back, I now recognize it as 10 minutes of sheer panic.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;My eyes filled with tears as visions flashed through my mind of the worst-case scenario: bald, weak, dying young, not fulfilling my ambitions or dreams.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;I tried calling my mom, who was at work, and Googled survival statistics, which calmed me a little.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Then, strangely, something switched in my mind.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;I became intensely practical, with absolute focus on the next appointment, scan or blood test. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;That focus lasted throughout my fight and I haven't been emotional about my cancer since then.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;A lot of that is down to how efficient my treatment plan was. From diagnosis to surgery was less than two weeks - startlingly fast.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;As a Briton whose grandfather had to wait six months to start treatment for stage 3 prostate cancer on the National Health Service, the speed of American healthcare, despite its flaws, felt surreal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;The timing of the cancer was terrible - I'd been due to move apartments. Pictured: I was fresh out of surgery and unable to lift heavy items, so I recruited the help of friends to move a sofa into my new home&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;When I visited my oncologist at Memorial Sloan Kettering - a surreal experience, given I'd spent years writing about the hospital&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Of course, it was reassuring to be treated so quickly. But the worst part of a cancer diagnosis is one that nobody talks about: when the doctor says 'you have cancer,' you still don't know your chance of survival.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Not until they figure out how big the tumor is, whether it has spread to nearby lymph nodes or organs and exactly what type of cancer it is. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Only then can doctors give an accurate picture of your outlook and the treatment you'll need.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;My blood tests came back the next day: no tumor markers. A feeling of shattering relief.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;CT scans followed a few days later - chest, abdomen, pelvis - to see if it had spread.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;It was a testament to the speed of the US health system that, later that day, I received the results: negative again. Another hurdle cleared.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Only after surgery could they confirm whether it was stage 1 - easily treatable, no chemotherapy required. It was looking good.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Based on the negative blood tests, scans and size of the tumor, my doctors had been confident I had a single 'seminoma,' a slow-growing tumor that develops over years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Instead, they found two tumors: one seminoma and one embryonal carcinoma - a far more aggressive type that can spread in weeks or months. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Pictured: A post-surgery thumbs up. The moment I woke from the operation, my years-long back pain was gone. It never returned&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;When I go out, I now try to stick to a two-drink max rule. The 'alcohol guilt' after cancer has been one of many surprises post-diagnosis &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;There were also early signs cancer cells had started migrating toward the bloodstream. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Tiny cells may have leaked into the blood which can, over time, raise the risk of growing new tumors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;When I visited my oncologist at Memorial Sloan Kettering - a surreal experience, given I'd spent years writing about the hospital - he told me plainly that with this combination, I had about a 40 percent chance of the cancer returning.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;To my surprise, despite the risk, my doctors advised against chemotherapy, even though it would reduce the risk to just one to three percent. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;As they told me, doctors are now rethinking the old blanket-chemo approach because the treatment is brutal - hospitalizations, infections, sepsis, even a small risk of secondary cancers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;For young, otherwise healthy patients, they said it was sometimes worth playing the odds. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;I was skeptical. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;It was tempting to just get it over with, to never have to worry about the cancer again, and I'd mentally prepared myself for chemo. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;I sought a second opinion at Mount Sinai. To my surprise, the oncologist there also recommended surveillance only. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;With two of the world's top cancer doctors in agreement, I felt I needed to be humble and listen. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;And as vain as it sounds, what unsettled me most was the thought of losing my hair.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The chemotherapy used for testicular cancer almost guarantees hair loss - even eyebrows. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;It's a brutal prospect, though many would feel it's a price worth paying for survival.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;&lt;p class="clear"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;I am now closely monitored with blood tests, scans and X-rays every few months. If the cancer returns, I'll need chemo. Pictured: Me at my latest checkup in November 2025 (left) and returning to work in September 2025 (right)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;My mindset is: If it can happen to me, it can happen to anyone. I now urge all my male friends to check for lumps regularly and stay vigilant&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;So what's the next step?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;I am now closely monitored with blood tests, scans and X-rays every few months. If it returns, I'll need chemo.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The cancer also affected my hormones.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;My testosterone crashed to the level of a 70-year-old, causing overwhelming fatigue.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;I now inject medication three times a week and feel stronger all the time. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;After two months off training, I'm back to working out five times per week, including three martial arts sessions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;While I'm eating the same, something curious has happened with my weight.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;I've shot up more than 10lbs in three months without gaining much, if any, new fat - almost certainly the result of my testosterone bouncing back.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;I now drink far less alcohol, and when I do, I stick to a two-drink maximum.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;One of the more surprising psychological changes is the guilt I feel after drinking.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Knowing alcohol is a class 1 carcinogen - and that I'm in a critical period where my cancer could return - it just feels reckless.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;By reading this, you know I haven't kept my cancer a secret. I decided long ago I wanted to be an advocate. My mindset is: If it can happen to me, it can happen to anyone.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;I now urge all my male friends to check their testicles regularly and stay vigilant.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Curiously, my weight has shot up 10lbs since returning to work and exercise - almost certainly a result of my testosterone bouncing back &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Pictured: On vacation in October 2025, trying to reclaim what I can of the summer I missed&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;I mentioned embarrassment I felt when I received the diagnosis. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Well, the second wave of it hit when I realized my symptoms had been there all along.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Two major health issues I'd battled for years - excruciating back pain and chronic fatigue - were almost certainly caused by the tumor.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;For two years, I'd suffered pain I attributed to slipped discs and jiu-jitsu. On surgery morning, I could barely walk, yet the moment I woke from surgery, the pain was gone. It never returned.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Doctors now think the tumor caused inflammation that radiated through my pelvis, irritating the nerves around my discs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;I also spent years chronically exhausted, no matter how much I slept. I blamed the move to America, stress and long hours, despite fatigue being one of the most common symptoms of cancer that shows itself before a diagnosis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Yet I, the person leading the Daily Mail's coverage of cancers in young people, had somehow missed my own. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;I initially thought my body had failed me, but perhaps it was my mind that had failed to listen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Testicular cancer appears to be one of those genetic lottery diseases - I was probably born with a defect in the cells that form the testicles, called germ cells.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;These are the cells that eventually develop into sperm, but if they go awry during development, they can later turn cancerous.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;We still don't fully understand what sparks the cancerous change, but we know testicular cancer is rising among young men.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Studies show its incidence has nearly doubled in the past 40 years in American men aged 20 to 34. It is now the most common form of cancer for men under 35.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;So, I urge anyone who notices anything unusual, no matter how small, to get it checked. It could save your life - I'm hoping it's saved mine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
            

            
            
            
            
            &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Daily Mail</author><pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 22:10:40 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipAFBVV95cUxQS2xoMDdRajFaMk0wVm5MWENZR0dycWdCN1VYQ2tPeXZreDBOeW10TjZzSThEWjdiTk1aSVhxaFJEbG1KSzM4M0FMWE5aR0cwZDFJTzVLRHMyQlBRbnh3TnNJQWNjMnQxQ184NGoxQlI3TFNEQnJrTEFrNHZzdGdDSXJLMmg0Y21OSWQwbTZHWXBzYXVxWkJYOFZpdVZ4NHhxNk1NOA</guid></item><item><title>房客专栏|幽灵灯和其他3个您应该注意的约会“橙色旗帜” -《华盛顿邮报》</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/wellness/2025/11/30/dating-advice-ghostlighting-depth-avoidance-orange-flags/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="67ZCRU6ZIRFLBFSSPW74OMEJAE" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;My patient showed me her phone. As I scrolled through the text thread, my stomach dropped. The previous Tuesday, the guy she had been seeing for two months had sent three paragraphs about how much he was looking forward to introducing her to his friends that weekend. By Friday, he had vanished — no response to her texts — nothing. Then Sunday night, he resurfaced with “Hey, what’s up?” It was as if the whole weekend hadn’t happened.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMirAFBVV95cUxPel9uZmJYTklyZUJjelYzTU0xZERvYkNyeGozdEpvN3B4dFRmN2VzbUZaNDROTE9zUnRlSDVtNjFRX3BXZ2ZqT21JRkJIeU9SSnNJWHpCcHpXWklMdjBTNGtoWUl2dlZ5R041eFBrNFJhWGpwYktyUHhyTWlfMEVUeUgyZnRSS1Z4bE1sTHgzSWFSTzJnd1Z5elJTMEhQTDVKR1VvY3Z2Q2MtV1RN</guid></item><item><title>皮肤科医生对新的头皮狂热给予侧视-新闻</title><link>https://www.newser.com/story/379332/were-spending-hundreds-to-take-care-of-our-scalps.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="divStoryBodyAbove"&gt;
                                
                                    &lt;span id="StoryTextTop"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
                                
                                
                                
                                    &lt;p class="storyParagraph"&gt;
                                        A rising beauty trend has Americans massaging their scalps and flocking to high-end head spas—sometimes for hundreds of dollars a session—all in pursuit of healthier hair, even if dermatologists aren't convinced most people need the help, per the &lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2025/11/20/style/scalp-care-beauty-trends-2025.html"&gt;&lt;em&gt;New York Times&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. The scalp has emerged as the latest focus of the beauty world, and the trend, fueled by TikTok and other social media, has seen a significant spike in interest: According to market insights company Spate, online searches and posts about "scalp serum" jumped 77% over the past year, while "scalp massagers" and "scalp treatment" also saw notable increases.
                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                    
                                
                                
                            &lt;/div&gt;

                            
                            
                            
                            
                            

                            &lt;div id="divStoryBodyBelow"&gt;
                                
                                    &lt;p class="storyParagraph"&gt;
                                        Influencers are documenting their intensive scalp routines—sometimes involving hours of massage or the use of expensive serums—and sharing with hundreds of thousands of followers, helping to drive the trend. Many major hair-care brands, from drugstore staples to high-end labels, have launched scalp-focused products. Beyonce's Cecred brand famously sells out of its Restoring Hair &amp;amp; Edge Drops serum; it reportedly moved one bottle every 16 seconds from last November through July.
                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                

                                
                                    &lt;p class="storyParagraph"&gt;
                                        While some dermatologists acknowledge that scalp care can improve hair health, they caution that elaborate routines aren't necessary for most people. "If you're not having a problem, there shouldn't be this huge drive to have to get all this stuff to put on your scalp," says Maryanne Senna, director of the Hair Loss Center of Excellence at Lahey Hospital &amp;amp; Medical Center.
                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                

                                
                                
                                
                                

                                
                                    &lt;p class="storyParagraph"&gt;
                                        Still, the allure of scalp care persists, with head spas—especially those offering microscopic analysis of hair follicles and customized treatments—drawing crowds in cities like New York and Los Angeles. Prices for these treatments range widely, with some sessions costing upward of $300. Even if they're not terribly helpful for most people, it's not likely you'll hurt yourself in any way by getting a scalp massage or similar treatment. "The only real danger is to a person's wallet," Senna tells the &lt;em&gt;Times&lt;/em&gt;. Meanwhile, &lt;a href="https://www.womenshealthmag.com/beauty/a69073403/scalp-steaming-benefits/"&gt;some dermatologists recommend&lt;/a&gt; "scalp steaming," while &lt;a href="https://www.today.com/shop/scalp-care-guide-t289360"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Today&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; notes the two most important things you can do for your scalp: Keep it clean and protected from the sun.
                                    &lt;/p&gt;
                                

                                



                            &lt;/div&gt;
                        &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Newser</author><pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 18:10:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilAFBVV95cUxOWU5JZmVxOGpOQlYxbE9PNG1vQmlqRFBNZ0pyMW1mbV81d01lX2RrNloyNU05ZHV5V0xpUU8xd3BaVjFfV1kwbzBjdDRDZ0s5NUtBMUVRT2VvOGRNN1Y2UU82TWxZbTBXMFlzN3p1dTU0WGQ3cDRRSTF3VzNqTXp5U2FfR0F1cDZCTDNHeWZDcFhuV2gz</guid></item><item><title>为什么美国人在20世纪80年代突然变胖？ - Daily Kos</title><link>https://www.dailykos.com/stories/2025/11/30/2356160/-Why-Did-Americans-Suddenly-Get-Fat-in-the-1980s</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="story__text"&gt;
          &lt;h2&gt;The Obesity Epidemic: What Really Happened in the 1980s&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You've seen the arguments. Seed oils are poison. Sugar is the devil. Fast food destroyed America. The government ruined everything. Or maybe it's all Big Pharma's fault.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Everyone's got a villain. Everyone's wrong.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The truth? Multiple things broke at once. Around 1980, several massive changes hit simultaneously, and we're still living with the consequences.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;The Data Doesn't Lie&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;figure class="image-captioned align-right"&gt;&lt;img alt="obesity_trends_by_age_sex.png" src="https://cdn.prod.dailykos.com/images/1503733/large/obesity_trends_by_age_sex.png?1764524981" title="obesity_trends_by_age_sex.png"&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/nchs/nhanes/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;NHANES surveys&lt;/a&gt; show something remarkable: obesity rates were relatively flat for decades, then suddenly bent upward between 1976–1980. Not a gradual drift—a sharp inflection point. Adult obesity jumped from roughly 15% to over 30% in just two decades.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That's not normal. That's not genetics. That's environmental.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;What Actually Changed&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;The Government Picked the Wrong Enemy&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In 1977, the &lt;a href="https://www.dietaryguidelines.gov/about-dietary-guidelines/history-dietary-guidelines" target="_blank"&gt;McGovern Committee&lt;/a&gt; told Americans to slash fat intake to 30% of calories and replace it with carbohydrates. Three years later, the first official Dietary Guidelines made it policy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The food industry listened. Boy, did they listen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Suddenly, everything was "low-fat." Cookies, yogurt, salad dressing, frozen dinners. But fat makes food taste good, so manufacturers replaced it with something else: sugar. Lots of sugar. And refined starches.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The result? Hyper-processed, hyper-palatable foods that were technically "low-fat" but absolutely terrible for metabolic health.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;High-Fructose Corn Syrup Went Supernova&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://ajcn.nutrition.org/article/S0002-9165(22)03883-7/fulltext" target="_blank"&gt;HFCS consumption increased roughly 1,000% between 1970 and 1990&lt;/a&gt;. It was cheap, stable, and sweeter than regular sugar. Food manufacturers dumped it into everything—soda, bread, ketchup, crackers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Total added sugar intake skyrocketed. We didn't peak until around 2000, but the damage was already done by the mid-1980s.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Portions Exploded&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.ers.usda.gov/data-products/food-availability-per-capita-data-system/" target="_blank"&gt;USDA data show&lt;/a&gt; average calorie intake rose 200–300 calories per day from the late 1970s to early 2000s. That's an extra meal's worth of energy, every single day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;McDonald's didn't introduce Super Size until the 1990s, but portions were already growing throughout the 1980s. Bigger sodas. Bigger burgers. Bigger everything.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Grain-based desserts, soft drinks, and fast food drove most of the increase.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;We Stopped Moving&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The shift from manual labor to desk jobs accelerated through the 1960s–1980s. More people drove everywhere. Fewer people walked or biked.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then came home computers and video games. Television watching was already high, but the 1980s added new reasons to sit still.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kids especially. Recess got shorter. PE programs got cut. Screen time went up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Smoking Declined (Yes, This Matters)&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Adult smoking rates &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/nchs/hus/topics/tobacco-use.htm" target="_blank" title=""&gt;dropped from 42% in 1965 to 25% by the early 1990s&lt;/a&gt;. That's overwhelmingly good news—smoking kills.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But quitting typically adds 4–5 kg. At the population level, that contributed roughly 1–2 percentage points to obesity prevalence. Not the main driver, but not nothing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Everything Else&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Restaurant eating increased. Ultra-processed foods were engineered to maximize consumption. Sleep patterns changed. Stress increased.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some researchers point to endocrine disruptors, though evidence for the 1980s timeframe remains speculative.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;The Bottom Line&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.aeaweb.org/articles?id=10.1257/089533003769204371" target="_blank"&gt;Peer-reviewed analyses&lt;/a&gt; attribute roughly 50–70% of the calorie increase to greater intake of refined grains, added sugars, and added fats (mostly seed oils used in processed and restaurant food). The rest comes from reduced physical activity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It wasn't &lt;em&gt;just&lt;/em&gt; seed oils. It wasn't &lt;em&gt;just&lt;/em&gt; sugar. It wasn't &lt;em&gt;just&lt;/em&gt; the government or &lt;em&gt;just&lt;/em&gt; fast food.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was all of it. At once.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The 1980s created a perfect storm: official dietary policy that backfired spectacularly, cheap hyper-palatable processed foods, massive portion increases, and a simultaneous collapse in physical activity. The effect was rapid and population-wide.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Why This Matters Now&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Understanding what actually happened matters because the simplistic answers—ban seed oils, ban sugar, ban carbs—miss the point.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The food environment changed fundamentally. We made calories cheaper, more available, more rewarding, and easier to overconsume. We built cities around cars instead of walking. We replaced recess with standardized tests.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fixing this requires addressing multiple systems simultaneously. Better food policy. Better urban design. Better food labeling. Better education about ultra-processed foods.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One villain makes for better social media engagement. But multiple causes make for better solutions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The 1980s broke something. We can't fix it by picking just one scapegoat.&lt;/p&gt;





&lt;p class="is-empty-p"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



        &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Daily Kos</author><pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 17:55:57 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiogFBVV95cUxOMGlKX0NYUFBuVUl3ZkVMUE56eG1tU1FXSUd4eFJlbUs0RUpseVJkdFBmYmw2Q211V1FzcklLeHNMeEhjQ1BhYXdHQVZXVmlfbDJNLWpKbDJmUFhVNXpTdnVjT3V2TXBLUU5MUlExTWlwUGRGZDhNdGFUVURicU9qbWZvRHdua0duQTJVWjNYcFpYN3dpV05oZFFQNjBwZzRjbnc</guid></item><item><title>自然降低胆固醇：每天吃黑小茴香种子，获得惊人的好处-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/lower-your-cholesterol-naturally-eat-black-cumin-seed-daily-for-surprising-benefits/articleshow/125676409.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;p&gt;For generations, black cumin seed has been sprinkled into breads, curries and traditional remedies, a quiet staple with an ancient reputation. Now emerging scientific evidence is shedding new light on its potential health benefits. A Japanese study published in &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/fsn3.70888" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;Food Science and Nutrition&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; suggests that eating black cumin seed daily could meaningfully lower cholesterol and even support weight loss, offering a natural route to better heart health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="5"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="6"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;br&gt;Black cumin seed: An age-old spice to lower cholesterol&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="7"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Black cumin seed, also known as Nigella sativa or kalonji, has long been valued in Middle Eastern and South Asian households for its warm, peppery bite. But the new research gives its traditional reputation a solid scientific foundation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="11"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="lOvcW vdo_embedd"&gt;&lt;div class="k7lcu"&gt;&lt;p class="efT4r"&gt;What Your Cholesterol Report Is Hiding — The Truth That Could Save Your Heart | Dr Vinayak Agarwal&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="13"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the study, adults who took a small daily dose of black cumin seed powder for eight weeks saw notable improvements in several key markers: LDL, or bad cholesterol, dropped, HDL, or good cholesterol, rose and overall lipid profiles shifted in a healthier direction.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="15"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Meanwhile, those in the control group, who made no changes to their diets, saw no improvement at all.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="17"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Perhaps the most intriguing part of the findings is that some participants lost weight during the trial. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Laboratory tests in the same study showed that black cumin seed extract slowed the formation of fat cells, hinting at an underlying anti-adipogenic effect.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="21"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; This dual benefit, supporting heart health while helping regulate body fat, is rare for such a simple dietary addition. It is one reason researchers believe black cumin could serve as a functional food in preventing lifestyle-related diseases, including obesity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="24"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="25"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;How to use black cumin seed daily&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="26"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to the study, even a teaspoon of black cumin seed powder a day was enough to produce measurable health benefits. For everyday use, the spice can be taken in several easy forms: mixed into warm water in the morning, stirred into yoghurt or smoothies, added to dal and vegetable dishes or sprinkled over salads.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="28"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; The simplest and often recommended option is to take a teaspoon of black cumin seed powder in warm water first thing in the morning. But you can just as easily mix it into yoghurt, smoothies or your daily meals. The key is taking it consistently.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="30"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="31"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="32"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="em" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Note: The information provided in this article is for educational purposes only and is not intended as medical advice. Always consult with a qualified healthcare professional before starting any new medication or treatment and before changing your diet or supplement regimen.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 17:11:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikAJBVV95cUxOWlI0T3pJTWs0WE4xdjlPcHNzMFl3bEYtak1pcTJzbXREZkFZMUFib1JZdGk4X2EyUnFLU09zVGx3eElySjBkLVQ0cXdnNHFPb0hhNmFockROSzdaNkpJZHBGV1JRVXBxQXc0Qk5lNG05VDZ1LTJ4STZFY1k3TExxd1BtNG00dUhfWDF6Vm13eFhocno4Z2ZzaTgtTXAyNF9iV1BWM28xUjdXeHVRYk83Q2RkeGdRSWh1UW9uZjlHZDdMQzgzUm02bGkybDlyZGZ3dFBrT1Z6THlLYzZLSzNER0FlTGNkaUhpVDBGNW1LSTNvZ1ViNXNWMHo2X2pvdi13TFEyS1U1cDZwajFoZm5xWQ</guid></item><item><title>Shelli经常头晕。医生发现她的大脑“脱落” -每日邮报</title><link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-15329481/doctors-dismissed-symptoms-brain-health-chiari-malformation.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div itemprop="articleBody"&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;A teacher whose symptoms were repeatedly dismissed by doctors actually had a serious neurological disorder: one she describes as feeling like her brain was 'falling out' of her head.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Shelli Gunnoe, 26, from South Carolina, was diagnosed with a Chiari malformation this year after more than a decade of confusing symptoms. Early on, doctors told her that issues like laughter-triggered headaches were nothing to worry about. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But Chiari malformation, which is a rare condition impacting around 300,000 Americans, or one in 1,000, causes the lower part of the brain to push down into the spinal canal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;This pressure, which disrupts nerves and the normal flow of cerebrospinal fluid, can cause a wide variety of symptoms, including headaches that worsen with straining, neck pain, balance issues and, in severe cases, coordination or vision problems.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;For Gunnoe, uncovering the cause of her symptoms took more than 14 years. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;As years went on, she began to experience tingling in her arms and fingers, bouts of nausea, heat intolerance and episodes in which her vision would dim. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;She recalled one incident at work when she became so dizzy and overwhelmed by heat that she collapsed in a restroom, saying she was 'unable to get up' until her fiancé arrived to take her home. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;That crisis finally led to a neurology referral and the MRI that revealed a 4mm Chiari malformation. Even then, &lt;a class="" rel="nofollow noreferrer noopener" target="_blank" href="https://www.instagram.com/onbrandbyshelli/"&gt;doctors initially said &lt;/a&gt;surgery wasn't needed. But Gunnoe's symptoms kept worsening, as simple movements like bending or standing provoked dizziness or instability. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Shelli Gunnoe, 26, from South Carolina, was diagnosed with a Chiari malformation after more than a decade of confusing symptoms&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    
    
    &lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;A follow-up MRI complicated matters further, as a neurologist suggested her symptoms more closely resembled pseudotumor cerebri, a condition where pressure inside the skull rises abnormally. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;This, along with enlarged brain ventricles (a network of fluid-filled cavities within the brain that produce, contain and circulate cerebrospinal fluid) and her earlier diagnosis of hydrocephalus, (a condition when there is too much fluid in the brain, causing swelling and pressure) hinted at a deeper issue. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Deep down, I knew something wasn't adding up,' she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Doctors now believe some of her symptoms may trace all the way back to birth. Chiari malformation is usually present at birth (congenital), although symptoms may not appear until childhood or adulthood.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Gunnoe was delivered by emergency C-section because she was breech, 'upright with my head positioned in my mother's rib cage,' she explained. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;She inhaled a large amount of amniotic fluid and initially needed NICU care. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Although her parents hoped for a routine infancy afterward, she soon required a hip brace for developmental support. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;She was also 'extremely irritable and only soothed by being held,' and her parents worried her head looked unusually large. Despite their concerns, a neurologist dismissed the issue at the time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Years later, in 2009, Gunnoe was taken to hospital for chronic migraines. CT and MRI scans revealed mild hydrocephalus, and she was treated with medication. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Early on, doctors told Gunnoe that issues like laughter-triggered headaches were nothing to worry about&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;That crisis finally led to a neurology referral and the MRI that revealed a 4mm Chiari malformation, pictured here&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Chiari malformation, which is a rare condition impacting around 300,000 Americans, causes the lower part of the brain to push down into the spinal canal&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Throughout childhood and her teen years she fainted often and lived with intense fatigue and headaches. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Doctors kept telling me it was my weight,' she said. But after losing 50lbs, the symptoms persisted. In January 2022, immediately after standing up from a bike in a cycling class, she fainted again.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Her symptoms escalated in the years that followed: blurry vision, vertigo, crushing fatigue, and mornings when she felt 'frozen and unable to wake.' &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;She described episodes that 'didn't feel normal for someone my age.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;When she finally received a clear diagnosis of Chiari malformation in November 2024, she felt both 'relieved, but frustrated.' &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;A neurologist used a skull model to show how her cerebellar tonsils were being pulled downward into the opening at the base of her skull. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'He explained that mine are pushed down further than they should be, slipping through the opening where the spinal cord runs,' she said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Because they're squeezed into a space that's too tight, they press on my spinal cord and disrupt the flow of cerebrospinal fluid.' &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;When that flow is slowed or blocked, she added, 'it irritates the nerves and causes many of the symptoms I've been dealing with.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Gunnoe was delivered by emergency C-section because she was breech, 'upright with my head positioned in my mother's rib cage,' she explained&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Throughout childhood and her teen years, Gunnoe fainted often and lived with intense fatigue and headaches&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;For now, Gunnoe is being closely monitored while her neurologist determines the best course of action. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Because of my combination of Chiari, hydrocephalus history, enlarged ventricles, and possible pseudotumor, my case is still being evaluated,' she said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;While waiting, she manages her symptoms through pacing, careful activity choices and prioritizing rest and hydration. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'I'm still very much in the 'watch and wait' stage,' she added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Despite the uncertainty, she tries to live fully. She still experiences dizziness when standing, visual disturbances, sensory overload and difficulty tolerating certain movements. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Simple tasks, looking upward, bending down or standing too quickly, can trigger symptoms instantly. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Even so, she continues teaching full-time, creates online content and models, and is training, with thoughtful modifications, in hopes of participating in the Hyrox race, a global, indoor fitness competition that combines eight 0.62m runs with eight different functional fitness workout stations. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'It's a strange balance,' she said, 'acknowledging the reality of a neurological condition while refusing to let it shrink my goals or identity.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Her symptoms escalated in the years that followed: blurry vision, vertigo, crushing fatigue, and mornings when she felt 'frozen and unable to wake'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Despite the uncertainty, Gunnoe tries to live fully. She is hopeful of participating in the Hyrox race: a global, indoor fitness competition that combines eight 1km runs with eight different functional fitness workout stations&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Gunnoe hopes her story encourages others not to ignore their symptoms or allow them to be dismissed. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Invisible illnesses don't always look dramatic,' she said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'People see me lifting weights, teaching, modelling, smiling online, and they don't see the hours I spend navigating dizziness, pressure or exhaustion behind the scenes.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;She wants to speak especially to women who feel overlooked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;She said: 'You can advocate for yourself. You can ask for second opinions. And you can still chase big dreams while living with something hard.' &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Her life, she insists, remains 'full, meaningful and ambitious, not because my neurological issues disappeared, but because I've learned to move with them while still moving forward.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
            

            
            
            
            
            &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Daily Mail</author><pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 16:41:08 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMitwFBVV95cUxNNGJwcjhLYTh0RXp3ejF2RzhlbTBXVElFM01pZDlwNy1uNGFiaG40bE1WMXdNU2VkdUlTZDRIOEZwQzc4aVVpaGtkOHl6ZWRwb3Q5Vk5DYkxUQkNSQ2FjWGVBTl8xNE81VjNaVWtKR3Z4Sm4zQ0ZIOThZNWV1VWVYRWxOV3J3ZzB3d3UzZkt1UmJhT2EtWmJKbkxndUJqT0NxQ1h3YXJWcWVPWTJmV2hvc3V6S2xGVGc</guid></item><item><title>医生揭示了您可能体内有寄生虫的5个警告信号-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/doctor-reveals-5-warning-signs-you-may-have-parasites-in-your-body/articleshow/125675180.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Parasites are far more common than most people realize, yet their symptoms are often subtle and easily misinterpreted as ordinary digestive issues, stress-related changes, or nutritional problems. When we talk about “parasites” in this context, we are mainly referring to intestinal parasites; organisms that live inside the digestive tract. Some parasites feed on nutrients, others irritate the intestinal lining, and some feed on blood and can cause anemia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="3"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="5"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Because these infections vary widely in severity, the symptoms they cause can be equally diverse and often nonspecific. Still, certain patterns have stronger scientific backing. In a recent &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/shorts/8AjFD2mM9mc" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;video&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, popular health educator Dr. Eric Berg, shared 5 symptoms that may signal the presence of parasites in the body, and two natural remedies that can help get rid of them. Below we explore. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="12"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="lOvcW vdo_embedd"&gt;&lt;div class="k7lcu"&gt;&lt;p class="efT4r"&gt;How Lifestyle Choices Can Increase Your Risk of Stomach Cancer&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="14"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;How dangerous are parasites&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="16"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="17"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://medlineplus.gov/ency/article/000629.htm" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;Parasite infections &lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;occur when parasites enter the body and begin living, reproducing, or feeding inside you. This usually happens through contaminated food, water, soil, insect bites, poor hygiene, or contact with infected animals/humans. Parasitic infections are not trivial; they can translate into serious health burdens, especially if recurrent or untreated. Parasites can cause damage in multiple ways:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="20"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some physically attach to the intestinal wall (or other organs), feed on blood or nutrients, and thereby deprive the host of essential nutrients. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="23"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some disturb the&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/books/NBK8191/" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt; intestinal lining&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; and interfere with absorption of nutrients, resulting in malnutrition even if diet is adequate. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="27"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chronic infections can trigger inflammation (in gut, liver, bladder, or other organs), cause tissue damage (e.g., scarring, fibrosis, cyst formation), or even lead parasites to migrate to and damage distant organs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="29"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;In heavy or uncontrolled infestations, especially in people with weak immunity, parasites can cause life‑threatening complications.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="32"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Five warning signs you may have parasites&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="34"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="35"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="37"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;1. Unexplained sugar cravings&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="39"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to Dr. Berg, unexplained sugar cravings, especially for dairy, is a sign of parasites. Dr. Berg adds, “Parasites love sugar, especially milk sugar. If you crave that, you could have parasites.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="41"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;2. Grinding teeth at night&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="43"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Night-time teeth grinding may also be connected to parasitic stress on the nervous system.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="45"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Parasites can release toxins that irritate the gut–brain axis, triggering restlessness, tension, and involuntary muscle activity during sleep.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="48"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;3. Itchy skin at night (especially in private parts) &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="50"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Night-time itching around the anal or genital area is one of the classic signs of parasites such as pinworms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="52"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Parasites tend to be more active at night, which is why symptoms often intensify when you lie down to sleep.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="54"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;4. Extreme bloating after eating- despite what you eat&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="56"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you experience constant bloating or gas regardless of the meal, parasites may be interfering with digestion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="58"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many of them reside in the small intestine, just below the stomach, where they:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="60"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;- ferment food, producing gas&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="62"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;- cause inflammation&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="64"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;- steal essential nutrients&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="66"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;This can leave you feeling overfull, heavy, or distended after even small meals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="69"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;5. Iron deficient anemia&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="71"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Certain parasites feed directly on blood or damage the intestinal lining, reducing iron absorption.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="73"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Over time, this can lead to:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="75"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;- chronic fatigue&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="77"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;- pale skin&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="79"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;- weakness&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="81"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;- low stamina&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="83"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr. Berg emphasizes that parasites can literally “steal your iron,” causing anemia in otherwise healthy individuals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="85"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;How parasites are actually diagnosed&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="87"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Parasitic infections are best confirmed through laboratory testing, since symptoms alone can be misleading and often overlap with other digestive or nutritional problems. The most common method is a stool examination, where a lab looks for parasite eggs, larvae, or cysts under a microscope. In many modern labs, more advanced stool antigen tests and PCR panels are used to detect parasites with higher accuracy. These diagnostic methods allow doctors to pinpoint the exact parasite and offer appropriate treatment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="89"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="em" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Disclaimer: This article is for informational purposes only and does not substitute for professional medical advice. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="91"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 16:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi-gFBVV95cUxPdVBxZ3NVZkhlS0U2M193UVMyZm95NVhCVk5NSzMwYTgzSndYbHJkdVBFWFJOU0tyd1hSN0Zpa3dYRjFTMDRFbnhIRXlpLWYzTkJ4OWEwRWZTX3VwUlo3YzUwYzc3c25DS015QUI0WW8zMEtVSWNHLTNnaDdEQklmVmJXdXozc2NPNndUSEhFb3g3T1ZYWEQ1YjdTMWpKcVBhTllmalhadk1aaWs4T0RFMFN3R2dDWUJ2aWVKQlYwWUYyM3VPckVzb2ltS2JlSk9UaDFFdkI5MnYzZmVwc1pmZ24tcVhyVGJhcF9XMUNBQTliMkhMOFV6Q2pR</guid></item><item><title>根据专家的说法，最佳的镁睡眠类型- GQ</title><link>https://www.gq.com/story/whats-the-best-type-of-magnesium-for-recovery-and-sleep-1</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="body__inner-container"&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you go hard at the gym, it’s important not to overlook recovery. &lt;a href="https://www.gq.com/story/flexibility-longevity-1"&gt;Stretching&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.gq.com/story/how-to-use-a-foam-roller"&gt;foam rolling&lt;/a&gt;, and hanging out in the &lt;a href="https://www.gq.com/story/sauna-benefits"&gt;sauna&lt;/a&gt; can all help reduce muscle soreness. You’ve probably heard rumblings about &lt;a href="https://www.gq.com/story/magnesium-nutrient-supplements-3"&gt;magnesium supplements&lt;/a&gt; helping too. Not only does the micronutrient play a crucial role in muscle function, but it also supports sleep—another key for crushing your workouts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But shopping for the right &lt;a href="https://www.gq.com/story/best-magnesium-supplements" target="_blank"&gt;magnesium product&lt;/a&gt; specifically for workout recovery is tricky. Not only are there different types of magnesium, but there are also different modalities. Beyond capsule supplements, different topical magnesium products, including oils, lotions, and sprays &lt;a href="https://www.latimes.com/lifestyle/story/2024-03-06/magnesium-supplement-benefits-mocktail-foot-spray"&gt;have multiplied&lt;/a&gt; in the marketplace recently.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But which is best to help you recover from a workout and, ideally, get a good night’s sleep? We talked to a doctor, pharmacist, and dietitian who have all studied the mineral to get advice on which products work best.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What exactly does magnesium do?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you’re going to spend money on a nutritional supplement, it helps to have a basic understanding of how it works. Brace yourself: This micronutrient does a lot.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Container-VgtPr ekoLDG"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Here’s a run-down of magnesium’s job description, according to &lt;a data-offer-url="https://www.hnfe.vt.edu/people/faculty/stella-volpe.html" class="external-link" data-event-click='{"element":"ExternalLink","outgoingURL":"https://www.hnfe.vt.edu/people/faculty/stella-volpe.html"}' href="https://www.hnfe.vt.edu/people/faculty/stella-volpe.html" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Stella Volpe, PhD, RDN,&lt;/a&gt; a registered dietitian and professor at Virginia Tech: It helps make protein, supports bone health by activating vitamin D (crucial for calcium absorption), and regulates blood sugar concentrations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That’s not even getting into how it supports muscle recovery and sleep. Sports medicine doctor and &lt;a data-offer-url="https://us.sunrider.com/" class="external-link" data-event-click='{"element":"ExternalLink","outgoingURL":"https://us.sunrider.com/"}' href="https://us.sunrider.com/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Sunrider International&lt;/a&gt; chief medical advisor &lt;a data-offer-url="https://www.linkedin.com/in/reuben-chen-0596233a/" class="external-link" data-event-click='{"element":"ExternalLink","outgoingURL":"https://www.linkedin.com/in/reuben-chen-0596233a/"}' href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/reuben-chen-0596233a/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Reuben Chen, MD&lt;/a&gt;, explains that magnesium supports workout recovery by relaxing the muscles, reducing post-exercise cramping, and restoring energy at the cellular level.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Magnesium also helps ease soreness, while keeping the nervous system calm and balanced, allowing your body to recover faster,” he says. Dr. Volpe adds to this, saying that magnesium helps reduce inflammation—another way it supports workout recovery.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As for sleep, Dr. Chen explains that magnesium calms the nervous system, priming the body for rest. “It also helps regulate melatonin, the hormone that guides our sleep-wake cycles, making it easier to fall asleep and stay asleep,” he adds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s important to note: all the experts we talked to said that most people get all the magnesium they need through their daily diet. “Generally speaking, people are not deficient in magnesium if they are eating a balanced diet,” says &lt;a data-offer-url="https://www.faculty.uci.edu/profile/?facultyId=6689" class="external-link" data-event-click='{"element":"ExternalLink","outgoingURL":"https://www.faculty.uci.edu/profile/?facultyId=6689"}' href="https://www.faculty.uci.edu/profile/?facultyId=6689" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Alexandre Chan, PharmD, MPH&lt;/a&gt;, a professor of clinical pharmacy at UC Irvine. Especially if you eat a primarily &lt;a href="https://www.gq.com/story/real-life-diet-simon-hill"&gt;plant-based diet&lt;/a&gt;, you’re likely getting enough. &lt;a href="https://ods.od.nih.gov/factsheets/Magnesium-HealthProfessional/"&gt;Some top food sources of magnesium&lt;/a&gt; include almonds, spinach, cashews, black beans, rice, potatoes, oatmeal, and salmon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>GQ</author><pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 16:28:18 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiigFBVV95cUxOcFN1cWJ5WmpaWHZTXzVYYkM4UUhjb0oxZ183TEdrRUo0MUE5SDZHWDBmRG1rcExJNml0c0JVWGdUYTdWNVFLUjlwZzkzVGJfY04xOFNmVDBxR0VEdS1nanIxcFZQR0lodXFic3BHSEJydW1NWGhUazREaEFuNEt2WTVZZUJKNXRWZlE</guid></item><item><title>这种常见的零食在16周的试验中增强了记忆力和脑血管功能- PsyPost</title><link>https://www.psypost.org/this-common-snack-enhanced-memory-and-brain-vascular-function-in-a-16-week-trial/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="content-inner "&gt;&lt;p&gt;A new study in &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.clnu.2025.10.020" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Clinical Nutrition&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; provides evidence that the regular consumption of unsalted, skin-roasted peanuts may enhance brain vascular function and memory in older adults. The research indicates that eating a moderate daily amount of peanuts improves blood flow to specific regions of the brain and aids in the retention of verbal information.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As individuals age, the vascular system in the brain often undergoes changes that can reduce the efficiency of blood flow. This reduction in cerebral blood flow is a known physiological marker associated with cognitive decline and neurodegenerative conditions such as dementia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Because the delivery of oxygen and nutrients is vital for maintaining neuronal health, researchers have focused on identifying modifiable lifestyle factors that can support vascular function. Diet is considered a significant factor in this regard.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While peanuts are botanically classified as legumes rather than tree nuts, they share a comparable nutritional profile. They are dense in protein, unsaturated fatty acids, and fiber. The researchers, led by Peter J. Joris and Lucia Kerkhof, initiated this study to investigate whether peanuts specifically could offer neuroprotective benefits similar to those observed with tree nuts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A primary motivation for the trial was the high content of L-arginine found in peanuts. L-arginine is an amino acid that serves as a precursor for the synthesis of nitric oxide, a molecule essential for relaxing blood vessels and regulating blood flow.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Additionally, the study focused on skin-roasted peanuts because the peanut skin is rich in bioactive compounds, including polyphenols like resveratrol, which have antioxidant properties that may further support vascular health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The number of people who suffer from age-related cognitive decline or are diagnosed with dementia is increasing rapidly. Currently, dementia is ranked as the 7th leading cause of death worldwide according to the World Health Organization,” said Joris, an associate professor at the Institute of Nutrition and Translational Research in Metabolism (NUTRIM) at Maastricht University.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“As researchers studying nutrition and brain health, we are very interested in how the food we consume can support healthy aging. Peanuts are widely consumed, affordable, and nutrient-dense, yet relatively little was known about their specific effects on the brain.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Earlier work from our group showed that mixed nuts can improve memory and blood flow in the brain in older adults. Adequate blood flow in the brain is important for the delivery of oxygen and nutrients to the brain cells. Without enough oxygen and nutrients, the highly metabolically active brain cannot function properly, and key functions like memory can be affected.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“In this study, we sought to determine whether peanuts, which are botanically classified as legumes rather than nuts, also exert beneficial effects on brain health,” Joris explained.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To test the effects of peanut consumption, the investigators designed a randomized, single-blind, controlled crossover trial. This study design allowed each participant to serve as their own control, reducing variability caused by individual differences.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The research team recruited 31 healthy older adults ranging in age from 60 to 75 years. The participants included both men and women with body mass indexes between 20 and 35 kg/m ². Individuals were excluded if they had a history of cardiovascular disease, diabetes, peanut allergies, or if they were current smokers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study consisted of two 16-week periods separated by an eight-week washout phase. During the intervention period, participants consumed 60 grams of unsalted, skin-roasted peanuts daily. This portion size is approximately equivalent to two servings or two handfuls.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The peanuts were of the runner variety and were eaten with the skins intact. Participants were instructed to incorporate the peanuts into their regular diet but were not permitted to heat or crush them, as this might alter their nutritional properties. During the control period, participants refrained from eating peanuts and avoided other nut-based products to ensure a clear comparison.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The primary measure for the study was cerebral blood flow, assessed using a non-invasive imaging technique called pseudo-continuous arterial spin labeling magnetic resonance imaging. This advanced method allows researchers to quantify the amount of blood reaching brain tissue without the use of radiation or contrast dyes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Secondary outcomes included cognitive performance, which was evaluated using the Cambridge Neuropsychological Test Automated Battery, a series of computerized tests designed to measure memory, psychomotor speed, and executive function. The researchers also monitored blood pressure and gathered data on dietary intake through food frequency questionnaires.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The imaging results revealed a statistically significant improvement in brain vascular responsiveness following the peanut intervention. Global cerebral blood flow increased by 3.6 percent compared to the control period.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When the analysis focused specifically on gray matter, which contains the cell bodies of the brain’s neurons, the increase in blood flow was 4.5 percent. The researchers observed regional improvements as well. Blood flow increased by 6.6 percent in the frontal lobes and 4.9 percent in the temporal lobes. These areas of the brain are intimately involved in processing memories, language, and executive control.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“We were intrigued to see improvements not only in specific brain regions, but also at the whole-brain level,” Joris told PsyPost. “That indicates a more widespread effect on brain vascular function than what we observed in earlier studies.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In parallel with the physiological changes, the researchers identified improvements in cognitive function. Participants demonstrated a 5.8 percent increase in verbal memory performance. This was measured by a delayed recall task where participants were asked to identify words they had seen on a list twenty minutes earlier. Those who had consumed the peanuts were able to correctly recognize more words than they did during the control period.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Our results suggest that eating unsalted, skin-roasted peanuts every day can support brain health as we age,” Joris said. “After 16 weeks, participants showed better brain blood flow and improved memory.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While memory improved, the study did not find significant changes in executive function or psychomotor speed. There was a slight increase in reaction latency during one of the multitasking tests, which the authors suggest might reflect a trade-off where participants prioritized accuracy over speed, although this particular finding requires further verification.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Beyond brain health, the intervention appeared to benefit cardiovascular metrics. Systolic blood pressure, the top number in a blood pressure reading, decreased by an average of 5 mmHg during the peanut consumption phase. Pulse pressure, which represents the difference between systolic and diastolic blood pressure, decreased by 4 mmHg. These reductions are relevant for older adults, as elevated blood pressure is a risk factor for both cardiovascular disease and cognitive impairment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dietary analysis confirmed that during the peanut intervention, participants had higher intakes of total fat, monounsaturated fatty acids, and fiber, while their carbohydrate intake was lower.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Despite the addition of approximately 340 calories per day from the peanuts, body weight remained generally stable across the study population, though there was a minor interaction effect depending on the order in which the participants completed the intervention and control phases. This suggests that participants may have naturally adjusted their intake of other foods to compensate for the added peanuts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study has several limitations that provide context for the findings. Due to the nature of the dietary intervention, it was not possible to blind the participants to the fact that they were eating peanuts. This awareness could potentially influence their behavior or self-reported data, although the researchers analyzing the MRI and cognitive data remained blinded to the treatment conditions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Additionally, while the results show a clear association between peanut consumption and improved vascular function, the specific biological mechanism remains to be fully elucidated. It is not yet known if the effects are driven primarily by L-arginine, the phenolic compounds in the skins, the fatty acid profile, or a synergistic combination of these nutrients.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The research was funded by The Peanut Institute Foundation. The authors state that the funding body had no role in the design of the study, the collection and analysis of data, or the decision to publish the results. The authors declared no conflicts of interest.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Future research directions include investigating whether different forms of peanut products offer similar benefits. The investigators also aim to explore the dose-response relationship to determine if smaller amounts of peanuts could yield comparable results.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“We would like to examine whether different peanut preparations, such as peanut butter, produce similar effects,” Joris said. “In addition, we seek to clarify which peanut components may underlie the observed benefits. To this end, we are now conducting a study assessing the effects of protein on the same outcomes, given that peanuts are rich in protein.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“One important point is that the peanuts were unsalted and skin-roasted,” the researcher added. “The skin contains many antioxidants and fibre that may contribute to the beneficial effects.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study, “&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.clnu.2025.10.020" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Longer-term skin-roasted peanut consumption improves brain vascular function and memory: A randomized, single-blind, controlled crossover trial in healthy older adults&lt;/a&gt;,” was authored by Lucia Kerkhof, Ronald P. Mensink, Jogchum Plat, Kevin M. R. Nijssen, and Peter J. Joris.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>PsyPost</author><pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 15:43:56 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiqAFBVV95cUxOUHFUSlVYMFEycUk0dlBrb0VFYmNFd2RPTXBWZlc3Z2pVSzVPUWwwLUdrYVJ3REUtV19Nc21hQ0l3X2NTaS1PR0k2cHR6MnZYNUlqa01XOFl6WXFRQjJqNmJiaTVRS2tpSDZaTXF4OU1OQlVaN0JpZEY0dVR1cGl3OWVIcHRaYXdPX2RNMnZMNzN2YkRMY0RxaG01ZFhaS0hGYWdrZnNWOFA</guid></item><item><title>疾病预防控制中心的破坏-黑客新闻</title><link>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=46097102</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Hacker News</author><pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 15:33:20 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiWEFVX3lxTFAxWmNxRGRLeGN0bFVrME5GQmtSVmE1cmhzWW1ZMW1KTi1hZExrU0trY0FoUmVXUzFUOFpTNHR6XzJUUDlhQV9XS0d2QklLTDhqWDZoZ0RUaks</guid></item><item><title>肿瘤学家揭示了4种最令人怀念的癌症迹象-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/oncologist-reveals-4-surprising-signs-of-cancer-that-most-miss/articleshow/125675080.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;div class="MwN2O"&gt;&lt;div class="vdo_embedd"&gt; &lt;div class="T22zO"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cancer is one disease that springs up as one of the most unwelcomed surprises in one's life. From unexpected symptoms to unending treatment, the disease wreaks a whole lot of havoc on a person's life and makes the day-to-day routine entirely tiring. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="3"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to the &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cancer.gov/about-cancer/understanding/statistics" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="_blank" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;National Cancer Institute&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, in 2025 an estimated 2,041,910 new cases of cancer will be diagnosed in the US. While cancers do have certain early symptoms, depending on their type and location there can be some surprising symptoms as well. In a conversation with The Washington Post, Mikkael A. Sekeres, MD, chief of the division of haematology and professor of medicine at the Sylvester Comprehensive Cancer Center, University of Miami, shared four symptoms that are mostly unknown to people. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="10"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="lOvcW vdo_embedd"&gt;&lt;div class="k7lcu"&gt;&lt;p class="efT4r"&gt;Cancer is curable if detected early: Signs to pay attention to&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="12"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="13"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Pain after drinking alcohol&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many people experience pain in the lower chest or abdomen after drinking alcohol. This can be due to inflammation of the oesophagus or stomach, conditions such as esophagitis or gastritis which can be relieved through antacids or proton pump inhibitors. However, consistent pain in a particular area of the body such as a lymph node or lower back, after ingesting alcohol can be a sign of cancer. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="15"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The doctor shared the case of a patient who experienced chest pain for a day or two every time she drank a glass of wine. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A CT scan of her chest revealed a large mass in her lungs and she was later diagnosed with Hodgkin lymphoma. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="19"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;A study published in the &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://acsjournals.onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/pdf/10.1002/1097-0142(197602)37:2%3C895::AID-CNCR2820370239%3E3.0.CO;2-1" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="_blank" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;American Cancer Society Journal&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, found that at least 5 % people experiencing the symptom were diagnosed with Hodgkin lymphoma. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="23"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="24"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Broken bone with little trauma&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bone density and strength decline with age. This is why there are approximately 2 million osteoporosis-related fractures every year in the US. However, a broken bone with little trauma is rare, especially in young adults. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="27"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Such fractures in some cases can indicate underlying cancer. It begins in the bones and can weaken the bone's strength, leading to "pathologic" fractures. About 8% of people with cancer in the bone sustain a pathologic fracture. These types of broken bones are 500 times more likely to occur due to cancer spreading to the bone. These might have originated in the breast, lung, thyroid, kidney and prostate. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="29"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="30"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Extremely high calcium levels&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Numerous conditions can cause high calcium levels, such as abnormalities in the parathyroid gland, hyperthyroidism or even some medications. However, in a 2014 study published in the &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC4183854/" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="_blank" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;British Journal of Cancer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, over 50,000 people with elevated calcium levels had more than twice the risk of being diagnosed with cancer the following year. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="35"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;In this case, people can experience normal symptoms that arrive with high calcium levels such as pain from kidney stones and in skeletal bones, nausea, constipation, mood changes, and changed cognitive function. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="37"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The most common cancers caused by high calcium are certain types of lung cancer, breast, kidney, bladder, ovarian, lymphoma and multiple myeloma, as per the doctor. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="39"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="40"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Painful, swollen breasts or nipple discharge&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mastitis is a benign condition that can cause painful, swollen or itchy breasts and it's most common in people who are breastfeeding. However, for those who are not breastfeeding, this can be a sign of inflammatory breast cancer, which accounts for 2-4% of the cases in the US. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="44"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The breast skin changes and resembles the pitted surface of an orange peel. This is when visiting a doctor is a must. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="46"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most cases of nipple discharge are also benign and only 2-15% were found to have an underlying breast cancer. The discharge is more likely to be caused by cancer when it occurs in only one breast, is intermittent and persists over time. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="49"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Keep in mind that these symptoms are not extremely common but are signs of cancer in rare cases. Thus, visiting a professional if you experience them is a must. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="51"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Note: &lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The information provided in this article is for educational purposes only and is not intended as medical advice. Always consult with a qualified healthcare professional before starting any new medication or treatment and before changing your diet or supplement regimen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="54"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 15:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi9AFBVV95cUxNclhvVjhZNVJEcUp6eU5nRDNOZWJZYkJuVDk0dk9nY0VGRzZJLXFFMzBfYTlxWkZwbXNfczlzRUZ1dmRRLVBmeVBWUU9CMzYwU0pVVWtKVFAtb0RlSFZTQ29mWkttMUNSMWdmMFBIQlFFTC1vLUUxTDhsb0RIUEQ2a29BbHcwbG5QSTNEVWx6UVlaeVNNV2JWLUQzb1M2YndUdE1jdXlyQmpzZnpCT2d0UzVsUkNSZEtDUFJGbTVGUDRmTjJKZGdDeG5DRE1rX2VnWk02YXVNRHQyNDhlUUljX3hFdFZUdUdOS1pCSnlxY3lKSGo10gH6AUFVX3lxTE9la1VzUmFqTlZ0dU1NdHRxbUV2Z3FCSVhJM2F2YlNHbTZ0alZNRjdaUmZfSElfNkFBUHdsSkpHUDlaS2Q3U24yR2dYdkx6Z1Q0VHN1RHBoR1BORXlqVG5GSGVRN1ZUSG1vbFdqMFZaLTJaYkVFLXJnNXFnN1czWlNvWTJjSjYyYVN2NFZGaGlETThIR29xLWZjZFRFcDZ5OGRpMGF2TFRyV3R1RGhldjhsZGNuM2kyV1RtY1N1QjZqT0JybFJ3Vy1Wd3V1OGdrQUM1UDJmcVJBMjJBZlNlTExMU0ZjRURLeC1uNjZPa0hIeUVXcUozZFFzMVE</guid></item><item><title>可以默默增加心力衰竭风险的5种常见假日习惯-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/5-common-holiday-habits-that-can-silently-increase-your-risk-of-heart-failure/articleshow/125668291.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;p&gt;The holiday season is a time for family, festivities, and indulgent meals, but for people with heart conditions, it can also bring hidden risks that often go unnoticed. Cardiologist &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/reel/DRj-49lALbj/?utm_source=ig_web_copy_link&amp;amp;igsh=NTc4MTIwNjQ2YQ==" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;Dr Dmitry Yaranov recently shared on Instagram&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; that small changes in daily routines during holidays, such as altered sleep patterns, heavier meals, alcohol consumption, travel stress, and emotional excitement, can quietly trigger heart failure flare-ups. Many patients experience preventable complications during festive periods simply because they overlook subtle warning signs or dismiss early symptoms. Dr Yaranov emphasises that being mindful of your body, recognising early changes, and taking prompt action can help prevent serious issues. With the right awareness and precautions, it is possible to enjoy celebrations safely without compromising heart health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="8"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="9"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;5 ways typical &lt;keyword id="22125639" type="General" weightage="20" keywordseo="holiday-habits" source="keywords"&gt;holiday habits&lt;/keyword&gt; may put your heart at risk&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="10"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="11"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Hidden sodium in festive meals&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="12"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;High sodium intake is one of the most common holiday triggers for heart issues. Traditional holiday dishes such as stuffing, gravy, ham, canned broths, and many restaurant-prepared foods contain large amounts of salt. Sodium causes the body to retain fluid, which increases blood volume and places extra stress on the heart. Even one particularly salty meal can lead to overnight fluid accumulation, resulting in swelling, breathlessness, or sudden weight gain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; For individuals with heart failure, carefully monitoring salt intake and reading labels for hidden sodium is essential. Moderation doesn’t mean missing out entirely; it means making smarter choices like limiting processed foods or choosing lower-salt alternatives.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="16"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="18"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="19"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Breathing changes after meals&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="20"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another important early warning sign is a change in breathing patterns following large meals. When the stomach is full, the increased venous return sends more blood to the heart, forcing it to work harder. Dr Yaranov notes that new shortness of breath, difficulty lying flat, or waking up feeling breathless after a meal can indicate fluid retention. These symptoms should not be ignored as they can precede more serious heart complications. Paying attention to breathing changes, eating smaller portions, and allowing the body time to digest before lying down can help reduce unnecessary stress on the heart.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="25"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="26"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Alcohol can worsen heart health&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="27"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alcohol consumption is often part of holiday celebrations, but even small amounts can be risky for people with heart failure. Alcohol can lower blood pressure, trigger arrhythmias, and interact with medications such as diuretics, blood pressure drugs, and heart rhythm medications. Dr Yaranov warns that even modest alcohol intake can cause sudden complications in patients taking these medications. For those with heart failure, the safest approach is to avoid alcohol altogether during holiday festivities. Choosing non-alcoholic alternatives or enjoying festive drinks in moderation while monitoring for any symptoms can make a meaningful difference in heart safety.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="33"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="34"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Fatigue shouldn’t be ignored&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="35"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The holidays often involve late nights, high activity levels, and emotional excitement, all of which can contribute to fatigue. While it is normal to feel tired occasionally, unusual or excessive tiredness may be an early sign that the heart is struggling to cope with additional stress. Dr Yaranov emphasises that persistent fatigue should never be dismissed, especially if it is accompanied by other symptoms like swelling or shortness of breath. Prioritising rest, pacing activities, and maintaining a consistent sleep routine are important strategies to help the heart handle holiday pressures without being overworked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="39"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="40"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Swelling and rapid weight gain&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="41"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sudden swelling or rapid weight gain is a clear indicator that fluid is building up in the body, a common problem in heart failure. Dr Yaranov explains that a 2–3 pound increase in weight overnight or new swelling in the ankles, hands, or abdomen is usually a red flag. These changes rarely occur from a single heavy meal; they often reflect underlying heart stress or fluid retention. Monitoring weight daily and checking for swelling can help catch early signs of decompensation. Acting promptly by contacting a doctor or adjusting medications under medical guidance can prevent serious complications.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="46"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Despite the risks, Dr Yaranov reassures patients that it is possible to enjoy the holidays safely. The key is awareness, moderation, and timely action. He advises taking medications as prescribed, monitoring for subtle warning signs, and seeking medical attention immediately if unusual symptoms appear. “You can absolutely enjoy Thanksgiving with your family. Just stay aware of how you feel, know your limits, and take symptoms seriously,” he says. By staying mindful of hidden sodium, changes in breathing, alcohol intake, fatigue, and sudden swelling, those with heart concerns can celebrate the season without compromising their health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="49"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="em" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Disclaimer: This content is intended purely for informational use and is not a substitute for professional medical, nutritional or scientific advice. Always seek support from certified professionals for personalised recommendations.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="51"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="52"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="53"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Also Read: &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/greasy-hair-even-after-washing-causes-prevention-tips-and-home-remedies-for-oily-scalp/articleshow/125637706.cms" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;Greasy hair even after washing: Causes, prevention tips, and home remedies for oily scalp&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 14:40:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiAJBVV95cUxOb2FqanpaLVkxZWNsakcwaldPLWVTSDY1d0dHT2x2LWZZTnhnd3o2M0R2aktQTDFKZXJSN3dGMGRzVFBraGhITUxLTXEtSThHa2JJd1VUYjNiZGxUSW5KTG5DOXpoazJJd3UzdWl3aXdWeWlhZmVKVTFZV1lvVFlKZmtDRGdIVElqYWtELWFkd3p4QWpzSXA2Z3BaVFBoMVMtdVI1Y1VMSVFoRjNuYVVNY1Q1dHNyR0wtdDdXb2tQTmRGWDJrWndYRXR5RFZ5VmtBM2dvNTZZSzhOU0VQdWcyWHJITlhqZjY1OU1feC01UUhjQVliYTE0WUJOZmZQVXdDOUUtLUtMS1PSAY4CQVVfeXFMTW1QZXk5QU1kTjUtOElCVjZDd3d5MS1mOGNMVjd0X0ZqN0cxeDN1eTM1QzZwVTV4aS1sM1gzOEJPNm9neENFZXFMWDdSckFMUnVJYV9vM0t3bHF1M0JmLTVtRUhTaTJIT1JJMy1YN1V3THFONHlQc3EyY01jTm4teHBtWmZ6N2wyZkFEUDJNcGZMMHRNT25CdV9OdUVnRjM3czhsYk9sQUg3U255b3VoTzFiUkZJdU5qdkxXMzlqZnNiV1hlWHliaHdQMTFXTEpwczIwWnhIYnpMdGdRclJVdDhxaFZfdTB3a0lxdi1Vc0JNYi1RYmlXWWxPcENrRm1Mc1lwa1BBWHhybHhKZmxR</guid></item><item><title>针对日常健康问题的4种输水疗法以及如何在家中制作-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/food-news/4-infused-water-remedies-for-everyday-health-issues-and-how-to-make-them-at-home/photostory/125673186.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="COQxt" data-ua-type="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;How to use: Soak 1 tsp fennel seeds in a glass of water, and drink it the next morning.&lt;br&gt;Benefits: It is said to cool the digestive tract, reduce mouth odor by improving the gut fire.&lt;br&gt;What does Ayurveda say: In Ayurveda, their sweet, cooling nature helps reduce excess Pitta in the mouth and gut — a major cause of sour odour, acidity, and heat-related digestion issues. Fennel seeds stimulate gentle digestion, prevent gas and bloating, and reduce the buildup of ama (toxins), which often manifest as unpleasant breath. Also, chewing fennel seeds after meals increases saliva production, cleanses the tongue, and releases essential oils with natural antimicrobial properties that help fight odor-causing bacteria.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 14:31:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi9AFBVV95cUxQRXhzNTJuZ3hwZ0F5YnA0UFNmZUpXU2lQNWU4MHJhNTZpVE9uOWgwcWpFZm41NGM2bkNSQXNDVUJpVXNzb1lPdWlCS0VQZVlHZDE5OFM4S1VRYURmcEV2T2lwOWVuV040VnJSOTFfaFNueG4tM25JRVBES0hwNzVsSThjdGREY08xck1UVVRDWUpTZVMtZ1Z3cHBpSWY4bFFfQUR4Mm1XSkM4T2dNSTZKa0ZvdXdLejlkZDZBcEVvM0hzRFJHVThTcEJubDFoajJLODhWOGtEZVhFOVU0Y1FFWGhxLUEzZTNObGpOMThwd1dvLVFQ0gH8AUFVX3lxTE5YS3FNOWJPUm9sY0FXM3lNLUt0ZE12bGhJX2pveHhwc0FhMzBKQ084UDNlbFFJZDBPZ2g2SFgybEJ5LXFNc2MtM255TzhlekxVdFR1YklLQVlJN0IwTS1ScTBMTGZQWW5OSWpINGFHTXgxYUtTRVU3WHk1OU15VEdvZ1p5YkhWdEd6TlhOdkNWYzhoN2RtWTJ1UHhJV3JVRmxNN0QyY0QwZk9XaFQ1ZW4ySFdoaHRPdElRaGxNanpkRVdFM3VrZURZYk0tZ1ZjTURBY09Oa05kT2p6WnphYWdRaVZKVFp3TjdpNG5xa0hhcktQNkV4YVVCc1FGbg</guid></item><item><title>大麻诱导的“Scromiting”正在上升，研究结果- Gizmodo</title><link>https://gizmodo.com/cannabis-induced-scromiting-is-on-the-rise-study-finds-2000691530</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content prose dark:prose-invert lg:prose-xl prose-science dark:prose-science"&gt;
                &lt;p&gt;As much fun and &lt;a href="https://gizmodo.com/cannabis-can-help-relieve-chronic-low-back-pain-major-trial-finds-2000665517"&gt;helpful&lt;/a&gt; as cannabis can be, every drug has its potential tradeoffs. Case in point, a study out this week finds that more Americans are coming down with a stomach-churning side effect of long-term use.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Researchers at the University of Illinois Chicago examined emergency department visits from across the country. They found evidence that ER visits for cannabinoid hyperemesis syndrome (CHS)—a condition characterized by constant, painful bouts of vomiting—have noticeably risen in the last several years, especially among younger adults. The researchers say that more doctors need to be aware of this debilitating, but ultimately treatable, health problem.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="not-prose my-8 -mx-5 xs:max-w-xs xs:mx-auto"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;“Cannabinoid hyperemesis syndrome is real, and it’s becoming a more routine part of emergency medicine in the U.S.,” lead author James Swartz, a professor at UIC’s Jane Addams College of Social Work, told Gizmodo.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;The scromiting syndrome&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;People with &lt;a href="https://my.clevelandclinic.org/health/diseases/21665-cannabis-hyperemesis-syndrome"&gt;CHS&lt;/a&gt; will experience cyclical periods of intense cramps, nausea, and vomiting. An acute episode can last one to two days, and the experience is often so intolerable that people will scream out in pain as they’re vomiting—a phenomenon that’s been given the charming nickname “&lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC6690288/#:~:text=Young%20people%2C%20typically%20between%20the,to%20the%20term%20%E2%80%9Cscromiting%E2%80%9D."&gt;scromiting&lt;/a&gt;.”&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;p&gt;CHS typically happens in people who have been using cannabis chronically for at least several years. Scientists aren’t sure why it develops, but it might be caused by the overstimulation of native cannabinoid receptors in the gastrointestinal tract. It’s thought to be a rare complication, but recent research has &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S0376871624013437"&gt;suggested&lt;/a&gt; that cases of CHS have been increasing in the U.S. and other places where cannabis legalization has expanded.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="not-prose"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;In this latest study, the researchers analyzed data from a nationwide sample of ER visits in the U.S. between 2016 and 2022. Until recently, doctors couldn’t diagnose CHS as a distinct medical condition for record-keeping and insurance purposes. So the researchers instead looked for diagnoses related to cyclical vomiting syndrome (severe, sudden vomiting that can’t be explained by other known causes) and cannabis use; cases where both diagnoses were present were used as a proxy for CHS.&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;p&gt;During the study period, roughly 100,000 cases of suspected CHS were documented. Prior to the covid-19 pandemic, they found, annual rates of CHS were steady. Starting in 2020, however, suspected cases of CHS seen in the ER surged. And though cases did decline in 2022, they were still above the pre-pandemic baseline. Importantly, cases of cannabis-related health problems in general also rose during that same period, while cases of cyclical vomiting syndrome without any cannabis link did not, further suggesting a real rise in CHS.&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;p&gt;The team’s findings were &lt;a href="https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jamanetworkopen/fullarticle/2841769"&gt;published&lt;/a&gt; Monday in JAMA Network Open.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;figure id="attachment_2000691635" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-2000691635" class="wp-caption alignleft"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-2000691635" src="https://gizmodo.com/app/uploads/2025/11/CHS-chart.jpg" alt="Chs Chart" srcset="https://gizmodo.com/app/uploads/2025/11/CHS-chart.jpg 1325w, https://gizmodo.com/app/uploads/2025/11/CHS-chart-336x161.jpg 336w, https://gizmodo.com/app/uploads/2025/11/CHS-chart-1280x613.jpg 1280w, https://gizmodo.com/app/uploads/2025/11/CHS-chart-768x368.jpg 768w, https://gizmodo.com/app/uploads/2025/11/CHS-chart-672x322.jpg 672w, https://gizmodo.com/app/uploads/2025/11/CHS-chart-960x460.jpg 960w" sizes="(max-width: 639px) 100vw, (max-width: 1023px) calc(100vw - 2rem), (max-width: 1258px) calc((100vw - 3.68rem) * 2 / 3), 800px"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-2000691635" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;The chart shows that the likelihood of CHS among people diagnosed with cannabis-related health problems at the ER rose over time. © Swartz et al./JAMA Network Open&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt; &lt;p&gt;Though this study can’t directly answer why CHS is becoming more common, the timing of this surge indicates that covid-19 probably played a role. At the same time, ongoing factors like the growing legalization of cannabis in the U.S. and perhaps the increased amounts of THC in today’s cannabis strains are also likely important, the researchers say.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;“The COVID-19 pandemic likely catalyzed the rise in CHS through stress, isolation, and increased cannabis use,” the authors wrote. “After peaking in 2021, CHS incidence declined but plateaued above prepandemic levels, suggesting sustained structural or clinical drivers.”&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;h2&gt;How to stay safe from CHS&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;CHS is a horrific experience, but it’s one that we know how to effectively manage and treat.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;For some reason, hot baths and showers can temporarily relieve an acute episode. The only way to truly keep it from happening, though, is to stop using cannabis altogether. It might take weeks, but the symptoms will eventually stop.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;And while the rate of CHS may be climbing, it’s still a relatively rare side effect, the authors say.&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;p&gt;“Our findings shouldn’t be interpreted as a reason to panic, but they do reinforce that cannabis is not risk-free, especially at higher doses and with long-term, heavy use,” Swartz said.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p class="not-prose"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Earlier this year, CHS was &lt;a href="https://adai.uw.edu/icd-10-code-chs/"&gt;officially added&lt;/a&gt; to the latest edition of the International Classification of Diseases (ICD), the codebook that’s used worldwide for diagnostic and billing purposes. So it’s now much easier for doctors to diagnose the condition and for researchers to track its prevalence. That said, doctors and hospitals will still need to know that CHS exists in order to make a timely diagnosis, the study authors say.&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;p&gt;“Given frequent misdiagnosis and costly, unnecessary testing, greater clinical awareness is needed,” the authors wrote. They also argue that more research is needed to figure out the exact causes of CHS and why only some long-term users develop it.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Days like these, I’m glad that I only occasionally indulge in the &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Sticky_icky"&gt;sticky icky.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;      &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Gizmodo</author><pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 14:00:55 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijgFBVV95cUxOWU1GbHFURmJzNDlreV9OZDBDdVJxTDJQb1JoQklZSGpJcHdudER3LW9YdWJicm5SUTZERnRweVB1RVFnMzlvSE1VVjZwM0YwRUFJbFVzbGRPNEl0ak1sUmRzVVFDTTJUSEJDVXdPUnRpMHRSRUxQMmtfNmgtTC0yTS1BbFdkeWpuY184NjZR</guid></item><item><title>科学家发现流行的糖尿病药物在令人惊讶的研究中影响大脑-预防</title><link>https://www.prevention.com/health/health-conditions/a69545377/metformin-brain-impact-study/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div data-journey-body="standard-article" class="article-body-content article-body standard-body-content css-n3hm4j et2g3wt7"&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="0" class="css-6wxqfj emevuu60"&gt;With buzzy medications like &lt;a href="https://www.prevention.com/food-nutrition/a64501989/ozempic-reshapes-the-food-people-eat-study/" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.prevention.com/food-nutrition/a64501989/ozempic-reshapes-the-food-people-eat-study/" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="Ozempic" data-node-id="0.1" class="body-link css-inlxvj emevuu60"&gt;Ozempic&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.prevention.com/health/health-conditions/a45250651/mounjaro-vs-ozempic/" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.prevention.com/health/health-conditions/a45250651/mounjaro-vs-ozempic/" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="Mounjaro" data-node-id="0.3" class="body-link css-inlxvj emevuu60"&gt;Mounjaro&lt;/a&gt; making headlines for blood sugar management, it’s easy to forget that some medications have been helping patients with &lt;a href="https://www.prevention.com/diabetes/" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.prevention.com/diabetes/" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="type 2 diabetes" data-node-id="0.5" class="body-link css-inlxvj emevuu60"&gt;type 2 diabetes&lt;/a&gt; for decades. Metformin is a popular one. But while this medication has been around for more than 60 years, scientists are uncovering what it does to the brain. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="1" class="css-6wxqfj emevuu60"&gt;New research published in the journal &lt;em data-node-id="1.1"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.science.org/doi/10.1126/sciadv.adu3700" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.science.org/doi/10.1126/sciadv.adu3700" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="Science Advances" data-node-id="1.1.0" class="body-link css-inlxvj emevuu60"&gt;Science Advances&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/em&gt;identifies a brain pathway that metformin seems to work through (along with the impact it has on other areas of the body). It’s been generally accepted that metformin lowers blood sugar by reducing how much glucose the liver puts out, but this study found that a lot of that glucose regulation seems to happen in the brain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="2" class="body-tip css-19jy3s emevuu60"&gt;&lt;strong data-node-id="2.0"&gt;Meet the experts&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;a href="https://rwjmg.rwjms.rutgers.edu/doctor_page.php?phys_id=115212" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://rwjmg.rwjms.rutgers.edu/doctor_page.php?phys_id=115212" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="Christoph Buettner, M.D., Ph.D." data-node-id="2.2" class="body-link css-inlxvj emevuu60"&gt;Christoph Buettner, M.D., Ph.D.&lt;/a&gt;, chief of the division of endocrinology at Rutgers Robert Wood Johnson Medical School; &lt;a href="https://www.medstarhealth.org/doctors/kelly-krisna-johnson-arbor-md" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.medstarhealth.org/doctors/kelly-krisna-johnson-arbor-md" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="Kelly Johnson-Arbor, M.D." data-node-id="2.4" class="body-link css-inlxvj emevuu60"&gt;Kelly Johnson-Arbor, M.D.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.medstarhealth.org/doctors/kelly-krisna-johnson-arbor-md" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.medstarhealth.org/doctors/kelly-krisna-johnson-arbor-md" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="," data-node-id="2.5" class="body-link css-inlxvj emevuu60"&gt;,&lt;/a&gt; a toxicologist at MedStar Health; &lt;a href="https://phmtox.msu.edu/people/alanjami" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://phmtox.msu.edu/people/alanjami" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="Jamie K. Alan, Ph.D.," data-node-id="2.7" class="body-link css-inlxvj emevuu60"&gt;Jamie K. Alan, Ph.D.,&lt;/a&gt; an associate professor of pharmacology and toxicology at Michigan State University&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="4" class="css-6wxqfj emevuu60"&gt;In a previous mouse study, the same research team found a protein in the brain called Rap1, which impacted how glucose is broken down in the body. During that study, the researchers found that metformin traveled to an area of the brain called the ventromedial hypothalamus, where it essentially turned off Rap1. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="5" class="css-6wxqfj emevuu60"&gt;The researchers then bred mice that didn’t have Rap1 and found that metformin had no impact on their blood sugar management, even though other medications did. Overall, the findings suggest that metformin has a big impact on the brain. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="6" class="css-6wxqfj emevuu60"&gt;But why does this matter? Here’s what doctors want you to know.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="what-is-metformin" data-node-id="7" class="body-h2 css-ne8qws emevuu60"&gt;&lt;strong data-node-id="7.0"&gt;What is metformin?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="8" class="css-6wxqfj emevuu60"&gt;Metformin is an oral medication in a class of drugs called biguanides that is commonly used to treat type 2 diabetes, according to the &lt;a href="https://medlineplus.gov/druginfo/meds/a696005.html" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://medlineplus.gov/druginfo/meds/a696005.html" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="U.S. National Library of Medicine" data-node-id="8.1" class="body-link css-inlxvj emevuu60"&gt;U.S. National Library of Medicine&lt;/a&gt;. The medication is designed to help control the amount of glucose (or sugar) in the blood. “Metformin has been used for decades to treat diabetes, although there has been extensive research on its use in other conditions like cancer and PCOS,” says &lt;a href="https://phmtox.msu.edu/people/alanjami" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://phmtox.msu.edu/people/alanjami" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="Jamie K. Alan, Ph.D.," data-node-id="8.3" class="body-link css-inlxvj emevuu60"&gt;Jamie K. Alan, Ph.D.,&lt;/a&gt; an associate professor of pharmacology and toxicology at Michigan State University.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="9" class="css-6wxqfj emevuu60"&gt;Metformin specifically decreases the amount of glucose you absorb from food, as well as the amount of glucose made by the liver, per Alan. At the same time, the drug increases the body’s response to insulin, a hormone that controls the amount of glucose in the blood. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="10" class="css-6wxqfj emevuu60"&gt;“There are likely more complex mechanisms also at play,” Alan says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="11" class="css-6wxqfj emevuu60"&gt;Metformin is being explored for other health conditions, too. “Because metformin can pass through the bloodstream and into the brain, scientists have also studied whether it may be an effective treatment for depression and neurological disorders,” says &lt;a href="https://www.medstarhealth.org/doctors/kelly-krisna-johnson-arbor-md" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.medstarhealth.org/doctors/kelly-krisna-johnson-arbor-md" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="Kelly Johnson-Arbor, M.D." data-node-id="11.1" class="body-link css-inlxvj emevuu60"&gt;Kelly Johnson-Arbor, M.D.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.medstarhealth.org/doctors/kelly-krisna-johnson-arbor-md" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.medstarhealth.org/doctors/kelly-krisna-johnson-arbor-md" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="," data-node-id="11.2" class="body-link css-inlxvj emevuu60"&gt;,&lt;/a&gt; a toxicologist at MedStar Health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="why-does-this-matter" data-node-id="12" class="body-h2 css-ne8qws emevuu60"&gt;&lt;strong data-node-id="12.0"&gt;Why does this matter?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="13" class="css-6wxqfj emevuu60"&gt;Even though metformin has been widely used for decades, the details about how it works haven’t been totally figured out. “Amazingly, even though metformin is a drug that has been used for more than six decades in the U.S., we still do not fully understand how it works,” says &lt;a href="https://rwjmg.rwjms.rutgers.edu/doctor_page.php?phys_id=115212" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://rwjmg.rwjms.rutgers.edu/doctor_page.php?phys_id=115212" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="Christoph Buettner, M.D., Ph.D." data-node-id="13.1" class="body-link css-inlxvj emevuu60"&gt;Christoph Buettner, M.D., Ph.D.&lt;/a&gt;, chief of the division of endocrinology at Rutgers Robert Wood Johnson Medical School. “It’s the most prescribed diabetes drug in the world.”&lt;br data-node-id="13.3"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="14" class="css-6wxqfj emevuu60"&gt;These findings suggest it could impact the brain, liver, and gut. “It is valuable to learn how this works in the brain,” Alan says. “There is so much we don’t know about satiety and central mechanisms behind appetite and blood sugar control.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="15" class="css-6wxqfj emevuu60"&gt;The findings “change the way we think about metformin,” Dr. Buettner says. “It supports the important role the brain plays in glucose metabolism,” he continues. “It also may explain why metformin causes modest weight loss, changes in appetite and hunger, and possible effects on brain aging or cognition, as these are brain effects.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="16" class="css-6wxqfj emevuu60"&gt;Metformin is also “extremely affordable,” Alan says. “It’s oral, so no injections are needed,” she adds. (By comparison, Ozempic and Mounjaro are injectable medications.) As a result, finding new ways to use it or similar treatments would be a big win for the diabetes community and beyond, she says. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="17" class="css-6wxqfj emevuu60"&gt;These findings could potentially lead to new and better treatments for a range of diseases, according to Dr. Johnson-Arbor. “By studying the effects of metformin outside of the liver, scientists may be able to find new applications of this decades-old drug, such as novel treatments for diabetes, neurological disorders, and heart disease,” she says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="what-happens-now" data-node-id="18" class="body-h2 css-ne8qws emevuu60"&gt;&lt;strong data-node-id="18.0"&gt;What happens now?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="19" class="css-6wxqfj emevuu60"&gt;These are new findings, so more research is needed. However, the study’s research team also shared in a &lt;a href="https://www.bcm.edu/news/how-does-metformin-lower-blood-sugar" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.bcm.edu/news/how-does-metformin-lower-blood-sugar" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="press release" data-node-id="19.1" class="body-link css-inlxvj emevuu60"&gt;press release&lt;/a&gt; that they plan to dive deeper into how metformin impacts the brain, including looking at humans.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="20" class="css-6wxqfj emevuu60"&gt;Still, experts say this is just the start. “The research is a long way from the clinic, but it is important,” Alan says. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-ad-exclude="true" id="journey-inline" class="css-ciejky e1ye6jr30"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Prevention</author><pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 13:32:12 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilgFBVV95cUxNQkxVc2dzaHM1c2hVbzZQYXRQelhNc0NQdmZDV0xPYkljMjR5SVNHb2wxSXZXLVptQ19VUTFEZFU4aEJtaWZKaW13dXVBN0RwWTlsNHZFM3Fla21XdHhYRWpmc2xTcllQc0t6MVpDM1Q4Q2lScldwcFpMRXluU2Nld3dOUVdNVWtGOWYxZTBud2R0TjJGSHc</guid></item><item><title>科学家发现流行的糖尿病药物在令人惊讶的研究中影响大脑-雅虎</title><link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/articles/scientists-popular-diabetes-drug-impacts-133000720.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="" data-article-body="true"&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;With buzzy medications like &lt;a href="https://www.prevention.com/food-nutrition/a64501989/ozempic-reshapes-the-food-people-eat-study/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Ozempic;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Ozempic&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.prevention.com/health/health-conditions/a45250651/mounjaro-vs-ozempic/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Mounjaro;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Mounjaro&lt;/a&gt; making headlines for blood sugar management, it’s easy to forget that some medications have been helping patients with &lt;a href="https://www.prevention.com/diabetes/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:type 2 diabetes;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;type 2 diabetes&lt;/a&gt; for decades. Metformin is a popular one. But while this medication has been around for more than 60 years, scientists are uncovering what it does to the brain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;New research published in the journal &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.science.org/doi/10.1126/sciadv.adu3700" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Science Advances;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Science Advances&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/em&gt;identifies a brain pathway that metformin seems to work through (along with the impact it has on other areas of the body). It’s been generally accepted that metformin lowers blood sugar by reducing how much glucose the liver puts out, but this study found that a lot of that glucose regulation seems to happen in the brain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Meet the experts&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;a href="https://rwjmg.rwjms.rutgers.edu/doctor_page.php?phys_id=115212" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Christoph Buettner, M.D., Ph.D.;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Christoph Buettner, M.D., Ph.D.&lt;/a&gt;, chief of the division of endocrinology at Rutgers Robert Wood Johnson Medical School; &lt;a href="https://www.medstarhealth.org/doctors/kelly-krisna-johnson-arbor-md" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Kelly Johnson-Arbor, M.D.;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Kelly Johnson-Arbor, M.D.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.medstarhealth.org/doctors/kelly-krisna-johnson-arbor-md" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:,;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;,&lt;/a&gt; a toxicologist at MedStar Health; &lt;a href="https://phmtox.msu.edu/people/alanjami" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Jamie K. Alan, Ph.D.,;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Jamie K. Alan, Ph.D.,&lt;/a&gt; an associate professor of pharmacology and toxicology at Michigan State University&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;In a previous mouse study, the same research team found a protein in the brain called Rap1, which impacted how glucose is broken down in the body. During that study, the researchers found that metformin traveled to an area of the brain called the ventromedial hypothalamus, where it essentially turned off Rap1.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The researchers then bred mice that didn’t have Rap1 and found that metformin had no impact on their blood sugar management, even though other medications did. Overall, the findings suggest that metformin has a big impact on the brain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;But why does this matter? Here’s what doctors want you to know.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mb-4 text-xl font-bold md:text-2xl"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What is metformin?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Metformin is an oral medication in a class of drugs called biguanides that is commonly used to treat type 2 diabetes, according to the &lt;a href="https://medlineplus.gov/druginfo/meds/a696005.html" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:U.S. National Library of Medicine;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;U.S. National Library of Medicine&lt;/a&gt;. The medication is designed to help control the amount of glucose (or sugar) in the blood. “Metformin has been used for decades to treat diabetes, although there has been extensive research on its use in other conditions like cancer and PCOS,” says &lt;a href="https://phmtox.msu.edu/people/alanjami" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Jamie K. Alan, Ph.D.,;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Jamie K. Alan, Ph.D.,&lt;/a&gt; an associate professor of pharmacology and toxicology at Michigan State University.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Metformin specifically decreases the amount of glucose you absorb from food, as well as the amount of glucose made by the liver, per Alan. At the same time, the drug increases the body’s response to insulin, a hormone that controls the amount of glucose in the blood.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“There are likely more complex mechanisms also at play,” Alan says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Metformin is being explored for other health conditions, too. “Because metformin can pass through the bloodstream and into the brain, scientists have also studied whether it may be an effective treatment for depression and neurological disorders,” says &lt;a href="https://www.medstarhealth.org/doctors/kelly-krisna-johnson-arbor-md" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Kelly Johnson-Arbor, M.D.;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Kelly Johnson-Arbor, M.D.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.medstarhealth.org/doctors/kelly-krisna-johnson-arbor-md" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:,;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;,&lt;/a&gt; a toxicologist at MedStar Health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mb-4 text-xl font-bold md:text-2xl"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why does this matter?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Even though metformin has been widely used for decades, the details about how it works haven’t been totally figured out. “Amazingly, even though metformin is a drug that has been used for more than six decades in the U.S., we still do not fully understand how it works,” says &lt;a href="https://rwjmg.rwjms.rutgers.edu/doctor_page.php?phys_id=115212" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Christoph Buettner, M.D., Ph.D.;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Christoph Buettner, M.D., Ph.D.&lt;/a&gt;, chief of the division of endocrinology at Rutgers Robert Wood Johnson Medical School. “It’s the most prescribed diabetes drug in the world.”&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;These findings suggest it could impact the brain, liver, and gut. “It is valuable to learn how this works in the brain,” Alan says. “There is so much we don’t know about satiety and central mechanisms behind appetite and blood sugar control.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The findings “change the way we think about metformin,” Dr. Buettner says. “It supports the important role the brain plays in glucose metabolism,” he continues. “It also may explain why metformin causes modest weight loss, changes in appetite and hunger, and possible effects on brain aging or cognition, as these are brain effects.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Metformin is also “extremely affordable,” Alan says. “It’s oral, so no injections are needed,” she adds. (By comparison, Ozempic and Mounjaro are injectable medications.) As a result, finding new ways to use it or similar treatments would be a big win for the diabetes community and beyond, she says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;These findings could potentially lead to new and better treatments for a range of diseases, according to Dr. Johnson-Arbor. “By studying the effects of metformin outside of the liver, scientists may be able to find new applications of this decades-old drug, such as novel treatments for diabetes, neurological disorders, and heart disease,” she says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mb-4 text-xl font-bold md:text-2xl"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What happens now?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;These are new findings, so more research is needed. However, the study’s research team also shared in a &lt;a href="https://www.bcm.edu/news/how-does-metformin-lower-blood-sugar" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:press release;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;press release&lt;/a&gt; that they plan to dive deeper into how metformin impacts the brain, including looking at humans.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Still, experts say this is just the start. “The research is a long way from the clinic, but it is important,” Alan says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You Might Also Like&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Yahoo</author><pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 13:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilgFBVV95cUxObzBTaWpqRVhBaENuWU9lTHBmVTZxRnQ1ZWlkaGI0b0Z2OGUySTZueDhDaDZuUVo0Q05fbFhDbm5rMlVHTGpjbzV2NGw3NFdhblEydlo2M0hrQ2JvbTJEemRlbTZma1dteG43Qi01RjZSakZ2RjZRNDdNUHd4ZTRDNksxYTNXOE1TdFV4YUNMTjlXMmYzNFE</guid></item><item><title>如果您在今天的挑战即将结束时一个月不手淫，您的身体会发生什么- LADbible</title><link>https://www.ladbible.com/news/health/no-nut-november-health-body-challenge-ends-today-554389-20251130</link><description>&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p class="loading-bar_loader__2fNms"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;main&gt;&lt;template id="B:0"&gt;&lt;/template&gt;&lt;p class="article-page-skeleton_background__h2J4n"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/main&gt;&lt;/body&gt;</description><author>LADbible</author><pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 13:20:24 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiowFBVV95cUxNeTFGZlN4bTNFRWh5T2l3T2NPcEhuWDlSaUNCZS1xSzBDU196SGU1VGZoOTdvYlVlXy1ZQWEyZlo1MmdXQ0xRa1lTRmhtZlVvSkZvX0d5b1JscjZDWnF6cHJZZTRyeTRTbXk1UWxQX3hJREdBbkdHc1ZncktyRmQ2TV84SV9XbkVYdk1BV0lpWVB4akxjQXp5Q0RwNzBwbUxyR1JJ</guid></item><item><title>寻找更浓密、更饱满的头发？专家权衡生物素补充剂-今日美国</title><link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/life/health-wellness/2025/11/30/biotin-hair-growth-benefits/87468315007/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="gnt_ar_b"&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;People looking to grow out thicker, fuller hair or stronger, healthier nails are presented with plenty of commercials and product recommendations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;Could &lt;a href="/story/life/health-wellness/2024/11/20/what-does-biotin-do/75900383007/" data-t-l=":b|e|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;biotin supplements&lt;/a&gt; offer you a solution to those &lt;a href="/story/life/health-wellness/2023/10/18/why-is-my-hair-falling-out/71180805007/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" data-t-l=":b|e|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;common beauty concerns&lt;/a&gt;?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;Proponents tout biotin's potential benefits for hair, nails and more. But do they offer benefits for some people more than others? And how necessary are the &lt;a href="/story/life/health-wellness/2024/08/15/what-is-vitamin-b6-good-for/74550359007/" data-t-l=":b|e|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;supplements&lt;/a&gt;? &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;Biotin deficiency is a relatively uncommon condition. Eating a well-rounded, &lt;a href="/story/life/health-wellness/2024/10/18/cauliflower-good-for-you/75478336007/#:~:text=Moreover%2C%20as%20a%20filling%20and,per%20cup%2C%22%20says%20Weintraub." target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" data-t-l=":b|e|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;balanced diet&lt;/a&gt; is how the &lt;a href="https://www.healthline.com/health/the-benefits-of-biotin" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" data-t-l=":b|z|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;vast majority of people&lt;/a&gt; can get enough biotin (also known as vitamin B7), per Healthline.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;We asked the experts to break down what you need to know about biotin. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="gnt_ar_b_h2"&gt;What does biotin do?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;Biotin supports several functions in the body, including the &lt;a href="/story/news/health/2021/09/13/fewer-calories-more-exercise-weight-loss-its-more-complicated/8274034002/?gnt-cfr=1&amp;amp;gca-cat=p" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" data-t-l=":b|e|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;metabolism&lt;/a&gt; of carbs, fats and proteins, said &lt;a href="https://www.uwmedicine.org/bios/misbah-keen" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" data-t-l=":b|z|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;Dr. Misbah K. Keen&lt;/a&gt;, MD, MBI, MPH, a professor of family medicine at the University of Washington School of Medicine. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;Biotin also plays an important role in supporting &lt;a href="https://reviewed.usatoday.com/beauty/features/its-a-10-miracle-leave-in-plus-keratin-review" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" data-t-l=":b|e|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;the structure of keratin&lt;/a&gt;, a protein that’s essential to the maintenance of healthy hair, skin and nails, Keen previously told USA TODAY. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;During pregnancy, biotin is an essential nutrient that supports the &lt;a href="https://www.mountsinai.org/health-library/supplement/vitamin-h-biotin" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" data-t-l=":b|z|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;growth of the embryo&lt;/a&gt;, per Mount Sinai.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="gnt_ar_b_h2"&gt;Who is at risk for biotin deficiency?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;It’s important to understand that most people can satisfy their need for biotin just from eating a variety of biotin-rich foods − think eggs, seeds, &lt;a href="/story/life/health-wellness/2024/07/26/are-walnuts-good-for-you/74323707007/#:~:text=No%20matter%20which%20variety%20you,the%20U.S.%20Department%20of%20Agriculture." target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" data-t-l=":b|e|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;nuts&lt;/a&gt;, meat and fish, said &lt;a href="https://wexnermedical.osu.edu/find-a-doctor/barbara-bawer-md-79613" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" data-t-l=":b|z|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;Dr. Barbara Bawer&lt;/a&gt;, a family medicine physician at The Ohio State University Wexner Medical Center. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;Biotin deficiency is very uncommon, but experiencing it can cause an array of side effects, including: &lt;a href="/story/life/health-wellness/2024/08/10/what-vitamins-are-good-for-hair-growth/74551135007/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" data-t-l=":b|e|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;hair thinning or loss&lt;/a&gt;, brittle nails, a red scaly rash (around the eyes, nose, and mouth), a swollen, painful tongue, neurological changes (such as numbness and tingling), and mental health changes (including depression and lethargy), Keen said.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;A very small group of people are born without the enzyme biotinidase. This is an inherited condition that impacts an individual’s biotin metabolism, said &lt;a href="https://www.stamfordhealth.org/find-a-doctor/lidya-bal/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" data-t-l=":b|z|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;Dr. Lidya Bal&lt;/a&gt;, MD, a physician with Stamford Health. Global estimates approximate that biotinidase deficiency ranges anywhere from one in 40,000 people to &lt;a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/books/NBK560607/#:~:text=Biotinidase%20deficiency%20is%20a%20rare,the%20Kingdom%20of%20Saudi%20Arabia." target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" data-t-l=":b|z|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;one in 60,000 people&lt;/a&gt;, per NCBI. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;Though rare, there is an elevated risk for &lt;a href="/story/life/health-wellness/2024/10/26/can-pregnant-women-eat-deli-meat/75594937007/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" data-t-l=":b|e|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;people who are pregnant&lt;/a&gt; or breastfeeding to experience biotin deficiency. As for why this may occur, during pregnancy, your body metabolizes biotin faster, Bawer explained. When breastfeeding, “you tend to excrete more biotin and therefore are at higher risk of being low,” she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;Individuals with chronic alcoholism, and people taking long-term antiseizure medications, are also at risk for biotin deficiency, Keen added. “These can interfere with biotin metabolism or absorption,” he said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="gnt_ar_b_h2"&gt;Who benefits from biotin supplements?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;“Biotin supplements are used to prevent or treat biotin deficiency,” and individuals with a biotin deficiency may benefit from taking them, said Bal. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;Biotin supplements should always be taken under medical supervision, underscores &lt;a href="https://utswmed.org/doctors/sarah-hemeida/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" data-t-l=":b|z|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;Dr. Sarah Hemeida&lt;/a&gt;, MD, MPH, an assistant professor and family physician at UT Southwestern Family Medicine Department and the co-director of Empowher Health, a women's health education program focused on dispelling cultural misinformation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;The adequate intake (AI) for biotin is 30 micrograms a day for adults and eight to 12 micrograms a day for children, Bal said. However, depending on the patient and the severity of their biotin deficiency, dosages will vary. For example, in certain cases, treatment could require taking a dosage of biotin supplements as high as 10mg per day, Bal noted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;Biotin supplements may offer benefits during pregnancy and times of lactation, when it’s especially important to maintain healthy biotin levels, Hemeida said. There are risks to taking biotin supplements during pregnancy, so always consult your doctor first, she recommended.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="gnt_ar_b_h2"&gt;Does biotin increase hair growth?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;Unfortunately, for most people, taking biotin supplements will probably not make much of an impact on hair growth. “Although biotin is widely marketed for hair loss, the evidence supporting its effectiveness is mixed,” Keen said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;&lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC5582478/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" data-t-l=":b|z|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;According to a 2017 review&lt;/a&gt;, some studies have shown biotin supplementation had positive outcomes for hair growth in individuals who had an acquired or inherited deficiency in biotin. However, these cases are still relatively uncommon. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;In healthy individuals who aren’t deficient in biotin, biotin supplementation will likely have no effect on hair growth, the same review concluded.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="gnt_ar_b_h2"&gt;Does biotin support nail health?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;Some &lt;a href="https://www.tandfonline.com/doi/full/10.1080/09546634.2017.1395799" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" data-t-l=":b|z|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;small clinical trials&lt;/a&gt; have shown biotin supplements may help strengthen brittle nails by improving their firmness, thickness and hardness. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;However, biotin supplements will likely have no strengthening effect on your nails if you aren’t deficient in biotin, said &lt;a href="https://school.wakehealth.edu/faculty/m/amy-mcmichael" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" data-t-l=":b|z|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;Dr. Amy McMichael&lt;/a&gt;, MD, FAAD, a board-certified dermatologist and professor of dermatology at Wake Forest University School of Medicine. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;If you’re facing brittle, &lt;a href="/story/life/health-wellness/2023/08/11/why-do-people-bite-their-nails/70429437007/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" data-t-l=":b|e|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;easily broken nails&lt;/a&gt;, biotin supplements may be used as a short-term treatment, McMichael said. But, if you are considering taking any kind of supplement for nail health, always have a conversation with your board-certified dermatologist first, McMichael underscored.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="gnt_ar_b_h2"&gt;What is the downside of taking biotin?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;Biotin is a &lt;a href="https://www.mountsinai.org/health-library/supplement/vitamin-h-biotin" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" data-t-l=":b|z|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;water soluble vitamin&lt;/a&gt;, meaning “when there's an excess supply, it's excreted through the urine,” said Hemeida. Overall, biotin is considered to be “a very safe vitamin."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;However, “there is too much of a good thing when it comes to biotin, because it can prevent you from accurately diagnosing other important issues,” and it may interfere with the results of certain laboratory tests, Hemeida warned. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;“For that reason, we now recommend to patients to really not take biotin unless they are biotin-deficient, and that is proven by their physician,” McMichael said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;&lt;em&gt;This article contains affiliate links. If you click on a link and make a purchase, we may earn a commission at no extra cost to you.&lt;/em&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="gnt_ar_b_h2"&gt;Shop top-rated related products: &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_s gnt_ar_s0"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_s gnt_ar_s25"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_s gnt_ar_s50"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_s gnt_ar_s75"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_s gnt_ar_s100"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>USA Today</author><pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 12:40:11 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipgFBVV95cUxPM0hFM0Vaek9VbUtPQVBxeHA5UGNsYmExQ180MGFoWE9LcmxaZllQUU5neXJJZTVBaWNqbG1aVlprRjE4S1pDdFBGUDVtWWplLXBBbURyd0w2cm1LQkU2Q2ZYQUtNUGxVbUhwRUlHdERNa0FDU3gzaE5NWWladjg5M2NXN1ZKRFNHek1ONThGUzU0Q0Zjd05YSnRVTlkwUHhaNXlaOFd3</guid></item><item><title>7个小的睡眠习惯，可以帮助你每天早上感到精力充沛-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/fitness/7-small-sleep-habits-that-can-help-you-feel-energised-every-morning/articleshow/125664301.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many people wake up feeling as if their rest never truly restored them, even after a full night in bed, and this pattern has become increasingly familiar across age groups and lifestyles. Sleep has shifted from a simple daily routine to a key area of scientific interest because disrupted sleep is now linked with memory decline, weakened immunity, metabolic disorders and emotional fatigue. As researchers explore how everyday behaviour influences the quality of rest, there is growing attention on small environmental cues, pre-bed routines and consistent patterns that shape how the body prepares for sleep. These insights have encouraged both specialists and the public to revisit what healthy sleep should look like and how small changes may improve it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="6"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="7"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;These 7 habits can help if you wake up tired every morning&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="8"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/p/DRmacpxCZtS/?utm_source=ig_web_copy_link&amp;amp;igsh=NTc4MTIwNjQ2YQ==" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;Gastroenterologist Dr Pal Manickam recently shared a widely circulated Instagram video&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; explaining why many people wake up tired and what small habits can help them restore morning energy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="11"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;His list includes:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="13"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="14"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fixing consistent sleep timings&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Blocking bright light before bed&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Keeping the room slightly cooler&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Using the bed only for sleep&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Eating &lt;keyword id="6381468" type="General" weightage="20" keywordseo="dinner" source="Orion"&gt;dinner&lt;/keyword&gt; earlier&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Avoiding &lt;keyword id="19957282" type="General" weightage="20" keywordseo="caffeine" source="keywords"&gt;caffeine&lt;/keyword&gt; after mid-afternoon &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Sitting in silence for a brief period to signal relaxation&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="15"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="17"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;These suggestions align with current research on circadian rhythm stability, melatonin regulation and behavioural conditioning, which together play an essential role in shaping sleep quality and next-day alertness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="20"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="21"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;1. Consistent sleep timings and circadian alignment&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="22"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The first suggestion emphasises going to bed and waking up at the same time, even on weekends, because irregular schedules interfere with the natural circadian rhythm that governs hormone release and body temperature changes across the night. A &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/29283283/" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;study published in the National Health and Nutrition Examination Survey&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; has shown that uneven sleep patterns disrupt melatonin onset and delay the body’s internal clock, which increases daytime sleepiness and reduces slow wave sleep. When the brain receives a predictable pattern, it prepares for rest in advance, strengthens the sleep drive and supports deeper sleep cycles. Establishing fixed timings gradually resets the rhythm, which many people experience as steadier energy and improved morning clarity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="28"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="29"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;2. Blocking bright light and supporting melatonin&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="30"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The second point focuses on reducing exposure to bright or blue light during the evening because artificial brightness delays melatonin release, which extends the time it takes to fall asleep. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC5877069/" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;Research published in the International Journal of Environmental Research and Public Health&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; demonstrates that blue light suppresses melatonin more sharply than warm light, which is why simple changes such as shifting to yellow-toned bulbs or dimming screens can make sleep onset smoother. The eye is particularly sensitive to short wavelength light during the two hours before bed, so creating a softer environment helps the brain interpret the evening as a transition into rest. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="36"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;This becomes even more important today as people spend long hours on phones and laptops, where LED screens emit concentrated blue wavelengths that disrupt circadian rhythm, suppress natural drowsiness, and interfere with the body’s internal sleep-wake regulation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="39"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="40"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;3. A cooler room and thermal comfort during sleep&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="41"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The third habit highlights temperature because the body naturally cools as part of the sleep cycle. A &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S0360132324008709" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;study published in Building and Environment&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; suggests that slightly cooler rooms help the body reach the thermal set point needed for efficient slow wave sleep, which supports memory consolidation and physical recovery. When the room is too warm, the body struggles to release heat, causing restlessness or fragmented sleep. Lowering the temperature by one or two degrees supports this natural cooling curve and allows the body to settle more quickly into deeper stages of rest.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="46"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="47"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;4. Using the bed only for sleep and behavioural conditioning&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="48"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The fourth point reflects behavioural psychology, where the brain forms associations based on repeated actions. When the bed becomes a space for working, reading or scrolling, the brain begins to link it with alertness rather than rest. Research shows that limiting the bed to sleep strengthens a mental cue that prepares the body to switch off when lying down. This simple shift reduces pre-sleep arousal, shortens sleep latency and helps restore a clean boundary between day activity and night rest, which many people lose when digital devices enter the bedroom.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="51"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="52"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;5. Earlier dinner timing and digestive rhythms&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="53"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The fifth suggestion centres on meal timing because digestion affects metabolic signals that influence sleep onset. A &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/34017207/" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;study published in Nature and Science of Sleep&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; describes how late meals increase core body temperature and activate glucose regulation processes that keep the body alert rather than relaxed. Finishing dinner two to three hours before bedtime allows digestion to progress without interfering with the early phases of sleep. This timing supports stable blood sugar levels through the night and helps prevent nocturnal awakenings linked to digestive discomfort.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="58"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="59"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;6. Limiting caffeine after mid-afternoon&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="60"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The sixth habit is widely recognised, but its scientific basis is often underestimated. Caffeine has a half-life of roughly five hours, although sensitivity varies between individuals, and a &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/9042530/" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;study published in Brain Research&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; shows that consuming caffeine even six hours before bed can significantly reduce total sleep time. By blocking adenosine receptors, caffeine masks the natural sleep drive and delays the onset of drowsiness, which shortens deep sleep and affects morning alertness. Switching to herbal tea or warm water supports a gentler transition into the evening.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="66"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="67"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;7. A few minutes of silence before bedtime&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="68"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The final point focuses on a ten-minute period of quiet, which encourages the shift from a sympathetic state to a parasympathetic one, preparing the body physiologically for rest. A &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/25398735/" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;study published in Advances in Nutrition&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; shows that brief moments of silence can lower heart rate, reduce cortisol levels and regulate breathing patterns, all of which signal to the brain that it is safe to enter a relaxed state. Even short, structured stillness acts as an anchor that slows internal activity and smooths the transition into sleep.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="74"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="75"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Why &lt;keyword id="92669" type="General" weightage="20" keywordseo="good-sleep" source="Orion"&gt;good sleep&lt;/keyword&gt; supports long term health&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="76"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Healthy sleep influences nearly every major biological system, including cardiovascular regulation, immune resilience, cognitive processing and emotional balance. Research links consistently poor sleep with higher risks of hypertension, weakened immunity, memory impairment and metabolic disorders such as insulin resistance. Quality sleep also supports hormone regulation, tissue repair and neural plasticity, which together shape long term wellbeing. As interest in preventive health grows, scientists continue to explore how small behavioural choices accumulate to form healthier sleep patterns that support physical and mental stability throughout life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="81"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Disclaimer: This article is for general informational purposes only and is not a substitute for professional medical advice, diagnosis, or treatment. Always seek the guidance of a qualified healthcare provider regarding any medical condition or lifestyle change.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="83"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Also Read | &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/fitness/5-common-workouts-that-silently-damage-your-joints/articleshow/125332235.cms" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;5 common workouts that silently damage your joints&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 12:40:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi9gFBVV95cUxPWTdobUI1UWJvTHdOT3ZwRFk4elBaWjZWLVJGZjBsM05wWWhoMGFmMTE1M3NVRWkxMjZUVUUxZk1yZDBSbWdMdXRONUlCcDNKMUFnOUNORzNRU0NESy1zNnMzWENEUUJ5V3hidXVSdFVwQWxtUjVyTTZBTWF6RVd2eFo4WTNINFpLeWc3eGJpQnE3UXF2T0hCMFZLVktaTWlkRWVVOTFxYURsOEU4MkxhRVJDa3dQNW9nbVBGcDFETFY3VDFDSlNuLVZmVXQwMUE1N2h1YVI2XzlMdDYxX3RTTlB3UDNtZFZuS0Itc2Z6M3JPY3NETVHSAfsBQVVfeXFMUFVHQkU5NkZnczJteE1pVFhfRWZ6dHhDcE9QcFNpUXkyZ1VDanZWZm5ZU25VcmVHNFh3dEl5QzFjZ2lKLVNmX3NlVFRPaTRjSlVmc0d3ZW5FT2VQdXFWUGdIUHozQzBTVXBSLWZldTJmazBRT3RVR1VkdXd1ZmE4YnBBOXdVdVlBWnBNMExNV05fR014TG5obW9KUl9BYWxiRnUxaFdqREdCRXJfTzE4Zkt0UzhHbEhqSFhKSEFKdXpjVWdnbWV4MUI5bGl6bllreWVucEhtMVAtYW5mVFJZdVk3RkVSd0p1N0FuQVZQZTI1UElGVHhNbWNfVHc</guid></item><item><title>野猪在加利福尼亚州变成“霓虹蓝” ，引发警告- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/wild-pigs-turned-neon-blue-in-california-triggering-warnings</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Game hunters have found startlingly 'neon blue' flesh inside of wild pigs in California, triggering advisory statements on potential contamination.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I'm not talking about a little blue," Dan Burton, owner of a wildlife control company, &lt;a href="https://www.latimes.com/california/story/2025-08-05/exposure-to-rat-poison-turns-meat-of-wild-pigs-blue-authorities-in-monterey-county-warn"&gt;told&lt;/a&gt; Salvador Hernandez at &lt;em&gt;The Los Angeles Times&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I'm talking about neon blue, blueberry blue."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;An investigation by local authorities found the dramatic color change was caused by rodenticide poisoning, prompting them to &lt;a href="https://wildlife.ca.gov/News/Archive/poison-detection-in-wild-pigs-brings-attention-to-pesticide-exposure-in-hunter-harvested-wildlife"&gt;issue a warning&lt;/a&gt; throughout the Monterey County area.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/researchers-propose-harnessing-the-stench-of-predatory-insects-as-a-pesticide-alternative"&gt;We Can Make Powerful Nature-Inspired 'Pesticides' Without Poison, Scientists Say&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rat poisons containing the chemical compound &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Diphenadione"&gt;diphacinone&lt;/a&gt; are often sold dyed blue for identification. The compound's use &lt;a href="https://www.cdpr.ca.gov/cac-letter/diphacinone-restricted-material-status-prohibitions-allowed-uses-and-questions-and-answers/"&gt;has been highly restricted&lt;/a&gt; in California since 2024.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Watch the video below for a summary:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Hunters should be aware that the meat of game animals, such as wild pig, deer, bear, and geese, might be contaminated if that game animal has been exposed to rodenticides," &lt;a href="https://wildlife.ca.gov/News/Archive/poison-detection-in-wild-pigs-brings-attention-to-pesticide-exposure-in-hunter-harvested-wildlife"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; pesticide investigations coordinator Ryan Bourbour from the California Department of Fish and Wildlife (CDFW).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Rodenticide exposure can be a concern for non-target wildlife in areas where applications occur in close proximity to wildlife habitat."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Concerningly, this isn't the first time wild pigs in the region &lt;a href="https://imgur.com/gallery/weird-pig-YTIx8"&gt;have had their innards tainted blue&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A popular rodent control in agriculture, diphacinone is a first-generation rodenticide that acts as an anticoagulant, causing severe internal bleeding.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It works by binding to &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Vitamin_K_epoxide_reductase"&gt;an enzyme&lt;/a&gt; that recycles  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/what-are-vitamins-and-do-we-really-need-to-take-them" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73116" data-postid="182084" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;vitamin&lt;/a&gt; K. This reduces available &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Vitamin_K"&gt;vitamin K&lt;/a&gt;, making it impossible for animal livers to produce enough of the clotting factors crucial to prevent internal bleeding.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_170925" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-170925" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/08/BlueDyedRodenticideBait-e1754899591347.jpg" alt="Blue dyed bait poisoned with rodenticide" class="wp-image-170925 size-full" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-170925" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Rodenticide bait. (&lt;a href="https://wildlife.ca.gov/News/Archive/poison-detection-in-wild-pigs-brings-attention-to-pesticide-exposure-in-hunter-harvested-wildlife"&gt;CDFW&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Predators, including humans, who eat an animal poisoned with the toxin can become ill themselves; while the chemical &lt;a href="https://www.apvma.gov.au/resources/frequently-searched-chemicals/rodenticides"&gt;breaks down faster&lt;/a&gt; than second-generation rodenticides, diphacinone remains active in the dead animal's tissues for some time, &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.fct.2011.05.014"&gt;even if it's cooked&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.audubon.org/magazine/poisons-used-kill-rodents-have-safer-alternatives"&gt;Wildlife groups&lt;/a&gt; globally have long been urging us to stop relying on chemical pesticides because of the collateral damage these poisons inflict. From &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.scitotenv.2022.153024"&gt;owls&lt;/a&gt; to &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/study-finds-family-of-pesticides-implicated-in-honeybee-deaths-also-hurt-ground-bees"&gt;bees&lt;/a&gt;, pesticides are causing great harm to wildlife.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Non-target animals either consume it directly or are impacted by secondary exposure when eating other animals that have ingested the poison, adding further strain on &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2016/apr/07/endangered-species-protection-animals-plants-pesticides-epa-insecticides"&gt;already endangered species&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/spark-into-space-comp?utm_source=promo_space"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro-642x272.jpg" alt="Win a $10,000 Space Coast Adventure Holiday" class="alignnone wp-image-177074 size-medium" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro-642x272.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro-768x326.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro-600x255.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro.jpg 844w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Diphacinone has been found in the systems of &lt;a href="https://www.latimes.com/opinion/story/2024-03-14/editorial-using-rat-poison-kills-wildlife-and-pets"&gt;many poisoned predators&lt;/a&gt;, including raptors, mountain lions, bobcats, foxes, as well as the &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/endangered-owls-fatally-poisoned-by-illegal-us-marijuana-weed-farms"&gt;endangered northern spotted owl&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.5070/V423110369"&gt;San Joaquin kit fox&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Though prognosis is typically poor, anticoagulation poisoning &lt;a href="https://todaysveterinarypractice.com/emergency-medicine-critical-care/rodenticide-poisoning-what-to-do-after-exposure/"&gt;can be treated&lt;/a&gt; in animals if caught before symptoms appear and vitamin K is administered as an antidote.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But this devastating impact on wildlife is what prompted its strict control in California.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Pesticide applicators are urged to take measures when applying rodenticides so as not to expose wildlife," the CDFW &lt;a href="https://wildlife.ca.gov/News/Archive/poison-detection-in-wild-pigs-brings-attention-to-pesticide-exposure-in-hunter-harvested-wildlife#:~:text=Rodenticide%20baits%20often%20contain%20dye,may%20not%20always%20be%20present."&gt;advises&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Prior to application, it is important to ensure non-target wildlife are not using the area where the pesticide is to be applied. It is also important to use appropriate bait stations and application methods that exclude access to non-target species."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_170926" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-170926" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/08/BlueInsidesWildPig2015.jpeg" alt="Black wild pig with skin pushed aside showing bright blue flesh." class="wp-image-170926 size-full" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/08/BlueInsidesWildPig2015.jpeg 2448w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/08/BlueInsidesWildPig2015-642x482.jpeg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/08/BlueInsidesWildPig2015-553x415.jpeg 553w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/08/BlueInsidesWildPig2015-768x576.jpeg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/08/BlueInsidesWildPig2015-1536x1152.jpeg 1536w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/08/BlueInsidesWildPig2015-2048x1536.jpeg 2048w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/08/BlueInsidesWildPig2015-600x450.jpeg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 2448px) 100vw, 2448px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-170926" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;A wild pig with blue innards discovered in 2015. (&lt;a href="https://imgur.com/gallery/weird-pig-YTIx8"&gt;GlendilTEK/imgur&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;California's wild pigs — which are hybrids between domestic pigs and &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/wild-pigs-in-germany-are-mysteriously-radioactive-and-we-finally-know-why"&gt;European wild boars&lt;/a&gt; that were intentionally released a century ago – are voracious &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/stomach-churning-theory-could-explain-mystery-of-neanderthal-diet"&gt;omnivores&lt;/a&gt;, so would happily eat both the poisoned rodents and the bait.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Since March this year, a local trapper, Dan Burton, &lt;a href="https://www.themeateater.com/conservation/wildlife-management/california-issues-warning-after-trapper-finds-pigs-with-slushie-blue-colored"&gt;observed multiple wild pigs&lt;/a&gt; going out of their way to obtain oats baited with rodenticide, used in squirrel traps.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The associated dye appears to affect only the pigs' fat, leaving the rest of their tissues normally colored.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pesticides are harmful to exposed humans as well. They have been linked to &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/50-years-of-data-links-insecticides-to-global-decline-of-human-sperm-counts"&gt;declining sperm rates&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1289/ehp.1104597"&gt;diabetes&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/S1470-2045(15)70134-8"&gt;cancers&lt;/a&gt;,  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/go/IaO" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73015" data-postid="182084" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;Alzheimer's&lt;/a&gt;, and other health conditions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_183399" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-183399" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/wild_pigs_blue_fat_642.jpg" alt="blue pig fat" class="wp-image-183399 size-full" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/wild_pigs_blue_fat_642.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/wild_pigs_blue_fat_642-600x421.jpg 600w" sizes="auto, (max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-183399" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;The meat of a contaminated pig remains a standard pink, while the fat is stained blue. (&lt;a href="https://imgur.com/gallery/weird-pig-YTIx8"&gt;GlendilTEK/imgur&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/common-pesticide-linked-to-widespread-brain-abnormalities-in-children"&gt;A recent US study&lt;/a&gt; found that the commonly used insecticide chlorpyrifos causes structural brain abnormalities and reduced motor function in children and adolescents.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/kale-is-now-one-of-the-most-pesticide-contaminated-vegetables-and-the-dangers-go-beyond-eating-salad"&gt;Many&lt;/a&gt; of &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1136/oem.2009.047811"&gt;these pesticides&lt;/a&gt; have been used at large scales without adequate long-term studies of their impacts on human health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/a-dangerous-banned-substance-is-lurking-in-trending-weight-loss-pills"&gt;A Dangerous, Banned Substance Is Lurking in Trending Weight-Loss Pills&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Excessive and uncontrolled pesticide use resulted in food contamination as well as environmental, agricultural, and aquatic pollution," a 2024 scientific review on pesticide use &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.heliyon.2024.e29128"&gt;concludes&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"To address the worldwide threats posed by pesticides, international coordination and cooperation between nations are essential."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://wildlife.ca.gov/HWC"&gt;Integrated pest management&lt;/a&gt; aims to mitigate the risks of such dangerous animal control practices by combining multiple &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/researchers-propose-harnessing-the-stench-of-predatory-insects-as-a-pesticide-alternative"&gt;safer strategies instead&lt;/a&gt;. These include encouraging natural predators and constructing fences, traps, and other barriers, like crawlspace vents.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hungryowls.org/nontoxic-rodent-control"&gt;Other animal deterrents&lt;/a&gt; can include the targeted &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/scientists-have-figured-out-the-type-of-light-bulb-to-use-if-you-want-to-avoid-insects"&gt;use of light&lt;/a&gt; and sound, such as playing talkback radio, or applying scents, such as peppermint essential oil.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The CDFW is urging anyone who encounters blue animals or other abnormalities to report them to the Wildlife Health Lab; &lt;a href="https://wildlife.ca.gov/News/Archive/poison-detection-in-wild-pigs-brings-attention-to-pesticide-exposure-in-hunter-harvested-wildlife"&gt;details are here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;An earlier version of this article was published in August 2025.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 12:02:54 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikwFBVV95cUxOVTVYSDRTUHozUkRzTWZlUlZhMV9IOUlycWFqLWJGRTlkQy0xUXFuVld3VWhHeW0zX21JTzhIbTFYQi1CRFRRN0tqNzdHT2tfRC1hT0R4cGlUQ2lpRGVybXhTZHZvc0RqZU1fUHNLY19qMFd3OG1TSjB0Q0RBbWpGZkdpTldfaElQZktoc1lhS1lkY2c</guid></item><item><title>研究人员发现了两种新的痴呆症风险因素。这就是它们的本质。- HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffpost.com/entry/dementia-research-new-risk-factors-goog_l_69209634e4b06c13afa4a363</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;section class="entry__content-list js-entry-content js-cet-subunit"&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Strides have been made in the world of dementia research compared with even just a few years ago. There’s now a blood test that can diagnose &lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2024/07/28/health/alzheimers-blood-test.html" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Alzheimer’s accurately 90% of the time" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="69209634e4b06c13afa4a363" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.nytimes.com/2024/07/28/health/alzheimers-blood-test.html" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="0"&gt;Alzheimer’s accurately 90% of the time&lt;/a&gt;, and more is understood about the factors (many of which are lifestyle habits) that can put you at higher risk for the condition.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a new &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/life/topic/dementia" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-internal-link" data-vars-item-name="dementia" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="69209634e4b06c13afa4a363" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="/life/topic/dementia" data-vars-target-content-type="feed" data-vars-type="web_internal_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="1"&gt;dementia&lt;/a&gt; report published in &lt;a href="https://www.thelancet.com/journals/lancet/article/PIIS0140-6736(24)01296-0/abstract" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="The Lancet journal" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="69209634e4b06c13afa4a363" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.thelancet.com/journals/lancet/article/PIIS0140-6736(24)01296-0/abstract" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="2"&gt;The Lancet journal&lt;/a&gt; by researchers who are part of The Lancet Commission, two new modifiable risk factors have been identified: high cholesterol after 40 and untreated vision loss.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;In 2020, these same researchers determined 12 modifiable risk factors that are known to put folks at higher risk of developing dementia. These are:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;Physical inactivity&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Smoking&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Excessive alcohol consumption&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Air pollution&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Head injury&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Infrequent social contact&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Less education&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Obesity&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Hypertension&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Diabetes&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Depression&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Hearing impairment&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to the report, these 12 factors, along with the two new ones, account for 49% of dementia cases across the world. Researchers determined these two new risk factors by looking at recent meta-analyses and studies on the topics; they looked at 14 papers on vision loss and 27 on high cholesterol. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“It makes a lot of mechanistic sense,” said &lt;a href="https://www.yalemedicine.org/specialists/arman-fesharaki" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Dr. Arman Fesharaki-Zadeh" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="69209634e4b06c13afa4a363" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.yalemedicine.org/specialists/arman-fesharaki" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="3"&gt;Dr. Arman Fesharaki-Zadeh&lt;/a&gt;, a behavioral neurologist and neuropsychiatrist at Yale Medicine in Connecticut. “A lot of these factors are very much interrelated.” (Fesharaki-Zadeh is not affiliated with the report.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“There are many sources of vision loss, of course, but it tends to be a lot more common in folks who have metabolic risk factors such as high blood pressure, such as poorly controlled diabetes, such as high cholesterol, which is the other risk factor [identified in the report],” he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Moreover, vision is our primary sensory organ — it’s how we process the world around us — and when you can’t see clearly, you’re less likely to spend time doing brain-boosting activities like puzzles, reading or even spending time with other people, said Fesharaki-Zadeh. And these activities are known to help prevent dementia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;When it comes to high LDL cholesterol (the so-called bad cholesterol), it can lead to the hardening of the blood vessels in the heart and brain, Fesharaki-Zadeh said, adding that high blood pressure and uncontrolled diabetes also affect the blood vessels.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;This can &lt;a href="https://www.hopkinsmedicine.org/health/conditions-and-diseases/atherosclerosis" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="make it more difficult for oxygen" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="69209634e4b06c13afa4a363" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.hopkinsmedicine.org/health/conditions-and-diseases/atherosclerosis" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="4"&gt;make it more difficult for oxygen&lt;/a&gt; to get to the brain, which over time can lead to neuron damage — “and dementia is essentially an end product of the neurons dying out, so it’s a neurodegenerative process,” Fesharaki-Zadeh explained.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I can’t tell you how often I see in our patient populations, especially folks above the age of 60, there are certain parts of the brain that are more vulnerable to damage ... and these are the areas that are especially vulnerable to hardening of blood vessels. Someone who has ... high cholesterol, the correlation between that and hardening of blood vessels is quite high, and we see it in our clinical setting very frequently as well.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The saying that I like to use with patients quite often is what affects your heart will affect your brain, and we see that time and time again,” the doctor said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure class="cli cli-image js-no-inject"&gt;&lt;p class="cli-image__spacer"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="cli-image__source-wrapper"&gt;&lt;div class="cli-image__credit" aria-label="Image Credit: Olena Ruban via Getty Images"&gt;&lt;p class="credit-container"&gt;&lt;span class="credit"&gt;Olena Ruban via Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption class="cli-image__caption caption-cli"&gt;If you suffer from vision loss, it's important to manage it for the sake of your future health.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You can lower your risk. First, have a good medical team and primary care doctor.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I cannot highlight the importance of a collaborative model between primary care physicians and specialties,” said Fesharaki-Zadeh. Having a primary care doctor who understands your health and is willing to share pertinent information with specialists, like cardiologists and neurologists, will help you stay on top of any issues putting your well-being at stake.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Your primary care doctor should also be proactively working to help you control the risk factors — like high cholesterol and high blood pressure — whether that’s through medication, diet or exercise.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fesharaki-Zadeh said you and your doctor should focus on these lifestyle changes as early as possible, at least in midlife, not when you’re at the point when dementia starts to show up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The front line of medical care are primary care physicians. These are the folks that, by having early discussions ... can go a long distance to prevent the onset of dementia,” he explained.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;There are also tests that can detect early signs of neurodegeneration and genetic markers of the disease. A primary care doctor can help you learn about these options.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Up to 40% of dementias are potentially preventable,” he added, but it’s worth noting that dementia can also be genetic, which makes prevention trickier. But someone who is diagnosed with dementia or mild cognitive impairment can benefit from managing these risk factors, too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The research is also showing that if you have two groups of individuals, someone who has comorbid metabolic diseases such as hypertension, high cholesterol, diabetes, versus somebody who doesn’t, and both of these individuals have dementia, the rates of progression of dementia in somebody who doesn’t have metabolic risk factors tend to be slower,” explained Fesharaki-Zadeh.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s never too late to make changes and corrections, he noted, whether you’re a young, seemingly healthy person, in your 80s or 90s, or someone who has already been diagnosed with dementia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Our brains are highly malleable, Fesharaki-Zadeh said. So if you decide to make healthy lifestyle changes at any point, your brain will respond and be healthier for it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>HuffPost</author><pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 12:00:17 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMingFBVV95cUxPR01raHVvZGdGai1LY0hsaVVuajRRYkN2Sm9lOFNFdW1IanVUWlRwRnVrN3dEaFFWQnNRTE5zRjJxbTVkOVFwQlktX1J6ZlF2MkdseGdYUzh5RjJsTmtWeVYydEliTll4TXA5RFF1R2hIX3cyb2s4WHpGMVVzY2hjU1pmOHJaUFNjVC00cnh0MW5BSWlJYUZBT2dPM2laUdIBowFBVV95cUxPN3BLM1ltSGtRVFJzVG1GZDA2RDFwYkNwdmVYSzlXRXpud1ZGT0l3NVp6ZmlrMEFHcVpydTUxajktU1pta1pYSkxLendmWG9LZlFFZFlUakFic3BnUDdxRVp3XzFBb1g1bjNWMkgwVEplTFZpQTdISlVXMThodmxWYTZORHlJd1d0MnZ5ODNOTXlSQnFFSXVCT1RwQjZHTWl2S3I0</guid></item><item><title>研究人员发现了两种新的痴呆症风险因素。以下是它们的内容。- Yahoo News Canada</title><link>https://ca.news.yahoo.com/researchers-discovered-2-dementia-risk-120017476.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="" data-article-body="true"&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Strides have been made in the world of dementia research compared with even just a few years ago. There’s now a blood test that can diagnose &lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2024/07/28/health/alzheimers-blood-test.html" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Alzheimer’s accurately 90% of the time;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Alzheimer’s accurately 90% of the time&lt;/a&gt;, and more is understood about the factors (many of which are lifestyle habits) that can put you at higher risk for the condition.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;In a new &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/life/topic/dementia" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:dementia;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;dementia&lt;/a&gt; report published in &lt;a href="https://www.thelancet.com/journals/lancet/article/PIIS0140-6736(24)01296-0/abstract" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:The Lancet journal;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;The Lancet journal&lt;/a&gt; by researchers who are part of The Lancet Commission, two new modifiable risk factors have been identified: high cholesterol after 40 and untreated vision loss.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Health: &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/entry/dissociation-protect-mental-health_l_69270610e4b0ee43600b68e5?utm_campaign=yahoo-recirc" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:This Coping Behavior Is Super Common Right Now — And It Says So Much About Where We Are As A Country;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;This Coping Behavior Is Super Common Right Now — And It Says So Much About Where We Are As A Country&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;In 2020, these same researchers determined 12 modifiable risk factors that are known to put folks at higher risk of developing dementia. These are:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ol class="mb-4"&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-decimal"&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-decimal"&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-decimal"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Excessive alcohol consumption&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-decimal"&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-decimal"&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-decimal"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Infrequent social contact&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-decimal"&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-decimal"&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-decimal"&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-decimal"&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-decimal"&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-decimal"&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;According to the report, these 12 factors, along with the two new ones, account for 49% of dementia cases across the world. Researchers determined these two new risk factors by looking at recent meta-analyses and studies on the topics; they looked at 14 papers on vision loss and 27 on high cholesterol.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“It makes a lot of mechanistic sense,” said &lt;a href="https://www.yalemedicine.org/specialists/arman-fesharaki" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Dr. Arman Fesharaki-Zadeh;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Dr. Arman Fesharaki-Zadeh&lt;/a&gt;, a behavioral neurologist and neuropsychiatrist at Yale Medicine in Connecticut. “A lot of these factors are very much interrelated.” (Fesharaki-Zadeh is not affiliated with the report.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“There are many sources of vision loss, of course, but it tends to be a lot more common in folks who have metabolic risk factors such as high blood pressure, such as poorly controlled diabetes, such as high cholesterol, which is the other risk factor [identified in the report],” he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Health: &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/entry/dementia-research-new-risk-factors-goog_l_68f10a1ae4b0ab08d3191f7d?utm_campaign=yahoo-recirc" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Researchers Have Discovered 2 New Dementia Risk Factors. Here's What They Are.;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Researchers Have Discovered 2 New Dementia Risk Factors. Here's What They Are.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Moreover, vision is our primary sensory organ — it’s how we process the world around us — and when you can’t see clearly, you’re less likely to spend time doing brain-boosting activities like puzzles, reading or even spending time with other people, said Fesharaki-Zadeh. And these activities are known to help prevent dementia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;When it comes to high LDL cholesterol (the so-called bad cholesterol), it can lead to the hardening of the blood vessels in the heart and brain, Fesharaki-Zadeh said, adding that high blood pressure and uncontrolled diabetes also affect the blood vessels.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;This can &lt;a href="https://www.hopkinsmedicine.org/health/conditions-and-diseases/atherosclerosis" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:make it more difficult for oxygen;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;make it more difficult for oxygen&lt;/a&gt; to get to the brain, which over time can lead to neuron damage — “and dementia is essentially an end product of the neurons dying out, so it’s a neurodegenerative process,” Fesharaki-Zadeh explained.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“I can’t tell you how often I see in our patient populations, especially folks above the age of 60, there are certain parts of the brain that are more vulnerable to damage ... and these are the areas that are especially vulnerable to hardening of blood vessels. Someone who has ... high cholesterol, the correlation between that and hardening of blood vessels is quite high, and we see it in our clinical setting very frequently as well.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“The saying that I like to use with patients quite often is what affects your heart will affect your brain, and we see that time and time again,” the doctor said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="relative mb-4"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="relative text-sm mt-1 pr-2.5"&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you suffer from vision loss, it's important to manage it for the sake of your future health. &lt;span class="copyright"&gt;Olena Ruban via Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;h2 class="mb-4 text-xl font-bold md:text-2xl"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You can lower your risk. First, have a good medical team and primary care doctor.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“I cannot highlight the importance of a collaborative model between primary care physicians and specialties,” said Fesharaki-Zadeh. Having a primary care doctor who understands your health and is willing to share pertinent information with specialists, like cardiologists and neurologists, will help you stay on top of any issues putting your well-being at stake.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Your primary care doctor should also be proactively working to help you control the risk factors — like high cholesterol and high blood pressure — whether that’s through medication, diet or exercise.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Health: &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/entry/hip-flexor-stretch-aging-goog_l_6920a1b1e4b0536e01acda27?utm_campaign=yahoo-recirc" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:This Is 1 Stretch You Should Be Doing More Of As You Age;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;This Is 1 Stretch You Should Be Doing More Of As You Age&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Fesharaki-Zadeh said you and your doctor should focus on these lifestyle changes as early as possible, at least in midlife, not when you’re at the point when dementia starts to show up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“The front line of medical care are primary care physicians. These are the folks that, by having early discussions ... can go a long distance to prevent the onset of dementia,” he explained.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;There are also tests that can detect early signs of neurodegeneration and genetic markers of the disease. A primary care doctor can help you learn about these options.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“Up to 40% of dementias are potentially preventable,” he added, but it’s worth noting that dementia can also be genetic, which makes prevention trickier. But someone who is diagnosed with dementia or mild cognitive impairment can benefit from managing these risk factors, too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Health: &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/entry/study-reveals-the-biggest-risk-factors-for-getting-early-dementia-goog_l_689e1d2fe4b048e97f076d0f?utm_campaign=yahoo-recirc" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Study Reveals The Biggest Risk Factors For Getting Early Dementia;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Study Reveals The Biggest Risk Factors For Getting Early Dementia&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“The research is also showing that if you have two groups of individuals, someone who has comorbid metabolic diseases such as hypertension, high cholesterol, diabetes, versus somebody who doesn’t, and both of these individuals have dementia, the rates of progression of dementia in somebody who doesn’t have metabolic risk factors tend to be slower,” explained Fesharaki-Zadeh.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;It’s never too late to make changes and corrections, he noted, whether you’re a young, seemingly healthy person, in your 80s or 90s, or someone who has already been diagnosed with dementia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Our brains are highly malleable, Fesharaki-Zadeh said. So if you decide to make healthy lifestyle changes at any point, your brain will respond and be healthier for it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="mb-4 text-lg font-bold"&gt;Related...&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/entry/dementia-research-new-risk-factors-goog_l_69209634e4b06c13afa4a363?utm_campaign=yahoo-recirc" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Read the original on HuffPost;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Read the original on HuffPost&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Yahoo News Canada</author><pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 12:00:17 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihgFBVV95cUxQZ1N4WFF6aTJHa1pHQW1URVM2cUl0TVlJX2Q5dDUxeUFjcTJfVkZOdlhDU0dWMVo5UlRNNmFCZjFmYllJNGdDUTlOYmF4NzRqNV81RVdSWklqbnQwVTBxS3lZRlU1VGZ6SkRKM3o4dTZzcWdWY1V3LWR2NFNVd1d4UWJCRnUxZw</guid></item><item><title>根据顶级营养学家的说法，冬季可以吃5种超级食物来增强免疫力-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/5-superfoods-to-eat-during-winter-foods-to-boost-immunity-according-to-top-nutritionist/articleshow/125670007.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;div class="MwN2O"&gt;&lt;div class="vdo_embedd"&gt; &lt;div class="T22zO"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is the season of festivities, flu, and everything in between. As the temperature drops and the holiday season begins, the germs lurking in the dark also grow stronger. Most people may experience sniffles, colds, and that constant feeling of being one step away from falling sick. How do you keep illnesses at bay during this winter? By eating the right foods. In an Instagram video, Suman Agarwal, an Oxford-trained nutritionist and qualified fitness expert, has shared a list of foods that can help to boost immunity and protect you from diseases. “These are the foods that strengthen your immunity, keep your energy stable, and protect you from common winter infections, so make sure they’re on your plate every single day,” she said. Let’s take a look.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="6"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="7"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Mustard greens&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; Eat your greens, especially mustard greens. These tiny greens are at the top of Agarwal’s winter food list. “They are rich in antioxidants like A, C, and K. Very good for immunity and heart health because they are naturally high in fibre, support digestion, and prevent constipation,” she said. Mustard greens belong to the Brassicaceae family. A recent study by researchers at Nanjing Agricultural University found that Brassica vegetables, including broccoli, kale, cabbage, and mustard greens, contain numerous phytonutrients.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; The study, published in the journal &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="em" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Horticulture Research&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;, found that the glucosinolates, vitamins, carotenoids, phenolics, and essential minerals can &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://academic.oup.com/hr/article/12/2/uhae302/7849786" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;reduce the risk of cancer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, cardiovascular disease, and other chronic conditions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="15"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="lOvcW vdo_embedd"&gt;&lt;div class="k7lcu"&gt;&lt;p class="efT4r"&gt;7 Foods that boost immunity before winter sets in&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="17"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="18"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Gond (edible gum)&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; The second on the nutritionist’s list is Gond, or edible gum. A personal favourite winter food, Agarwal swears by gond ladoos. This edible gum is a natural resin obtained from the sap of acacia trees. “It helps you to maintain your body heat and provides energy. The presence of magnesium and zinc improves your immune system. Rich in calcium, it supports your bone health, and the presence of zinc and magnesium makes your immune system robust,” she said. The nutritionist also added that the gum acts as a galactagogue and naturally improves milk production.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="23"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="24"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Indian gooseberries&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; Indian gooseberry, or amla, is known for its numerous health benefits. An excellent source of vitamin C, this fruit also has potential antioxidant and heart-health benefits. A 2015 study published in the journal &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="em" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Oxidative Medicine and Cellular Longevity&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; found that gooseberry has potential &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1155/2015/950890" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;anticancer properties&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;. “It is very rich in vitamin C. But did you know that vitamin C in all fruits and vegetables starts getting oxidised after you cut it? But in amla, oxidation of vitamin C is very slow,” the nutritionist said. Consuming this fruit during winter boosts immunity and also improves hair and skin health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="32"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="33"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Sesame&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; Another kitchen staple, sesame, used in both sweet and savoury dishes, is a superfood. “Sesame seeds are thermogenic, meaning they naturally generate heat in your body. They have the highest calcium content among all seeds — 975 mg in just 100 grams,” she said. A 2012 American Heart Association meeting report also found that sesame oil is linked to a significant &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://newsroom.heart.org/news/sesame-and-rice-bran-oil-lowers-238424" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;drop in blood pressure and improved cholesterol levels&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="38"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="39"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Fresh turmeric&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; According to the nutritionist, turmeric, a popular spice used in Asian cuisines, is also a winter superfood. She noted that this yellow-coloured spice “is rich in antioxidants, has anti-inflammatory properties, and boosts your immunity.” A 2023 review of several studies has shown that turmeric contains several bioactive compounds that &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S2667142523000088" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;improve gut health&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; and the immune system. Agarwal revealed that she likes to add turmeric to her tea. “My winter tea is made from grated ginger and turmeric, maybe half and half a teaspoon, and by adding a little bit of honey and lime to it. This winter tea reduces gas and bloating, and is one of the best anti-inflammatory drinks you can have in the winter,” she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="43"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="44"&gt;&lt;i&gt;Note: The information provided in this article is for educational purposes only and is not intended as medical advice. Always consult a qualified healthcare professional before starting any new medication or treatment, or before changing your diet or supplement regimen.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="45"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 11:55:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilgJBVV95cUxNMS1CS0xRY3FwRUZCQzNyUWgzc1ZhVjczZjZKd0RrWjJBZVNYVk5pY3U4LXRSUzU5U3dXM0JoV0Zmb1FNWUtMcVlQS0FDZ01rZUxZNDhIQy1NSGJRNnI3TmpOMTMxSFdqbjZzVk5SazNJTG1xd04tYWdDcUJlc25xcWwxa1RCVE9DaXBQdlZjd2JUNHFOMTZJN3U4TlBWUFUxM1JVYll0OWVkRTRYUk5Xa1JIZ08xTi1LV0hiMEFOblRIT253ZkozZUM1RFhmdU9OSGtOUEEwVENBWHhjLUx3RHNxc3BGb3RsTXJLUHU4WVY3bEdOdHZDaXBPRDA1V1hBeExoN3N5UWZuQVZUQ251WDBNNFYyUQ</guid></item><item><title>慢性打鼾如何给心脏带来风险：早期迹象、原因和早期诊断的必要性-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/how-chronic-snoring-might-signal-risks-to-heart-early-signs-causes-and-the-need-for-early-diagnosis/articleshow/125664109.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Snoring is often treated as a minor nuisance, tolerated by partners or household members rather than the individual themselves. Yet habitual snoring can indicate a much more serious condition known as Obstructive Sleep Apnea (OSA). In OSA, the airway repeatedly collapses during sleep, causing intermittent pauses in breathing, drops in oxygen levels, and fragmented rest. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/reel/DRnpXqEgh_z/?utm_source=ig_web_copy_link&amp;amp;igsh=NTc4MTIwNjQ2YQ==" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;Dr. Kunal Sood highlighted this in an Instagram video&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, stating, “When you find out chronic snoring doesn’t just keep your partner up, it can signal Obstructive Sleep Apnea (OSA), linked to higher risks of high blood pressure, stroke, and heart failure.” Recognising snoring as a potential warning sign is vital, as early detection and intervention can significantly reduce the risk of long-term health complications and improve overall wellbeing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="7"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="9"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="10"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Symptoms and early signs of obstructive sleep apnea&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="11"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;OSA can develop gradually, making early recognition essential. Common symptoms include:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="13"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="14"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Loud, persistent snoring that occurs most nights and can disrupt sleep for others. Chronic snoring is often the first noticeable signal of underlying airway obstruction.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="15"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="16"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Pauses in breathing during sleep, sometimes observed by a partner, with gaps lasting several seconds to a minute.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="17"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="18"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Abrupt awakenings or gasping episodes caused by the body’s reflex to reopen the airway, often leaving the individual unaware of the disturbance.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="19"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="20"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Excessive daytime sleepiness despite apparently sufficient sleep hours, which may affect concentration, productivity, and daily functioning.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="21"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="22"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Morning headaches, sometimes caused by repeated drops in oxygen or elevated blood pressure during the night.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="23"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="24"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Cognitive difficulties, including memory lapses, poor attention, and slower reaction times.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="25"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="26"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Mood changes, such as irritability, anxiety, or reduced patience, linked to the cumulative effects of disrupted sleep.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="27"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;A comprehensive review &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.mdpi.com/2077-0383/13/11/3223" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;published in the Journal of Clinical Medicine&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; confirms that the combination of snoring and daytime fatigue often precedes cardiovascular complications, emphasising the need for vigilance. Early detection of these symptoms allows for timely evaluation and intervention, reducing the potential for long-term harm. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="31"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many people mistake these symptoms as harmless, but sleep specialists note that habitual, vibrating snoring, especially when paired with fatigue, choking episodes or irregular breathing, often reflects airway collapse linked to OSA, poor sleep quality and nighttime oxygen drops.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="34"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="35"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Causes of obstructive sleep apnea&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="36"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;OSA develops when the airway collapses or becomes partially blocked during sleep, preventing normal airflow. Several contributing factors increase the risk:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="38"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="39"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Excess body weight, particularly fat deposits around the neck, which can compress the airway and increase obstruction.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Enlarged tonsils or adenoids, especially common in children and younger adults, which physically narrow the airway.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Structural anomalies, such as a small jaw, recessed chin, or deviated septum, which predispose individuals to airway collapse.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Age-related muscle tone reduction, which allows throat muscles to relax more than usual during sleep.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Lifestyle factors, including smoking, excessive alcohol consumption, and chronic nasal congestion, which exacerbate airway instability.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Genetic predisposition, as family members may share similar airway anatomy or body types that increase vulnerability.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="40"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Understanding these causes is critical to identify those at risk and implement early strategies, whether through lifestyle adjustments, weight management, or medical interventions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="42"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="43"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Risks associated with untreated obstructive sleep apnea&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="44"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;If OSA remains unaddressed, it can lead to severe health consequences:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="46"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="47"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Hypertension, caused by repeated oxygen drops and increased sympathetic nervous activity during apnoeic events.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Heart disease, including arrhythmias and structural changes in the heart, resulting from chronic cardiovascular stress.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Stroke, as intermittent hypoxia and vascular strain increase clot formation risk.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Heart failure, which may develop due to long-term overwork of the heart in response to oxygen deprivation.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Metabolic disorders, such as insulin resistance and worsening glucose control, increasing diabetes risk.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Cognitive impairment, including reduced memory, attention deficits, and slowed mental processing, which can affect work performance and daily functioning.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Daytime fatigue, leading to decreased productivity, impaired driving, and higher accident risk.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="48"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Individuals with pre-existing conditions like diabetes, high cholesterol, or obesity are particularly vulnerable, as OSA compounds the stress on cardiovascular and metabolic systems.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="51"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="52"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;The need for early diagnosis of obstructive sleep apnea&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="53"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Early diagnosis is crucial for effective management and reducing long-term health risks. Sleep studies, including in-lab polysomnography or home-based monitoring, measure breathing patterns, oxygen saturation, and sleep disruptions. Recognising snoring alongside symptoms such as daytime fatigue, morning headaches, or observed apnoeic events can prompt timely evaluation. Evidence suggests that treatment options, including continuous positive airway pressure (CPAP), oral devices, weight management, and lifestyle changes, can reduce the physiological stress caused by OSA, improving sleep quality and overall cardiovascular health. Routine screening in at-risk populations, particularly those with hypertension, obesity, or diabetes, is increasingly recommended as a preventive health measure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="57"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="58"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;When to consult a doctor about chronic snoring&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="59"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Medical consultation is recommended if individuals experience:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="61"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="62"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Persistent loud snoring that disturbs sleep regularly.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Pauses in breathing or gasping episodes during sleep, observed by partners or household members.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Daytime sleepiness or fatigue, affecting daily functioning or alertness.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Morning headaches, difficulty concentrating, or mood changes, suggesting disrupted oxygen supply during sleep.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="63"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Seeking professional evaluation from a sleep specialist or primary care physician can lead to appropriate diagnostic testing and a personalised management plan. Individuals with cardiovascular conditions, high blood pressure, or metabolic disorders should be particularly attentive, as early intervention can mitigate long-term health risks. Addressing OSA promptly helps improve sleep quality, daytime alertness, and overall wellbeing, highlighting the importance of recognising snoring as a potential early warning sign rather than a trivial annoyance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="65"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="em" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Disclaimer: This article is for general informational purposes only and is not a substitute for professional medical advice, diagnosis, or treatment. Always seek the guidance of a qualified healthcare provider regarding any medical condition or lifestyle change.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="67"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="68"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="69"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Also Read | &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/why-non-smokers-in-delhi-are-facing-rising-lung-cancer-risks/articleshow/125663647.cms" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;Why non-smokers in Delhi are facing rising lung cancer risks&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 11:40:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipgJBVV95cUxPN3FZdzNWdFRjdEhYeURLLXZrdmx6N3BSbDF2Q1k4NE8xbHpucU5zMGoyYlVKcEhPUGFCQ1ZFSmZOeTFDTk1TMjNSaWJZZVRxcndWVDVXa2NSdEUzV2l0eGRieXc0NjltOG1PdjNIVVU1dmhPZjF2NENPMmhLVE5Ma3hRVUZjRkRSazV0RWdJajNrTFNlSlFUenhfLUxzNGUyU1RFMVROSjl3T3N1NHhpQ0ZJa3F6X25hNkRTLXh5M04tNDRNX3lMLXNyU3dGS1BRSXc0cnRTWkR1VEJmcVo1Mk9NMDZ3eGRzYjRBdXV1YjZDUUg4NzFJWlYwZndFU2VIdkp3WTViMVNKckEzQWdySDBkQzhTQk93TDY5SG1hSkd3anF1T2fSAasCQVVfeXFMT0lEa2NUNlZ5MUNaaWtld3p5eHVQOUtfajNDNGZiX2dlNnJiN1JWYkJPY19iNUFsMjRnblp2bldnMVhyc2R3VWh3NEtUcVN2VmFVMmplNjlzYWpCb3RqTGlZWjZQTWs2b01BbGx1MHhpZzhCWDJ2MXBYaTgzcmNiWWtIRE1XdTc4SjBzaFlGdWNNcFB1c3F3OW1DWThEV0FyNlZCU0hxTXdUOGV2YXlJczhpSE12SGQyQWcyalAwZ1Q4Q04zd2dqZG5OQ05kZWUzVnZ1Z1hoNGQzWURHZW5wTG1iTkEzTGhfVzNETXFXM0NJMmVidV82VGhEelZIdHhMMWlMd0VFMHlXaHRULWg0S3NFRlZWOC12a3dHQVdyVFV0ZFRucnFHdDYwaTg</guid></item><item><title>微塑料和Forever Chemicals无处不在，包括您的水-这款水壶有助于过滤它们- EatingWell</title><link>https://www.eatingwell.com/lifestraw-water-filter-pitcher-amazon-11857656</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-page_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-page mntl-block structured-content" data-sc-sticky-offset="90" data-sc-ad-label-height="24" data-sc-ad-track-spacing="100" data-sc-min-track-height="250" data-sc-max-track-height="600" data-sc-breakpoint="50em" data-sc-load-immediate="4" data-sc-content-positions="[1, 1250, 1550, 1950, 2350, 2750, 3150, 3550, 3950]" data-bind-scroll-on-start="true"&gt;&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Water is something we all need. There are quite a few side effects &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/292133/10-dangerous-side-effects-of-not-drinking-enough-water/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;if you don’t drink enough every day&lt;/a&gt;. Not only can you experience brain fog, low energy, mood swings and weakness, but it can also lead to headaches, weight gain, an increased risk of stroke, a slower metabolism, overeating and skin damage. While &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/how-much-water-you-should-drink-daily-11739359" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;optimal hydration&lt;/a&gt; can vary from person to person, we generally recommend that women drink 11.5 cups of water per day, while men should aim for 15.5 cups. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_2-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_3-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; The only issue? Water doesn’t always taste good, &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/8072180/why-does-some-water-taste-better-than-others/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;nor does it taste the same&lt;/a&gt; everywhere. There can be unwanted minerals and even &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/why-is-the-california-prop-65-warning-label-on-my-food-containers-8420160" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;forever chemicals&lt;/a&gt; that make it far less motivating to pour a glass. The easiest solution is to invest in a &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/dp/B09R6211QP?tag=eatingwell-onsite-backup-20" data-component="amazon" data-source="affiliate" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="3" rel="sponsored nofollow noskim"&gt;water filter pitcher&lt;/a&gt;, and we found what might be the perfect one. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_4-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-lifestraw-home-water-pitcher"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_5-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; LifeStraw Home Water Pitcher &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure id="mntl-sc-block_6-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image--no-theme no-theme figure-landscape figure-high-res"&gt; 
&lt;figcaption id="mntl-figure-caption_1-0" class="comp mntl-figure-caption text-utility-100 figure-article-caption"&gt; &lt;span class="figure-article-caption-owner"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Amazon&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_8-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_9-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; The LifeStraw is a sleek, double-filtered water pitcher that claims to remove all unwanted impurities from your water. It’s made from glass, meaning your risk of adding &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/scientist-recommended-plastic-kitchen-tools-to-replace-amazon-11720768" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;additional microplastics&lt;/a&gt; from the container itself is mitigated. It does have a plastic BPA-free filter system, although it’s challenging to find a water filter pitcher without one, unfortunately. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_10-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_11-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; So, how does it work, exactly? The top section of the white insert includes a tall, slim membrane filter that removes microplastics, and potentially bacteria, according to the brand. Once the water passes through this filter, it makes its way through a carbon and ion exchange filter that can eliminate chemicals like PFAs (aka forever chemicals), lead, mercury and other heavy metals. LifeStraw claims that between the two filters, you’ll be weeding out over 30 contaminants while still maintaining the presence of minerals like magnesium and potassium. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_12-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_13-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; The membrane filter needs replacing once a year, and the carbon and ion filter every two months. Thankfully, the initial purchase of the pitcher includes filters, plus the brand sells a year's worth of filters in a &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/LifeStraw-Complete-Replacement-Membrane-Microfilter/dp/B092DN3W2B?tag=eatingwell-onsite-backup-20" data-component="amazon" data-source="affiliate" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1" rel="sponsored nofollow noskim"&gt;convenient kit&lt;/a&gt; for repurchase. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_14-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_15-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; This particular bottle holds up to 7 cups of water. It has a nifty spout on top and a flip-top lid to refill it easily. And, to make sure it doesn’t move around, the base is fitted with a removable silicone sleeve. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_16-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_17-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Amazon shoppers rave about this pitcher’s “&lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/gp/customer-reviews/RUSCBYPKJDST3?tag=eatingwell-onsite-backup-20" data-component="amazon" data-source="affiliate" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1" rel="sponsored nofollow noskim"&gt;perfect&lt;/a&gt;” design. “I have used numerous water filter pitchers over the years from numerous brands. This is by far the best-designed one as well as the one that produces the best-tasting filtered water,” &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/gp/customer-reviews/RSZ6EPDW7X08E?tag=eatingwell-onsite-backup-20" data-component="amazon" data-source="affiliate" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="2" rel="sponsored nofollow noskim"&gt;one reviewer wrote&lt;/a&gt;. “You can actually fill this one with water and use it immediately after without unfiltered water being poured out.” 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_18-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_19-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; “I notice a stark difference between water before the filter and after the filter,” a &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/gp/customer-reviews/R22YF1L1CT9XV4?tag=eatingwell-onsite-backup-20" data-component="amazon" data-source="affiliate" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1" rel="sponsored nofollow noskim"&gt;third person&lt;/a&gt; added, speaking to the filters’ effectiveness. “We like the design, how easy it is to clean and how easy it is to replace the filters,” a &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/gp/customer-reviews/R1M5AFUBJ6537M?tag=eatingwell-onsite-backup-20" data-component="amazon" data-source="affiliate" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="2" rel="sponsored nofollow noskim"&gt;fourth shopper&lt;/a&gt; noted. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_20-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_21-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; For cleaner water that’ll help you hit those necessary hydration goals, opt for the smart &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/LifeStraw-Home-Protection-parasites-microplastics/dp/B09R6211QP?tag=eatingwell-onsite-backup-20" data-component="amazon" data-source="affiliate" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1" rel="sponsored nofollow noskim"&gt;LifeStraw water pitcher&lt;/a&gt;. While it runs for $49, it’s undoubtedly “&lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/gp/customer-reviews/R1RA3788I14XH6?tag=eatingwell-onsite-backup-20" data-component="amazon" data-source="affiliate" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="2" rel="sponsored nofollow noskim"&gt;worth the money&lt;/a&gt;." 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_22-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-shop-more-glass-water-pitchers-on-amazon"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_23-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Shop More Glass Water Pitchers on Amazon &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-waterdrop-7-cup-glass-water-filter-pitcher"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_24-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Waterdrop 7-Cup Glass Water Filter Pitcher &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure id="mntl-sc-block_25-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image--no-theme no-theme figure-landscape figure-high-res"&gt; 
&lt;figcaption id="mntl-figure-caption_2-0" class="comp mntl-figure-caption text-utility-100 figure-article-caption"&gt; &lt;span class="figure-article-caption-owner"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Amazon&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_27-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-waterdrop-glass-large-22-cup-rechargeable-water-filter-dispenser"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_28-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Waterdrop Glass Large 22-Cup Rechargeable Water Filter Dispenser &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure id="mntl-sc-block_29-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image--no-theme no-theme figure-landscape figure-high-res"&gt; 
&lt;figcaption id="mntl-figure-caption_3-0" class="comp mntl-figure-caption text-utility-100 figure-article-caption"&gt; &lt;span class="figure-article-caption-owner"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Amazon&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_31-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-zerowater-40-cup-ready-pour-glass-water-filter-dispenser"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_32-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; ZeroWater 40-Cup Ready-Pour Glass Water Filter Dispenser &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure id="mntl-sc-block_33-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image--no-theme no-theme figure-landscape figure-high-res"&gt; 
&lt;figcaption id="mntl-figure-caption_4-0" class="comp mntl-figure-caption text-utility-100 figure-article-caption"&gt; &lt;span class="figure-article-caption-owner"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Amazon&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_35-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-aarke-purifier-5-cup-glass-water-pitcher"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_36-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Aarke Purifier 5-Cup Glass Water Pitcher &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure id="mntl-sc-block_37-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image--no-theme no-theme figure-landscape figure-high-res"&gt; 
&lt;figcaption id="mntl-figure-caption_5-0" class="comp mntl-figure-caption text-utility-100 figure-article-caption"&gt; &lt;span class="figure-article-caption-owner"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Amazon&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_39-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_40-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;em&gt;At the time of publishing, the price was $49.&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>EatingWell</author><pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 11:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMifkFVX3lxTE1Sb1dFQXlOX1pKRW5rNVp4NnY2cmV0bE5rRXZhMGhHM1ZwSUx0QS0zWXNCTEpSa2VXQVBTYk5WaDI0cllXemZ4bEZoMlpZQVJ1UzFHdF90UVprdDJjdnlYdndRblJ1cmtKSnJJQXhsQzkzRXNIenhIRnB2Mld1Zw</guid></item><item><title>为什么有些记忆会持续一生，而其他记忆会快速褪色- ScienceDaily</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/11/251130050712.htm</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p id="first" class="lead"&gt;Every day, the brain turns passing impressions, creative sparks, and emotional experiences into lasting memories that shape our identity and guide our decisions. A central question in neuroscience has been how the brain determines which pieces of information are worth storing and how long those memories should remain.&lt;/p&gt;

						&lt;div id="text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Recent findings show that long-term memories form through a sequence of molecular timing mechanisms that activate across different parts of the brain. Using a virtual reality behavioral system in mice, scientists identified regulatory factors that help move memories into increasingly stable states or allow them to fade entirely.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A study published in &lt;em&gt;Nature&lt;/em&gt; highlights how several brain regions work together to reorganize memories over time, with checkpoints that help assess how significant each memory is and how durable it should be.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"This is a key revelation because it explains how we adjust the durability of memories," says Priya Rajasethupathy, head of the Skoler Horbach Family Laboratory of Neural Dynamics and Cognition. "What we choose to remember is a continuously evolving process rather than a one-time flipping of a switch."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Moving Beyond the Classic Memory Model&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For many years, researchers focused on two primary memory centers: the hippocampus, which supports short-term memory, and the cortex, which was believed to store long-term memories. These long-term memories were thought to sit behind biological on-and-off switches.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Existing models of memory in the brain involved transistor-like memory molecules that act as on/off switches," says Rajasethupathy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="insertion_middle"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This older view suggested that once a memory was marked for long-term storage, it would persist indefinitely. Although this framework provided useful insights, it did not explain why some long-term memories last for weeks while others remain vivid for decades.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A Key Pathway Linking Short and Long-Term Memory&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In 2023, Rajasethupathy and colleagues described a brain circuit that connects short-term and long-term memory systems. A central element of this pathway is the thalamus, which helps determine which memories should be kept and directs them to the cortex for long-term stabilization.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These discoveries opened the door to deeper questions: What happens to memories once they leave the hippocampus, and what molecular processes decide whether a memory becomes lasting or disappears?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Virtual Reality Experiments Reveal Memory Persistence&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To investigate these mechanisms, the team built a virtual reality setup that allowed mice to form specific memories. "Andrea Terceros, a postdoc in my lab, created an elegant behavioral model allowed us to break open this problem in a new way," Rajasethupathy says. "By varying how often certain experiences were repeated, we were able to get the mice to remember some things better than others, and then look into the brain to see what mechanisms were correlated with memory persistence."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Correlation alone could not answer the key questions, so co-lead Celine Chen created a CRISPR-based screening platform to alter gene activity in the thalamus and cortex. This approach showed that removing certain molecules changed how long memories lasted, and each molecule operated on its own timescale.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="insertion_bottom"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Timed Programs Guide Memory Stability&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The results indicate that long-term memory relies not on a single on/off switch, but on a sequence of gene-regulating programs that unfold like molecular timers across the brain.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Early timers activate quickly but fade fast, allowing memories to disappear. Later timers turn on more gradually, giving important experiences the structural support needed to persist. In this study, repetition served as a stand-in for importance, letting researchers compare frequently repeated contexts with those seen only occasionally.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The team identified three transcriptional regulators essential for maintaining memories: Camta1 and Tcf4 in the thalamus, and Ash1l in the anterior cingulate cortex. These molecules are not required to form the initial memory but are crucial for preserving it. Disrupting Camta1 and Tcf4 weakened connections between the thalamus and cortex and caused memory loss.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;According to the model, memory formation begins in the hippocampus. Camta1 and its downstream targets help keep that early memory intact. Over time, Tcf4 and its targets activate to strengthen cell adhesion and structural support. Finally, Ash1l promotes chromatin remodeling programs that reinforce memory stability.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Unless you promote memories onto these timers, we believe you're primed to forget it quickly," Rajasethupathy says.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Shared Memory Mechanisms Across Biology&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ash1l is part of a protein family known as histone methyltransferases, which help maintain memory-like functions in other systems. "In the immune system, these molecules help the body remember past infections; during development, those same molecules help cells remember that they've become a neuron or muscle and maintain that identity long-term," Rajasethupathy says. "The brain may be repurposing these ubiquitous forms of cellular memory to support cognitive memories."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These discoveries may eventually help researchers address memory-related diseases. Rajasethupathy suggests that, by understanding the gene programs that preserve memory, scientists may be able to redirect memory pathways around damaged brain regions in conditions such as Alzheimer's. "If we know the second and third areas that are important for memory consolidation, and we have neurons dying in the first area, perhaps we can bypass the damaged region and let healthy parts of the brain take over," she says.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Next Steps: Decoding the Memory Timer System&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rajasethupathy's team now aims to uncover how these molecular timers are activated and what determines their duration. This includes investigating how the brain evaluates the importance of a memory and decides how long it should last. Their work continues to point toward the thalamus as a central hub in this decision-making process.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"We're interested in understanding the life of a memory beyond its initial formation in the hippocampus," Rajasethupathy says. "We think the thalamus, and its parallel streams of communication with cortex, are central in this process."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

					&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceDaily</author><pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 11:15:07 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMib0FVX3lxTE1RQ0FZWklFeVptb1RfclhRc0pTd1lMTWR5U2VtY0s1WUNaZV83X24yQVJaYkFXU2Z3U2tmeHBlb3dKYUpmclFkZ0JkYWIwa3FlNHliRHNsa25EZ292YXkzMUNLX2Y5b29ra0lXcFU0NA</guid></item><item><title>英国中世纪皮肤病爆发导致患者皮肤“爬行” - LADbible</title><link>https://www.ladbible.com/news/uk-news/scabies-outbreak-uk-devon-school-closed-434211-20251130</link><description>&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p class="loading-bar_loader__2fNms"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;main&gt;&lt;template id="B:0"&gt;&lt;/template&gt;&lt;p class="article-page-skeleton_background__h2J4n"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/main&gt;&lt;/body&gt;</description><author>LADbible</author><pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 10:13:31 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimAFBVV95cUxPS2Znc2Zvc0ZVQTQyaHEtSzFuMHpEM3dYa2pkSVFjckQ0Nk14YTBxcHZNWWVYZ2otekkySGVSa1R2bDM3eWhpQVU3MjUyNGNCWHVpd1I1bGQxcWtCb0IwMkhOMjF1WUEwRnlCcDJZSFl4eWc4dV81Uk1CSUo5dXNTRW1WQnBZQVhfeDVrRllKMTI2cDkzSmt4OA</guid></item><item><title>如何在寒冷的冬季增加卡路里消耗的棕色脂肪- BBC</title><link>https://www.bbc.com/future/article/20251128-how-to-boost-your-calorie-crunching-brown-fat-in-the-cold-winter-months</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="sc-85f9acf9-0 kfxpiP"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;However, it's possible that, while brown fat might not help you shed the pounds, it could still boost your health in other ways. For instance, instead of burning calories, brown fat could help &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.pnas.org/doi/10.1073/pnas.2216435119" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;to improve metabolic health&lt;/a&gt; – the body’s ability to process and use energy from food effectively. People who have poor metabolic health are unable to clear glucose from their blood quickly, raising their risk of type 2 diabetes. Brown fat could act simply by taking up glucose from the bloodstream, or by secreting hormones that act on other tissues to regulate insulin sensitivity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"In terms of whole-body energy expenditure, it [brown fat] probably does not play as large of a role in humans as it does in mice," says Cohen. "So my personal feeling, based on the data, is that brown fat activation is not going to be a good means to treat obesity or to lose significant amounts of weight." &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"However, the data is much stronger to suggest that activating brown fat might lower glucose levels and improve metabolic health. So, I think if there is going to be a therapeutic side to this, it's much more likely going to be in treating the complications of obesity and ageing than in treating obesity per se."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="sc-2b8ea91d-0 faEbjU"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-2b8ea91d-2 ejktow"&gt;The shock of cold-water immersion causes the body to think it's in danger&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;But how can we activate brown fat, and harness the superpowers it may – or may not – contain? One way is to expose yourself to cold, as uncomfortable as it may be. Think ice baths, cold water swimming, or cryotherapy chambers – a specialised device that exposes the body to extremely low temperatures for one to three minutes to promote healing and wellness. The shock of cold-water immersion causes the body to think it's in danger, activating the fight-or-flight response. This releases the neurotransmitter noradrenalin, which binds to and "activates" brown fat cells.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BBC</author><pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMitgFBVV95cUxOajZuN2h4MjBvaUFJZ25lNmNKU2steGpQS2M0Qk50OGZaVEdta0duTEJwWWJ1a056X2FFbGZ1My1MMURHNVN1UWtSQnAzWGYtNzM0bWdYR3R3QUk3M0ZlTlRwSUVaRkVwUUN6aXF4ZDljSV9vQk9Ta1NZRkl5akFKVXlrMHVLUDJoQTNzSlBQanluRGlKWC1SbUs5NUs2c3FYbHpVVTYyS0MtS2dlUTdmYW5NRTVDQQ</guid></item></channel></rss>