<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>GNews Health</title><link>https://news.google.com/</link><description></description><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>Human bodies have 'head-to-toe' microbiomes that are unique like fingerprints - Earth.com</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMilgFBVV95cUxNUGZLSDBlT0xHQ3l4T0dXeGtCeHY1OXJhRUJ1MUJLcnAybEdMd2V1RUdETEIzNTduVTg3SUU1TDdoRjhkeXRzZklmeDBadlpyQWhmaHJiX1d3TUNIMTlzSkdKVnBwREp5eW5wWnd4VThyYUEyWEdUNlZDMDFLRlRFS2dEcE1YX204dnZJM2FKSWZkVzdXenc?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="page_content__AwOj6"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Trillions of bacteria occupy human bodies – from head to toe, inside and out – forming a microbiome that is as personal as a fingerprint. Each individual’s microbial mix affects digestion, immunity, and many other human processes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For six years, scientists tracked the microbiomes of people ranging from 29 to 75 years old. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They collected samples from the gut, mouth, nose, and skin, observing how these organisms changed during short-term illnesses, chronic conditions, and daily life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Michael Snyder, Ph.D., from &lt;a href="https://www.stanford.edu" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Stanford University&lt;/a&gt; and director of the Stanford Center for Genomics and Personalized Medicine, led this wide-ranging effort with the late George Weinstock at &lt;a href="https://www.jax.org/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Jackson Laboratory&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-trillions-of-microbes-shape-who-we-are"&gt;Trillions of microbes shape who we are&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Researchers confirm that the human microbiome contains about 39 trillion microbes. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Our results underscore the idea that we each have individualized microbiomes in our bodies that are special to us,” Snyder states. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Genes, diet, and the &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/sleep-may-be-the-best-strategy-to-boost-your-immune-system/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;immune system&lt;/a&gt; all shape these communities, which vary greatly between people.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This diversity matters for health. Each person’s bacteria respond to internal factors, refuting any notion that everyone shares identical microbial residents. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Investigators suggest that understanding these differences could open new possibilities for personalized care.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-temporary-microbial-changes-observed"&gt;Temporary microbial changes observed&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Over 5,432 biological samples produced more than 118 million measurements. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Scientists used genetic sequencing to identify microbial populations during routine checkups or unusual events, such as vaccinations or &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/antibiotic-resistance-increasing-enterococci-looming-global-crisis/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;antibiotic use&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Xin Zhou, Ph.D., notes, “People with Type 2 diabetes showed a less stable and less diverse microbiome,” hinting that limited variety may connect with certain illnesses.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Short-term infections caused temporary disruptions. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“We found that when you get sick with something like a cold, you have this temporary change in the microbiome; it becomes &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/antibiotic-resistance-could-cause-a-health-crisis-globally/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;very dysregulated&lt;/a&gt;,” Zhou explained. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“With diabetes, that signature is the same in many ways except that it is long-term rather than temporary.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-personal-microbes-are-the-most-stable"&gt;Personal microbes are the most stable&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another finding challenged expectations about which bacteria remain most consistent. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“A lot of people would suspect that the bacteria shared among us would be the most important and thus the most stable. We found the complete opposite – the personal microbiome is the most stable,” Snyder expounded.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Researchers discovered that unique &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/household-plumbing-is-full-of-microbial-communities-that-might-be-a-health-risk/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;microbial communities&lt;/a&gt; within each person often stay steady despite environmental influences. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This insight highlights how individual baselines shape resilience during illness or dietary changes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-interconnection-across-human-microbiomes"&gt;Interconnection across human microbiomes&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shifts in the nose, mouth, or skin coincided with changes in the gut, suggesting that these microbes behave like “a single, fluid system,” according to Snyder. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Certain immune proteins in the blood moved in sync with these shifts, indicating strong ties between microbial balance and immune reactions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Environmental factors, including humidity and seasonal effects, influenced &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/warming-waters-are-dramatically-changing-microbial-life-in-antarctica/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;microbial composition&lt;/a&gt; but could not explain the large differences seen across participants. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study underscores that each person’s body creates a unique habitat for bacteria, making it hard to define a universal standard.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-why-does-the-human-microbiome-matter"&gt;Why does the human microbiome matter?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Scientists propose that the &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/deep-meditation-transforms-gut-microbes-for-optimal-health/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;composition and stability&lt;/a&gt; of a person’s microbiome may help predict how they respond to illnesses or treatments. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The microbiome varies enormously between people. How you feed it and what it’s exposed to probably makes a big impact on your health, and we still have to work that out in many ways,” Snyder concluded.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Insights from this work point to individualized strategies that account for specific microbial features. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;By focusing on personal baselines, future research may offer medical guidance tailored to each individual’s microbes, potentially improving &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/gut-microbes-have-an-unexpected-link-to-anxiety/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;long-term wellness&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-evolution-of-scientific-understanding"&gt;Evolution of scientific understanding&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Interest in microbes dates back to the late 1600s, when early microscopes revealed tiny organisms in water droplets. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For centuries, scientists concentrated on harmful bacteria, overlooking beneficial ones. Over time, researchers uncovered the &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/nasa-says-the-international-space-station-is-too-clean-add-microbes/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;importance of friendly bacteria&lt;/a&gt; that assist with immune function.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The term “microbiome” gained traction in the early 2000s, accompanied by growing awareness that these microbial residents are not merely passengers. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ongoing projects, including broad genetic investigations, have shown that microbial diversity can shift with diet, medications, and aging. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This evolution in understanding has prompted deeper studies into how each person’s bacterial signature may influence everything from metabolism to mood.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-what-happens-next"&gt;What happens next?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Experts see ways to use microbiome knowledge in personalized medical plans, &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/chocolate-could-be-the-next-probiotic-powerhouse/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;designing probiotics&lt;/a&gt; or targeted therapies for each person. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some researchers suggest that small changes, like altering meal routines, might strengthen bacterial communities that enhance metabolic health. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Others propose monitoring microbial markers to identify subtle shifts before chronic conditions take hold.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Scientists continue to probe how gut microbes connect to the brain through chemical signals, raising questions about links to mental well-being. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Investigators are also examining &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/secrets-of-aging-have-been-found-in-the-skin-microbiome/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;skin microorganisms&lt;/a&gt; to see if they affect issues like dryness or irritation. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As methods for genetic analysis improve, more precise mapping of these bacterial populations may offer fresh approaches for supporting long-term health without a one-size-fits-all framework.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-human-microbiome-and-future-health"&gt;Human microbiome and future health&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Growing interest in this field suggests that bacteria can influence nutrient processing. Studies look beyond the gut, revealing microbial identities in body areas.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Variety appears vital, prompting further work on how personal bacterial communities support resilience. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Simple lifestyle shifts may nurture helpful microbes, guiding approaches that honor each person’s unique health profile.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While these microbial mysteries continue to unfold, it’s clear that our personal armies of bacteria deserve more attention in the pursuit of better, individualized care.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These findings, published in &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cell.com/cell-host-microbe/fulltext/S1931-3128(24)00056-8" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Cell Host &amp;amp; Microbe&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;, are part of the &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41586-019-1238-8" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Integrative Human Microbiome Project&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;—–&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Like what you read? &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/subscribe/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Subscribe to our newsletter&lt;/a&gt; for engaging articles, exclusive content, and the latest updates.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Check us out on &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/earthsnap/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;EarthSnap&lt;/a&gt;, a free app brought to you by &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/author/eralls/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Eric Ralls&lt;/a&gt; and Earth.com.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;—–&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Earth.com</author><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 12:11:39 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilgFBVV95cUxNUGZLSDBlT0xHQ3l4T0dXeGtCeHY1OXJhRUJ1MUJLcnAybEdMd2V1RUdETEIzNTduVTg3SUU1TDdoRjhkeXRzZklmeDBadlpyQWhmaHJiX1d3TUNIMTlzSkdKVnBwREp5eW5wWnd4VThyYUEyWEdUNlZDMDFLRlRFS2dEcE1YX204dnZJM2FKSWZkVzdXenc</guid></item><item><title>Woman, 84, is 'cured' of terminal lung cancer...and shocked doctors have fascinating theory - Daily Mail</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMisAFBVV95cUxQNUdvU1JfQ2RXY1dGR0V1WDljODNyMVVpdkdhSDFKS3dRVkFweFF3X0RocWJoVElCcHpXckpTZHNxTkpBM1AtNkJ6N01fbXJrMVBtQk1HNHVWZVp4Ykw0VVZwSjBKeXlIUWhOelE3dGNSMnBtelExTndzTGpLQkVTcmU1TlZtTEFrQ2F0cE96MUZNeDZvbEZlZWtuWVIxQlg2WkJ5NWJmOWt0eWZoR0JWbNIBtgFBVV95cUxQdklWZHcwVWJVYXB3RWRqZnpuWnRnclByWEJadUxJOGZOM3U2NHlheXUxV2VwYXhld0xLeUU4R3liZnNSTW5LTjVQSjJ2cEl3YVllTDlZZUpkUThrdHhUYU1TR1JWekNmd1dZWmdkNC1sbDFGYkxyZDZ0Q0MtU3ZBYzEtTUZEdm9OcnRtTVQ5YW80MktBcFFiMDJCbGRIclJNMG1YZUZuQ1h3UmV5ZzBIMVQzdEdtZw?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div itemprop="articleBody"&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;A &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/utah/index.html" id="mol-a6bd1860-0e23-11f0-a7a4-ff1614c058e1"&gt;Utah&lt;/a&gt; grandmother given just six months to live after she was diagnosed with an aggressive lung &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/cancer/index.html" id="mol-a6b37b70-0e23-11f0-a7a4-ff1614c058e1" class=""&gt;cancer&lt;/a&gt; has confounded doctors by seemingly beating the disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Dukhi Hong, 84, was devastated when she was diagnosed with small cell lung cancer in 2019.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Medics told her the rare cancer had spread to her brain and her family braced themselves to say their goodbyes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;However, last week she defied all expectations to receive her 100th immunotherapy dose.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'It feels like a dream,' the Korea-born patient told &lt;a class="" rel="nofollow noreferrer noopener" target="_blank" href="https://whnt.com/news/national/utah-woman-receives-100-cancer-treatments-living-far-beyond-doctors-expectations/"&gt;News19&lt;/a&gt; from the Salt Lake City hospital where she has been receiving treatment for the last six years. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The senior has further astounded doctors after her latest lung scan came back cancer-free.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'We certainly don't understand everything,' Dr. Stephan Kendall said, explaining that it could be the grandmother's immune system which has helped her respond so effectively to the drugs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Immunotherapy is a cancer treatment which uses the body's own immune system to fight carcinogenic cells. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;&lt;p class="clear"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Utah grandmother Dukhi Hong (center), who was given just six months to live after she was diagnosed with an aggressive lung cancer, has confounded doctors by 'beating' the disease&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'I've never had a patient receive 100 doses of any kind of treatment, honestly.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;While the outlook is promising, Hong is not completely in the clear year as small lung cell cancer can reoccur and is harder to treat second time around.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The scan also revealed some cancer in the brain, although at an early stage.&lt;br&gt;&lt;span&gt;'She's doing really well,' Dr. Kendall said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Hong was first diagnosed with cancer after she was hospitalized following a seizure.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span&gt;'Our whole world crashed,' her daughter, Mitzi Maughan, told &lt;a class="" rel="nofollow noreferrer noopener" target="_blank" href="https://www.news10.com/news/national/utah-woman-receives-100-cancer-treatments-living-far-beyond-doctors-expectations/amp/"&gt;KTVX.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span&gt;But Hong has always been a survivor, managing to make a whole new life for herself in the US after emigrating from Korea while seven months pregnant in 1965.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Seven years after her arrival, she became a single mom to her four children.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span&gt;'It was tough, but somehow, I just lived on,' she explained. &lt;/span&gt;'I didn't know how to speak English. I had just learned the ABCs.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Her resilience has stood in her good stead for the tough fight against her cancer, which includes monthly immunotherapy treatments.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Hong, 84, was devastated when she was diagnosed with small cell lung cancer in 2019&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;She began an intensive course of immunotherapy administered every three to four weeks which has proven extremely effective&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Her latest scans showed that there is no cancer in her lungs and only minimal cancer in her brain&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;While the sessions used to cause her family anxiety, they have learned to live with their new reality and now use it as an occasion to spend time with the beloved matriarch. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Her 100th dose was marked with a huge celebration featuring cake and balloons. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'She's our hero,'  Maughan added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Lung cancer kills more than 127,000 in the US each year, figures show. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Smoking is the most common cause of lung cancer, accounting for more than 70 percent of cases, according to health experts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;However, even people who have never smoked can also develop the disease, which mainly affects older people. More than four out of 10 people diagnosed are over 75.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;There are two main forms of the disease — non-small cell lung cancer (NSCLC) and small-cell lung cancer (SCLC).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The former accounts for eight in ten cases and is a less aggressive form of the disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Whereas the latter, small-cell lung cancer, is very aggressive and usually spreads faster. The survival rate tends to be lower for SCLC.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Hong arrived in the US while seven months pregnant in 1965 and set up a new life for herself&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Lung cancer kills more than 127,000 in the US each year, figures show&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The main warning signs of lung cancer can include having a persistent cough, such as one that doesn't go away after three weeks, or a long-standing cough which gets worse.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Breathlessness is another common sign, as well as recurrent or lingering chest infections.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Aches and pains when breathing or coughing, pain in your shoulder, or coughing up blood are also signs to watch out for.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Daily Mail</author><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 12:03:24 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMisAFBVV95cUxQNUdvU1JfQ2RXY1dGR0V1WDljODNyMVVpdkdhSDFKS3dRVkFweFF3X0RocWJoVElCcHpXckpTZHNxTkpBM1AtNkJ6N01fbXJrMVBtQk1HNHVWZVp4Ykw0VVZwSjBKeXlIUWhOelE3dGNSMnBtelExTndzTGpLQkVTcmU1TlZtTEFrQ2F0cE96MUZNeDZvbEZlZWtuWVIxQlg2WkJ5NWJmOWt0eWZoR0JWbNIBtgFBVV95cUxQdklWZHcwVWJVYXB3RWRqZnpuWnRnclByWEJadUxJOGZOM3U2NHlheXUxV2VwYXhld0xLeUU4R3liZnNSTW5LTjVQSjJ2cEl3YVllTDlZZUpkUThrdHhUYU1TR1JWekNmd1dZWmdkNC1sbDFGYkxyZDZ0Q0MtU3ZBYzEtTUZEdm9OcnRtTVQ5YW80MktBcFFiMDJCbGRIclJNMG1YZUZuQ1h3UmV5ZzBIMVQzdEdtZw</guid></item><item><title>If Vaccines Don’t Cause Autism, What Does? - The Wall Street Journal</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMijAFBVV95cUxQLWlCaXdhSU5aYXM2RnlfXy1lMnRQTllVYWdqb1dJYWx4YnU1enJRVHVISGRzRkNnaUlyd0NiV214aHVXZUMzX3Z2Z200dk56dmJwdnBjdjdfVFliX1FINWNlLUtMSEp5c241NlpMTC1JWEF1OW5teTd1QTlTVklnX2lqREQ4UGJrMENKRQ?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Wall Street Journal</author><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijAFBVV95cUxQLWlCaXdhSU5aYXM2RnlfXy1lMnRQTllVYWdqb1dJYWx4YnU1enJRVHVISGRzRkNnaUlyd0NiV214aHVXZUMzX3Z2Z200dk56dmJwdnBjdjdfVFliX1FINWNlLUtMSEp5c241NlpMTC1JWEF1OW5teTd1QTlTVklnX2lqREQ4UGJrMENKRQ</guid></item><item><title>The CDC buried a measles forecast that stressed the need for vaccinations - CNN</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMihwFBVV95cUxQdDQzbTlHUW9pemFXaTFvc2pqeXltbXNFM09uLXc4SGQxSkpVNmZqa3Q5OEU1cVFtaVZ2emo1cFZMclRYY0RvVU1hOW5lTk5LMk82VjRKeGlIRnZNTjdzNHRsZkpRYTloU3VxRDRGeWlxWXpubVNkUmVfQnlsWXl2WFlyYmRxVmfSAX5BVV95cUxORHJXZHBlMVZfbWpRUFAxZEJ5LWxuZVgyYnZwZ1RhQnA3S2hzNGFRdVczZEE1N2FfTDA4OHhXT1B0TG9yblJnZjBJTFNSSTdzemhNSUVEQUlPNnVFLTF2SzZiZE5KZWRMRGtGanQyQ29HY19hbmM2eTNtb0RoSFE?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article__content" data-editable="content" itemprop="articleBody" data-reorderable="content"&gt;
                    &lt;p class="paragraph inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cm8w9267300003b6m46kc3fa0@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            &lt;em&gt;This story was originally published on &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.propublica.org/article/measles-vaccine-rfk-cdc-report" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;em&gt;ProPublica&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;, a nonprofit newsroom that investigates abuses of power. Sign up to receive &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.propublica.org/newsletters/the-big-story?source=www.propublica.org&amp;amp;placement=top-note%C2%AEion=national" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;em&gt;our biggest stories&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt; as soon as they’re published.&lt;/em&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/source/instances/cm8w9245r009h2cp94k2242mo@published" data-component-name="source" class="source inline-placeholder" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
    &lt;cite class="source__cite"&gt;
      &lt;span class="source__location" data-editable="location"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;span class="source__text" data-editable="source"&gt;ProPublica&lt;/span&gt;
         — 
    &lt;/cite&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cm8w9245r009i2cp9gdt0852u@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Leaders at the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention ordered staff this week not to release their experts’ assessment that found the risk of catching measles is high in areas near outbreaks where vaccination rates are lagging, according to internal records reviewed by ProPublica.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cm8w93awn00073b6mzer0z4i6@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            In an aborted plan to roll out the news, the agency would have emphasized the importance of vaccinating people against the highly contagious and potentially deadly disease that has spread to 19 states, the records show.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/html-embed/instances/cm8w98h8r001b3b6ms543q2a1@published" class="html-embed" data-editable="settings" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
    
&lt;/p&gt;


    &lt;p class="paragraph inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cm8w93awn00083b6mwi0jvi4d@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            A CDC spokesperson told ProPublica in a written statement that the agency decided against releasing the assessment “because it does not say anything that the public doesn’t already know.” She added that the CDC continues to recommend vaccines as “the best way to protect against measles.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





    &lt;p class="paragraph inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cm8w93awn00093b6m5fbj68o3@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            But what the nation’s top public health agency said next shows a shift in its long-standing messaging about vaccines, a sign that it may be falling in line under Health and Human Services Secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr., a longtime critic of vaccines:
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cm8w93awn000a3b6m99umk2r6@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “The decision to vaccinate is a personal one,” the statement said, echoing a line from a &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/opinion/robert-f-kennedy-jr-measles-outbreak-call-action-all-us" target="_blank"&gt;column Kennedy wrote&lt;/a&gt; for the Fox News website. “People should consult with their healthcare provider to understand their options to get a vaccine and should be informed about the potential risks and benefits associated with vaccines.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cm8w93awn000b3b6m72h8dovv@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            ProPublica shared the new CDC statement about personal choice and risk with Jennifer Nuzzo, director of the Pandemic Center at Brown University School of Public Health. To her, the shift in messaging, and the squelching of this routine announcement, is alarming.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cm8w93awn000c3b6mddad3wwr@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “I’m a bit stunned by that language,” Nuzzo said. “No vaccine is without risk, but that makes it sound like it’s a very active coin toss of a decision. We’ve already had more cases of measles in 2025 than we had in 2024, and it’s spread to multiple states. It is not a coin toss at this point.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cm8w93awn000d3b6mgyhnzwiu@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            For many years, the CDC hasn’t minced words on vaccines. It &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/vaccines/partners/vaccinate-with-confidence.html" target="_blank"&gt;promoted them with confidence&lt;/a&gt;. One campaign was called “&lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/flu/spotlights/2022-2023/ad-council-flu-campaign.htm" target="_blank"&gt;Get My Flu Shot&lt;/a&gt;.” The agency’s website &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/vaccines-children/hcp/conversation-tips/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;told medical providers&lt;/a&gt; they play a critical role in helping parents choose vaccines for their children: “Instead of saying ‘What do you want to do about shots?,’ say ‘Your child needs three shots today.’”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cm8w93awn000e3b6m6x0p8ae0@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Nuzzo wishes the CDC’s forecasters would put out more details of their data and evidence on the spread of measles, not less. “The growing scale and severity of this measles outbreak and the urgent need for more data to guide the response underscores why we need a fully staffed and functional CDC and more resources for state and local health departments,” she said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cm8w93awn000f3b6mad8c1rzu@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Kennedy’s agency oversees the CDC and on Thursday announced it was poised to eliminate 2,400 jobs there.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





    &lt;p class="paragraph inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cm8w93awn000g3b6m9856546b@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            When asked what role, if any, Kennedy played in the decision to not release the risk assessment, HHS’ communications director said the aborted announcement “was part of an ongoing process to improve communication processes — nothing more, nothing less.” The CDC, he reiterated, continues to recommend vaccination “as the best way to protect against measles.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cm8w93awn000h3b6mngdfwh2g@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “Secretary Kennedy believes that the decision to vaccinate is a personal one and that people should consult with their healthcare provider to understand their options to get a vaccine,” Andrew G. Nixon said. “It is important that the American people have radical transparency and be informed to make personal healthcare decisions.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cm8w93awn000i3b6m4albktm3@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Responding to questions about criticism of the decision among some CDC staff, Nixon wrote, “Some individuals at the CDC seem more interested in protecting their own status or agenda rather than aligning with this Administration and the true mission of public health.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cm8w93awn000j3b6mam4ruvvf@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The CDC’s risk assessment was carried out by its Center for Forecasting and Outbreak Analytics, which relied, in part, on new disease data from the outbreak in Texas. The CDC created the center to address a major shortcoming laid bare during the COVID-19 pandemic. It functions like a National Weather Service for infectious diseases, harnessing data and expertise to predict the course of outbreaks like a meteorologist warns of storms.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cm8w93awn000k3b6mo60xaua8@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Other risk assessments by the center have been posted by the CDC even though their conclusions might seem obvious.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cm8w93awn000l3b6m1pwrxjs8@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            In late February, for example, &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/cfa-qualitative-assessments/php/data-research/h5-risk-assessment.html" target="_blank"&gt;forecasters analyzing the spread of H5N1&lt;/a&gt; bird flu said people who come “in contact with potentially infected animals or contaminated surfaces or fluids” faced a moderate to high risk of contracting the disease. The risk to the general U.S. population, they said, was low.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cm8w93awn000m3b6mcalm0irp@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            In the case of the measles assessment, modelers at the center determined the risk of the disease for the general public in the U.S. is low, but they found the risk is high in communities with low vaccination rates that are near outbreaks or share close social ties to those areas with outbreaks. The CDC had moderate confidence in the assessment, according to an internal Q&amp;amp;A that explained the findings. The agency, it said, lacks detailed data about the onset of the illness for all patients in West Texas and is still learning about the vaccination rates in affected communities as well as travel and social contact among those infected. (The H5N1 assessment was also made with moderate confidence.)
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





    &lt;p class="paragraph inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cm8w93awn000n3b6mfpsj9c0h@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The internal plan to roll out the news of the forecast called for the expert physician who’s leading the CDC’s response to measles to be the chief spokesperson answering questions. “It is important to note that at local levels, vaccine coverage rates may vary considerably, and pockets of unvaccinated people can exist even in areas with high vaccination coverage overall,” the plan said. “The best way to protect against measles is to get the measles, mumps, and rubella (MMR) vaccine.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cm8w93awn000o3b6mzyzns02f@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            This week, though, as the number of confirmed cases rose to 483, more than 30 agency staff were told in an email that after a discussion in the CDC director’s office, “leadership does not want to pursue putting this on the website.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cm8w93awn000p3b6mvaa12lo2@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The cancellation was “not normal at all,” said a CDC staff member who spoke anonymously for fear of reprisal with layoffs looming. “I’ve never seen a rollout plan that was canceled at that far along in the process.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cm8w93awn000q3b6mwd9oz3p8@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Anxiety among CDC staff has been building over whether the agency will bend its public health messages to match those of Kennedy, a lawyer who founded an anti-vaccine group and referred clients to a law firm suing a vaccine manufacturer.
    &lt;/p&gt;



    &lt;p class="paragraph inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cm8w93awn000r3b6m3y7jqizm@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            During Kennedy’s first week on the job, HHS halted the CDC campaign that encouraged people to get flu shots during a ferocious flu season. On the night that the Trump administration began firing probationary employees across the federal government, some key CDC flu webpages were taken down. Remnants of some of the campaign webpages were restored after &lt;a href="https://www.npr.org/sections/shots-health-news/2025/02/19/nx-s1-5302906/cdc-flu-vaccine-campaign-terminated" target="_blank"&gt;NPR reported&lt;/a&gt; this.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cm8w93awn000s3b6mpt6lxnjy@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            But some at the agency felt like the new leadership had sent a message loud and clear: When next to nobody was paying attention, long-standing public health messages could be silenced.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cm8w93awn000t3b6m12hta2mt@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            On the day in February that the world learned that an unvaccinated &lt;a href="https://perma.cc/R8XT-4XUB" target="_blank"&gt;child had died&lt;/a&gt; of measles in Texas, the first such death in the U.S. since 2015, the HHS secretary &lt;a href="https://www.factcheck.org/2025/02/rfk-jr-minimizes-measles-outbreak-in-texas/" target="_blank"&gt;downplayed the seriousness&lt;/a&gt; of the outbreak. “We have measles outbreaks every year,” he said at a cabinet meeting with President Donald Trump.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





    &lt;p class="paragraph inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cm8w93awn000u3b6mwhpkavzs@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            In an interview on Fox News this month, Kennedy championed doctors in Texas who he said were treating measles with a steroid, an antibiotic and cod liver oil, a supplement that is high in vitamin A. “They’re seeing what they describe as almost miraculous and instantaneous recovery from that,” Kennedy said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cm8w93awn000v3b6majninky5@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            As parents near the outbreak in Texas stocked up on vitamin A supplements, doctors there raced to assure parents that &lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/doctors-push-back-parents-embrace-kennedy-vitamin-texas-measles-outbreak-2025-03-08/" target="_blank"&gt;only vaccination, not the vitamin, can prevent measles&lt;/a&gt;.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cm8w93awn000w3b6m34wu54tt@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Still, the CDC added &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/measles/hcp/clinical-overview/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;an entry on Vitamin A&lt;/a&gt; to its measles website for clinicians.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cm8w93awn000x3b6mgfh3dkyr@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            On Wednesday, CNN reported that &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2025/03/26/health/texas-measles-vitamin-a-toxicity/index.html"&gt;several hospitalized children in Lubbock, Texas, had abnormal liver function&lt;/a&gt;, a likely sign of toxicity from too much vitamin A.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cm8w93awn00103b6mvczsn4g3@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Texas health officials also said that the Trump administration’s decision to rescind $11 billion in pandemic-related grants across the country &lt;a href="https://www.texastribune.org/2025/03/26/texas-measles-public-health-funding-cut/" target="_blank"&gt;will hinder their ability to respond&lt;/a&gt; to the growing outbreak, according to The Texas Tribune.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cm8w93awn00113b6mzq7hx24m@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Measles is among the most contagious diseases and can be dangerous. About 20% of unvaccinated people who get measles wind up in the hospital. And &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/measles/signs-symptoms/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;nearly 1 to 3 of every 1,000 children&lt;/a&gt; with measles will die from respiratory and neurologic complications. The virus can &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/measles/causes/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;linger in the air&lt;/a&gt; for two hours after an infected person has left an area, and patients can spread measles before they even know they have it.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cm8w93awn00123b6mmvew12fd@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            This week Amtrak said it was notifying customers that they may have been exposed to the disease this month when a passenger with measles &lt;a href="https://abc7ny.com/post/amtrak-confirms-passenger-measles-traveled-new-york-washington-dc/16085440/" target="_blank"&gt;rode one of its trains&lt;/a&gt; from New York City to Washington, D.C.
    &lt;/p&gt;

              &lt;/div&gt;
                            &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>CNN</author><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihwFBVV95cUxQdDQzbTlHUW9pemFXaTFvc2pqeXltbXNFM09uLXc4SGQxSkpVNmZqa3Q5OEU1cVFtaVZ2emo1cFZMclRYY0RvVU1hOW5lTk5LMk82VjRKeGlIRnZNTjdzNHRsZkpRYTloU3VxRDRGeWlxWXpubVNkUmVfQnlsWXl2WFlyYmRxVmfSAX5BVV95cUxORHJXZHBlMVZfbWpRUFAxZEJ5LWxuZVgyYnZwZ1RhQnA3S2hzNGFRdVczZEE1N2FfTDA4OHhXT1B0TG9yblJnZjBJTFNSSTdzemhNSUVEQUlPNnVFLTF2SzZiZE5KZWRMRGtGanQyQ29HY19hbmM2eTNtb0RoSFE</guid></item><item><title>Trump makes sweeping HIV research and grant cuts: ‘setting us back decades’ - The Guardian US</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMilwFBVV95cUxQVEVZTmlTWS0yNU9xNl9vX2FiY1FVOVNoZERHQmNGUkVDeS0xZUhMZVJwcUdDVjZSZmFYRVBYQTNXbnBKcGVVVnVrVzFjUUFlTzNURENtam5uUmFMNWFqNzVvV09PX2lueE9LV2todnhtM054dFBkRHZKNlAtbDhxZUplbDRlU0o4NXQ0U0dkM3N3anRNaTJJ?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body-commercial-selector article-body-viewer-selector dcr-11jq3zt"&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-s3ycb2"&gt;The federal government has cancelled dozens of grants to study how to prevent new &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/society/aids-and-hiv" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;HIV&lt;/a&gt; infections and expand access to care, decimating progress toward eliminating the epidemic in the United States, scientists say.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-s3ycb2"&gt;Over the last month, more than 300 research projects funded by the National Institutes of Health (NIH) have been &lt;a href="https://taggs.hhs.gov/Content/Data/HHS_Grants_Terminated.pdf" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;terminated&lt;/a&gt; – 65 of them were specifically related to researching advancements in HIV care. Some scientists were notified about losing funding as recently as last Thursday. NIH, a division of the Department of Health and Human Services, is the largest funding source of medical research in the world, leaving many scientists scrambling to figure out how to continue their work.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="sign-in-gate"&gt;&lt;gu-island name="SignInGateSelector" priority="feature" deferuntil="visible" props='{"contentType":"Article","sectionId":"us-news","tags":[{"id":"us-news/trump-administration","type":"Keyword","title":"Trump administration"},{"id":"society/aids-and-hiv","type":"Keyword","title":"Aids and HIV"},{"id":"science/science","type":"Keyword","title":"Science"},{"id":"us-news/us-politics","type":"Keyword","title":"US politics"},{"id":"society/health","type":"Keyword","title":"Health"},{"id":"us-news/us-news","type":"Keyword","title":"US news"},{"id":"us-news/usdomesticpolicy","type":"Keyword","title":"US domestic policy"},{"id":"us-news/donaldtrump","type":"Keyword","title":"Donald Trump"},{"id":"us-news/healthcare","type":"Keyword","title":"US healthcare"},{"id":"type/article","type":"Type","title":"Article"},{"id":"tone/news","type":"Tone","title":"News"},{"id":"tracking/commissioningdesk/us-news","type":"Tracking","title":"US News"}],"isPaidContent":false,"isPreview":false,"host":"https://www.theguardian.com","pageId":"us-news/2025/mar/31/trump-administration-hiv-research-grant-cuts","idUrl":"https://profile.theguardian.com","switches":{"lightbox":true,"prebidCriteo":true,"personaliseSignInGateAfterCheckout":true,"abSignInGateMainVariant":true,"prebidAppnexusUkRow":true,"prebidMagnite":true,"commercialMetrics":true,"prebidTrustx":true,"scAdFreeBanner":false,"adaptiveSite":true,"prebidPermutiveAudience":true,"compareVariantDecision":false,"enableSentryReporting":true,"lazyLoadContainers":true,"ampArticleSwitch":false,"remarketing":true,"articleEndSlot":true,"keyEventsCarousel":true,"registerWithPhone":false,"darkModeWeb":true,"targeting":true,"remoteHeader":true,"slotBodyEnd":true,"ampPrebidOzone":false,"extendedMostPopularFronts":true,"emailInlineInFooter":true,"showNewPrivacyWordingOnEmailSignupEmbeds":true,"prebidAnalytics":true,"extendedMostPopular":true,"ampContentAbTesting":false,"imrWorldwide":true,"acast":true,"twitterUwt":true,"abAuxiaSignInGate":true,"abDeferPermutiveLoad":true,"prebidAppnexusInvcode":true,"ampPrebidPubmatic":false,"a9HeaderBidding":true,"prebidAppnexus":true,"enableDiscussionSwitch":true,"prebidXaxis":true,"stickyVideos":true,"interactiveFullHeaderSwitch":true,"discussionAllPageSize":true,"prebidUserSync":true,"audioOnwardJourneySwitch":true,"brazeTaylorReport":false,"externalVideoEmbeds":true,"abTheTradeDesk":true,"callouts":true,"sentinelLogger":true,"geoMostPopular":true,"weAreHiring":false,"relatedContent":true,"thirdPartyEmbedTracking":true,"prebidOzone":true,"ampLiveblogSwitch":false,"ampAmazon":false,"prebidAdYouLike":true,"mostViewedFronts":true,"optOutAdvertising":true,"abSignInGateMainControl":true,"googleSearch":true,"brazeSwitch":true,"prebidKargo":true,"consentManagement":true,"idProfileNavigation":true,"confiantAdVerification":true,"discussionAllowAnonymousRecommendsSwitch":false,"absoluteServerTimes":false,"permutive":true,"comscore":true,"ampPrebidCriteo":false,"prebidTheTradeDesk":true,"newsletterOnwards":false,"youtubeIma":true,"webFonts":true,"liveBlogTopSponsorship":true,"ophan":true,"crosswordSvgThumbnails":true,"prebidTriplelift":true,"prebidPubmatic":true,"serverShareCounts":false,"autoRefresh":true,"enhanceTweets":true,"prebidIndexExchange":true,"prebidOpenx":true,"prebidHeaderBidding":true,"idCookieRefresh":true,"discussionPageSize":true,"smartAppBanner":false,"historyTags":true,"brazeContentCards":true,"remoteBanner":true,"emailSignupRecaptcha":true,"prebidSmart":true,"shouldLoadGoogletag":true,"inizio":true,"europeBetaFront":true,"prebidBidCache":false},"contributionsServiceUrl":"https://contributions.guardianapis.com","editionId":"US"}'&gt;&lt;/gu-island&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-s3ycb2"&gt;“The loss of this research could very well result in a resurgence of HIV that becomes more generalized in this country,” said Julia Marcus, a professor at Harvard Medical School who recently had two of her grants cancelled. “These drastic cuts are rapidly destroying the infrastructure of scientific research in this country and we are going to lose a generation of scientists.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="596b667d-a0f9-4cfc-ab46-ec5a985c2993" data-spacefinder-role="richLink" data-spacefinder-type="model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.RichLinkBlockElement" class="dcr-1your1i"&gt;&lt;gu-island name="RichLinkComponent" priority="feature" deferuntil="idle" props='{"richLinkIndex":3,"element":{"_type":"model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.RichLinkBlockElement","prefix":"Related: ","text":" ‘It’s back to drug rationing’: the end of HIV was in sight. Then came the cuts ","elementId":"596b667d-a0f9-4cfc-ab46-ec5a985c2993","role":"richLink","url":"https://www.theguardian.com/global-development/2025/mar/18/global-health-trump-usaid-cuts-hiv-aids-2030-drugs-vaccine-research-africa"},"ajaxUrl":"https://api.nextgen.guardianapps.co.uk","format":{"design":0,"display":0,"theme":0}}'&gt;&lt;/gu-island&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-s3ycb2"&gt;In 2012, the FDA approved pre-exposure prophylaxis (PrEP), an antiviral drug taken once a day that is highly successful at preventing new HIV infections. While the drug has been a powerful tool to contain the virus, inequities remain in accessing those drugs and sustaining a daily treatment. Despite major progress, there are still 30,000 new infections each year in the US.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-s3ycb2"&gt;Many of the terminated HIV-related studies focused on improving access to drugs like PrEP in communities that have higher rates of infections – including trans women and Black men. One of Marcus’s projects was examining whether making PrEP available over the counter would increase the use of the drug in vulnerable communities.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-s3ycb2"&gt;“The research has to focus on the populations that are most affected in order to have an impact and be relevant,” said Marcus.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-s3ycb2"&gt;Yet, this may be the justification for defunding so many HIV-related studies. A termination letter reviewed by the Guardian dated 20 March cited that “so-called diversity, equity and inclusion (DEI) studies are often used to support unlawful discrimination on the basis of race and other protected characteristics, which harms the health of Americans.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;aside data-spacefinder-role="supporting" class="dcr-1eyan6r"&gt;&lt;svg viewbox="0 0 22 14" class="dcr-scql1j"&gt;&lt;path d="M5.255 0h4.75c-.572 4.53-1.077 8.972-1.297 13.941H0C.792 9.104 2.44 4.53 5.255 0Zm11.061 0H21c-.506 4.53-1.077 8.972-1.297 13.941h-8.686c.902-4.837 2.485-9.411 5.3-13.941Z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;blockquote class="dcr-zzndwp"&gt;Scrapping an entire category of disease from research will have innumerable downstream effects on the rest of healthcare&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;footer&gt;&lt;cite&gt;Erin Kahle, University of Michigan&lt;/cite&gt;&lt;/footer&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-s3ycb2"&gt;The National Institutes of &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/society/health" data-link-name="in body link" data-component="auto-linked-tag"&gt;Health&lt;/a&gt; did not expand on why the grants were terminated in response to questions from the Guardian. In a statement it said it is “taking action to terminate research funding that is not aligned with NIH and HHS priorities. We remain dedicated to restoring our agency to its tradition of upholding gold-standard, evidence-based science.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-s3ycb2"&gt;Many researchers were left stunned by the scale of the cancellations since in 2019, &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/donaldtrump" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;Donald Trump&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://trumpwhitehouse.archives.gov/briefings-statements/president-donald-j-trumps-state-union-address-2/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;announced&lt;/a&gt; in his State of the Union address a commitment to eliminate the HIV epidemic in the country over the next 10 years. As part of this initiative, his &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/trump-administration" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;administration&lt;/a&gt; negotiated a deal with drug companies to provide free PrEP for 200,000 low-income patients.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-s3ycb2"&gt;“Scientific breakthroughs have brought a once-distant dream within reach,” said Trump in his address. “Together we will defeat Aids in America.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="8ca2f65f-63f0-4233-916e-329e08f8075f" data-spacefinder-role="richLink" data-spacefinder-type="model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.RichLinkBlockElement" class="dcr-1your1i"&gt;&lt;gu-island name="RichLinkComponent" priority="feature" deferuntil="idle" props='{"richLinkIndex":12,"element":{"_type":"model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.RichLinkBlockElement","prefix":"Related: ","text":"Aid cuts predicted to cause 2.9 million more HIV-related deaths by 2030 – study","elementId":"8ca2f65f-63f0-4233-916e-329e08f8075f","role":"richLink","url":"https://www.theguardian.com/global-development/2025/mar/26/aid-cuts-pepfar-epidemic-prediction-cause-29-million-more-hiv-related-deaths-by-2030-lancet-study"},"ajaxUrl":"https://api.nextgen.guardianapps.co.uk","format":{"design":0,"display":0,"theme":0}}'&gt;&lt;/gu-island&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-s3ycb2"&gt;Amy Nunn, a professor at the Brown University School of Public Health, said she had even tailored grant proposals to fit the policy goals of the initiative, which included geographically targeting HIV prevention efforts. One of her studies that was terminated last week focused on closing disparities of PrEP use among African American men in Jackson, Mississippi.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-s3ycb2"&gt;“They finally adopted those policies at the federal level,” Nunn said, noting that Trump was the first president to make ending the epidemic a priority. “Now they’re undercutting their own successes. It’s so strange.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-s3ycb2"&gt;The total amount of NIH funds allocated to supporting the 65 grants was $35m. Canceling the grants will not recoup all of that money for the administration, since many are years into their work. Some are even already finished.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-s3ycb2"&gt;Nathaniel Albright learned last Tuesday that an NIH grant supporting his doctoral research was cancelled even though his project had already been completed. A PhD candidate at Ohio State University, Albright is defending his dissertation at the end of the month. Still, Albright is concerned how the cuts impact the future of the field.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-s3ycb2"&gt;“It’s created an environment in academia where my research trajectory is now considered high risk to institutions,” said Albright, who is currently struggling to find postdoctorate positions at universities.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-s3ycb2"&gt;Pamina Gorbach, an epidemiologist who teaches at University of California, Los Angeles, had been following hundreds of men living with HIV in Los Angeles for 10 years to learn their needs. She had been awarded an NIH grant to better facilitate their treatment through a local clinic. Her funding was cancelled last week as well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-s3ycb2"&gt;“It’s really devastating,” said Gorbach. “If you’re living with HIV and you’re not on meds, you know what happens? You get sick and you die.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="acb3dd82-8517-4629-a090-114be722086e" data-spacefinder-role="richLink" data-spacefinder-type="model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.RichLinkBlockElement" class="dcr-1your1i"&gt;&lt;gu-island name="RichLinkComponent" priority="feature" deferuntil="idle" props='{"richLinkIndex":20,"element":{"_type":"model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.RichLinkBlockElement","prefix":"Related: ","text":"US urged to ‘think bigger’ on healthcare amid Trump onslaught on sector","elementId":"acb3dd82-8517-4629-a090-114be722086e","role":"richLink","url":"https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2025/mar/22/us-healthcare-trump"},"ajaxUrl":"https://api.nextgen.guardianapps.co.uk","format":{"design":0,"display":0,"theme":0}}'&gt;&lt;/gu-island&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-s3ycb2"&gt;Clinic staff in Los Angeles will likely be laid off as a result of the cuts, said Gorbach. Others agreed one immediate concern was how to pay their research staff, since the funds from a grant are immediately frozen once it is terminated. The NIH funds also often make up at least a portion of university professor’s salaries, all said they were most alarmed by the impact on services for their patients and the loss of progress toward ending the epidemic.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-s3ycb2"&gt;“This is erasing an entire population of people who have been impacted by an infectious disease,” said Erin Kahle, the director of the Center for Sexuality and Health Disparities at the University of Michigan who lost an NIH grant last week. Scrapping an entire category of disease from research will have innumerable downstream effects on the rest of healthcare, she added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-s3ycb2"&gt;“This is setting us back decades,” said Kahle.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Guardian US</author><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilwFBVV95cUxQVEVZTmlTWS0yNU9xNl9vX2FiY1FVOVNoZERHQmNGUkVDeS0xZUhMZVJwcUdDVjZSZmFYRVBYQTNXbnBKcGVVVnVrVzFjUUFlTzNURENtam5uUmFMNWFqNzVvV09PX2lueE9LV2todnhtM054dFBkRHZKNlAtbDhxZUplbDRlU0o4NXQ0U0dkM3N3anRNaTJJ</guid></item><item><title>Is Your Diet Drink Making You Hungrier? New Research Explains Why - SciTechDaily</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMilAFBVV95cUxOSmJfaEJEQzIyRnBJZ19YRElsRmFjTXN3WXFZY2tZY3dYN3hnMzdLMHJtN3BoMnFsVDhHMnhiQkd4a3BSbVZqTEpvWUt5NWVEaURlRDA3Y1NSZ3ZLdUg3c3VXQjA0N244X2tES1FmQVFUc25VQnJQOVBReEVsQ2hiZWJJRzgwa1VEMXRxMmZlaHFudnRI?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>SciTechDaily</author><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 02:15:11 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilAFBVV95cUxOSmJfaEJEQzIyRnBJZ19YRElsRmFjTXN3WXFZY2tZY3dYN3hnMzdLMHJtN3BoMnFsVDhHMnhiQkd4a3BSbVZqTEpvWUt5NWVEaURlRDA3Y1NSZ3ZLdUg3c3VXQjA0N244X2tES1FmQVFUc25VQnJQOVBReEVsQ2hiZWJJRzgwa1VEMXRxMmZlaHFudnRI</guid></item><item><title>Sometimes Alzheimer's Strikes Early. This Experimental Drug May Help. - ScienceAlert</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMimwFBVV95cUxNU3djNWNPbk1YR1NkYzJidVAzZmlJSXZLZ2tDZ0xEeHYxVzhFbGNuUUF2LUN5ajF6b01LejlnWmNicVQyUHNXME5WQThxY1cwX3J2NExLOGNwNHNWbS1qanRzRzdSVzZsRXBpNmRGWm1fWkpOdk9NN05FWFRiTWVBYVRfVmMwRlRiejJmYld6ZGw2TzdDeGV2b2ZDOA?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/go/IaO" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73015" data-postid="156759" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;Alzheimer's&lt;/a&gt; disease is usually associated with old age. But &lt;a href="https://www.nia.nih.gov/health/alzheimers-causes-and-risk-factors/alzheimers-disease-genetics-fact-sheet"&gt;around 5%-10% of all Alzheimer's cases&lt;/a&gt; occur in people under the age of 65.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.alz.org/alzheimers-dementia/what-is-alzheimers/younger-early-onset"&gt;Early-onset Alzheimer's disease&lt;/a&gt; progresses more rapidly and often strikes people in the prime of their lives. Treatment options remain limited.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But new data from a &lt;a href="https://www.thelancet.com/journals/laneur/article/PIIS1474-4422%2825%2900024-9/abstract"&gt;recent clinical trial&lt;/a&gt; suggests that a previously discontinued experimental drug, called gantenerumab, could help. The study found that gantenerumab reduced the buildup of amyloid plaques – one of the hallmarks of Alzheimer's disease – in the brain.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This may help slow cognitive decline in people with early-onset Alzheimer's.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Early-onset Alzheimer's is often linked to &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC5871104/"&gt;genetic mutations&lt;/a&gt; in three specific genes. These mutations cause the brain to produce excessive amounts of amyloid beta, a protein that clumps together to form plaques. These plaques disrupt brain function, leading to memory loss.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Early-onset Alzheimer's advances quickly – and the rapid decline is devastating. That's why researchers are racing to find treatments that can slow the disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_142437" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-142437" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/11/AmyloidPlaquesAmongNeurons_R_U_642-642x500.jpg" alt="Clumps of yellow forming among purple neurons" class="size-medium wp-image-142437" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/11/AmyloidPlaquesAmongNeurons_R_U_642-642x500.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/11/AmyloidPlaquesAmongNeurons_R_U_642-533x415.jpg 533w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/11/AmyloidPlaquesAmongNeurons_R_U_642-768x598.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/11/AmyloidPlaquesAmongNeurons_R_U_642-600x467.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/11/AmyloidPlaquesAmongNeurons_R_U_642.jpg 1204w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-142437" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Illustration of amyloid plaques (&lt;a href="https://www.canva.com/photos/MADq3tpYQR4/"&gt;Science Photo Library/Canva&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;The recent  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/clinical-trials" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73032" data-postid="156759" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;clinical trial&lt;/a&gt; was a randomised, placebo-controlled study to evaluate gantenerumab's effects on people with early-onset Alzheimer's.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Researchers monitored changes in the participants' cognitive abilities, and also used brain imaging and blood biomarkers (the presence of specific proteins in the blood which are linked to Alzheimer's), to track the disease's progress throughout the study.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The trial included 73 participants with rare inherited genetic mutations known to cause early-onset Alzheimer's. These participants were either asymptomatic or had mild Alzheimer's symptoms at the start of the study.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The results were intriguing. In a subgroup of 22 participants, who hadn't had any cognitive issues at the start of the study, taking the treatment for an average of eight years reduced the risk of developing symptoms from a nearly 100% likelihood, to 50%. Brain scans also showed a notable decrease in amyloid buildup.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Immune defenders&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.alzforum.org/therapeutics/gantenerumab"&gt;Gantenerumab&lt;/a&gt; is a monoclonal  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/antibody" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73081" data-postid="156759" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;antibody&lt;/a&gt; – a lab-engineered protein designed to attach to amyloid beta in the brain. By binding to these plaques, it signals the immune system to clear them away. This may potentially slow Alzheimer's progression.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The drug works by engaging &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/22613055/"&gt;microglial cells&lt;/a&gt;. These are the brain's primary immune defenders. Microglia constantly monitor the brain for damage and remove harmful substances, including amyloid beta. However, in people with Alzheimer's disease, microglia often &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41582-020-00435-y"&gt;fail to clear plaques efficiently&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Gantenerumab enhances this natural defence mechanism by tagging amyloid plaques, making them easier for the microglia to recognise and break down.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Amyloid beta is thought to play a central role in Alzheimer's by triggering inflammation, interfering with cell communication and ultimately killing neurons. By removing these plaques, gantenerumab may help to protect brain function. However, it doesn't reverse existing damage – which is why early intervention is critical.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;An advantage of gantenerumab is that it can cross the &lt;a href="https://fluidsbarrierscns.biomedcentral.com/articles/10.1186/s12987-020-00230-3"&gt;blood-brain barrier&lt;/a&gt; – the protective shield that blocks many drugs and harmful substances from reaching the brain. This allows it to act directly on amyloid plaques, making it more effective than some earlier treatments that &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC2756824/"&gt;struggled with drug delivery&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But as promising as these results are, gantenerumab isn't without risks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A major concern is &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC10629981/"&gt;amyloid-related imaging abnormalities&lt;/a&gt;. These are swelling or small spots of bleeding in the brain that show up on  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/magnetic-resonance-imaging" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73063" data-postid="156759" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;MRI&lt;/a&gt; scans. This is a common side-effect of amyloid-targeting therapies.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this latest trial, 53% of participants experienced these amyloid-related imaging abnormalities, including small brain bleeds in 27% of participants, brain swelling in 30% of participants and iron deposits from bleeding in 6%.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While no participants had major brain haemorrhages or died from the treatment, these side-effects remain a serious concern – requiring regular monitoring through brain scans.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Another limitation is the modest cognitive benefit observed in the trial. While gantenerumab reduced amyloid plaques, the extent to which this translates into meaningful improvements in memory and thinking skills remains unclear.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Gantenerumab is also expensive to manufacture, which could make widespread access difficult if it gains regulatory approval. As this is an experimental drug, we do not currently know how much it would cost. But other similar anti-amyloid therapies, such as donanemab, currently cost around &lt;a href="https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/articles/c1e7pllez0xo"&gt;£25,000 per patient per year&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The study also had a small sample size and only focused on a rare genetic form of early-onset Alzheimer's. More research is needed to see how these results may apply to the wider dementia community.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;The future of treatment&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Although the trial was terminated early after the study's sponsor pulled out, these findings contribute to the ongoing debate over the causes of Alzheimer's disease.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;According to the amyloid hypothesis, the buildup of amyloid plaques in the brain is the main cause of Alzheimer's disease. Clearing these plaques will slow the disease's progression. The success of the Alzheimer's drugs &lt;a href="https://www.alz.org/alzheimers-dementia/treatments/lecanemab-leqembi"&gt;lecanemab&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.alz.org/alzheimers-dementia/treatments/donanemab"&gt;donanemab&lt;/a&gt; and now gantenerumab, lend themselves to this theory.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This study also underscores the importance of early diagnosis. Amyloid-targeting therapies appear to work best in the early stages of Alzheimer's, before &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-024-00756-8#:%7E:text=Clinical%20trials%20generally%20enrol%20early,before%20the%20disease%20takes%20hold."&gt;significant brain damage occurs&lt;/a&gt;. Advances in biomarker testing – including &lt;a href="https://www.alzheimersresearchuk.org/news/uk-wide-study-into-dementia-blood-tests-recruits-first-participants/"&gt;blood tests&lt;/a&gt; and brain scans – could help identify at-risk people sooner. This would improve the effectiveness of drugs such as gantenerumab.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Although gantenerumab is not a cure and &lt;a href="https://www.alzheimer-europe.org/news/roche-discontinues-clinical-trials-gantenerumab-after-graduate-studies-fail-meet-their-primary?language_content_entity=en"&gt;was discontinued&lt;/a&gt; by its manufacturer in 2022 because it failed to demonstrate efficacy in slowing the progression of Alzheimer's disease, this new data could perhaps lead to gantenerumab being manufactured again. It also represents another step forward in the fight against Alzheimer's.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alzheimer's research is advancing faster than ever before. Whether a success or a setback, each new study adds to our understanding of the disease and brings us closer to more effective treatments. For now, the gantenerumab trial offers a hopeful sign that scientists are making progress in slowing the course of this devastating condition.&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://counter.theconversation.com/content/253049/count.gif?distributor=republish-lightbox-basic" alt="The Conversation" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" loading="lazy"&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/profiles/rahul-sidhu-1511734"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Rahul Sidhu&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;, PhD Candidate, Neuroscience, &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/institutions/university-of-sheffield-1147"&gt;University of Sheffield&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This article is republished from &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com"&gt;The Conversation&lt;/a&gt; under a Creative Commons license. Read the &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/early-onset-alzheimers-new-drug-shows-promise-in-slowing-the-disease-253049"&gt;original article&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 01:43:40 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimwFBVV95cUxNU3djNWNPbk1YR1NkYzJidVAzZmlJSXZLZ2tDZ0xEeHYxVzhFbGNuUUF2LUN5ajF6b01LejlnWmNicVQyUHNXME5WQThxY1cwX3J2NExLOGNwNHNWbS1qanRzRzdSVzZsRXBpNmRGWm1fWkpOdk9NN05FWFRiTWVBYVRfVmMwRlRiejJmYld6ZGw2TzdDeGV2b2ZDOA</guid></item><item><title>3 surprising ways to reverse insulin resistance and obesity — 3 is the craziest! - KSL.com</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMitgFBVV95cUxOdHU1a0UyeUt4WFI3SzdCSnVPY0NxOVV1MzNNYnI5WFJDV3otVGFMb2Qwd2RnRUJDYUpvT2pYNTlaUndKQVdNUk5lblZqMHN3LXFLSHZEVnZDb3BSLXVHV0t2YzRnQ2xWMFpQRUx3elliNk9RdVFwRDBlV2luTnVYSzR3eVZTbVR5azdGaUV4T3ppaWFRb3dPT292dm5VNHRKMWhDallxX040NkVvMGpabldaMk5MUQ?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;
                                        Estimated read time: 6-7
                                        minutes&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div id="articleContainer"&gt;&lt;p&gt;You're fat and tired.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It's not insulin's fault. Insulin is just the messenger. When sugar levels are high in the bloodstream, insulin instructs body cells to open their doors and allow sugar in. But under certain circumstances cells ignore insulin's message and the doors remain shut.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When the doors stay shut, you've got two problems. One, you don't get enough fuel (sugar) into the cells, so you're tired. Two, sugar stays in the bloodstream where it causes damage. In an effort to prevent this damage, the sugar is removed and stored as fat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So, you're fat and tired.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;How likely is it that you have insulin resistance? "Pretty likely ,and getting more likely all the time," says Dr. Whit Roberts, D.C. of &lt;a href="https://utcountyhealth.com/2-for-1-weight-loss?UTM_source=IR6" target="_blank" rel="sponsored"&gt;Health Utah&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The percentage of adults with insulin resistance has doubled in the last 20 years, &lt;a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/books/NBK507839/" target="_blank" rel="sponsored"&gt;according to research&lt;/a&gt; published in the National Library of Medicine. &lt;a href="https://my.clevelandclinic.org/health/diseases/22206-insulin-resistance" target="_blank" rel="sponsored"&gt;Cleveland Clinic reports&lt;/a&gt; this is due to many factors including worsening diets, the exposure to more drugs and toxins, more stress and more fat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Insulin resistance is perhaps the most serious epidemic in the world today, Roberts says. "It can lead to all the major killers including heart disease, obesity, strokes, diabetes and &lt;a href="https://www.mdanderson.org/cancerwise/sugar--insulin-resistance-and-cancer--what-is-the-link.h00-159461634.html" target="_blank" rel="sponsored"&gt;13 types of cancer&lt;/a&gt;. The good news is that we are learning all the time better ways to reverse it. Some are surprising."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt; Photo: Pixel-Shot - stock.adobe.com&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;One: Sleep&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;A &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC9036496/" target="_blank" rel="sponsored"&gt;2022 study&lt;/a&gt; published in the National Library of Medicine showed that people who get less than seven hours of sleep have higher levels of insulin resistance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"This is a problem since well over half my patients have some form of insomnia. They struggle falling asleep, staying asleep, or just getting sound sleep," Roberts says. "That's why at &lt;a href="https://utcountyhealth.com/2-for-1-weight-loss?UTM_source=IR6" target="_blank" rel="sponsored"&gt;Health Utah&lt;/a&gt;, improving our patients' quality and quantity of sleep is one of our highest priorities."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Getting enough sleep, however, is easier said than done.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Fortunately, we have found that lowering total body inflammation through a proprietary combination of herbs, foods and therapies leads to improved sleep in almost all of our patients," Roberts says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt; Photo: Nasnunt - stock.adobe.com&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Two: Antioxidants&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The second surprising way to reverse insulin resistance is to increase your consumption of antioxidants. &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC1865087/" target="_blank" rel="sponsored"&gt;One study showed&lt;/a&gt; that taking 2 grams of vitamin C for two weeks resulted in a significant change in insulin resistance. Roberts explains this is why Health Utah's health and weight loss program relies heavily on eating foods rich in antioxidants. Additionally certain foods with &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC7602234/" target="_blank" rel="sponsored"&gt;high polyphenol and phytonutrient content&lt;/a&gt; are recommended as they have also been found to help.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Of course, this is the hard part. Everyone knows they should be eating better. It's just hard when low-quality foods are flavor-enhanced, sugar-laced, caffeine boosted and so convenient. That's why the health and weight loss program at Health Utah focuses heavily on making the transition to healing foods easier. They use a process called framework that engages the subconscious mind to reframe your relationship with food. Weekly classes and educational materials also provide skills, tools, and strategies necessary to achieve sustainable weight loss.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt; Photo: hocine - stock.adobe.com&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Three: Lemon juice&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The craziest way science has found to help reverse insulin resistance is drinking lemon juice. &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC7468735/" target="_blank" rel="sponsored"&gt;Scientific research&lt;/a&gt; is now reflecting what holistic healers have suggested for years, that lemon juice has a powerful effect for good in the body, even improving sensitivity to insulin and lowering blood sugar levels.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Roberts and &lt;a href="https://utcountyhealth.com/2-for-1-weight-loss?UTM_source=IR6" target="_blank" rel="sponsored"&gt;Health Utah&lt;/a&gt; utilize this kind of knowledge in working with their patients. Lemon juice has been a consistent part of their health and weight loss program for over 10 years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"When our patients start their health and weight loss program, they begin by cleaning out the body. This requires improving liver function," Roberts says. "Lemons, herbs and in-office therapies facilitate this detoxification as well as the reversal of insulin resistance."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Health Utah specializes in sustainable weight loss. Everything they do is geared toward this goal. Their coaching, their classes, their work with the subconscious mind, the fact that they don't count calories or cut out carbs and their focus on reversing insulin resistance create a lasting solution to the health and weight issues of their patients.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://utcountyhealth.com/2-for-1-weight-loss?UTM_source=IR6" target="_blank" rel="sponsored"&gt;Health Utah&lt;/a&gt; invites KSL readers to take advantage of a $59 weight loss package. The package allows two people to get body scans. These scans identify potential underlying conditions that cause insulin resistance and stubborn weight. You will walk away with a 17-page report detailing the findings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Roberts will review the results of the scan with you, correlate its findings with your health history. This provides a tremendous amount of information allowing him to make valuable recommendations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You will also be able to fill out a proprietary survey that will give you insight into health issues that likely compromise your weight loss efforts. Thousands of KSL readers have taken this survey and been amazed at the information it provides.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There is no obligation. Find out now why you are struggling with your health and weight issues. Call Health Utah at (801) 609-3478 or &lt;a href="https://utcountyhealth.com/2-for-1-weight-loss?UTM_source=IR6" target="_blank" rel="sponsored"&gt;click here&lt;/a&gt; to get your $59 weight loss package.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The opinions and conclusions expressed in this article are the sponsor's own and do not reflect the views or opinions of KSL.com. This Site Does Not Provide Medical Advice. Any content on this Site, such as text, graphics, images, information obtained from, or contained on this Site are for informational purposes only. The content is not intended to be a substitute for professional medical advice, diagnosis, or treatment. Always seek the advice of your physician or other qualified health provider with any questions you may have regarding a medical condition. Never disregard professional medical advice or delay in seeking it because of something you have read on this site! The owner and operator of this site do not recommend or endorse any specific tests, physicians, products, procedures, opinions, or other information that may be mentioned on the site. Reliance on any information provided by the Operator, including their employees, contractors or others appearing on the Site at the invitation of the Operator, or other visitors to the Site is solely at your own risk. If you think you may have a medical emergency, call your doctor or 911 immediately.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>KSL.com</author><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 01:35:03 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMitgFBVV95cUxOdHU1a0UyeUt4WFI3SzdCSnVPY0NxOVV1MzNNYnI5WFJDV3otVGFMb2Qwd2RnRUJDYUpvT2pYNTlaUndKQVdNUk5lblZqMHN3LXFLSHZEVnZDb3BSLXVHV0t2YzRnQ2xWMFpQRUx3elliNk9RdVFwRDBlV2luTnVYSzR3eVZTbVR5azdGaUV4T3ppaWFRb3dPT292dm5VNHRKMWhDallxX040NkVvMGpabldaMk5MUQ</guid></item><item><title>Dangerous Fungal Infection Sees a Dramatic Increase in US Hospitals - ScienceAlert</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMinAFBVV95cUxNN25TNWVWQklyUTBpT2dUVUlTM0hiZFZ5WjBQbmxBVTRGMVNPTDJaZU1NRlpmYVFCTXdkbWtiRmQweGRJSWx6UjZVeGE4aHJHMEtXcHVRVUQ5NnVqRVFFMERka3Y4Y2M2NXVpTXlFT01JVTBUMVB2Nmoxb1p4dm12WFRjWXpTT0dLeTN3QVhyMTgtUkQwYUlobk9JcGw?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Cases of the fungal infection &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Candida_auris"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Candida auris&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; are rising rapidly and coming from more sources too, a new US study reveals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;C. auris&lt;/em&gt; was first reported in the US &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/a-deadly-drug-resistant-fungus-has-arrived-in-the-us"&gt;in 2016&lt;/a&gt; and is considered an "urgent antimicrobial resistance threat" in hospitals, &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/media/releases/2023/p0320-cauris.html"&gt;according&lt;/a&gt; to the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention (CDC).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Focusing on a large health system in Miami, Florida, the new research found that reported clinical cases had risen from 5 in 2019 to 115 in 2023 – a considerable jump of 2,200 percent in four years.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Consistent with US national trends, &lt;em&gt;C. auris&lt;/em&gt; rapidly spread in our community as noted by a sharp increase in the identification of &lt;em&gt;C. auris&lt;/em&gt; from clinical cultures in 2020 and 2021, followed by a less steep rise in 2022 and 2023," &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.ajic.2025.03.013"&gt;writes&lt;/a&gt; the US team in their published paper.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Many strains of &lt;em&gt;C. auris&lt;/em&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/genome-study-reveals-this-deadly-fungus-has-been-having-sneaky-sex"&gt;don't respond to regular treatments&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/candida-auris/hcp/infection-control/index.html"&gt;and are resistant&lt;/a&gt; to common cleaners and disinfectants too. The fungus spreads quickly in hospitals, often via equipment like catheters and breathing and feeding tubes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="aspect-w-16 aspect-h-9 youtube-iframe relative"&gt;&lt;iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/2AkI5NeD4Ec?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen&gt;VIDEO&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When it takes hold, a &lt;em&gt;C. auris&lt;/em&gt; infection can cause various serious &lt;a href="https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-us-canada-65055878"&gt;and even fatal illnesses&lt;/a&gt; in the bloodstream, the respiratory system, the central nervous system, in organs, and in the skin.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The fungus doesn't pose much risk to the general public. Most healthy people are unlikely to pick up an infection as they're less exposed to C. auris, and their bodies are better able to repel it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;However, for people who are already ill and in the hospital, the &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/fungal-pathogens-are-mutating-dangerously-as-the-world-gets-hotter"&gt;growing threat&lt;/a&gt; is a very real one. Bloodstream infections continue to be the most common, but infections in soft tissue or bone, and in &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cerebrospinal_fluid"&gt;cerebrospinal fluid&lt;/a&gt;, are increasing. The more bases there are to cover, the harder &lt;em&gt;C. auris&lt;/em&gt; will be to control.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_156397" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-156397" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/03/HospitalClean.jpg" alt="Hospital cleaning" class="wp-image-156397 size-full" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/03/HospitalClean.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/03/HospitalClean-600x339.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-156397" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;The CDC has issued guidelines for limiting &lt;em&gt;C. auris&lt;/em&gt; spread. (CDC)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;The pattern that's emerging in the US is being repeated &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/a-deadly-fungus-is-spreading-across-the-world-and-we-don-t-know-how-to-stop-it"&gt;across the rest of the world&lt;/a&gt;, and health experts have been struggling to contain &lt;em&gt;C. auris&lt;/em&gt; since it was first discovered in Japan in 2009. The first US cases were reported in 2016.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Several &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/deadly-fungus-could-be-linked-to-climate-change-study-suggests"&gt;warnings have been issued&lt;/a&gt; about the threat posed by &lt;em&gt;C. auris&lt;/em&gt; – including a study released &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/new-deadly-superfungus-can-now-be-found-in-half-of-us-states"&gt;almost exactly two years ago&lt;/a&gt;, announcing that infections had reached half of the states in the US – but as this Miami study shows, the surge is continuing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The CDC &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/candida-auris/hcp/infection-control/index.html"&gt;has a lengthy list of recommendations&lt;/a&gt; for stopping the spread of &lt;em&gt;C. auris&lt;/em&gt; infections, including diligent cleaning routines for surfaces and devices, and the use of single-patient rooms where possible.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Measures to prevent the spread of &lt;em&gt;C. auris&lt;/em&gt; rely on isolation and contact precautions," &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.ajic.2025.03.013"&gt;write&lt;/a&gt; the researchers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Our findings suggest that early identification of patients colonized with &lt;em&gt;C. auris&lt;/em&gt; and the prompt deployment of infection prevention strategies can potentially impact the incidence of bloodstream infections."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The research has been published in the &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.ajic.2025.03.013"&gt;&lt;em&gt;American Journal of Infection Control&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 01:31:38 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMinAFBVV95cUxNN25TNWVWQklyUTBpT2dUVUlTM0hiZFZ5WjBQbmxBVTRGMVNPTDJaZU1NRlpmYVFCTXdkbWtiRmQweGRJSWx6UjZVeGE4aHJHMEtXcHVRVUQ5NnVqRVFFMERka3Y4Y2M2NXVpTXlFT01JVTBUMVB2Nmoxb1p4dm12WFRjWXpTT0dLeTN3QVhyMTgtUkQwYUlobk9JcGw</guid></item><item><title>People Are Just Now Realizing These Everyday Behaviors Are Actually Symptoms Of Adult ADHD - Yahoo Life</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMif0FVX3lxTE5zNnZQUk5NVUY1OTlMUmRTOWxfTzNUR29YUExvQldpdmtlS0RNUnVTeEN3SmxrczBoek1oaXRfMWVkREkzbl9ta2RIQ01PLU9seDdpZFJkaTQ1ZzVnZExQdFdRMUk3RldicjY1cHl4VTNTNGxwRG9VQTVQay1iVkU?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="" data-article-body="true"&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;With everything there is to juggle in life, it’s easy to assume that everyone experiences that sinking-in-quicksand feeling as they navigate another busy day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;But if you find this feeling is paired with extreme levels of disorganization, inattention and overwhelm, these might be signs of attention-deficit/hyperactivity disorder.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Roughly &lt;a href="https://go.redirectingat.com/?id=74679X1524629&amp;amp;sref=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.buzzfeed.com%2Fkrissybrady%2Fadult-adhd-signs-symptoms&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fchadd.org%2Ffor-adults%2Foverview%2F&amp;amp;xcust=7852141%7CRSS&amp;amp;xs=1" data-i13n="elm:affiliate_link;elmt:premonetized" rel="sponsored" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:10 million American adults;elm:affiliate_link;elmt:premonetized;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link  rapid-with-clickid etailiffa-link"&gt;10 million American adults&lt;/a&gt; (and over &lt;a href="https://go.redirectingat.com/?id=74679X1524629&amp;amp;sref=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.buzzfeed.com%2Fkrissybrady%2Fadult-adhd-signs-symptoms&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov%2Fpmc%2Farticles%2FPMC7916320%2F&amp;amp;xcust=7852141%7CRSS&amp;amp;xs=1" data-i13n="elm:affiliate_link;elmt:premonetized" rel="sponsored" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:365 million globally;elm:affiliate_link;elmt:premonetized;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link  rapid-with-clickid etailiffa-link"&gt;365 million globally&lt;/a&gt;) are thought to have ADHD — and because symptoms can show up differently in adults, realizing you might have the disorder is typically a slow burn, the overlooked signs of which can cause significant strain on your life and health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“Adults looking for diagnosis often have many subtle signs rather than completely failing,” &lt;a href="https://go.redirectingat.com/?id=74679X1524629&amp;amp;sref=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.buzzfeed.com%2Fkrissybrady%2Fadult-adhd-signs-symptoms&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fbrainandmind.org&amp;amp;xcust=7852141%7CRSS&amp;amp;xs=1" data-i13n="elm:affiliate_link;elmt:premonetized" rel="sponsored" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Dede O’Shea;elm:affiliate_link;elmt:premonetized;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link  rapid-with-clickid etailiffa-link"&gt;Dede O’Shea&lt;/a&gt;, a neuropsychologist at &lt;a href="https://go.redirectingat.com/?id=74679X1524629&amp;amp;sref=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.buzzfeed.com%2Fkrissybrady%2Fadult-adhd-signs-symptoms&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fphysicians.lahey.org%2Fdetails%2F4345%2Fdede-oshea-psychiatry__behavioral_medicine-burlington&amp;amp;xcust=7852141%7CRSS&amp;amp;xs=1" data-i13n="elm:affiliate_link;elmt:premonetized" rel="sponsored" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Beth Israel Lahey Health;elm:affiliate_link;elmt:premonetized;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link  rapid-with-clickid etailiffa-link"&gt;Beth Israel Lahey Health&lt;/a&gt; in Cambridge, Massachusetts, told HuffPost.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The hallmark symptoms of ADHD — inattention, impulsivity and hyperactivity — typically aren’t as noticeable in adulthood, likely because adults whose ADHD wasn’t diagnosed in childhood have had a lifetime to parse together the skills necessary to compensate for their symptoms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“Some symptoms of ADHD also mimic those of anxiety or depression,” &lt;a href="https://go.redirectingat.com/?id=74679X1524629&amp;amp;sref=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.buzzfeed.com%2Fkrissybrady%2Fadult-adhd-signs-symptoms&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.peacehumanistic.com&amp;amp;xcust=7852141%7CRSS&amp;amp;xs=1" data-i13n="elm:affiliate_link;elmt:premonetized" rel="sponsored" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Cristina Louk;elm:affiliate_link;elmt:premonetized;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link  rapid-with-clickid etailiffa-link"&gt;Cristina Louk&lt;/a&gt;, a clinical psychologist based in Washington state, told HuffPost. “Most people will first get diagnosed with these disorders and get frustrated when treatment fails to alleviate their symptoms.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;In the moment, you might find yourself attributing certain feelings and behaviors to other things — blaming feelings of hype on too much coffee or snapping at your frozen computer on sleep deprivation — when really, they’re symptoms of adult ADHD.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Here are some of the sneakier signs you might be overlooking:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. Procrastinating to the extreme&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="relative mb-4"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="relative text-sm mt-1 pr-2.5"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; Henrik Sorensen / Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;ADHD brains are always on the lookout for activities that will cause a rush of dopamine, a chemical in the brain that leads to feelings of reward and pleasure and that &lt;a href="https://go.redirectingat.com/?id=74679X1524629&amp;amp;sref=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.buzzfeed.com%2Fkrissybrady%2Fadult-adhd-signs-symptoms&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov%2Fpmc%2Farticles%2FPMC2626918%2F&amp;amp;xcust=7852141%7CRSS&amp;amp;xs=1" data-i13n="elm:affiliate_link;elmt:premonetized" rel="sponsored" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:tends to be lower;elm:affiliate_link;elmt:premonetized;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link  rapid-with-clickid etailiffa-link"&gt;tends to be lower&lt;/a&gt; in people with the disorder.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Because people with ADHD have trouble sustaining enough dopamine during routine tasks that aren’t as interesting to them, they might find themselves doing everything possible to avoid them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“The average person might feel bored by a routine task, but with ADHD, the negative feeling is more extreme — and so, too, the avoidance of it,” O’Shea said. “It can be missed as a potential ADHD symptom because it looks like intentional laziness and lack of motivation.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2. Hyperfocusing on the same task for hours&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="relative mb-4"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="relative text-sm mt-1 pr-2.5"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; Microgen / Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;If you have ADHD, starting tasks can be a grind — especially tasks you find daunting or believe will be time-consuming — but once you get started, you might find yourself so absorbed by what you’re doing that other important tasks end up neglected as a result.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“Hyperfocus is a symptom that can easily be missed because it looks like the person is only motivated to do certain activities,” O’Shea said. “It’s sometimes mistaken as selfishness and overzealousness.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Difficulty switching gears is thought to be caused by low dopamine levels in the brain: The more engrossed you are in a task, the greater the dopamine boost. It’s similar to being in the zone, only in this context, it feels like you’re trapped there.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“Hyperfocus at its worst can look like writing and rewriting your response to a simple email and being unable to transition to a new task or missing an important event because you’re unable to pull yourself away from a work project,” Louk said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3. Spending impulsively&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="relative mb-4"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="relative text-sm mt-1 pr-2.5"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; Moyo Studio / Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Adults with ADHD are more likely to &lt;a href="https://shopping.yahoo.com/rdlw?merchantId=7562d9f6-4b98-4357-9937-0f9854c93912&amp;amp;siteId=us-y4p&amp;amp;pageId=1p-autolink&amp;amp;contentUuid=fbb9ac53-0db8-3c96-bd97-76edf292ba24&amp;amp;featureId=text-link&amp;amp;merchantName=Springer+Science+%2B+Business+Media&amp;amp;custData=eyJzb3VyY2VOYW1lIjoiV2ViLURlc2t0b3AtVmVyaXpvbiIsImxhbmRpbmdVcmwiOiJodHRwczovL2xpbmsuc3ByaW5nZXIuY29tL2FydGljbGUvMTAuMTAwNy9zMDA3MDItMDIxLTAyMzIzLTEiLCJjb250ZW50VXVpZCI6ImZiYjlhYzUzLTBkYjgtM2M5Ni1iZDk3LTc2ZWRmMjkyYmEyNCIsIm9yaWdpbmFsVXJsIjoiaHR0cHM6Ly9saW5rLnNwcmluZ2VyLmNvbS9hcnRpY2xlLzEwLjEwMDcvczAwNzAyLTAyMS0wMjMyMy0xIn0&amp;amp;signature=AQAAAW2YaTDl588drFLq_hrkMdV7ugk07BO4qPbOArmAT4XL&amp;amp;gcReferrer=https%3A%2F%2Flink.springer.com%2Farticle%2F10.1007%2Fs00702-021-02323-1&amp;amp;refurl=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.buzzfeed.com%2Fkrissybrady%2Fadult-adhd-signs-symptoms" data-i13n="elm:affiliate_link;sellerN:Springer Science + Business Media;elmt:" class="link  rapid-with-clickid etailiffa-link" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:make poor financial decisions;elm:affiliate_link;sellerN:Springer Science + Business Media;elmt:;itc:0;sec:content-canvas"&gt;make poor financial decisions&lt;/a&gt; — say, making impulsive purchases for that hit of dopamine, putting off the boredom of paying bills or losing track of when they’re due.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Deficiencies in the basal ganglia — a &lt;a href="https://go.redirectingat.com/?id=74679X1524629&amp;amp;sref=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.buzzfeed.com%2Fkrissybrady%2Fadult-adhd-signs-symptoms&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fmy.clevelandclinic.org%2Fhealth%2Fbody%2F23962-basal-ganglia&amp;amp;xcust=7852141%7CRSS&amp;amp;xs=1" data-i13n="elm:affiliate_link;elmt:premonetized" rel="sponsored" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:set of structures in the brain;elm:affiliate_link;elmt:premonetized;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link  rapid-with-clickid etailiffa-link"&gt;set of structures in the brain&lt;/a&gt; that process how you evaluate emotions, motivations, goals and risks — may be a factor.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;These structures act as a communication highway for different areas of the brain that need to work together to help you learn and form habits (like following a budget), as well as plan and carry out tasks (like saving for the future).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“In a way, the basal ganglia in a person with ADHD can be found to almost short-circuit when it comes to its ability to manage the signals that are passing through,” &lt;a href="https://go.redirectingat.com/?id=74679X1524629&amp;amp;sref=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.buzzfeed.com%2Fkrissybrady%2Fadult-adhd-signs-symptoms&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.mindpath.com%2Fstaff%2Fzishan-khan-md%2F&amp;amp;xcust=7852141%7CRSS&amp;amp;xs=1" data-i13n="elm:affiliate_link;elmt:premonetized" rel="sponsored" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Dr. Zishan Khan;elm:affiliate_link;elmt:premonetized;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link  rapid-with-clickid etailiffa-link"&gt;Dr. Zishan Khan&lt;/a&gt;, a psychiatrist with &lt;a href="https://go.redirectingat.com/?id=74679X1524629&amp;amp;sref=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.buzzfeed.com%2Fkrissybrady%2Fadult-adhd-signs-symptoms&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.mindpath.com&amp;amp;xcust=7852141%7CRSS&amp;amp;xs=1" data-i13n="elm:affiliate_link;elmt:premonetized" rel="sponsored" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Mindpath Health;elm:affiliate_link;elmt:premonetized;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link  rapid-with-clickid etailiffa-link"&gt;Mindpath Health&lt;/a&gt;, told HuffPost.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;4. Losing all sense of time&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="relative mb-4"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="relative text-sm mt-1 pr-2.5"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; AaronAmat / Getty Images/iStockphoto&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Better known as time blindness, people with ADHD find it tricky to keep track of time or to know how much time they’ll need to do an activity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;So far, no single brain region has been identified as the one responsible for time perception, but time estimation seems to be linked to the prefrontal cortex (the part of the brain that assists with executive functioning, focus and attention, as well as organizational skills, Khan said), which &lt;a href="https://go.redirectingat.com/?id=74679X1524629&amp;amp;sref=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.buzzfeed.com%2Fkrissybrady%2Fadult-adhd-signs-symptoms&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov%2Fpmc%2Farticles%2FPMC8293837%2F&amp;amp;xcust=7852141%7CRSS&amp;amp;xs=1" data-i13n="elm:affiliate_link;elmt:premonetized" rel="sponsored" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:relies on signals from dopamine-related pathways;elm:affiliate_link;elmt:premonetized;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link  rapid-with-clickid etailiffa-link"&gt;relies on signals from dopamine-related pathways&lt;/a&gt; to function properly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“This might translate into always running late — thinking you have enough time and then rushing,” O’Shea said. “You might know the exact time of an appointment, but leave the house at that time rather than in advance to give yourself room to travel there, park and sign yourself in.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;5. Experiencing emotional outbursts&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="relative mb-4"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="relative text-sm mt-1 pr-2.5"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; Skynesher / Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;From anxious and edgy to happy and chatty to angry and aggressive, people with ADHD can experience emotional dysregulation that causes them to have strong emotional reactions even they don’t see coming.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“This is related to the difficulties that can come with managing attention and directing energy, as well as finding the appropriate level of mental stimulation,” O’Shea said. “By only focusing on the result — which looks like an emotional disorder — and not the underlying problem, it’s another adult ADHD symptom that’s easily overlooked.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;6. Forgetting to eat&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="relative mb-4"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="relative text-sm mt-1 pr-2.5"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; apos tophy via Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Research suggests a strong link between &lt;a href="https://go.redirectingat.com/?id=74679X1524629&amp;amp;sref=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.buzzfeed.com%2Fkrissybrady%2Fadult-adhd-signs-symptoms&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov%2Fpmc%2Farticles%2FPMC4780667%2F&amp;amp;xcust=7852141%7CRSS&amp;amp;xs=1" data-i13n="elm:affiliate_link;elmt:premonetized" rel="sponsored" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:ADHD and abnormal eating patterns;elm:affiliate_link;elmt:premonetized;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link  rapid-with-clickid etailiffa-link"&gt;ADHD and abnormal eating patterns&lt;/a&gt;, the more prominent patterns being binge eating and forgetting to eat entirely.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The exact mechanisms &lt;a href="https://go.redirectingat.com/?id=74679X1524629&amp;amp;sref=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.buzzfeed.com%2Fkrissybrady%2Fadult-adhd-signs-symptoms&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.sciencedirect.com%2Fscience%2Farticle%2Fpii%2FS027273581630232X&amp;amp;xcust=7852141%7CRSS&amp;amp;xs=1" data-i13n="elm:affiliate_link;elmt:premonetized" rel="sponsored" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:have yet to be sussed out;elm:affiliate_link;elmt:premonetized;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link  rapid-with-clickid etailiffa-link"&gt;have yet to be sussed out&lt;/a&gt; by researchers, but there could be a combination of factors at play, including impaired brain activity in the prefrontal cortex and limbic system.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;When the prefrontal cortex lacks the dopamine necessary to function properly, this can mess with your ability to organize, plan and execute healthy meals and maintain consistent eating habits in general. The dopamine drought can also increase the likelihood of your grabbing convenience foods to satisfy the brain’s reward centers and give it the stimulation necessary to focus.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Meanwhile, the limbic system is in charge of regulating our emotions, in addition to attention, Khan said. As a result, you might use food as a way to unconsciously cope with boredom and emotional distress — or get sucked into a task to the point where you forget to eat for hours, thanks to feeling disconnected from your body’s hunger and fullness cues.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;7. Having trouble sleeping&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="relative mb-4"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="relative text-sm mt-1 pr-2.5"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; PonyWang / Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Insomnia doesn’t necessarily mean you have ADHD, but research suggests adults with ADHD may be &lt;a href="https://go.redirectingat.com/?id=74679X1524629&amp;amp;sref=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.buzzfeed.com%2Fkrissybrady%2Fadult-adhd-signs-symptoms&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.sciencedirect.com%2Fscience%2Farticle%2Fpii%2FS0006322320313810&amp;amp;xcust=7852141%7CRSS&amp;amp;xs=1" data-i13n="elm:affiliate_link;elmt:premonetized" rel="sponsored" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:predisposed to sleep issues;elm:affiliate_link;elmt:premonetized;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link  rapid-with-clickid etailiffa-link"&gt;predisposed to sleep issues&lt;/a&gt;. It could be a side effect of impaired activity in the reticular activating system (RAS) — a network of nerve pathways in the brainstem that are essential in mediating a person’s level of consciousness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The RAS &lt;a href="https://go.redirectingat.com/?id=74679X1524629&amp;amp;sref=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.buzzfeed.com%2Fkrissybrady%2Fadult-adhd-signs-symptoms&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.researchgate.net%2Ffigure%2FFrontal-View-of-the-Brain-Showing-the-Reticular-Formation-and-the-Locus-Ceruleus_fig1_261580973&amp;amp;xcust=7852141%7CRSS&amp;amp;xs=1" data-i13n="elm:affiliate_link;elmt:premonetized" rel="sponsored" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:acts as a screening device;elm:affiliate_link;elmt:premonetized;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link  rapid-with-clickid etailiffa-link"&gt;acts as a screening device&lt;/a&gt; that filters through incoming sensory data and sends bat signals to the brain as it comes across important sensory stimuli that need to be addressed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Only, for people with ADHD, RAS dysregulation makes it difficult to distinguish between what’s important sensory information and what’s just noise. The result? “Difficulty regulating arousal and sleep-wake transitions,” Khan said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Some people with ADHD can also have biological disruptions to their circadian rhythm, O’Shea said. &lt;a href="https://go.redirectingat.com/?id=74679X1524629&amp;amp;sref=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.buzzfeed.com%2Fkrissybrady%2Fadult-adhd-signs-symptoms&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov%2Fpmc%2Farticles%2FPMC4340974%2F&amp;amp;xcust=7852141%7CRSS&amp;amp;xs=1" data-i13n="elm:affiliate_link;elmt:premonetized" rel="sponsored" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Two such disruptions;elm:affiliate_link;elmt:premonetized;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link  rapid-with-clickid etailiffa-link"&gt;Two such disruptions&lt;/a&gt; are delayed sleep phase disorder — where your sleep is persistently delayed by two or more hours past what’s considered a standard bedtime — and delayed onset of melatonin production, the sleep hormone that kicks in at night to help you doze off.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;8. Taking forever to make decisions&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="relative mb-4"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="relative text-sm mt-1 pr-2.5"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; LaylaBird / Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“People with ADHD may experience &lt;a href="https://go.redirectingat.com/?id=74679X1524629&amp;amp;sref=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.buzzfeed.com%2Fkrissybrady%2Fadult-adhd-signs-symptoms&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fjournals.plos.org%2Fplosone%2Farticle%3Fid%3D10.1371%252Fjournal.pone.0256228&amp;amp;xcust=7852141%7CRSS&amp;amp;xs=1" data-i13n="elm:affiliate_link;elmt:premonetized" rel="sponsored" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:slower processing speeds;elm:affiliate_link;elmt:premonetized;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link  rapid-with-clickid etailiffa-link"&gt;slower processing speeds&lt;/a&gt;,” Louk said. Processing speed refers to how quickly you can react to a given stimulus (in this case, a set of choices) within a limited time frame.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;It’s not necessarily a sign you’re indecisive — rather, that you need more time to navigate the decision-making process.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;You might have difficulty with things like putting together the details necessary to see the big picture, foreseeing the potential outcomes of each option, or getting stuck on one idea and having trouble weighing all of the options to make a decision.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“This is a result of &lt;a href="https://go.redirectingat.com/?id=74679X1524629&amp;amp;sref=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.buzzfeed.com%2Fkrissybrady%2Fadult-adhd-signs-symptoms&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.frontiersin.org%2Farticles%2F10.3389%2Ffpsyt.2021.519840%2Ffull&amp;amp;xcust=7852141%7CRSS&amp;amp;xs=1" data-i13n="elm:affiliate_link;elmt:premonetized" rel="sponsored" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:controlling attention;elm:affiliate_link;elmt:premonetized;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link  rapid-with-clickid etailiffa-link"&gt;controlling attention&lt;/a&gt; well enough to sort through the pros and cons of a decision and remember what you were thinking,” O’Shea said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;9. Feeling perpetually restless&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="relative mb-4"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="relative text-sm mt-1 pr-2.5"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; Bymuratdeniz / Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Restlessness tends to be one of the sneakier signs of adult ADHD, largely due to how easily the external behaviors of restlessness can be attributed to other things, like an intense workload or drinking too much coffee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“Adults are more likely to show restlessness through having to get up and pace around,” O’Shea said. “They might not be able to sit through a movie without talking or getting out their phone.” Some may even avoid more subdued activities like this entirely.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Persistent fidgeting of the hands, legs and feet, as well as picking at your skin, can also be subtle signs of restlessness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;10. Rambling and monopolizing conversations&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="relative mb-4"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="relative text-sm mt-1 pr-2.5"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; Maskot via Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;People with ADHD can have trouble tracking a conversation thanks to poor attention control and retaining information in the moment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“This can lead to frequent interrupting because they might not remember what they want to say or what the other person said,” O’Shea said. “They can also feel restless and have an urge to jump in with a thought that interests them.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Here’s when you should get tested for ADHD&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="relative mb-4"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="relative text-sm mt-1 pr-2.5"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; Yana Iskayeva / Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;You might want to get evaluated for ADHD if you’re experiencing five or more &lt;a href="https://go.redirectingat.com/?id=74679X1524629&amp;amp;sref=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.buzzfeed.com%2Fkrissybrady%2Fadult-adhd-signs-symptoms&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.cdc.gov%2Fncbddd%2Fadhd%2Fdiagnosis.html&amp;amp;xcust=7852141%7CRSS&amp;amp;xs=1" data-i13n="elm:affiliate_link;elmt:premonetized" rel="sponsored" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:symptoms of ADHD;elm:affiliate_link;elmt:premonetized;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link  rapid-with-clickid etailiffa-link"&gt;symptoms of ADHD&lt;/a&gt; — and these symptoms have been persisting for longer than six months, are present in two or more settings (say, at work and in your relationships) and are reducing the quality of how you function in your life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“Talking to your primary care doctor is a good place to start with an initial review of your symptoms, followed by connecting with an ADHD specialist in your area,” O’Shea said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The diagnosis of ADHD is made by taking a proper history and gathering relevant information and data to help not only diagnose ADHD but also rule out other causes for the presenting symptoms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Important aspects of the exam include the collection of details regarding the presenting complaint, a complete psychiatric review of symptoms, and both personal and family psychiatric and medical histories.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;ADHD rating scales and psychological tests can also be used to further confirm the diagnosis of ADHD.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“Psychological testing is typically used in adults where it’s not clear from the history alone that the symptomatology is indicative of ADHD,” Khan said. “This is because a lot of the rating scales and tests to help diagnose ADHD haven’t been studied in adults and therefore can’t be utilized as sole diagnostic tools or proof an adult has ADHD.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Once you’re diagnosed with ADHD, what’s next?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="relative mb-4"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="relative text-sm mt-1 pr-2.5"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; Klaus Vedfelt / Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;An official ADHD diagnosis can be a game changer for so many adults who were struggling all their lives. Having a diagnosis starts a journey to build back confidence and motivation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“You may have been called or thought of yourself as ‘lazy’ or ‘unsuccessful’ and the diagnosis can provide a framework for your lifelong struggles,” &lt;a href="https://go.redirectingat.com/?id=74679X1524629&amp;amp;sref=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.buzzfeed.com%2Fkrissybrady%2Fadult-adhd-signs-symptoms&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fweillcornell.org%2Fheather-goodman-md&amp;amp;xcust=7852141%7CRSS&amp;amp;xs=1" data-i13n="elm:affiliate_link;elmt:premonetized" rel="sponsored" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Dr. Heather Goodman;elm:affiliate_link;elmt:premonetized;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link  rapid-with-clickid etailiffa-link"&gt;Dr. Heather Goodman&lt;/a&gt;, a psychiatrist at Weill Cornell Medicine and NewYork-Presbyterian, told HuffPost.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Treatment for adult ADHD is similar to treatment for childhood ADHD and includes medication, psychotherapy focused on improving organization and functioning in your daily life, and treatment for any mental health conditions that you have along with ADHD.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“Gaining clarity as a result of your ADHD diagnosis is the first step on a healing path,” O’Shea said. “Finally, what’s next can feel more in your control.”&lt;em&gt;This article originally appeared on&lt;/em&gt; &lt;a href="https://go.redirectingat.com/?id=74679X1524629&amp;amp;sref=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.buzzfeed.com%2Fkrissybrady%2Fadult-adhd-signs-symptoms&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.huffpost.com%2Fentry%2Fadult-adhd-signs-symptoms_l_634dbbe6e4b04cf8f37b8e6f&amp;amp;xcust=7852141%7CRSS&amp;amp;xs=1" data-i13n="elm:affiliate_link;elmt:premonetized" rel="sponsored" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:HuffPost.;elm:affiliate_link;elmt:premonetized;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link  rapid-with-clickid etailiffa-link"&gt;&lt;em&gt;HuffPost.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Yahoo Life</author><pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 23:16:02 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMif0FVX3lxTE5zNnZQUk5NVUY1OTlMUmRTOWxfTzNUR29YUExvQldpdmtlS0RNUnVTeEN3SmxrczBoek1oaXRfMWVkREkzbl9ta2RIQ01PLU9seDdpZFJkaTQ1ZzVnZExQdFdRMUk3RldicjY1cHl4VTNTNGxwRG9VQTVQay1iVkU</guid></item><item><title>People Are Just Now Realizing These Everyday Behaviors Are Actually Symptoms Of Adult ADHD - BuzzFeed</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMib0FVX3lxTE1xUUZ6RF9ENFJFT1M0UWZDNm5WNzlEYkg5dlI4ejlnWXgxY1BzVDl3al84TG5ycy1HZ3pBaURHV3cxVzFtUHhUQ29Ld2JRQ3RLMG5fLXl5SUxmNFFFdXloazNZS190ZlJ6RDFpMlVGNA?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="subbuzz buzz-width--standard__subbuzz buzz-type--long__subbuzz subbuzz-text
  subbuzz-index-1
  
  
  
  
  " data-keywords="skincare" data-module="subbuzz-text"&gt;
  
  &lt;p id="138407861" class="subbuzz-anchor"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;





&lt;p&gt;With everything there is to juggle in life, it’s easy to assume that everyone experiences that sinking-in-quicksand feeling as they navigate another busy day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But if you find this feeling is paired with extreme levels of disorganization, inattention and overwhelm, these might be signs of attention-deficit/hyperactivity disorder.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Roughly &lt;a href="https://chadd.org/for-adults/overview/" target="_blank" data-skimlinks-tracking="7852141" data-affiliate="true"&gt;10 million American adults&lt;/a&gt; (and over &lt;a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC7916320/" target="_blank" data-skimlinks-tracking="7852141" data-affiliate="true"&gt;365 million globally&lt;/a&gt;) are thought to have ADHD — and because symptoms can show up differently in adults, realizing you might have the disorder is typically a slow burn, the overlooked signs of which can cause significant strain on your life and health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Adults looking for diagnosis often have many subtle signs rather than completely failing,” &lt;a href="https://brainandmind.org" target="_blank" data-skimlinks-tracking="7852141" data-affiliate="true"&gt;Dede O’Shea&lt;/a&gt;, a neuropsychologist at &lt;a href="https://physicians.lahey.org/details/4345/dede-oshea-psychiatry__behavioral_medicine-burlington" target="_blank" data-skimlinks-tracking="7852141" data-affiliate="true"&gt;Beth Israel Lahey Health&lt;/a&gt; in Cambridge, Massachusetts, told HuffPost.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The hallmark symptoms of ADHD — inattention, impulsivity and hyperactivity — typically aren’t as noticeable in adulthood, likely because adults whose ADHD wasn’t diagnosed in childhood have had a lifetime to parse together the skills necessary to compensate for their symptoms. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Some symptoms of ADHD also mimic those of anxiety or depression,” &lt;a href="https://www.peacehumanistic.com" target="_blank" data-skimlinks-tracking="7852141" data-affiliate="true"&gt;Cristina Louk&lt;/a&gt;, a clinical psychologist based in Washington state, told HuffPost. “Most people will first get diagnosed with these disorders and get frustrated when treatment fails to alleviate their symptoms.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the moment, you might find yourself attributing certain feelings and behaviors to other things — blaming feelings of hype on too much coffee or snapping at your frozen computer on sleep deprivation — when really, they’re symptoms of adult ADHD.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Here are some of the sneakier signs you might be overlooking:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. Procrastinating to the extreme&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BuzzFeed</author><pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 23:16:02 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMib0FVX3lxTE1xUUZ6RF9ENFJFT1M0UWZDNm5WNzlEYkg5dlI4ejlnWXgxY1BzVDl3al84TG5ycy1HZ3pBaURHV3cxVzFtUHhUQ29Ld2JRQ3RLMG5fLXl5SUxmNFFFdXloazNZS190ZlJ6RDFpMlVGNA</guid></item><item><title>AI lung disease test to be rolled out in GP surgeries - The Independent</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMihwFBVV95cUxOOFFOUjVHNXN6cFpORmJJWHk5bV85UzVVM2hHYUpnX01PaUtxRThXV2NIV29oOVRYeDBNUDdyaTFzV3NRNUIteTZ1NUoyRnlIazVMWWpBcGtKZVhnVHJ2bjVtejBZVFMzODAtU2JRR0dqalpoR1B5UXpZNV9hM3FUQ19DTllHWHc?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="sc-jbiisr-0 fsDBBo sc-jbiisr-1 gfSVvz" id="main"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="hydrate-root sc-10wlkbs-0 cwDkqf" data-component="SupportNSCNative" data-loading="lazy" data-theme-name="base-light"&gt;&lt;aside class="sc-hez36s-0 guIZJM"&gt;&lt;div class="sc-hez36s-1 ghpvHl"&gt;&lt;h3 data-testid="support-nsc-title" class="sc-hez36s-2 dyeFNc"&gt;Your support helps us to tell the story&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;div class="sc-hez36s-8 QyvDf"&gt;&lt;div class="sc-hez36s-13 hjfIlW"&gt;&lt;div class="sc-aja53j-0 bXNazX sc-hez36s-16 eFHwkn"&gt;&lt;div class="sc-aja53j-6 lpmrWp"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="dropdown-with-gradient-collapsed-content-container" class="sc-aja53j-5 kHOfxf"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div data-testid="dropdown-with-gradient-collapsed-content" class="sc-aja53j-4 llSPWP"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div data-testid="support-nsc-collapsed-content-tablet" class="sc-hez36s-7 ctaaNX"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-1uza6dc-0 zTiwj"&gt;From reproductive rights to climate change to Big Tech, The Independent is on the ground when the story is developing. Whether it's investigating the financials of Elon Musk's pro-Trump PAC or producing our latest documentary, 'The A Word', which shines a light on the American women fighting for reproductive rights, we know how important it is to parse out the facts from the messaging.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-1uza6dc-0 zTiwj"&gt;At such a critical moment in US history, we need reporters on the ground. Your donation allows us to keep sending journalists to speak to both sides of the story.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-1uza6dc-0 zTiwj"&gt;The Independent is trusted by Americans across the entire political spectrum. And unlike many other quality news outlets, we choose not to lock Americans out of our reporting and analysis with paywalls. We believe quality journalism should be available to everyone, paid for by those who can afford it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;strong class="sc-1uza6dc-1 jjnSjU"&gt;Your support makes all the difference.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;button class="sc-aja53j-1 eEsFcE sc-aja53j-7 ftfOXG"&gt;&lt;span data-testid="dropdown-with-gradient-dropdown-tablet" class="sc-aja53j-3 hJQdyb"&gt;&lt;span data-action-type="Read more" class="sc-aja53j-2 lnspNG"&gt;Read more&lt;/span&gt;&lt;svg class="sc-eaj12q-0 fyzsgJ sc-culv3z-0 dfspto sc-a5wy94-0 bpMmxj"&gt;&lt;use href="#ee6613da15642019"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;A revolutionary AI-powered diagnostic test for chronic obstructive pulmonary disease (COPD) is set to be introduced in GP surgeries across England from 14 April, offering a faster and more accurate diagnosis of this common lung condition. The technology, known as N-Tidal Diagnose, uses carbon dioxide sensors and AI to analyse a patient's normal breathing patterns, delivering results in just minutes. The rollout is expected to extend to the rest of the UK soon after.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Currently, COPD diagnosis relies on spirometry, a time-consuming procedure requiring patients to forcefully exhale into a device. Appointments can take between 30 and 90 minutes. N-Tidal Diagnose simplifies this process significantly, measuring carbon dioxide (CO2) concentration in normal breaths and providing a diagnosis within five minutes. This efficiency has led medical professionals to hail the device as "game-changing".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="article-im-prompt"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;COPD encompasses a group of lung conditions, including emphysema and chronic bronchitis, that cause breathing difficulties. The N-Tidal Diagnose device has received regulatory clearance and CE-marking under EU Medical Device Regulations for COPD diagnosis. Its developer, TidalSense, is also exploring its potential for asthma diagnosis. This innovative technology promises to transform COPD diagnosis, offering a quicker, more convenient, and potentially more accurate method for detecting this prevalent lung condition.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr Ameera Patel, chief executive of TidalSense, said: “For decades, respiratory diagnostics have lagged behind other areas of medicine, despite lung disease being one of the UK’s greatest healthcare challenges.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The N-Tidal Diagnose device represents the first real breakthrough in COPD diagnosis in several decades, addressing both the needs of the patient and of the health system – and it’s designed to be deployed at scale across the NHS.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="taboola-mid-article-thumbnails-ii" class="sc-looa6c-0 WWPRF"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Our goal is to make respiratory diagnosis fast, accurate, and accessible to everyone who needs it, at the instant that they present.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="sc-482ou5-2 IoAJj sc-482ou5-3 dzDedB image align-center"&gt;&lt;figure class="sc-1cbdeug-0 bZqoQk"&gt;&lt;div data-gallery-length="2" class="sc-482ou5-0 bqSiOl"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.independent.co.uk/2025/03/30/17/28/01JQJYWRY0XW9K22ZQJAKF2X0P-(1).jpg" srcset="https://static.independent.co.uk/2025/03/30/17/28/01JQJYWRY0XW9K22ZQJAKF2X0P-(1).jpg?quality=75&amp;amp;width=320&amp;amp;auto=webp 320w, https://static.independent.co.uk/2025/03/30/17/28/01JQJYWRY0XW9K22ZQJAKF2X0P-(1).jpg?quality=75&amp;amp;width=640&amp;amp;auto=webp 640w" loading="lazy" alt="Dr Simon Rudland, a GP in Suffolk, showing the N-Tidal Diagnose test to a patient" class="sc-1mc30lb-0 cpasWE inline-gallery-btn"&gt;&lt;p class="hydrate-root sc-10wlkbs-0 sc-482ou5-1 cwDkqf edasoI" data-component="AutoGalleryButton" data-theme-name="base-light"&gt;&lt;button class="sc-ohzviw-0 IQpjM inline-gallery-btn" id="trigger-autogallery-230636"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-ohzviw-1 imeAUH"&gt;open image in gallery&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-1cbdeug-1 sc-1cbdeug-3 bWFKX dpkjCF"&gt;Dr Simon Rudland, a GP in Suffolk, showing the N-Tidal Diagnose test to a patient&lt;span class="sc-1cbdeug-7 Rqdgl"&gt; (TidalSense/PA Wire)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;It is estimated about 1.2 million people in the UK have COPD, with as many as two million people undiagnosed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr Patel claims the test could help the Government meet its goal of slashing NHS waiting times.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She added: “The NHS is under immense pressure and the Government has laid out ambitious plans to change the way services are delivered.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Its targets against reducing waiting times and using staff time more efficiently will be easier to meet with the introduction of new tools like N-Tidal Diagnose.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“This simple device can help significantly reduce waiting lists, improve patient experience, deliver accurate diagnoses and ultimately provide a better standard of care for the millions of people in the UK who have COPD.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;N-Tidal is also being tested for asthma, with the hopes it will one day be used to diagnose the condition once research trials are complete.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr Simon Rudland, a GP in Suffolk, hailed the test as a “game changing”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="taboola-mid-article-thumbnails-iii" class="sc-looa6c-0 WWPRF"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“COPD is one of the most underdiagnosed and misdiagnosed conditions we see in the NHS, and because spirometry testing can only be carried out by specially trained practitioners, it can lead to sizeable wait lists for diagnosis,” he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Having the ability to assess a patient’s lung health quickly and accurately with a device that gives near-instant results will be game-changing for respiratory care across both primary and secondary healthcare settings.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Independent</author><pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 23:09:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihwFBVV95cUxOOFFOUjVHNXN6cFpORmJJWHk5bV85UzVVM2hHYUpnX01PaUtxRThXV2NIV29oOVRYeDBNUDdyaTFzV3NRNUIteTZ1NUoyRnlIazVMWWpBcGtKZVhnVHJ2bjVtejBZVFMzODAtU2JRR0dqalpoR1B5UXpZNV9hM3FUQ19DTllHWHc</guid></item><item><title>Researchers Discover New Mechanism for Rapid Liver Regeneration to Restore Damaged Livers - Good News Network</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMivwFBVV95cUxOTFhXZkJrd1hheG9IVDVZQ0J0d2VsUVQ0WWpuRldyUzViWTlmZXBacDhHUE0teExVS0ZHU0FhU1BKc2NTcU05dy11YnpIMkluVXhXNHFrMzRDX2NrbTFnY1FYRGNzZi1zZGxsbDBZX19ocGZVeS1UX01MQXpPV3hSM3dGOGhrWWZUZy1PeE9rWVhVYUk5dEY5YjUyNXBzWS1mNjZ0RDZCT2MwblpqWF9uMkhOZ1ZDeE00YVRocWtzVQ?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="td-post-content"&gt;
        &lt;figure id="attachment_216293" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-216293" class="wp-caption aligncenter"&gt;&lt;img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" class="size-large wp-image-216293" src="https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/Liver-disease-transplant-doctor-Getty-Images-For-Unsplash-PCcG8ouwzPQ-1024x552.jpg" alt="" srcset="https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/Liver-disease-transplant-doctor-Getty-Images-For-Unsplash-PCcG8ouwzPQ-1024x552.jpg 1024w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/Liver-disease-transplant-doctor-Getty-Images-For-Unsplash-PCcG8ouwzPQ-326x176.jpg 326w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/Liver-disease-transplant-doctor-Getty-Images-For-Unsplash-PCcG8ouwzPQ-768x414.jpg 768w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/Liver-disease-transplant-doctor-Getty-Images-For-Unsplash-PCcG8ouwzPQ-696x375.jpg 696w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/Liver-disease-transplant-doctor-Getty-Images-For-Unsplash-PCcG8ouwzPQ-1068x576.jpg 1068w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/Liver-disease-transplant-doctor-Getty-Images-For-Unsplash-PCcG8ouwzPQ-779x420.jpg 779w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/Liver-disease-transplant-doctor-Getty-Images-For-Unsplash-PCcG8ouwzPQ-530x286.jpg 530w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/Liver-disease-transplant-doctor-Getty-Images-For-Unsplash-PCcG8ouwzPQ.jpg 1400w" sizes="(max-width: 696px) 100vw, 696px"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-216293" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Getty Images for Unsplash+&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Researchers at the National Cancer Research Centre in Spain (CNIO) have discovered a mechanism that is triggered just minutes after acute liver damage occurs—and it could lead to treatments for those with severe liver problems.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The avenues for future treatments of liver damage include a diet enriched with the amino acid glutamate.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Glutamate supplementation can promote liver regeneration and benefit patients in recovery following hepatectomy or awaiting a transplant,” wrote the authors&lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41586-025-08778-6" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt; in a paper published&lt;/a&gt; in ‘Nature’.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The liver is a vital organ, crucial to digestion, metabolism, and the elimination of toxins. It has a unique ability to regenerate, which allows it to replace liver cells damaged by the very toxins that these cells eliminate.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;However, the liver stops regenerating in cases of diseases that involve chronic liver damage–such as cirrhosis—and such diseases are becoming increasingly prevalent, associated with poor dietary habits or alcohol consumption. So activating liver regeneration is key to treating the disease.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="pgs-dpg-flex" data-pgs-partner-id="good-news-network"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Learning to activate liver regeneration is therefore a priority today, to benefit patients with liver damage and also those who’ve had part of their liver cut out to remove a tumor.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The research has discovered in animal models this previously unknown mechanism of liver regeneration. It is a process that is triggered very quickly, just a few minutes after acute liver damage occurs, with the amino acid glutamate playing a key role.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Our results describe a fundamental and universal mechanism that allows the liver to regenerate after acute damage,” explained Nabil Djouder, head of the CNIO Growth Factors, Nutrients and Cancer Group and senior author of the study.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ANOTHER BREAKTHROUGH:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a title="Edible Carbon Beads Can Reduce Cirrhosis Liver Disease By Restoring Gut Microbiome" href="https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/edible-carbon-beads-can-reduce-cirrhosis-liver-disease-by-restoring-gut-microbiome/" rel="bookmark"&gt;Edible Carbon Beads Can Reduce Cirrhosis Liver Disease By Restoring Gut Microbiome&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;A “complex and ingenious” perspective on liver regeneration&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Liver regeneration was known to occur through the proliferation of liver cells, known as hepatocytes. However, the molecular mechanisms involved were not fully understood. This current discovery is very novel, as it describes communication between two different organs, the liver and bone marrow, involving the immune system, &lt;a href="https://www.cnio.es/en/news/cnio-researchers-discover-a-new-mechanism-for-rapid-liver-regeneration-triggered-by-glutamate/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;according to a CINO news release&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The results show that liver and bone marrow are interconnected by glutamate. After acute liver damage, liver cells, called hepatocytes, produce glutamate and send it into the bloodstream; through the blood, glutamate reaches the bone marrow, inside the bones, where it activates monocytes, a type of immune system cell. Monocytes then travel to the liver and along the way become macrophages – also immune cells. The presence of glutamate reprograms the metabolism of macrophages, and these consequently begin to secrete a growth factor that leads to an increase in hepatocyte production.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In other words, a rapid chain of events allows glutamate to trigger liver regeneration in just minutes, through changes in the macrophage metabolism. It is, says Djouder, “a new, complex and ingenious perspective on how the liver stimulates its own regeneration.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The research also clarifies a previously unanswered question: how the various areas of the liver are coordinated during regeneration. In the liver, there are different types of hepatocytes, organized in different areas; the hepatocytes in each area perform specific metabolic functions. The study reveals that hepatocytes producing a protein known as glutamine synthetase, which regulates glutamate levels, play a key role in regeneration.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;MORE PROGRESS:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a title="Tumor-Destroying Sound Waves Treatment Coming to a Hospital Near You For Liver Cancer" href="https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/tumor-destroying-sound-waves-treatment-coming-to-a-hospital-near-you-for-liver-cancer/" rel="bookmark"&gt;Tumor-Destroying Sound Waves Treatment Coming to a Hospital Near You For Liver Cancer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;According to the CNIO group, when glutamine synthetase is inhibited, there is more glutamate in circulation, which accelerates liver regeneration. This is what happens when the liver suffers acute damage: glutamine synthase activity decreases, blood glutamate increases, and from there, the connection with the bone marrow is established, reprogramming macrophages and stimulating hepatocyte proliferation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Possible therapeutic applications&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The experiments have been carried out in mice, but the results have been tested with bioinformatics tools, using databases of mouse and human hepatocytes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;According to Djouder, “&lt;a href="https://amzn.to/4l4mjlP" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;dietary glutamate supplementation&lt;/a&gt; may simply be recommended in the future after liver extirpation, and also to reduce liver damage caused by cirrhosis.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CAFFEINE ALERT&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;a title="Coffee is Now Linked to Reduced Risk of Many Ailments, Including Liver Disease, Parkinson’s, Melanoma, Even Suicide" href="https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/all-of-coffees-beneficial-effects-liver-disease-cancers-obesity/" rel="bookmark"&gt;Coffee is Now Linked to Reduced Risk of Many Ailments, Including Liver Disease, Parkinson’s, Melanoma, Even Suicide&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The first author of the paper, CNIO researcher María del Mar Rigual also wants future research to explore using glutamate supplements in humans who have undergone liver resection for tumor removal.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SPREAD THE GOOD NEWS With Patients Worldwide on Social Media…&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;


    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Good News Network</author><pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 22:23:24 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMivwFBVV95cUxOTFhXZkJrd1hheG9IVDVZQ0J0d2VsUVQ0WWpuRldyUzViWTlmZXBacDhHUE0teExVS0ZHU0FhU1BKc2NTcU05dy11YnpIMkluVXhXNHFrMzRDX2NrbTFnY1FYRGNzZi1zZGxsbDBZX19ocGZVeS1UX01MQXpPV3hSM3dGOGhrWWZUZy1PeE9rWVhVYUk5dEY5YjUyNXBzWS1mNjZ0RDZCT2MwblpqWF9uMkhOZ1ZDeE00YVRocWtzVQ</guid></item><item><title>Colorectal Cancer Is on the Rise: Mayo Clinic Doctor Reveals 4 Keys Symptoms You Should Know - SciTechDaily</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiuAFBVV95cUxQei0tVlJTcEtsSy1XejJHeGtYMHk5c0toeDNGRnY5MGpSOFdpSEtnZUpiRFFUQjM5ZUJpTDJQNHhkTVlZeUYtSGFOS0RqMld1eG1sV0lzN0c0TWJBUzUwNnlZMXRSOU0wWEhTdEVHQURXUlVzX1pIcUFQeGFYODlNdUIyVkZGNXplWWZ5TlZkOVlGcGZvdUNlblZtRG55UEdfeTZSVGYySWV0RjY1dmwtUEZhVmVtbkdF?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>SciTechDaily</author><pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 21:33:03 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiuAFBVV95cUxQei0tVlJTcEtsSy1XejJHeGtYMHk5c0toeDNGRnY5MGpSOFdpSEtnZUpiRFFUQjM5ZUJpTDJQNHhkTVlZeUYtSGFOS0RqMld1eG1sV0lzN0c0TWJBUzUwNnlZMXRSOU0wWEhTdEVHQURXUlVzX1pIcUFQeGFYODlNdUIyVkZGNXplWWZ5TlZkOVlGcGZvdUNlblZtRG55UEdfeTZSVGYySWV0RjY1dmwtUEZhVmVtbkdF</guid></item><item><title>How Cold Water Rewires Your Cells to Fight Stress and Aging - SciTechDaily</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMijgFBVV95cUxNcjhIZU9jUEoya0RJZFhnaVhtbEVGUnVtWTZKUjhJZ1dTeW1FTzRITG9jemhZRkdqZVpzMzVuX0pYd0d0cjZIM0tIb2JTOWNBS0pPRHhDY3BBOVpKMVVJQjh0TXQ3eUVTaXRpZnYtYnlJQkVOYkhtRVZGS2ZzZ2RFSzJiRjlTYy1fTkhhbm5B?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>SciTechDaily</author><pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 20:24:14 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijgFBVV95cUxNcjhIZU9jUEoya0RJZFhnaVhtbEVGUnVtWTZKUjhJZ1dTeW1FTzRITG9jemhZRkdqZVpzMzVuX0pYd0d0cjZIM0tIb2JTOWNBS0pPRHhDY3BBOVpKMVVJQjh0TXQ3eUVTaXRpZnYtYnlJQkVOYkhtRVZGS2ZzZ2RFSzJiRjlTYy1fTkhhbm5B</guid></item><item><title>Dementia’s links to diabetes, herpes explored as research widens - South China Morning Post</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMi2gFBVV95cUxQVXFwU18wUDU5Q2hENDlJTmpOMk1qMzFXTHFOQW5wdGg2LTN2eThVeDNhWG1aejNQamxxMTF2MndYRlVTbENtMWhqUktQNG1nRkE0MVRRU0kwVnZqVFljNnZoUnFOTG10YWRiRFdoUVFLenVUTXJ5N3FDYnRnemt2TEs0R2xxOGNXSy1VOTdGbFhfSUd6UWlzbXdUY3d2R1NmNEdIRDFpVWNwYkNmeldFMHBoMG9PZXVEVnRGaXQ0cm9EQU54WDZXUFhCTDVwMGRhbEhMQ3hNQy1sZ9IB2gFBVV95cUxQT1lJZllOVmRfX0dpZlVjS19YeXo0VVNMNE9GTE0yOW5KeE9hcnhkR3IweHNXMkRKTm1aV0dNY19wNFhCRzNWWk9RblNPTnZtUHh0Yk03bWNCZWYxQkZRZGpraFZUOXhxT0hxaDJyM2Q5QUFjZ3NoQUVhOE8yR2xmT3ZSeGZ2TG83VFFqVl82dXNYUFZWZEs1aVgxWEZzTzV2RkFyMDhoMTZiRDBGbWt1RlBoc0ctZ0ZwZWpkcU5fbmVuMDQ4cUdta0xPQ2VOOVdFb3ZfZTlhTXVoUQ?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;section class="er6t7fe38 css-19sk4h4 e1pqt1t0" data-qa="ContentBody-ContentBodyContainer"&gt;&lt;p class="js-reading-0-percent-completion-tracker css-19icq8a ekyy9du0" data-qa="useTrackViewedPercentageRender-trackViewedPercentageRenders-TrackPercentageBlock"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div datatype="p" data-qa="Component-Component" class="e8zc9q40 css-1xdhyk6 ec74h0k0"&gt;&lt;em data-qa="ContentSchemaRender-defaultRenderMapFunctions-Component-0" class="css-1mniedq ex3nmsa15"&gt;This is the 59th instalment in&lt;/em&gt; &lt;a target="_self" class="e1yy41x40 ef9u0v01 css-1ankfgb ecgc78b0" href="https://www.scmp.com/lifestyle/health-wellness/series/3206510/decoding-dementia?module=inline&amp;amp;pgtype=article?module=inline&amp;amp;pgtype=article?module=inline&amp;amp;pgtype=article?module=inline&amp;amp;pgtype=article?module=inline&amp;amp;pgtype=article?module=inline&amp;amp;pgtype=article?module=inline&amp;amp;pgtype=article?module=inline&amp;amp;pgtype=article?module=inline&amp;amp;pgtype=article?module=inline&amp;amp;pgtype=article?module=inline&amp;amp;pgtype=article?module=inline&amp;amp;pgtype=article" data-qa="BaseLink-renderAnchor-StyledAnchor"&gt;&lt;span data-qa="Component-Text" class="css-0 ef9u0v00"&gt;&lt;em data-qa="ContentSchemaRender-defaultRenderMapFunctions-Component-0" class="css-1mniedq ex3nmsa15"&gt;a series on dementia&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em data-qa="ContentSchemaRender-defaultRenderMapFunctions-Component-3" class="css-1mniedq ex3nmsa15"&gt;, including the research into its causes and treatment, advice for carers and stories of hope.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p datatype="p" data-qa="Component-Component" class="e8zc9q40 css-1c6uqr6 ec74h0k1"&gt;The so-called amyloid hypothesis has dominated thinking on Alzheimer’s disease for more than a century – since German psychiatrist and neuropathologist Alois Alzheimer found abnormal clumps of proteins called amyloids in a deceased patient’s brain in 1906.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div datatype="p" data-qa="Component-Component" class="e8zc9q40 css-1xdhyk6 ec74h0k0"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Their occurrence can set up a catastrophic chain reaction that ultimately leads to the symptoms we associate with &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a target="_self" class="e1yy41x40 ef9u0v01 css-1ankfgb ecgc78b0" href="https://www.scmp.com/lifestyle/health-wellness/article/3293280/how-tcm-could-help-fight-dementia-cases-set-triple-hong-kong-expert-explains?module=inline&amp;amp;pgtype=article" data-qa="BaseLink-renderAnchor-StyledAnchor"&gt;&lt;span data-qa="Component-Text" class="css-0 ef9u0v00"&gt;dementia&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="image-inline-container e1a5rv550 css-1llrc1m e1yqhwb40" data-qa="Component-renderMap-StyledDiv"&gt;&lt;div class="image-inline caption e1fvabeq0 css-19sk4h4 ea9pn0s0" data-qa="Component-Container"&gt;&lt;figure class="image-inline caption ea9pn0s1 css-1qeofuq e1gf69pb0" data-qa="ArticleImage-ArticleImageContainer"&gt;&lt;figcaption data-qa="ArticleImage-DescriptionContainer" class="css-6potyr e1gf69pb1"&gt;Some people exhibit amyloid plaques and tau tangles associated with Alzheimer’s but never develop dementia. Illustration: Shutterstock&lt;p data-qa="ArticleImage-Spacer" class="css-mkkf9p e11xd9ce0"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p datatype="p" data-qa="Component-Component" class="e8zc9q40 css-1c6uqr6 ec74h0k1"&gt;But having amyloid deposits in the brain does not always lead to dementia. Some people exhibit amyloid plaques and tau tangles but never develop the characteristic symptoms of dementia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="js-reading-20-percent-completion-tracker css-19icq8a ekyy9du0" data-qa="useTrackViewedPercentageRender-trackViewedPercentageRenders-TrackPercentageBlock"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>South China Morning Post</author><pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 20:15:08 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi2gFBVV95cUxQVXFwU18wUDU5Q2hENDlJTmpOMk1qMzFXTHFOQW5wdGg2LTN2eThVeDNhWG1aejNQamxxMTF2MndYRlVTbENtMWhqUktQNG1nRkE0MVRRU0kwVnZqVFljNnZoUnFOTG10YWRiRFdoUVFLenVUTXJ5N3FDYnRnemt2TEs0R2xxOGNXSy1VOTdGbFhfSUd6UWlzbXdUY3d2R1NmNEdIRDFpVWNwYkNmeldFMHBoMG9PZXVEVnRGaXQ0cm9EQU54WDZXUFhCTDVwMGRhbEhMQ3hNQy1sZ9IB2gFBVV95cUxQT1lJZllOVmRfX0dpZlVjS19YeXo0VVNMNE9GTE0yOW5KeE9hcnhkR3IweHNXMkRKTm1aV0dNY19wNFhCRzNWWk9RblNPTnZtUHh0Yk03bWNCZWYxQkZRZGpraFZUOXhxT0hxaDJyM2Q5QUFjZ3NoQUVhOE8yR2xmT3ZSeGZ2TG83VFFqVl82dXNYUFZWZEs1aVgxWEZzTzV2RkFyMDhoMTZiRDBGbWt1RlBoc0ctZ0ZwZWpkcU5fbmVuMDQ4cUdta0xPQ2VOOVdFb3ZfZTlhTXVoUQ</guid></item><item><title>This Brain Mechanism Explains Why Teens Love Risk More Than You - ScienceAlert</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMilwFBVV95cUxOemlGMm1EUG9jR3JHQ05kcl9EX2tVX3BqVVJ0RVlxSGxzUDZFN1A2Y0FrUll4QmRvOUJ6alRRZTVzLW84LWdfRnlDTlFPNnFNQzU1VWNsZVJ3YVg4V0tnSG80ODZybFh0ZW4yUEtPNkkxQXBDMTlFOVhwdjdqd0wwTWZLQjNaRTd1NXVnVkxLazFQZkxSajdr?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;The developmental progress from daredevil teen to risk-averse senior is more complex than we thought, according to a new study that identified changing relationships between neural structures related to risk avoidance at different life stages.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Neuroscientists from the University of California, Los Angeles, led an investigation into a critical part of the brain that help us determine whether we ought 'take the leap' or avoid life-threatening danger.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ours isn't the only species where adolescents engage in markedly risky behaviors – a pattern that's at odds with protecting ones' survival at all costs. Other animals, &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/S0149-7634(03)00006-X"&gt;such as mice&lt;/a&gt; for example, share this trait.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"These behaviors may compete with the drive to avo&lt;span&gt;id threatening situations, leading to a reduction in avoidance behaviors in PMA (platform-mediated avoidance assays)," the authors &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41593-025-01890-w"&gt;report&lt;/a&gt; in their new paper.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"&lt;span&gt;Here, we uncover a circuit mechanism that causally contributes to lower levels of threat avoidance in adolescence."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By studying the brains of mice, they found the &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Dorsomedial_prefrontal_cortex"&gt;dorso-medial prefrontal cortex&lt;/a&gt; (dmPFC) 'referees' neural pathways that take on distinct structures at certain points throughout life.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It's as if the prefrontal cortex – the part of the brain credited for our ability to steer our emotional meat ship on a &lt;a href="https://academic.oup.com/brain/article/147/3/794/7424860"&gt;more deliberate course&lt;/a&gt; – is negotiating with the structures that advocate for what we might call 'instinct' (the &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Basolateral_amygdala"&gt;basolateral amygdala&lt;/a&gt;, or BA, being the locus of fear and pain memory; the &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Nucleus_accumbens"&gt;nucleus accumbens&lt;/a&gt;, NA, being crucial to reward, reinforcement and aversion).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These negotiations, the experiments showed, depend greatly on age.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In an experiment reminiscent of James Dean's game of 'chicken run' in &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=BGtEp7zFdrc"&gt;Rebel without a cause&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;/em&gt;mice were trained to step on a platform to dodge a threat; a decision made more difficult with a smorgasbord laid out in front of them just out of reach of the platform.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Despite knowing very well how to escape the beep they'd come to associate with an electric shock, juvenile and adolescent mice chose to take their chances and keep on eating for longer, while older mice generally stepped dutifully onto the platform, waiting until the threat had passed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"A&lt;span&gt;lthough mice of all ages had similar levels of conditioned fear and some exploratory behaviors during the retrieval test, juveniles and adolescents explored the threatening part of the environment more than adults," the authors &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41593-025-01890-w"&gt;report&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Fluorescent molecules injected into the test subjects' brains allowed the researchers to track the physiology underpinning these behaviors. Higher levels of glowing molecules generally indicate greater amounts of neural activity. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Activating genes using light through a process of optogenetics revealed further details on how activity in these brain structures related to threat avoidance strategies in juvenile, adolescent and adult mice.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_155753" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-155753" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/03/threat-avoidance-model.jpg" alt="three similar diagrams showing dmPFC, nucleus accumbens and basolateral amygdyla connections at juvenile, adolescent and adult stages." class="size-full wp-image-155753" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/03/threat-avoidance-model.jpg 1509w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/03/threat-avoidance-model-642x197.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/03/threat-avoidance-model-1024x314.jpg 1024w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/03/threat-avoidance-model-768x236.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/03/threat-avoidance-model-600x184.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 1509px) 100vw, 1509px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-155753" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Proposed model of the development of dmPFC circuits underlying threat avoidance. Further detail &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41593-025-01890-w/figures/8"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. (Klune et al., &lt;em&gt;Nature Neuroscience&lt;/em&gt;, 2025)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;The dmPFC, it turns out, becomes more sensitive to threats with age. Much like aging in the rest of the body, however, changes in the structure's configuration occur in staggered stages characterized by maturation of synapses and re-arrangement of the circuits connecting the&lt;span&gt; BA and NA. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The brain's risk-avoidance system may be wired to best suit age-specific challenges as they arise, prioritizing risk when the nest is getting too crowded, and safety when it comes time to settle down.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a mouse study, so it's not clear if these same patterns hold true for humans. But, as mammals, we aren't &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/animal-testing"&gt;&lt;em&gt;too &lt;/em&gt;far-removed from mice&lt;/a&gt;, providing us with a proxy understanding of how our own brains might navigate the tug-of-war between rewarding risk and safety.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"&lt;span&gt;The lack of studies on the causal functions of the mPFC, BLA and NAc circuits in the developing brain has left a major gap in our understanding of how interactions between these regions produce developmental transitions in threat-induced behaviors," the authors &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41593-025-01890-w"&gt;write&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"&lt;span&gt;In revealing the processes by which top-down circuit maturation guides changes in threat-induced behaviors, we establish a foundation to understand how they can become disrupted.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This research is published in &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41593-025-01890-w"&gt;Nature Neuroscience&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 19:01:21 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilwFBVV95cUxOemlGMm1EUG9jR3JHQ05kcl9EX2tVX3BqVVJ0RVlxSGxzUDZFN1A2Y0FrUll4QmRvOUJ6alRRZTVzLW84LWdfRnlDTlFPNnFNQzU1VWNsZVJ3YVg4V0tnSG80ODZybFh0ZW4yUEtPNkkxQXBDMTlFOVhwdjdqd0wwTWZLQjNaRTd1NXVnVkxLazFQZkxSajdr</guid></item><item><title>Medication taken by 1 in 8 Americans linked to substantial increase in the risk of sudden cardiac death - Fortune</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMijAFBVV95cUxQMW1VMDN4cHRzd0pqTG9GNVlLZU5VZlExbjBHRjhKRnZGNHRWUnVobzEwei1sOHdTYTFLS3g4VThmOTRJUndKandzeDRobWJ2VW52NVpTSWhBZDNoMXNCcENkMmc3allIeWp1cG90UWhNWk5aYVkweVg0Q1JZWU9ZV09pUjVQYmdqTE1qQg?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Fortune</author><pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 15:35:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijAFBVV95cUxQMW1VMDN4cHRzd0pqTG9GNVlLZU5VZlExbjBHRjhKRnZGNHRWUnVobzEwei1sOHdTYTFLS3g4VThmOTRJUndKandzeDRobWJ2VW52NVpTSWhBZDNoMXNCcENkMmc3allIeWp1cG90UWhNWk5aYVkweVg0Q1JZWU9ZV09pUjVQYmdqTE1qQg</guid></item><item><title>Short-term reactivation of brain between encoding of memories enhances recall, study finds - Medical Xpress</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiigFBVV95cUxQWlA3cnRSbmdIZm1yWk1OenZVRU9uMElwSjFVanl2Rk01TmhPRjdxd2VKWDZ4SlRIbE5BRFlNQnZwbVNxLS04SHZ1cVVkZWhfM0ljSl9QYllwc19FekgwU0pWZzZvbzEwVU8wcGlNOUFXeWpQMUdIeFVkOE5DbW1kRVhGZmFVSDJTX0E?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="article-byline text-low"&gt;
                                        by Ingrid Fadelli                                                                                , Medical Xpress
                                                                            &lt;/p&gt;
                                    &lt;div class="mt-4 article-main"&gt;
									    
&lt;div class="article-gallery lightGallery"&gt;
    &lt;div data-thumb="https://scx1.b-cdn.net/csz/news/tmb/2025/the-short-term-reactiv.jpg" data-src="https://scx2.b-cdn.net/gfx/news/hires/2025/the-short-term-reactiv.jpg" data-sub-html="Experimental tasks and methods for experiments 1 and 2. Credit: &amp;lt;i&amp;gt;Nature Neuroscience&amp;lt;/i&amp;gt; (2025). DOI: 10.1038/s41593-025-01884-8"&gt;
        &lt;figure class="article-img"&gt;
            &lt;img src="https://scx1.b-cdn.net/csz/news/800a/2025/the-short-term-reactiv.jpg" alt="The short-term reactivation of the brain between the encoding of memories enhances memory recall" title="Experimental tasks and methods for experiments 1 and 2. Credit: Nature Neuroscience (2025). DOI: 10.1038/s41593-025-01884-8"&gt;
             &lt;figcaption class="text-darken text-low-up text-truncate-js text-truncate mt-3"&gt;
                Experimental tasks and methods for experiments 1 and 2. Credit: &lt;i&gt;Nature Neuroscience&lt;/i&gt; (2025). DOI: 10.1038/s41593-025-01884-8
            &lt;/figcaption&gt;        &lt;/figure&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Past neuroscience and psychology studies have shown that after the human brain encodes specific events or information, it can periodically reactivate them to facilitate their retention, via a process known as memory consolidation. The reactivation of memories has been specifically studied in the context of sleep or rest, with findings suggesting that during periods of inactivity, the brain reactivates specific memories, allowing people to remember them in the long term.&lt;/p&gt;

                                        
                                                                                  
                                         

                                                                                                                                    &lt;p&gt;Researchers at the University of Pennsylvania and other institutions in the United States recently conducted a study exploring the possibility that the brain engages in a similar reactivation process during wakefulness to store important information for shorter periods of time. Their findings, &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41593-025-01884-8" target="_blank"&gt;published&lt;/a&gt; in &lt;i&gt;Nature Neuroscience&lt;/i&gt;, suggest that the spontaneous reactivation of specific stimuli in the brain during the brief intervals between their encoding predicts the accuracy with which people remember them at the end of a &lt;a href="https://medicalxpress.com/tags/memory/" rel="tag" class="textTag"&gt;memory&lt;/a&gt; task.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Mike Kahana and I were both quite interested in the long history of thinking about rehearsal and its effects on the way in which people later recalled things," Dr. David Halpern, the first author of the paper, told Medical Xpress. "Rehearsal is challenging to study since people often do it without any overt behavior (unless we ask them to rehearse out loud)."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dr. Michael J. Kahana's lab at the University of Pennsylvania has been conducting studies related to memory processes for some time. This led to the creation of a dataset that includes memory task performance and matching intracranial electroencephalography (EEG) recordings from several people, offering insight into what happens in the brain while people attempt to remember information for short periods of time.&lt;/p&gt;

                                                                                                                                                         
                                                                                                                                                                                                &lt;p&gt;"We decided to try to look at when neural activity related to specific words seemed to be reactivated while they were looking at other words and see if that looked like what theorists in psychology thought was going on," said Dr. Halpern. "In addition, there is this parallel literature on consolidation in neuroscience that also suggested that reactivation was key to understanding what gets remembered later."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Many previous studies and theoretical psychology models suggest that memory consolidation processes primarily take place during sleep and over extended periods of rest. During these periods, the brain is not actively engaged in &lt;a href="https://medicalxpress.com/tags/everyday+activities/" rel="tag" class="textTag"&gt;everyday activities&lt;/a&gt; and external perceptions, but rather focused on internal thoughts or processes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"In addition, past works suggest that certain neurotransmitters are involved in long timescales, much longer than the time between two-word presentations," said Dr. Halpern. "This meant that looking at neural reinstatement in our data would also have interesting implications for those theories as well."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As part of their study, the researchers analyzed the data collected by the Kahana Lab, which measured neural activity using intracranial EEG. This is a technique that relies on implanted electrodes, which some patients diagnosed with epilepsy are already exposed to as part of their treatment (i.e., to identify the brain tissue that should be surgically removed to diminish or entirely stop their epileptic seizures).&lt;/p&gt;

                                                                                                                                            &lt;p&gt;"These patients need to wait in the hospital until they get enough measurements to determine the source, so a network of our research assistants across the country asked them if they would be willing to do a memory task while their neural activity is being recorded," explained Dr. Halpern.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"The task we usually use is called free recall: we ask the patients to look at a sequence of words on a screen and then, after a short delay, recall as many of them as they can in any order."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dr. Halpern, Dr. Kahana and their collaborators combined intracranial EEG recordings collected while patients were completing a short-term memory task with their performance on the task (i.e., what they remembered and the order in which they remembered stimuli). The study participants' ability to recall information and the order in which they remember it offers valuable insight into how memories are organized in their brains.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Firstly, we found that there seems to be some process happening involving reinstatement of &lt;a href="https://medicalxpress.com/tags/neural+activity/" rel="tag" class="textTag"&gt;neural activity&lt;/a&gt; on a sub-second scale that is related to later memory performance," said Dr. Halpern.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"This is a way in which the brain/mind can, after having an experience, make it more likely to be remembered later and perhaps alter the way in which it is remembered. It is interesting that the processes are, at first glance, quite similar to what we think is going on during sleep."&lt;/p&gt;

                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                    &lt;p&gt;Overall, the initial findings gathered by this team of researchers suggest that the brain also re-activates stimuli that we are trying to remember over short periods of time while we are awake. Further research could help to better understand the brain re-activation processes they observed and determine how they differ from those associated with &lt;a href="https://medicalxpress.com/tags/memory+consolidation/" rel="tag" class="textTag"&gt;memory consolidation&lt;/a&gt; during sleep or rest.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the future, these results could also help devise interventions aimed at improving people's ability to remember information in the short-term, which could be beneficial for both students and people diagnosed with memory disorders. Dr. Halpern has now left the Kahana Lab and now works in another research lab that is exploring the connections between memory and decision-making.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"I am very interested in the way in which rehearsal and reinstatement might be involved in the evaluation process that leads us to make a choice," added Dr. Halpern. "Another question I am quite interested in exploring is, if we are routinely (perhaps subconsciously) rehearsing our past experiences, how does our brain keep these separate from our ongoing veridical perceptual experience?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"In theory, this should cause some interference in terms of remembering the order in which things happened, but this doesn't seem to be the case, even in our data."&lt;/p&gt;

                                                                                                                                                                            
                                        											&lt;div class="article-main__more p-4"&gt;
												                                                    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;More information:&lt;/strong&gt;
                                                    David J. Halpern et al, Study-phase reinstatement predicts subsequent recall, &lt;i&gt;Nature Neuroscience&lt;/i&gt; (2025). &lt;a data-doi="1" href="https://dx.doi.org/10.1038/s41593-025-01884-8" target="_blank"&gt;DOI: 10.1038/s41593-025-01884-8&lt;/a&gt;.
																								
																								&lt;/p&gt;
																							&lt;/div&gt;
                                        											
										                                                                                    &lt;p class="article-main__note mt-4"&gt;
                                                © 2025 Science X Network
                                            &lt;/p&gt;
                                                                                
                                        
                                        &lt;div class="d-none d-print-block"&gt;
                                            &lt;p class="mb-4"&gt;
                                                 &lt;strong&gt;Citation&lt;/strong&gt;:
                                                 Short-term reactivation of brain between encoding of memories enhances recall, study finds (2025, March 30)
                                                 retrieved 30 March 2025
                                                 from https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-03-short-term-reactivation-brain-encoding.html
                                            &lt;/p&gt;
                                            &lt;p class="border text-muted p-3"&gt;
                                            This document is subject to copyright. Apart from any fair dealing for the purpose of private study or research, no
                                            part may be reproduced without the written permission. The content is provided for information purposes only.
                                            &lt;/p&gt;
                                        &lt;/div&gt;
                                        
									&lt;/div&gt;
								&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Medical Xpress</author><pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 14:50:03 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiigFBVV95cUxQWlA3cnRSbmdIZm1yWk1OenZVRU9uMElwSjFVanl2Rk01TmhPRjdxd2VKWDZ4SlRIbE5BRFlNQnZwbVNxLS04SHZ1cVVkZWhfM0ljSl9QYllwc19FekgwU0pWZzZvbzEwVU8wcGlNOUFXeWpQMUdIeFVkOE5DbW1kRVhGZmFVSDJTX0E</guid></item><item><title>Veterinarian Reveals Why You Shouldn’t Let Your Dog Drink From Public Water Bowls - SciTechDaily</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiqgFBVV95cUxOS2hTblRrUFZ1aXItcDd6UVA2WlQ2Vlhldi16cHFncHkzZ0lvd1RSVEI5b0JOYmwyWUxTQnpfeDhudTdRQU50X2xzQ3doTDlCeDBNVUswSHlKbVFZOWFoR0ZSNFE0dVhIU1hjSm9LQmRLbkdGSC1aV2pvclExdDlmX0t6a19aLWV3Z2h6elpBZHlCNnYzYl9YbUpaenpwX1JWcGdxNUllbi1RZw?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>SciTechDaily</author><pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 14:45:41 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiqgFBVV95cUxOS2hTblRrUFZ1aXItcDd6UVA2WlQ2Vlhldi16cHFncHkzZ0lvd1RSVEI5b0JOYmwyWUxTQnpfeDhudTdRQU50X2xzQ3doTDlCeDBNVUswSHlKbVFZOWFoR0ZSNFE0dVhIU1hjSm9LQmRLbkdGSC1aV2pvclExdDlmX0t6a19aLWV3Z2h6elpBZHlCNnYzYl9YbUpaenpwX1JWcGdxNUllbi1RZw</guid></item><item><title>Fort Bend County confirms first case of the measles - KPRC Click2Houston</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMipAFBVV95cUxQUVVTd25HaUN4OUp5OXRaLXlhNFlhRGhxaEExdXdueU43ekFxQTNCdVU2cDMxQmNLX0tOM1lvZjhDUGM2UENzN3VvZ3hZMlEtMkJWZXdVNXJaYzVoUkpUOXB4Q2FaOEJVUXJkTnJWYXFxZjhaRHNqVFY0WUNZVGdmazEwM3Rvdk04QjdHc1h2Q1JXMzNRZ0hKYTlmRFVtbFVxdmg4Vg?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;section class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__StackBase-sc-1fnzlkn-7 fURyTV iQviKm articleBody" itemprop="articleBody"&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__TextBase-sc-1fnzlkn-3 bYFsJw cuqaEv article-text"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fort Bend County&lt;/strong&gt; – Fort Bend County Health and Human Services announced on Sunday that the first reported measles case in 2025 has been confirmed in the county. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__TextBase-sc-1fnzlkn-3 bYFsJw cuqaEv article-text"&gt;Health officials said that the case involves an adult female, age 50-60. Fort Bend County Health officials said that case is associated with recent international travel and that they are actively investigating the case. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__TextBase-sc-1fnzlkn-3 bYFsJw cuqaEv article-text"&gt;“We want to reassure residents that our public health team is actively conducting case investigations and notifying potential contacts,” said Dr. Gale-Lowe, Director and Local Health Authority of Fort Bend County Health &amp;amp; Human Services. “The best way to protect yourself and your loved ones is through vaccination. The MMR vaccine is safe, effective and provides strong protection against measles.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__FlexBase-sc-1fnzlkn-1 jGlKin adWrapper" aria-label="Advertisement"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__TextBase-sc-1fnzlkn-3 bYFsJw cuqaEv article-text"&gt;In a statement that was released by the county, Fort Bend County Judge KP George, urged residents to stay vigilant for symptoms. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__TextBase-sc-1fnzlkn-3 bYFsJw cuqaEv article-text"&gt;“Your safety and well-being remain my top priority. I urge all residents to check their immunization records, get vaccinated if necessary and stay vigilant for symptoms. Together, we can protect our families, neighbors and the greater Fort Bend community,” said Fort Bend County Judge KP George. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__TextBase-sc-1fnzlkn-3 nALdY copyright"&gt;Copyright 2025 by KPRC Click2Houston - All rights reserved.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>KPRC Click2Houston</author><pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 14:41:57 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipAFBVV95cUxQUVVTd25HaUN4OUp5OXRaLXlhNFlhRGhxaEExdXdueU43ekFxQTNCdVU2cDMxQmNLX0tOM1lvZjhDUGM2UENzN3VvZ3hZMlEtMkJWZXdVNXJaYzVoUkpUOXB4Q2FaOEJVUXJkTnJWYXFxZjhaRHNqVFY0WUNZVGdmazEwM3Rvdk04QjdHc1h2Q1JXMzNRZ0hKYTlmRFVtbFVxdmg4Vg</guid></item><item><title>Researchers discovered a hair loss breakthrough that’s shockingly simple - BGR</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMinAFBVV95cUxPeWdNZWE5cHUya3lfUXpGUVNoTndlWjZKTjhlMW5ta2JfZlN5OXE3al9OYjFPWkFSM0JnTFJ5WW1RaGY4emhhaTlodFE5R2VfN3dUcldMWk0tREVsMDRNcy1wczVLb2xoOXZRRGNTZExqb3B2bkEwR25jR0lFWGN2VUxCQW1kb2Fzdi1TdWg0bDY0R283NTRYdkFWd1I?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content no-dropcap"&gt;
								
&lt;p&gt;Hair loss affects millions, yet treatments remain frustratingly complex. Some require a daily commitment, others have side effects—and many simply don’t work for everyone. But scientists may have uncovered a simple hair loss cure that’s been hiding in plain sight: sugar.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Not just any sugar, though. This new cure is heavily based on one that’s already part of your DNA. Researchers from the University of Sheffield and COMSATS University were studying how a natural sugar called deoxyribose helps heal wounds in mice.

&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;During those experiments, they noticed something odd: fur near the treated areas was growing back faster and thicker than expected. That accidental observation turned into a &lt;a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://www.frontiersin.org/journals/pharmacology/articles/10.3389/fphar.2024.1370833/full"&gt;focused study&lt;/a&gt; on what would become one of the simplest hair loss cures scientists have developed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To test the sugar’s &lt;a href="https://bgr.com/science/an-actual-cure-for-male-pattern-baldness-may-have-been-discovered/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;potential for treating hereditary-patterned baldness&lt;/a&gt;, the researchers created a gel infused with deoxyribose and applied it to mice with testosterone-induced hair loss. Within weeks, the treated skin began to sprout new fur—dense, long, and healthy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="bgr-newsletter-signup-form newsletter-signup-form black-bg"&gt;	&lt;h4&gt;Tech. Entertainment. Science. Your inbox.&lt;/h4&gt;	&lt;p class="signup-form-info"&gt;Sign up for the most interesting tech &amp;amp; entertainment news out there.&lt;/p&gt;		&lt;p class="signup-form-tos"&gt;By signing up, I agree to the &lt;a rel="noopener" href="https://pmc.com/terms-of-use/" target="_blank"&gt;Terms of Use&lt;/a&gt; and have reviewed the &lt;a rel="noopener" href="https://pmc.com/privacy-policy/" target="_blank"&gt;Privacy Notice.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;	&lt;span class="success hidden text-white font-bold items-center"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure class="is-wp-image-block wp-block-image size-full"&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" decoding="async" src="https://bgr.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/02/baldness-cure.jpg?quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all" alt="Baldness Cure" class="is-wp-image-block wp-image-5906065" srcset="https://bgr.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/02/baldness-cure.jpg?quality=82 1599w, https://bgr.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/02/baldness-cure.jpg?resize=150%2C100&amp;amp;quality=82 150w, https://bgr.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/02/baldness-cure.jpg?resize=300%2C200&amp;amp;quality=82 300w, https://bgr.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/02/baldness-cure.jpg?resize=768%2C512&amp;amp;quality=82 768w, https://bgr.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/02/baldness-cure.jpg?resize=1024%2C683&amp;amp;quality=82 1024w, https://bgr.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/02/baldness-cure.jpg?resize=1536%2C1024&amp;amp;quality=82 1536w, https://bgr.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/02/baldness-cure.jpg?resize=63%2C42&amp;amp;quality=82 63w" sizes="(max-width: 1599px) 100vw, 1599px"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="is-wp-image-block wp-element-caption"&gt;A man analyzing his hairline in the mirror. Image source: goodluz/Adobe&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;The results weren’t subtle either. In fact, the sugar gel matched the effectiveness of minoxidil, a popular over-the-counter treatment also known as Rogaine. What makes this finding even more compelling is how safe and accessible it could be as a &lt;a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://bgr.com/science/the-key-to-a-permanent-cure-for-baldness-may-have-been-discovered/"&gt;hair loss treatment&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Deoxyribose is already a naturally occurring sugar in the body, and the gel developed by the research team is biodegradable and non-toxic. In photos comparing different treatments, mice given the sugar gel showed regrowth as strong as those given minoxidil—without needing to combine the two.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers also noticed that the sugar in the simple hair loss cure appeared to increase blood vessel growth and skin cell activity around the hair follicles. Since better blood supply often translates to healthier, thicker hair, this may be one reason the treatment worked so well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When examined under a microscope, the regrown hairs were visibly thicker than those in the control groups. While it’s not yet clear exactly how deoxyribose triggers this response, the findings are promising—especially given the limited options currently available.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This simple hair loss cure could potentially help treat alopecia or even aid hair regrowth after chemotherapy. And because it’s built on a naturally occurring molecule, it might offer a gentler alternative for those who can’t tolerate existing medications.

&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For now, the team is focused on understanding how the sugar works and whether these results can be replicated in humans. But the early signs suggest that an easier, safer approach to treating hair loss could be just around the corner.&lt;/p&gt;
							&lt;/div&gt;

															&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BGR</author><pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 14:34:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMinAFBVV95cUxPeWdNZWE5cHUya3lfUXpGUVNoTndlWjZKTjhlMW5ta2JfZlN5OXE3al9OYjFPWkFSM0JnTFJ5WW1RaGY4emhhaTlodFE5R2VfN3dUcldMWk0tREVsMDRNcy1wczVLb2xoOXZRRGNTZExqb3B2bkEwR25jR0lFWGN2VUxCQW1kb2Fzdi1TdWg0bDY0R283NTRYdkFWd1I</guid></item><item><title>Human bodies begin breaking down at two very precise ages - Earth.com</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiigFBVV95cUxQZEUxdHBzNS1NN3NjZVJPQTBUcXhhYklQVURZbW80UnpTUENGdzhpOFFVQ2hibkdVYVhxVndERzEzcnJJT2pBSWFLWGVMVHMzdHBwLWdYNl9FVkJnbGEwbzJoRmtjOC1GTl96Yk5TRHB6VjdWSWdRa2twMnEyMFM1X3VDeUd4OHFKQmc?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="page_content__AwOj6"&gt;&lt;p&gt;We all know the human body takes some hits as we age – that’s nothing new. But here’s the kicker: the process isn’t as slow and steady as most of us thought.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A comprehensive study reveals some eye-opening insights about aging, focusing on exactly “when” things start to shift and how our bodies begin to break down, both inside and out. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aging isn’t just about wrinkles and gray hairs – there’s a whole internal, built-in timeline, surprisingly similar for all humans, that we’re only beginning to understand.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-when-the-human-body-start-to-age"&gt;When the human body start to age&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The man at the helm of the study is Michael Snyder, chair of genetics at &lt;a href="https://med.stanford.edu/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Stanford School of Medicine&lt;/a&gt;. His team’s research provides some fascinating insights into the specifics of our &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/drinking-tea-delays-biological-aging/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;biological aging process&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Snyder and his team explored data from individuals ranging from 25 to 75 years old. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Their research focused on the different molecules playing significant roles in aging, including those constituting our &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/your-microbiome-trillions-of-bacteria-unique-like-your-fingerprint/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;microbiomes&lt;/a&gt; – the microcosm of bacteria, viruses, and fungi that exist within us.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Interestingly, they discovered that 81% of these molecules don’t follow a predictable, chronological pattern as one might expect. Instead, our bodies experience two periods of rapid change as we age. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sharp molecular and microbial shifts occur precisely at ages 44 and 60, a finding that may alter our understanding of how our bodies age.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-understanding-the-microbiome-the-basics"&gt;Understanding the microbiome – the basics&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Your microbiome is basically the bustling community of trillions of microbes – like bacteria, fungi, and viruses – that live in and on your body. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most of them live in your gut, especially in your large intestine, and they’re not just there for lack of anywhere better to be. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They help you digest food, &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/plant-based-meat-less-protein-lacks-certain-nutrients/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;absorb nutrients&lt;/a&gt;, and even produce vitamins like B12 and K. Think of them as your behind-the-scenes health squad, working 24/7 to keep things running smoothly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The microbiome also plays a huge role in your immune system, mood, and even how your brain functions. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When the balance of good and bad microbes gets thrown off – like from antibiotics, stress, or a poor diet – it can mess with everything from your energy levels to how well you sleep. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That’s why you hear so much buzz about probiotics, fermented foods, and fiber. They’re like fuel for your inner ecosystem, helping your microbiome thrive and keeping you feeling your best.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-correlation-between-aging-and-diseases"&gt;Correlation between aging and diseases&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The molecules related to &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/a-century-of-progress-in-the-fight-against-cardiovascular-disease/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;cardiovascular disease&lt;/a&gt;, a leading cause of death worldwide, showed substantial changes at both of these age intervals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Furthermore, molecules connected to our immune function – our body’s vital defense mechanism against disease – changed significantly in individuals entering their early 60s.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers were driven to investigate these trends after noticing a sharp rise in the risk of developing age-related conditions like &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/how-why-some-brains-resist-alzheimers-disease-symptoms/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Alzheimer’s disease&lt;/a&gt; and cardiovascular disease during mid-life, rather than a steady increase.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-studying-age-and-the-human-body"&gt;Studying age and the human body&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study’s findings are based on data obtained from 108 participants, aiming to unlock the mysteries of the &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/intermittent-fasting-could-be-the-key-to-better-health/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;biology of aging&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Over several years, participants’ biological samples were analyzed every few months, allowing the scientists to track an astonishing 135,000 age-related changes in different molecules.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The team discovered thousands of molecules and microbes that undergo shifts, either increasing or decreasing in their abundance. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A whopping 81 percent of the molecules studied experienced dramatic changes at specific ages. Notably, these transformations were most prevalent when participants were in their mid-40s and early 60s.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr. Xiaotao Shen, who was part of the Stanford Medicine team, pointed out significant changes in the number of molecules related to &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/genetics-behind-different-levels-alcohol-consumption-health/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;alcohol&lt;/a&gt;, caffeine, and lipid metabolism; cardiovascular disease; and skin and &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/molecule-in-coffee-trigonelline-keeps-muscles-young/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;muscle health&lt;/a&gt; in individuals in their 40s.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For those in their 60s, changes were observed in carbohydrate and &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/is-coffee-good-for-you-it-may-depend-on-your-genes/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;caffeine metabolism&lt;/a&gt;, immune regulation, kidney function, cardiovascular disease, and skin and muscle health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-is-lifestyle-a-factor"&gt;Is lifestyle a factor?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Could our lifestyles be contributing to these &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/losing-loved-ones-can-speed-up-biological-aging/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;age-related changes&lt;/a&gt;? Snyder suggests it’s a possibility worth considering. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For instance, alcohol metabolism may falter due to the increased alcohol consumption that often occurs in people’s mid-40s, a decade frequently marked by significant life stressors such as career changes, family obligations, or personal challenges. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This shift in behavior can lead to a cascade of &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/muscles-defy-aging-with-remarkable-resilience/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;physiological changes&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The scientists plan to delve deeper into the various triggers for these periods of rapid change, exploring how factors like diet, exercise, and stress management interplay with aging.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Understanding these connections could pave the way for &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/harvard-scientists-fountain-of-youth-pill-sparks-controversy/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;healthier aging strategies&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-role-of-genetics-in-aging"&gt;Role of genetics in aging&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alongside our environment and lifestyle choices, our genes significantly impact &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/exposure-certain-odors-pheromones-speeds-up-aging-process/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;how we age&lt;/a&gt;. Everyone has a unique genetic blueprint that can make them more susceptible to certain health issues as they get older.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For example, some gene variations can affect how well our bodies break down substances, handle stress, and even heal from injuries. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;By understanding these genetic markers, we can gain valuable insights into why some people face age-related health problems sooner than others. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This knowledge opens the door to personalized medicine, allowing us to create tailored interventions that could boost prevention efforts and enhance our quality of life as we age.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Given these findings, paying special attention to our health in our 40s and 60s becomes even more critical. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Simple measures like increasing physical activity to protect heart health and maintain muscle mass, or reducing alcohol consumption, could go a long way in &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/monthly-aging-treatment-helps-you-live-long-die-healthy/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;delaying the ‘break down’ process&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I’m a big believer that we should try to adjust our lifestyles while we’re still healthy,” Snyder aptly concludes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study is published in the journal &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/nataging" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Nature Aging&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;—–&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Like what you read? &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/subscribe/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Subscribe to our newsletter&lt;/a&gt; for engaging articles, exclusive content, and the latest updates. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Check us out on &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/earthsnap/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;EarthSnap&lt;/a&gt;, a free app brought to you by &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/author/eralls/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Eric Ralls&lt;/a&gt; and Earth.com.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;—–&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Earth.com</author><pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 14:26:19 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiigFBVV95cUxQZEUxdHBzNS1NN3NjZVJPQTBUcXhhYklQVURZbW80UnpTUENGdzhpOFFVQ2hibkdVYVhxVndERzEzcnJJT2pBSWFLWGVMVHMzdHBwLWdYNl9FVkJnbGEwbzJoRmtjOC1GTl96Yk5TRHB6VjdWSWdRa2twMnEyMFM1X3VDeUd4OHFKQmc</guid></item><item><title>Take your fitness to the next level with the 7-Minute Power Workout - The Washington Post</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMilwFBVV95cUxNNnA0dGxNZXZGN3V3WDg2WjlTcllHMU9kdWJReGhDTzg3X2dSRHBsbkExMFN1MmlkWXRBYzMyaF8zSGYzZm1BcnMtV1A2OWtNSDVJWVI3Y3U4WExtUXVuY2dELTMzRnEwMTA2MVBVcjU5c2QtSzVfRmh1UlVwaHJNUFZiQnd0Snh1MzdrdG9SS181cG1pZDJZ?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="story relative"&gt;&lt;p id="GEZCQLHENFABJD2FR3UFSORUOQ" data-contentid="GEZCQLHENFABJD2FR3UFSORUOQ" class="wpds-c-foYyTm wpds-c-foYyTm-idAgRsb-css"&gt;The more you exercise, the easier it gets. That’s why, at some point, you may need to power up your workouts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="TOD7TLGENVFWVM5JY5JNDM672Y" data-contentid="TOD7TLGENVFWVM5JY5JNDM672Y" class="wpds-c-foYyTm wpds-c-foYyTm-idAgRsb-css"&gt;It’s important to “find ways to challenge yourself again,” said Chris Jordan, an exercise physiologist and the creator of the &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/wellness/interactive/2025/7-minute-workout-science-original/?itid=lk_inline_enhanced-template"&gt;original, science-based 7-minute workout&lt;/a&gt;. Our bodies adapt to the demands of our current workouts, he continued, adding more heart and lung capacity and other changes that make the same workout you’ve been doing for months feel progressively easier.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="PJLV PJLV-igWRsMW-css"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="ZRYOLSDLRFBB3K2GBO4DTDN3XM" data-contentid="ZRYOLSDLRFBB3K2GBO4DTDN3XM" class="wpds-c-foYyTm wpds-c-foYyTm-idAgRsb-css"&gt;This process, known as exercise adaptation, &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41574-020-0377-1?itid=lk_inline_enhanced-template"&gt;makes us more athletic and fit&lt;/a&gt;. But, even more important, it can “contribute toward the delayed onset of age-related disease,” according to a comprehensive 2018 &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC5983157/?itid=lk_inline_enhanced-template"&gt;review&lt;/a&gt; of how regular exercise benefits our bodies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="PJLV ad--enterprise"&gt;&lt;div class="PJLV PJLV-ikOErwM-css"&gt;&lt;div aria-hidden="true" class="hide-for-print relative flex justify-center content-box items-center b bh mb-lg mt-lg pt-md pb-md flex"&gt;&lt;div class="center absolute w-100 border-box"&gt;&lt;p class="dib flex divider gray-dark pl-xs pr-xs font-sans-serif light font-xxxxs lh-md"&gt;Story continues below advertisement&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p id="OZGSLJEMZ5CYHESZJXSN7GYA7E" data-contentid="OZGSLJEMZ5CYHESZJXSN7GYA7E" class="wpds-c-foYyTm wpds-c-foYyTm-idAgRsb-css"&gt;To help increase your fitness, Jordan developed the 7-Minute Power Workout for The Washington Post. It builds on the scientific principles he used in the original 7-minute workout — featuring 12 movements that increase strength, power and endurance. The exercises focus alternately on the upper and lower body and are meant to be completed at a relatively high intensity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div target="_blank" class="wpds-c-PJLV wpds-c-PJLV-hHnAni-type-inline wpds-c-PJLV-iPJLV-css"&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-ciKXky wpds-c-ciKXky-hNRVRD-type-inline"&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-bmgAQv"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Save this story to do the workout again&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p id="DHL4PHAGCRFHZF4KBPMXFFBYJU" data-contentid="DHL4PHAGCRFHZF4KBPMXFFBYJU" class="wpds-c-foYyTm wpds-c-foYyTm-idAgRsb-css"&gt;That means your effort should feel like an eight on a scale from zero to 10, Jordan said. Or, more informally, you should be able to speak a few words before pausing for breath, he said, but you shouldn’t be able to sing during the workout.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="ES5PBWA2WNCYBALJJUXNDRCMOM" data-contentid="ES5PBWA2WNCYBALJJUXNDRCMOM" class="wpds-c-foYyTm wpds-c-foYyTm-idAgRsb-css"&gt;Since the exercises in the new workout are more complex than before, involving a greater range of muscles and coordination, it’s fine to start deliberately and dial in the proper form, Jordan said. Then gradually speed up until you’re pushing yourself during each move for the full seven minutes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="VSUHTFVRA5E7XIGJMRU52OWJLQ" data-contentid="VSUHTFVRA5E7XIGJMRU52OWJLQ" class="wpds-c-foYyTm wpds-c-foYyTm-idAgRsb-css"&gt;As always, consider talking with your doctor before trying a new exercise routine. Warm up with a few stretches, jumping jacks or high knees. Then complete as many of each exercise as you can in 30 seconds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="OLX2NOXZQVHFPKZB6U24AZNLK4" data-contentid="OLX2NOXZQVHFPKZB6U24AZNLK4" class="wpds-c-foYyTm wpds-c-foYyTm-idAgRsb-css"&gt;So, how can you tell if you’re ready for this power version? If you’ve been doing &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/wellness/interactive/2025/7-minute-workout-low-impact-exercises-modified/?itid=lk_inline_enhanced-template"&gt;the 7-Minute Gentle Workout&lt;/a&gt; and feel ready for a new challenge, try the &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/wellness/interactive/2025/7-minute-workout-science-original/?itid=lk_inline_enhanced-template" target="_blank"&gt;original 7-minute workout&lt;/a&gt; first, before progressing to the power workout, Jordan suggested.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="VRADHSYSX5EQXCPBEYKR43DE7U" data-contentid="VRADHSYSX5EQXCPBEYKR43DE7U" class="wpds-c-foYyTm wpds-c-foYyTm-idAgRsb-css"&gt;“But if you can easily hold a conversation with someone without gasping, or you can sing” while completing the original 7-minute workout, he said, it’s time to level up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="PJLV PJLV-igWRsMW-css"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-gFGKna"&gt;&lt;p class="intro"&gt;&lt;h4 class="wpds-c-blyyIN wpds-c-blyyIN-jiHlZe-as-h4 wpds-c-blyyIN-ifkTeWT-css"&gt;More 7-minute workouts&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div role="group" aria-roledescription="carousel" class="wpds-c-cFpcyF wpds-c-cFpcyF-iiWZbEr-css"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div tabindex="0" role="group" class="wpds-c-ioDwQx wpds-c-ioDwQx-imJXpR-css"&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-feEbKl wpds-c-feEbKl-igjZdiI-css"&gt;&lt;div aria-label="3 of 0" aria-hidden="true" id="null-item2" role="group" aria-roledescription="slide" class="wpds-c-lnwwct wpds-c-lnwwct-iifuYt-css"&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-kZOjlJ"&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-hvVbTP wpds-c-hvVbTP-kTPqca-grayscale-true wpds-c-hvVbTP-igyvecA-css"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;h5&gt;7-Minute Workout with Kids&lt;/h5&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-gPkNXM wpds-c-gPkNXM-ileKTjg-css"&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV"&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-fYIIRZ"&gt;Stay up to date on the 7-minute workout series by signing up for the weekly Well+Being newsletter.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="PJLV ad--enterprise"&gt;&lt;div class="PJLV PJLV-icAbLfl-css"&gt;&lt;div aria-hidden="true" class="hide-for-print relative flex justify-center content-box items-center b bh mb-lg mt-lg pt-md pb-md flex"&gt;&lt;div class="center absolute w-100 border-box"&gt;&lt;p class="dib flex divider gray-dark pl-xs pr-xs font-sans-serif light font-xxxxs lh-md"&gt;Story continues below advertisement&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-iZPJvs"&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-hEgojh"&gt;&lt;h5 class="wpds-c-blyyIN wpds-c-blyyIN-cpxyFJ-as-h5 wpds-c-blyyIN-idGqeAE-css"&gt;About this story&lt;/h5&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-foYyTm wpds-c-foYyTm-ikHxsIg-css"&gt;Workout and audio narration by Chris Jordan. Art direction by Chelsea Conrad. Design by Chelsea Conrad and Carson TerBush. Development by Carson TerBush. Additional development by Yutao Chen. Audio production by Bishop Sand. Video production by Luis Velarde. Video graphics support by Sarah Hashemi. Editing by Christian Font and Emily Codik. Copy editing by Gaby Morera Di Núbila.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-foYyTm wpds-c-foYyTm-ikHxsIg-css"&gt;The workout illustrations and animations were created by &lt;a href="https://www.christajarrold.com/?itid=lk_inline_enhanced-template"&gt;Christa Jarrold&lt;/a&gt; based on a demonstration by Chris Jordan.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 14:19:27 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilwFBVV95cUxNNnA0dGxNZXZGN3V3WDg2WjlTcllHMU9kdWJReGhDTzg3X2dSRHBsbkExMFN1MmlkWXRBYzMyaF8zSGYzZm1BcnMtV1A2OWtNSDVJWVI3Y3U4WExtUXVuY2dELTMzRnEwMTA2MVBVcjU5c2QtSzVfRmh1UlVwaHJNUFZiQnd0Snh1MzdrdG9SS181cG1pZDJZ</guid></item><item><title>Fort Bend County confirms its first case of measles this year - KHOU.com</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiqgFBVV95cUxQelN3a1FLYW5xWjBUZDJfUXBXdFVpa2g3b0g1SG1QWEhFVjB0RFJqZDlucnJGSXN5cFJPTmVlT0diSGFWWWloLW5oUzMzSDhHT3VkMElRSnlKMnpGQ01PTkgySHJ4ekFsZFY3Uldodm1rcjhrZEt3SlJuQmtOd0lXYkdVOXJEWlVWQ2ZHbk9XX3BHcE1remxNcDlaUk05SHA5a3dzWEY0WTI3QQ?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="article__summary"&gt;"The best way to protect yourself and your loved ones is through vaccination," Fort Bend County Local Health Authority Dr. Gale-Lowe said.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;div class="article__body"&gt;
                    &lt;div class="article__section article__section_type_text utility__text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;FORT BEND COUNTY, Texas — Fort Bend County Health and Human Services on Sunday announced that it has confirmed its first case of the measles in 2025.&lt;/p&gt;                    &lt;/div&gt;
                    &lt;div class="article__section article__section_type_text utility__text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The county said the case is in a woman between the ages of 50 and 60. They said the case is associated with international travel and is not connected to the &lt;a href="/article/news/health/measles/measles-texas-outbreak-march-25-update/285-a1c5e8c8-37fd-4dbb-975f-4e3af739b9b8" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;West Texas outbreak&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;                    &lt;/div&gt;
                    &lt;div class="article__section article__section_type_text utility__text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Your safety and well-being remain my top priority," said Fort Bend County Judge KP George. "I urge all residents to check their immunization records, get vaccinated if necessary and stay vigilant for symptoms. Together, we can protect our families, neighbors and the greater Fort Bend community."&lt;/p&gt;                    &lt;/div&gt;
                        
                    &lt;div class="article__section article__section_type_text utility__text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;FBCHHS is investigating the case and working to identify any potential exposures to limit the spread of the disease.&lt;/p&gt;                    &lt;/div&gt;
                    &lt;div class="article__section article__section_type_text utility__text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"The best way to protect yourself and your loved ones is through vaccination," Fort Bend County Local Health Authority Dr. Gale-Lowe said. "The MMR vaccine is safe, effective and provides strong protection against measles."&lt;/p&gt;                    &lt;/div&gt;
                    &lt;div class="article__section article__section_type_text utility__text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;FBCHHS listed the following measles symptoms to be on the lookout for:&lt;/p&gt;                    &lt;/div&gt;
                    &lt;div class="article__section article__section_type_text utility__text"&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;High fever (101 degrees or higher)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Cough&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Runny nose&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Red, watery eyes&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Rash, typically starting on the face and spreading downward two to five days after initial symptoms&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Koplik spots (bluish-white specks or a red-rose background appearing on the buccal and labial mucosa usually opposite the molars)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;                    &lt;/div&gt;
                    &lt;div class="article__section article__section_type_text utility__text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The health authority said people with the measles are contagious from four days before the rash appears to four days after.&lt;/p&gt;                    &lt;/div&gt;
                    &lt;div class="article__section article__section_type_text utility__text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you believe you've been exposed to the measles or are experiencing measles symptoms, FBCHHS says to isolate yourself to prevent the spread and to contact your healthcare provider via phone before getting tested.&lt;/p&gt;                    &lt;/div&gt;
                                &lt;p class="article__section article__section_type_embed"&gt;
                                    
                                &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>KHOU.com</author><pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 14:09:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiqgFBVV95cUxQelN3a1FLYW5xWjBUZDJfUXBXdFVpa2g3b0g1SG1QWEhFVjB0RFJqZDlucnJGSXN5cFJPTmVlT0diSGFWWWloLW5oUzMzSDhHT3VkMElRSnlKMnpGQ01PTkgySHJ4ekFsZFY3Uldodm1rcjhrZEt3SlJuQmtOd0lXYkdVOXJEWlVWQ2ZHbk9XX3BHcE1remxNcDlaUk05SHA5a3dzWEY0WTI3QQ</guid></item><item><title>Study decodes who actually needs statin medication to lower cholesterol - Gujarat Samachar</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiuwFBVV95cUxOX3FtQnJOOHV4bmJhaVZKVmx4UGtWUzlhRGtxaUxYNkVKc05lb0Zzck51b1FOY0tZLWlPY1o5VDZVWHZKeGxDS0FfcFVWdDBpMkZCaHpxUmxJQ21fd1piQVhlc21pbDV6Tzdwb05sNFd6WmM0VzdkR05tT2NZVDA1aGdheWg0V3Q2R2dER0FjaUo4Y2Eybmk0aGRWRXNhR3BMUG5kTkg2bDFwcFlkME8zMzlITXdOVW9KRm44?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="text-center text-md-start pe-0 lh-1 d-flex align-items-center py-md-3 col-lg-4 col-auto"&gt;&lt;div class="logo"&gt;&lt;h1 class="mb-0"&gt;&lt;a title="Gujarat Samachar" role="button" class="light"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;img alt="" aria-hidden="true" src=""&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;img alt="" srcset="https://english.gujaratsamachar.com/api/image?url=https://www.gujaratsamachar.com/assets/logo.png&amp;amp;w=384&amp;amp;q=75 1x, https://english.gujaratsamachar.com/api/image?url=https://www.gujaratsamachar.com/assets/logo.png&amp;amp;w=640&amp;amp;q=75 2x" src="https://english.gujaratsamachar.com/api/image?url=https://www.gujaratsamachar.com/assets/logo.png&amp;amp;w=640&amp;amp;q=75" decoding="async" data-nimg="intrinsic" class="img-fluid "&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;p class="logo_date_time"&gt;&lt;span&gt;31st March 2025 | &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="time"&gt;7:39 AM&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Gujarat Samachar</author><pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 13:33:31 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiuwFBVV95cUxOX3FtQnJOOHV4bmJhaVZKVmx4UGtWUzlhRGtxaUxYNkVKc05lb0Zzck51b1FOY0tZLWlPY1o5VDZVWHZKeGxDS0FfcFVWdDBpMkZCaHpxUmxJQ21fd1piQVhlc21pbDV6Tzdwb05sNFd6WmM0VzdkR05tT2NZVDA1aGdheWg0V3Q2R2dER0FjaUo4Y2Eybmk0aGRWRXNhR3BMUG5kTkg2bDFwcFlkME8zMzlITXdOVW9KRm44</guid></item><item><title>Is your workplace coffee machine hurting your health? - Euronews</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiygFBVV95cUxQUmlBckJVTnUxNTJLWE1aWUl3b0Jndl9nOG1kZEpDWkwzZi04X0M3MlFfYTdjaVZRdUkwcTRPYU82aG1WdFMwWkJPWFNNSUpFUFc0OVFkSEJsN2hVYVhpdDB1UUJJb2IwNHh2OEVkT3g3RW1JRmFSQm9iWVZsd1ZmVEtTeVZhSFVoOE1fdFNEWF9kdXlfQ1pCVDJOWU5CUDgxR1FlbmNtVUV2UWdkNFUxUlU4MC0xVDBzdkNxUGF0YTRHNU1FZXZHWXV3?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="c-article-summary"&gt;
        Samples taken by a Swedish team of researchers show how daily coffee drinkers may be at risk of higher cholesterol levels and cardiovascular disease.
    &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="c-article-content c-article-content--health js-article-content poool-content"&gt;&lt;div class="c-ad c-ad-halfpage u-show-for-mobile-only"&gt;&lt;p data-ad-id="adzone-halfpage_1" data-ad-type="halfpage" data-ad-position="1" class="c-ad__adzone advertising js-adzone"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="c-ad__placeholder"&gt;&lt;img class="c-ad__placeholder__logo" src="https://static.euronews.com/website/images/logos/logo-euronews-grey-6-180x22.svg" alt="" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;span&gt;ADVERTISEMENT&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;You may want to rethink that coffee on your work break and drink tea for a change. A new study by Swedish researchers has found that high levels of cholesterol-elevating substances were present in most coffee machines in workplaces. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The two substances in question are cafestol and kahweol, both found in coffee beans. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Researchers from Uppsala University, in collaboration with the Chalmers University of Technology, took samples from fourteen coffee machines in break rooms at different workplaces using five different coffee brands. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The concentrations varied depending on the machine and the time, according to the findings published in the journal &lt;a href="https://www.nmcd-journal.com/article/S0939-4753(25)00087-0/fulltext"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Nutrition, Metabolism &amp;amp; Cardiovascular Diseases&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Brewing machines - the most common type of coffee machine in the workplaces studied - and boiled coffee in a pot showed the highest concentration of cholesterol-elevating substances.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"From this, we infer that the filtering process is crucial for the presence of these cholesterol-elevating substances in coffee," David Iggman, a researcher at Uppsala University in Sweden and the study’s lead author, said in a statement. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Obviously, not all coffee machines manage to filter them out. But the problem varies between different types of coffee machines, and the concentrations also showed large variations over time," he added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-ad-id="adzone-outstream_1" data-ad-type="outstream" data-ad-position="1" class="advertising advertising--no-label js-adzone outstream"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Most of the coffee samples contained levels that could feasibly affect the levels of LDL cholesterol of people who drank the coffee, as well as their future risk of cardiovascular disease".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;LDL - or low-density lipoprotein - cholesterol is often referred to as the "bad" cholesterol.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Filtered coffee 'is preferable'&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;"For people who drink a lot of coffee every day, it’s clear that drip-filter coffee, or other well-filtered coffee, is preferable," he added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Using paper filters was found to almost completely filter out the molecules.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-ad-id="adzone-native_1" data-ad-type="native" data-ad-position="1" class="advertising advertising--no-label advertising--native js-adzone"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;More research is needed to determine the precise effects on cholesterol levels among consumers, according to Iggman. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Naturally present in the body, cholesterol can become a problem if there’s too much of it. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It can build up in plaque in the walls of arteries making them arteries hard and narrow, according to the US-based Mayo Clinic. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sometimes a piece of plaque can break loose and form a blood clot that may cause a heart attack or stroke.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="c-ad c-ad-halfpage u-margin-bottom-3 u-show-for-mobile-only"&gt;&lt;p data-ad-id="adzone-halfpage_2" data-ad-type="halfpage" data-ad-position="2" class="c-ad__adzone advertising js-adzone"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="c-ad__placeholder"&gt;&lt;img class="c-ad__placeholder__logo" src="https://static.euronews.com/website/images/logos/logo-euronews-grey-6-180x22.svg" alt="" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;span&gt;ADVERTISEMENT&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Europe is the region with the highest prevalence of cholesterol in the world, with over 50 per cent of adults estimated to be living with higher than average levels.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to Statista data from 2021, Lithuania had one of the highest average cholesterol levels in Europe, whereas Greece was among the lowest.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Euronews</author><pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 13:13:49 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiygFBVV95cUxQUmlBckJVTnUxNTJLWE1aWUl3b0Jndl9nOG1kZEpDWkwzZi04X0M3MlFfYTdjaVZRdUkwcTRPYU82aG1WdFMwWkJPWFNNSUpFUFc0OVFkSEJsN2hVYVhpdDB1UUJJb2IwNHh2OEVkT3g3RW1JRmFSQm9iWVZsd1ZmVEtTeVZhSFVoOE1fdFNEWF9kdXlfQ1pCVDJOWU5CUDgxR1FlbmNtVUV2UWdkNFUxUlU4MC0xVDBzdkNxUGF0YTRHNU1FZXZHWXV3</guid></item><item><title>World's Most Common Pain Relief Drug May Induce Risky Behavior, Study Finds - ScienceAlert</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMipAFBVV95cUxOZ2dtT1lVU054U0dZUjJLbnJReVdHc2J6cU53VmFWV09MdW5DMVpaN3F0aEkxX3hPSEhYeU5ZUmNLOWNFZjBlNGE4NGx1OUxLam8wQ2xUejIxU3BRMW1nMUdmZXRGRFppYXdpYUlHNFdzZG9xY0pFd2pyNFktZTNfMHRTUEdlTzNxbzVMc2JUcExhWXVJcnpGVXkxc2lYMEUxdk1Kdg?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;One of the most consumed drugs in the US – and the&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.drugbank.ca/drugs/DB00316"&gt;most commonly taken analgesic worldwide&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;– may do a lot more than simply take the edge off your headache.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A&lt;span&gt;cetaminophen, also known as paracetamol and sold widely under the brand names Tylenol and Panadol, may also increase risk-taking, according to a study from 2020 that measured changes in people's behavior when under the influence of the common over-the-counter medication.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Acetaminophen seems to make people feel less negative emotion when they consider risky activities – they just don't feel as scared,"&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.osu.edu/a-pain-reliever-that-alters-perceptions-of-risk/"&gt;explained&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;neuroscientist Baldwin Way from The Ohio State University when the findings were published.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"With nearly 25 percent of the population in the US taking acetaminophen each week, reduced risk perceptions and increased risk-taking could have important effects on society."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The findings add to a growing body of research suggesting that acetaminophen's effects on pain reduction also extend to various psychological processes, lowering people's&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://journals.sagepub.com/doi/10.1177/0956797610374741"&gt;receptivity to hurt feelings&lt;/a&gt;, experiencing&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://academic.oup.com/scan/article/11/9/1345/2224135"&gt;reduced empathy&lt;/a&gt;, and even&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/tylenol-may-make-it-harder-for-users-to-spot-errors-says-study"&gt;blunting cognitive functions&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_147551" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-147551" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/12/ParacetamolMolecule.jpg" alt="World's Most Common Pain Relief Drug May Induce Risky Behavior" class="wp-image-147551 size-full" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/12/ParacetamolMolecule.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/12/ParacetamolMolecule-545x415.jpg 545w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/12/ParacetamolMolecule-600x457.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-147551" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;A 3D molecule of acetaminophen. (&lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/File:Paracetamol-from-xtal-3D-vdW.png"&gt;Ben Mills/Wikimedia Commons/Public Domain&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&lt;span&gt;n a similar way, the research suggests people's affective ability to perceive and evaluate risks may potentially be altered or impaired when they take acetaminophen.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;While the effects might be slight – and should be considered hypothetical for now – they're worth noting, given acetaminophen is the&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://liverfoundation.org/wp-content/uploads/2022/06/Common-Medicines-with-Acetaminophen-Know-Your-Dose.pdf"&gt;most common drug ingredient in America&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;, found in over 600 different kinds of over-the-counter and prescription medicines.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In a series of experiments involving over 500 university students as participants, Way and his team measured how a single 1,000 mg dose of acetaminophen (the recommended maximum adult single dosage) randomly assigned to participants affected their risk-taking behavior, compared against placebos randomly given to a control group.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In each of the experiments, participants had to pump up an un-inflated balloon on a computer screen, with each single pump earning imaginary money.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Their instructions were to earn as much imaginary money as possible by pumping the balloon as much as possible, but to make sure not to pop the balloon, in which case they would lose the money.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The results showed that the students who took acetaminophen engaged in significantly more risk-taking during the exercise, relative to the more cautious and conservative  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/what-is-a-placebo" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="102371" data-postid="156692" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;placebo&lt;/a&gt; group. On the whole, those on acetaminophen pumped (and burst) their balloons more than the controls.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_147552" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-147552" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/12/BaldwinWay.jpg" alt="World's Most Common Pain Relief Drug May Induce Risky Behavior" class="wp-image-147552 size-full" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/12/BaldwinWay.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/12/BaldwinWay-303x415.jpg 303w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/12/BaldwinWay-600x821.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-147552" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Baldwin Way, who led the research. (&lt;a href="https://news.osu.edu/a-pain-reliever-that-alters-perceptions-of-risk/"&gt;Ohio State News&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;"If you're risk-averse, you may pump a few times and then decide to cash out because you don't want the balloon to burst and lose your money,"&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.osu.edu/a-pain-reliever-that-alters-perceptions-of-risk/"&gt;Way said&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"But for those who are on acetaminophen, as the balloon gets bigger, we believe they have less anxiety and less negative emotion about how big the balloon is getting and the possibility of it bursting."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In addition to the balloon simulation, participants also filled out surveys during two of the experiments, rating the level of risk they perceived in various hypothetical scenarios, such as betting a day's income on a sporting event, bungee jumping off a tall bridge, or driving a car without a seatbelt.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In one of the surveys, acetaminophen consumption did appear to reduce perceived risk compared to the control group, although in another similar survey, the same effect wasn't observed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;While an experiment like this doesn't necessarily reflect how acetaminophen might affect people in real-life scenarios, based on an average of results across the various tests, the team concluded that there is a significant relationship between taking acetaminophen and choosing more risk, even if the observed effect appears slight.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That said, the researchers acknowledged the drug's apparent effects on risk-taking behavior could also be interpreted via other kinds of psychological processes, such as reduced anxiety, perhaps.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"It may be that as the balloon increases in size, those on placebo feel increasing amounts of anxiety about a potential burst,"&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://academic.oup.com/scan/advance-article/doi/10.1093/scan/nsaa108/5897711"&gt;the researchers explained&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"When the anxiety becomes too much, they end the trial. Acetaminophen may reduce this anxiety, thus leading to greater risk taking."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Exploring such psychological alternative explanations for this phenomenon – as well as investigating the biological mechanisms responsible for acetaminophen's effects on people's choices in situations like this – should be addressed in future research, the team said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Despite the potential impact of acetaminophen's effect on people's risk perception, the drug nonetheless remains one of the most important and highly used medications in the world, considered an&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/WHO_Model_List_of_Essential_Medicines"&gt;essential medicine by the World Health Organization&lt;/a&gt;, even if other questions linger&lt;span&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"We really need more research on the effects of acetaminophen and other over-the-counter drugs on the choices and risks we take," &lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.osu.edu/a-pain-reliever-that-alters-perceptions-of-risk/"&gt;Way said&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The findings were reported in&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1093/scan/nsaa108"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Social Cognitive and Affective Neuroscience&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;An earlier version of this article was published in September 2020.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;A subsequent commentary published in 2021 highlighted some criticisms of the original study and its interpretation in the media.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This article has been updated to better reflect the hypothetical nature of the study and its findings. For further information, &lt;a href="https://academic.oup.com/scan/article/16/5/537/6149315"&gt;see here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 13:01:39 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipAFBVV95cUxOZ2dtT1lVU054U0dZUjJLbnJReVdHc2J6cU53VmFWV09MdW5DMVpaN3F0aEkxX3hPSEhYeU5ZUmNLOWNFZjBlNGE4NGx1OUxLam8wQ2xUejIxU3BRMW1nMUdmZXRGRFppYXdpYUlHNFdzZG9xY0pFd2pyNFktZTNfMHRTUEdlTzNxbzVMc2JUcExhWXVJcnpGVXkxc2lYMEUxdk1Kdg</guid></item><item><title>Is It Bad to Eat an Apple Every Day? - AOL</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiakFVX3lxTE9BTjRheEgwZ0JYaGZRLTRQZ2R1aE96VXlndl9VeVBXejdMXzVXaEhkYzhBbjFhenVXRlRJZjk5dDhGYnlsNWxmb1lOMDYzYnVGMDNTVmhhYjJwUGdlZm1GWFR5SnpaQW9lb3c?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="caas-body"&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure"&gt;&lt;p class="caption-wrapper caption-aligned-with-image"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption-collapse"&gt;&lt;span class="caption"&gt;Is an Apple a Day Good for You?&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="photo-credit"&gt;Elizabeth Fernandez - Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;The familiar saying that “an &lt;a href="https://www.prevention.com/food-nutrition/g20481875/apple-varieties-and-recipes/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:apple;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;apple&lt;/a&gt; a day keeps the doctor away” may be true. But instead of taking it for granted, we asked nutritionists: Are apples good for you? Plus, we looked at what the research says about eating the fruit every day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Meet the experts: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/stephani-johnson-dcn-rdn-88856120/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Stephani Johnson;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Stephani Johnson&lt;/a&gt;, D.C.N., R.D.N., is an adjunct professor in the department of clinical and preventive nutrition sciences at &lt;a href="https://shp.rutgers.edu/?_gl=1%2Ai4adtj%2A_gcl_au%2AMTUyNTkyNDg3Mi4xNzQwNTA4MTQ2&amp;amp;_ga=2.151383929.1366124760.1742845226-227429285.1738870850" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Rutgers University School of Health Professions;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Rutgers University School of Health Professions&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/evelyn-arteche-rdn-a6854611/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Evelyn Arteche;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Evelyn Arteche&lt;/a&gt;, M.S., R.D.N., C.P.T., C.G.F.I. is at &lt;a href="https://www.cooperhealth.org/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Cooper University Health Care;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Cooper University Health Care&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Is it bad to eat an apple every day?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Actually, no. “While apples contain fructose, a natural sugar in all fruits, they are a valuable part of a healthy diet,” says Stephani Johnson, D.C.N., R.D.N., adjunct professor in the department of clinical and preventive nutrition sciences at Rutgers University School of Health Professions. “Their nutrient density and &lt;a href="https://www.prevention.com/weight-loss/a33382312/fiber-for-weight-loss/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:fiber;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;fiber&lt;/a&gt; content contribute to overall health, making them a beneficial choice for daily consumption.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To get more specific, medium apples typically have about 4.4 grams of fiber, which can help you to meet the daily recommended fiber intake of 25 grams for women and 38 grams for men. Apples also count as one of your five servings of fruits and vegetables, which should be a daily goal, says Johnson.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Since they do contain sugar, to minimize blood sugar spikes, control the portion size of apples and pair them with protein and healthy fats, such as nut butter, cheese, or yogurt.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What is the nutritional value of apples?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Here’s the breakdown for &lt;a href="https://fdc.nal.usda.gov/food-details/1750341/nutrients" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:one medium apple;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;one medium apple&lt;/a&gt; with skin, which is about three inches in diameter (roughly the size of a baseball or a small fist):&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Health benefits of apples&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ahead, Johnson and Evelyn Arteche, M.S., R.D.N., C.P.T., C.G.F.I., at Cooper University Health Care, break down some of the reasons to consider eating apples regularly. “It is important to note that you get more nutrition value from eating a whole apple with the skin,” Arteche says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Smoother digestion: &lt;/strong&gt;The fiber in apples can help promote bowel regularity. “Additionally, the pectin in apple skin serves as a prebiotic, supporting a healthy microbiome and overall gut health,” says Johnson. “Research indicates that the gut microbiome plays a crucial role in various aspects of health, including mental well-being, disease risk, and immune function.” Studies explicitly examining the effects of apples on gut health are limited, but extensive research supports the beneficial impacts of fiber and pectin on gut health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Weight management: &lt;/strong&gt;“Apples can aid in weight management, particularly when consumed in place of higher-calorie, less healthy options,” says Johnson. Research specifically evaluating the effects of apple consumption on weight management in humans is limited. But, Johnson points to &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/26394033/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:one 2015 study;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;one 2015 study&lt;/a&gt; which found that higher fruit and vegetable intake, as well as increased intake of apples and pears, was inversely associated with weight gain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;High-fiber foods with high water content, such as apples, promote satiety so you feel fuller longer than if you, say, ate a cookie. “Fiber slows down gastric emptying and induces a feeling of fullness lasting longer when compared to drinking juice, for example, which does not contain much fiber,” says Arteche.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Heart health: &lt;/strong&gt;Studies have yielded mixed results specifically regarding apple consumption and heart health. “Despite these mixed findings, substantial research links diets rich in fruits and vegetables and low in processed foods to a reduced risk of cardiovascular disease and hypertension, as seen in those following the &lt;a href="https://www.prevention.com/food-nutrition/a20455774/lower-blood-pressure-dash-diet/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:DASH diet;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;DASH diet&lt;/a&gt;,” says Johnson. “Increasing fruit and vegetable intake, including apples, may contribute to cardiovascular health by supporting gut microbiome balance, promoting weight management, and providing antioxidants that help neutralize free radicals implicated in cardiovascular disease risk.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Potential side effects of eating apples&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul class="caas-list caas-list-bullet"&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Diarrhea:&lt;/strong&gt; “Fiber in excess can cause diarrhea in some people,” says Arteche. “For example, people with conditions such as Crohn’s disease, diverticulitis, gastroparesis, ulcerative colitis, a new colostomy, or a new ileostomy may need to avoid apples, especially apples with skin on them.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul class="caas-list caas-list-bullet"&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Food allergies:&lt;/strong&gt; “People who are allergic to apricot, plum, almond, peach, pear, and strawberry can also be allergic to apples and should avoid them,” says Arteche.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Blood sugar elevation:&lt;/strong&gt; “Although apples are a healthy, low-calorie food, they are naturally high in sugar, which may contribute to blood sugar elevations, especially in individuals with impaired glucose tolerance or diabetes,” says Johnson. “However, in comparison to other fruits, apples have a lower glycemic index, meaning that they do not spike blood sugar to the same extent as some other carbohydrate foods.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The bottom line&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Apples generally are safe to eat daily unless you have a food allergy, or other medical reason to avoid them. (Always talk to your healthcare provider if you’re unsure whether a food is for you or not.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Due to their fiber and water content, apples promote digestive regularity and also may help you feel fuller longer, so they can play a role in weight management. They also contribute to your daily goal for both fiber and servings of fruits and vegetables.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You Might Also Like&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>AOL</author><pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 13:00:05 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiakFVX3lxTE9BTjRheEgwZ0JYaGZRLTRQZ2R1aE96VXlndl9VeVBXejdMXzVXaEhkYzhBbjFhenVXRlRJZjk5dDhGYnlsNWxmb1lOMDYzYnVGMDNTVmhhYjJwUGdlZm1GWFR5SnpaQW9lb3c</guid></item><item><title>Tech for babies is booming. Here’s what one parent found helped most - The Seattle Times</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMirgFBVV95cUxPUEJBVGtDMGNvbzNQSXIycjFxOGxvYjNicDNnXzdMSzBBcnVRTG1rUWFqSW1Nc2RjTDNjZUhkcHZDOG1yT0o2N0s0czJvWERFUXNadklMdHRiSlZDNVpRckM0cmFSVUxGSFRVTWJ6OFhlZWZOTW5KOWpkWFpvM3BPUDFhczVobUVrTGR3Q2VCcGNscjEybmFDU19Va3BnNjF5WFdsRkhwQmhna2todkE?oc=5</link><description>&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMirgFBVV95cUxPUEJBVGtDMGNvbzNQSXIycjFxOGxvYjNicDNnXzdMSzBBcnVRTG1rUWFqSW1Nc2RjTDNjZUhkcHZDOG1yT0o2N0s0czJvWERFUXNadklMdHRiSlZDNVpRckM0cmFSVUxGSFRVTWJ6OFhlZWZOTW5KOWpkWFpvM3BPUDFhczVobUVrTGR3Q2VCcGNscjEybmFDU19Va3BnNjF5WFdsRkhwQmhna2todkE?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;Tech for babies is booming. Here’s what one parent found helped most&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Seattle Times&lt;/font&gt;</description><author>The Seattle Times</author><pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 13:00:04 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMirgFBVV95cUxPUEJBVGtDMGNvbzNQSXIycjFxOGxvYjNicDNnXzdMSzBBcnVRTG1rUWFqSW1Nc2RjTDNjZUhkcHZDOG1yT0o2N0s0czJvWERFUXNadklMdHRiSlZDNVpRckM0cmFSVUxGSFRVTWJ6OFhlZWZOTW5KOWpkWFpvM3BPUDFhczVobUVrTGR3Q2VCcGNscjEybmFDU19Va3BnNjF5WFdsRkhwQmhna2todkE</guid></item></channel></rss>