<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>GNews Health</title><link>https://news.google.com/</link><description></description><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>波士顿、威斯特伯勒可能有麻疹暴露，官员警告-《波士顿环球报》</title><link>https://www.bostonglobe.com/2025/12/24/metro/massachusetts-measles-alert/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="body | gutter_16--desktop gutter_16--tablet paywalled_content
              "&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;The Massachusetts Department of Public Health is working with the US Centers for Disease Control and Prevention and local partners to identify and notify those who may have been exposed, officials said. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;“Measles is a highly contagious, airborne disease, which has increased significantly in the United States because of the unfortunate decrease in vaccination rates. It is also a preventable disease,” Public Health Commissioner Dr. Robbie Goldstein said in a statement. “This current situation serves as an important reminder of the critical role vaccination plays in protecting our communities.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;While Massachusetts has not had a measles case this year, the United States has seen the highest number of nationwide cases in more than a decade – nearly 2,000 in 44 jurisdictions, which included three confirmed deaths from measles, Goldstein said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;“Fifteen years ago, measles had been considered eliminated in the United States, but that tremendous progress is at risk,” Goldstein said. “Vaccines are one of the most important public health interventions ever – they are safe, effective, and lifesaving.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Officials said the exposures may have occurred at Logan Airport Terminal B on Dec. 11 from 2:30 p.m. to 4:45 p.m.; at the DoubleTree hotel in Westborough from 3:30 p.m. on Dec. 11 to 9 p.m. on Dec. 12; and at Logan Airport Terminal C from 6 p.m. to 11:30 p.m. on Dec. 12.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;“Those who could have been exposed and begin to develop symptoms of measles should call their healthcare provider before visiting an office, clinic, or emergency department,” public health officials said in the statement. “Visiting a healthcare facility may put others at risk and should be avoided if possible.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Those who have had measles in the past or have received two doses of the Measles, Mumps, and Rubella (MMR) vaccine are unlikely to develop measles even if they were exposed, officials said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Boston Public Health Commissioner Dr. Bisola Ojikutu also encouraged people to get vaccinated for measles.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;“With multiple measles outbreaks across the country and increased travel around the holidays, now is an important time to ensure that you and your family are protected,” she said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Ojikutu said two doses of MMR vaccine are 97 percent effective at preventing measles and provide protection against mumps and rubella. Children should receive the vaccine at 12-15 months of age and again before kindergarten, she said. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Children who are at least 6 months old and traveling internationally or to areas of the US with active outbreaks should receive an early dose of vaccine before traveling, Ojikutu said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;“It is never too late for children or adults to get the measles vaccine even if they are past the recommended age,” Ojikutu said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Early symptoms of measles occur one to three weeks after exposure and may resemble a cold, with symptoms fever, cough, runny nose, and red eyes. A rash occurs on the skin two to four days after the initial symptoms develop and usually appears first on the head, officials said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;People with measles may be contagious up to four days before the rash appears and for four days after the rash starts, officials said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;State public health officials are urging anyone who has not been vaccinated or doesn’t know their measles immunization status to contact their healthcare provider to get vaccinated with at least one dose of the MMR vaccine. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;“Measles vaccine given within 72 hours of exposure may prevent measles disease,” officials said in the statement. “Vaccination beyond this window will provide protection from subsequent exposures.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr class="tagline_hr | border_foreground border_half gutter_20_28--mobile
               margin_none text_align_left width_100px"&gt;&lt;p class="tagline | font_primary inline_block  margin_top_32"&gt;Emily Sweeney can be reached at &lt;a href="mailto:emily.sweeney@globe.com" class="" target="_blank"&gt;emily.sweeney@globe.com&lt;/a&gt;. Follow her &lt;a href="https://www.twitter.com/emilysweeney" class="" target="_blank"&gt;@emilysweeney&lt;/a&gt; and on Instagram &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/emilysweeney22" class="" target="_blank"&gt;@emilysweeney22&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Boston Globe</author><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 19:48:59 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMifkFVX3lxTE1OeVREUmk0Rl94TFdHYUFmSEJvazZtQUp6Rm5Rc1NZU2ZmUHFTMlUwcm1PWWQtX3NNS041TEpzR3dUQktKazZYMlgwT21tUnhsNlR5V21pdDVJTzk0NTJIV2hwSGw1dkxpZV9Fa2cxREotdFB5ZWhaam1SdFYzQQ</guid></item><item><title>性建议：自从我们有了孩子，我妻子就说有一部分性行为是禁止的。这没有道理。-石板</title><link>https://slate.com/advice/2025/12/sex-advice-baby-wife-off-limits.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article__content" itemprop="mainEntityOfPage"&gt;
          &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="18" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjhh3ynj0012j6m2jups7zvm@published"&gt;&lt;em&gt;How to Do It is Slate’s sex advice column. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Have a question? &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLSdx34-uOijrCIKqMdw5hnyYahSJBKa4AaSzDCu1nfcpmd3IjA/viewform"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Send it to Stoya and Rich here.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt; It’s anonymous!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="5" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjhh5jte00143b79nl3xmywh@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dear How to Do It,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

    


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="39" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjhh5esz000o3b79ovij47bn@published"&gt;My wife and I used to attend sex parties all the time. Ever since she got pregnant, that came to a halt. Our son is now nearly a year old, and I’m really eager to return to the scene.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="59" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjhm50pl003q3b797fkwyevp@published"&gt;However, she says that because we have a kid now, that chapter of our lives needs to remain closed. It’s not like we would be hosting parties at our place, and the fact that we have a kid seems neither here nor there in terms of going back to what we were doing. How can I ease her hang-ups?&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="4" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjhh5evg000p3b799n7ygoke@published"&gt;—Ready to Party On&lt;/p&gt;

  

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="5" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjhh5ey7000q3b792kppr3a4@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dear Ready to Party On,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="99" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjhh5f0r000r3b79ijey3535@published"&gt;Regardless of the fact that you’ll likely creep into coercion territory, convincing a person to have sex they aren’t comfortable with is a recipe for destroying your relationship. You don’t ease your wife’s hang-ups. You respect her current boundaries. Where you’re saying your son is nearly a year old, I’m seeing a woman who is not even a year out from giving birth for the first time. Your wife’s position might change again if you can exercise patience. If you push the subject, though, you’re likely to create distance, resentment, and a rigid and eternal “no” on this practice.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="160" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjhh5f3b000s3b7911mq45mp@published"&gt;It feels telling that you omit any mention of what your wife’s reasons are for her decision. OK, yes, because the two of you have a child, but is this about fear of STIs? Does the fact of motherhood mean a change in the boundaries of what she considers acceptable conduct? Has something about the physical and hormonal process of pregnancy changed her relationship to her body or her desires? Is it that time with your infant, or protecting precious sleep, is a higher priority, and sex parties interfere with that? It doesn’t seem like you have this information, and it does seem like you’ve assumed one (probably not the actual case) reason and immediately dismissed it. If you do want to understand your wife’s reasoning, ask her with genuine curiosity. Those answers are likely to help you come to terms with this particular manifestation of the fact that your lives are profoundly different now, because they need to be.&lt;/p&gt;

  


  


  


  


  
  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="109" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjhh5f71000t3b792o5njz2e@published"&gt;It also might help to understand what you’re missing about these parties. What are the emotional needs that were being met? Excitement? Novelty? Attention? Can you come up with potential ways to satisfy those desires while staying within your wife’s boundaries? This can be a second conversation. If you’re able to really hear your wife, and she’s able to feel that you’re hearing her, there will probably be at least some room for compromise and negotiation. This has to be collaborative, though, and you’ll be wise to proceed cautiously, gently, and with grace extended regarding how she may be reacting to the massive life experience she’s just been through.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="1" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjhhdmad001f3b79sd9hiwbs@published"&gt;&lt;span class="slate-paragraph--tombstone"&gt;—Jessica&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;h3 class="subhead subhead--none" data-uri="slate.com/_components/subhead/instances/cmjhhdri100213b79v620jyzs@published"&gt;
&lt;p class="subhead__marker"&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
More Advice From Slate

&lt;/h3&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="69" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjhhdohb001q3b794pdcv7ox@published"&gt;Recently, my long-term boyfriend got me a new dildo. It’s pale green, fairly large, and has stylized eyes painted onto it. I thought it looked freaky, but he thought it was funny and it went to live on the rack with most of our other sex toys near the bed. It’s never actually been used for any sexual activity, &lt;a href="https://slate.com/human-interest/2022/04/haunted-dildo-sex-advice.html"&gt;but I thought I’d try it under the right circumstances…&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;section class="newsletter-signup   " data-list="Advice" data-uri="slate.com/_components/newsletter-signup/instances/cmjhh3ynj0015j6m2efdcih95@published"&gt;


    &lt;p class="newsletter-signup__intro"&gt;
        &lt;svg class="newsletter-signup__arrow"&gt;
          &lt;use xlink:href="/media/components/newsletter-signup/sprite.svg#arrow"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;
        &lt;/svg&gt;
&lt;h1 class="newsletter-signup__headline"&gt;Never miss new Slate Advice columns&lt;/h1&gt;
      &lt;span class="newsletter-signup__description"&gt;Get the latest from Prudie and our columnists in your inbox each weekday, plus special bonus letters on Saturdays.&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;
    



&lt;/section&gt;

  

&lt;/div&gt;

      &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Slate</author><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMieEFVX3lxTE9oTjNXVGZPVzZCRnF1VlIzaXB3MGUycVE3Y1duMmRreHd5alp1MVYtcktjUUVKVmVWRFR0clY2QW5WeG1mVDFEZ0lhRUtwZHZYbU1pMTBaTzlkaGx5QTBlc1hiZnF4UDRXQTlndllKQXg4SUIxWmFQZg</guid></item><item><title>“这完全失控” ：科学家警告禽流感可能在2026年引发人类大流行-英国广播公司科学焦点杂志</title><link>https://www.sciencefocus.com/news/bird-flu-2026-analysis</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div _ngcontent-pxp-c1839238051 class="purple-inner-container purple-content-body-inner"&gt;&lt;p&gt;When a highly pathogenic strain of bird flu strain of avian influenza (H5N1) began sweeping across wild birds and poultry in 2020, it already looked concerning. Five years on, the picture has grown darker and stranger than most would have imagined. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The virus has infected hundreds of millions of farm animals, spilled into mammals at an unprecedented scale, devastated wildlife, and – in the United States – established itself in dairy cattle, a species no one expected to see implicated.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Human cases remain rare. But virologists say the trajectory is troubling, the data patchy and the future uncertain.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It’s now a global problem,” says &lt;a href="https://www.gla.ac.uk/schools/infectionimmunity/staff/edwardhutchinson/"&gt;Dr Ed Hutchinson&lt;/a&gt;, professor of molecular and cellular virology at the University of Glasgow. “As a disease of wild animals, it’s completely out of control. It’s raging around the world, and there’s no feasible containment method other than just watching it infect huge populations of animals.” &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;How quickly has the virus spread?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The current lineage of H5N1 emerged in Asia in the late 1990s and has since swept from continent to continent. Since 2020, a particularly aggressive branch of the virus – known to scientists as clade 2.3.4.4b – has spread explosively through wild birds.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;More than &lt;a href="https://www.aphis.usda.gov/livestock-poultry-disease/avian/avian-influenza/hpai-detections/commercial-backyard-flocks"&gt;180 million poultry&lt;/a&gt; have been infected in the US alone, and over &lt;a href="https://www.aphis.usda.gov/livestock-poultry-disease/avian/avian-influenza/hpai-detections/hpai-confirmed-cases-livestock"&gt;1,000 dairy farms&lt;/a&gt; have reported outbreaks. Egg prices have soared, and the US government has spent more than &lt;a href="https://www.congress.gov/crs-product/R48518"&gt;$1.19bn&lt;/a&gt; (£881m) reimbursing farmers for losses.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For now, the human toll remains limited: only &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/bird-flu/situation-summary/index.html"&gt;71 confirmed cases&lt;/a&gt; in the US, resulting in two deaths. Historically, though, H5N1 has been far deadlier: since 2003, &lt;a href="https://cdn.who.int/media/docs/default-source/wpro---documents/emergency/surveillance/avian-influenza/ai_20250131.pdf"&gt;almost half&lt;/a&gt; of all known human infections globally have proved fatal.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Even so, something unprecedented has happened. In early 2024, H5N1 was found in dairy cattle in the United States. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“This was to everyone’s astonishment,” Hutchinson says, “You now have a situation where a large proportion of consumer milk in the US at any given time contains genetic material from these highly pathogenic viruses.” &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thankfully, pasteurisation destroys the virus. But raw milk, along with close contact for workers on dairy farms, still poses significant risks of infection.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure class="wp-block-image size-large"&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" decoding="async" src="https://c02.purpledshub.com/uploads/sites/41/2025/12/eggs.jpg?webp=1&amp;amp;w=1200" alt="A customer, holding a carton of eggs, is seen during shopping at a supermarket as packages of eggs are seen on the shelves of the egg aisle in New York City, United States on December 20, 2024." class="wp-image-210606"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="wp-element-caption"&gt;Average egg prices in the US peaked at more than $6 (£4.40 approx) per dozen in March 2025 as swathes of flocks of hens were culled due to bird flu infections - Photo credit: Getty&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That unexpected species jump – along with growing evidence of infection in mammals from seals to foxes to bears – increases opportunities for the virus to change and adapt. Flu viruses are unusually good at evolving because their genome is segmented. If two different strains infect the same host cell, their gene segments can mix and match, producing a new hybrid virus.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This process, known as genome reassortment, has played a key role in sparking past pandemics, and many experts are concerned the same could happen if a person infected with a human influenza were also infected with bird flu. This may, for example, allow the virus to gain the ability to transmit effectively in humans, while maintaining a structure which is alien and undetectable to our immune systems. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“In a sense,” Hutchinson says, “the question about reassortment is not ‘When is it going to happen?’, but ‘Why isn't it happening all the time?’ Because there are so many influenza variants out there, and we don't really know the barriers to it taking off.” &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Beyond farms and factories, the outbreak has become a wildlife crisis. In South America, mass die-offs have struck &lt;a href="https://eswi.org/education-hub/pacific-and-atlantic-sea-lion-mortality-caused-highly-pathogenic-avian-influenza" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;sea lions&lt;/a&gt;. And on the Antarctic coast, almost half of the world’s female breeding population of southern elephant seals may already have been killed, according to a recent &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s42003-025-09014-7"&gt;study&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;The US: epicentre and outlier&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The US today is one of the most active hotspots for avian influenza transmission. Yet the national response is fragmented. Farm biosecurity measures remain the primary line of defence, even as&lt;a href="https://www.propublica.org/article/bird-flu-airborne-usda-pandemic"&gt; evidence grows&lt;/a&gt; that the virus may be travelling between farms on the wind – a mode that fences, disinfectant and clean boots cannot stop.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Meanwhile, virologists say monitoring and reporting are weakening. US surveillance varies dramatically between states, complicating assessments of how widespread H5N1 infections really are. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.kent.ac.uk/biosciences/people/1028/rossman-jeremy"&gt;Dr Jeremy Rossman&lt;/a&gt;, honorary senior lecturer in virology at the University of Kent, says effective containment hinges on broad, coordinated surveillance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“This requires extensive surveillance of infection in multiple animal populations, as well as monitoring and testing for animal workers at these farms,” he says. “This can allow for management of any infected flocks or herds, rapid identification of human spillover cases and early detection of new mutations in the virus that may affect transmissibility.” &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But in the US, Rossman argues, that isn’t happening consistently. “The response is more limited and variable from state to state and farm to farm,” he says. “Without strategic and coordinated surveillance and containment, the risks of a human transmissible H5N1 virus will steadily rise, with unknown, but potentially critical consequences.”  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hutchinson shares this concern. Not only are human and animal infections rising, he says, but data sharing has become patchier and harder to interpret, raising the risk that early warning signs could be missed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The good news is that effective vaccines already exist to protect both humans and animals – and the US is thought to have &lt;a href="https://www.unmc.edu/healthsecurity/transmission/2025/01/22/the-us-has-bird-flu-vaccines-heres-why-you-cant-get-one/"&gt;millions of doses stockpiled&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;How successful is vaccination? France adopted poultry vaccination in 2023 and saw outbreaks fall by&lt;a href="https://avinews.com/en/france-avian-influenza-nearly-eradicated-thanks-to-vaccination/#:~:text=France%20has%20achieved%20a%20major,vaccination%20campaign%20in%20October%202023."&gt; 96 per cent&lt;/a&gt; in two years, which is impressive. But progress elsewhere has been slow.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the US, poultry producers and lawmakers have opposed vaccination on trade grounds, warning that it could harm export markets and cost the chicken industry &lt;a href="https://www.congress.gov/crs-product/R48518"&gt;$10bn&lt;/a&gt; (£7.4bn) if other countries ban US meat.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is despite the outbreak already costing the country billions of dollars, not least ordinary people whose grocery bills have risen as egg prices &lt;a href="https://fred.stlouisfed.org/series/APU0000708111"&gt;soared 300 per cent&lt;/a&gt; in 2 years.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure class="wp-block-image size-large"&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" decoding="async" src="https://c02.purpledshub.com/uploads/sites/41/2025/12/bird-flu-virus.jpg?webp=1&amp;amp;w=1200" alt="Colorised transmission electron micrograph of avian influenza A H5N1 virus particles (gold)." class="wp-image-210607"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="wp-element-caption"&gt;This transmission electron micrograph shows avian influenza A H5N1 particles (gold), grown in a cell culture (blue) - Credit: Getty&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;So how worried should we be?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The central fear is human-to-human transmission. So far, it has not happened in any sustained way. But influenza evolves fast, and every new infected host is another throw of the genetic dice.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rossman warns that high levels of circulation across species increase the odds “of the virus evolving into a strain that has both high transmissibility and high lethality. Given the catastrophic implications if it did, tracking and mitigating the spread of H5N1 virus is of critical importance.” &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are reasons for optimism: vaccines and antivirals should be effective against avian influenza, and the world is far better prepared thanks to lessons learned from COVID, particularly in diagnostics and global surveillance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But there are caveats too. Scaling vaccines to a global population would take time; antiviral resistance has already appeared in poultry in Canada, and our immunity to H1 and H3 seasonal flu offers little protection against H5 strains.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Perhaps the sharpest warning comes from computer modelling of an outbreak. A 2025 &lt;a href="https://link.springer.com/article/10.1186/s12889-025-25358-5"&gt;study&lt;/a&gt; from Indian researchers found that once a pandemic strain began spreading in humans, the window for effective containment could be just 2 to 10 detected cases. Beyond that, containment would become almost impossible.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;What happens next&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As 2026 begins, H5N1 is circulating in more species, across more continents, than ever before. It is entrenched in global wildlife. It has destabilised farming. It is mutating, spreading and defying prediction.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hutchinson’s message is clear: vigilance, not panic. “There are reasons to hope as well as reasons to be alarmed,” he says. “But there’s definitely no reason to be relaxed about this one.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What scientists want next is simple: more surveillance, more transparency, more vaccination and more urgency, especially in the United States, where the virus is spreading rapidly, and surveillance remains uneven. Whether they’ll get their wishes, however, remains to be seen.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Read more:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BBC Science Focus Magazine</author><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiZ0FVX3lxTE5HcjlNTGlSdFhVcEhYbzB0cTdkNFIySFpnV3MtVmV4MTFHaFE3bkpqOUxBNmlpZWdvNWpaTnhzZkt1U3dUcGxWa2U4b2JydUpqUkdlOHBocWZzaVEyNDhRYk5QSzlnQWc</guid></item><item><title>阿拉巴马州流感爆发让男孩在圣诞节为生命而战：休伊镇祈求奇迹- AL.com</title><link>https://www.al.com/news/2025/12/alabama-flu-outbreak-leaves-boy-fighting-for-his-life-at-christmas-hueytown-praying-for-a-miracle.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content   "&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="3CXGONLGDJG2FE3M7UE7BZXQMM"&gt;A Hueytown boy diagnosed with the flu is battling for his life on Christmas Eve in critical condition at Children’s of Alabama.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-1" data-gaid="inarticle-1"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="2ASAC4Q2EFDB3AYLXRXPWRHRV4"&gt;Jace Watkins, 11, was sick on Thursday, visited a doctor Friday, then had a seizure on Saturday, his family said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-2" data-gaid="inarticle-2"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="UFSA3ZPEAZD7XL5BCZFS3I3RBQ"&gt;A crowd including family and friends gathered in Hueytown City Park on Tuesday night to pray for Jace.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-3" data-gaid="inarticle-3"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="YHT2MPCPLVHYFJXLYH3RMMMPGA"&gt;“God hears our prayers,” said Amanda Aloia, a friend of the family who organized the prayer vigil. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-4" data-gaid="inarticle-4"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="IC7UFFP7VRBF5GA733CPTVLGAQ"&gt;“Tonight, we’re here to pray for his healing, that he receives a huge miracle, that he wakes up and he is refreshed and new and God heals every broken part of him, he wakes up with no negative side effects from this, and that his family receives some peace and comfort during this hard time.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-5" data-gaid="inarticle-5"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="TWJCZ6GYORC2JJOWWNXMYJMQWY"&gt;Jace’s life hangs in the balance as he’s on a ventilator in the Intensive Care Unit at Children’s.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-6" class="middleParagraph" data-gaid="inarticle-6"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="RECDXWTKE5F6PDZRHDVMU5KVM4"&gt;“They didn’t know if he’s going to make it,” the boy’s aunt, Sabrina Parsons, &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=z2o-acEp43g" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=z2o-acEp43g"&gt;told Fox 6&lt;/a&gt;. “The doctors did say if he did not have any brain activity in the next couple days, that he would be brain dead.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-7" data-gaid="inarticle-7"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="FSIWB3H6KRELFNCDNAZMX5ZT6I"&gt;New &lt;a href="https://www.al.com/news/2025/12/flu-season-is-here-just-in-time-for-christmas-these-areas-in-alabama-are-getting-hit-hardest.html" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://www.al.com/news/2025/12/flu-season-is-here-just-in-time-for-christmas-these-areas-in-alabama-are-getting-hit-hardest.html"&gt;cases of the flu have been doubling &lt;/a&gt;during the holidays, state officials say.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-8" data-gaid="inarticle-8"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="JT2OCRPKQJEFLA6HLH2ENCME7Y"&gt;The &lt;a href="https://www.alabamapublichealth.gov/data/respiratory.html" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://www.alabamapublichealth.gov/data/respiratory.html"&gt;Alabama Department of Public Health&lt;/a&gt; reports roughly 2.7% of emergency room visits in the week ending Dec. 3 were for flu-like illness. That’s more than twice the rate from the previous week.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-9" data-gaid="inarticle-9"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="EE22KCWN3NE75NC4FNAIYRCJNE"&gt;“ADPH is monitoring influenza activity statewide through our routine surveillance systems, and we are seeing increased flu activity consistent with the seasonal trend,” Ryan Easterling, director of health media and communications at ADPH said in an email to AL.com this week. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-10" data-gaid="inarticle-10"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-enter:VMO724EMTBEZLDSKN7S4N4NCFE" data-fusion-component="VMO724EMTBEZLDSKN7S4N4NCFE"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-exit:VMO724EMTBEZLDSKN7S4N4NCFE" data-fusion-component="VMO724EMTBEZLDSKN7S4N4NCFE"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-11" data-gaid="inarticle-11"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>AL.com</author><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 16:41:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMizwFBVV95cUxPVlI1S2lXTV9rT3hFenRkaWYwdFFVVV85RGFYeVlNNzNiVTBRTHdHckpHWldyY3R6SXdISHAxdlVGOGxXX3B0UDdoeE5TTWhhU3VOZHJFaHRLVmotMm1KUElNU3BhUzNaclNxYnl6cWJ1V0lzelZxQmRsd2pLV1hUUF9PTGpsRGh1emtRZE11UnZpem1EcmZlR0JrX1dKTW9GWDlVb0lESlBRMXdtRHdub1NxNHQzWlVhYXBJUVM4Z0l2OUt1dUliNTNoQUx4ZmfSAeMBQVVfeXFMTl9oOGdobVZNUHBBMXZFSTdyZl8yN0JMcVlUUFl0NnVtUFpxOHU2NGhfT3FyTm9iS3FOZkdkRUl3c21uY3E5dHE4Sm55QkJ4RWNqYldCTHJxcXNYVE5jeVRvSEVnRlJhLTJBTWVSOEVVQ0JpM21KSTZPNkVkSlVfRmJxaldiLVAwdGNLc2k5QU9pYkV0bllpQ0VwT1BzUHNYV3BvMklUelB4VGZ4Zjg1aHVicTNERXc5SXNZWDhaU2JmVHhEMnNkc1N2RHc5SWZ5UGJBaFZTRXpXV3pNRTMyU1czNmM</guid></item><item><title>健康日志：父母的秘密武器-拼车之间</title><link>https://betweencarpools.com/the-health-log-a-parents-secret-weapon/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content"&gt;
&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;They say a mother’s intuition is key – but a mother’s information may help you do the best job possible when advocating for your child.&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;A while back, I shared &lt;a href="https://betweencarpools.com/one-trick-make-sure-never-forget-dose-antibiotics/"&gt;this medicine hack&lt;/a&gt; that was recently discovered by my much younger sister-in-law, who found it to be a game-changer for her and her friends. As I was discussing another parenting and medical idea with her, she encouraged me to share it with the BCP readers. Thanks, Tzipora, for being my cheerleader!&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="has-prata-font-family"&gt;In my experience, navigating Western medicine requires us to be our own advocates.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Fortunately, with the convenience of urgent care centers and late hours, we often find ourselves in various medical offices with our children. However, this can also mean that no one is keeping track of our kids’ medical history for us.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;That’s why I started a note on my phone called “The Family Health Log.” I listed my children’s names and underlined them, then created bullets for each medical episode, including the treatment and sometimes a brief note. This simple hack has helped me stay organized and informed, and I hope it can do the same for you.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;This is a sneak peak at what a segment of my log looks like : &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;[Child’s Name]&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;•⁠  ⁠March 16th, 2020: Strep (rapid positive) – Cephalexin for 10 days&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;•⁠  ⁠May 27th, 2020: Strep (overnight positive) – Amoxycillin (switched to Duricef after 4 days)&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;•⁠  ⁠Feb 25th, 2021: Toe infection – Cephalexin&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;•⁠  ⁠April 26th, 2021: Strep (positive after multiple cultures and behavioral issues) – Duricef&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;•⁠  ⁠July 15th, 2021: Toe infection – Duricef&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;This tool is especially valuable for young parents who travel frequently, perhaps between Eretz Yisroel, their childhood home for Bain Hazmanim, and their in-laws in another city. With their baby experiencing recurring ear infections in different locations, it can be challenging to keep track of treatments and dates.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;This smart tool allows a responsible mom to maintain a detailed list of dates and treatments, making it easier to share with an ENT specialist and determine the best course of action. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;figure class="wp-block-image size-full"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" data-pin-url="https://betweencarpools.com/the-health-log-a-parents-secret-weapon/?tp_image_id=83702" data-pin-title="The Health Log: A Parent’s Secret Weapon" src="https://cdn.betweencarpools.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/shutterstock_1677873781-scaled.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-83702" srcset="https://cdn.betweencarpools.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/shutterstock_1677873781-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cdn.betweencarpools.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/shutterstock_1677873781-300x200.jpg 300w, https://cdn.betweencarpools.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/shutterstock_1677873781-1024x683.jpg 1024w, https://cdn.betweencarpools.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/shutterstock_1677873781-768x512.jpg 768w, https://cdn.betweencarpools.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/shutterstock_1677873781-1536x1024.jpg 1536w, https://cdn.betweencarpools.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/shutterstock_1677873781-2048x1366.jpg 2048w, https://cdn.betweencarpools.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/shutterstock_1677873781-150x100.jpg 150w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Here’s another example of how the Health Log proved helpful. My nine-year-old was complaining of frequent headaches, and I couldn’t quite pinpoint the cause. I decided to track the occurrences, jotting down the date and time in his Health Log whenever he mentioned a headache. After a few weeks, a pattern emerged: his headaches always seemed to occur on Sunday evenings. Armed with this insight, we made a few adjustments – we shifted his bedtime on Motzai Shabbos and added an extra water bottle to his Sunday backpack. The headaches significantly decreased. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;mark class="has-inline-color"&gt;My camera roll has also been an empowering tracking tool, as long as it’s organized.&lt;/mark&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;I learned from BCP to caption photos and I’ve created and labeled albums to monitor specific issues. For example, track your teen’s acne journey for a couple of months to identify which creams or medicines are most effective, and have photos readily available to share with their dermatologist. I’ve used this hack to track my son’s eczema journey, and it’s been incredibly helpful.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="has-prata-font-family"&gt;While playing the big sister role,&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;I’d like to share a tip that seemed obvious to me until a great-grandmother told me she wasn’t aware of it. When you or your child take antibiotics, try to wait 2–3 hours before giving probiotics or a yogurt/probiotic snack. Don’t stress if the timing isn’t perfect – even 1.5 hours can make a difference. Waiting 2–3 hours helps protect against diarrhea, upset stomach, diaper rash, and yeast infections caused by antibiotics.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Just a heads up, sometimes kids can throw up after taking antibiotics. If that happens, definitely check with your pediatrician, but I’ve heard that if it’s more than 30 minutes after the dose, it’s probably absorbed and you don’t need to worry about giving another one. Best to get their advice, though!&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="has-prata-font-family"&gt;The last tip is one I’ve found incredibly helpful:&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;mark class="has-inline-color"&gt;I often ask a doctor for permission to record or film a visit.&lt;/mark&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Here’s why. When I’m with my infant and we’re at the ENT for a procedure like a tongue clip, I can’t focus on the nurse’s instructions while tending to my screaming baby. By filming the exercises, I can review them later at a calmer time. Similarly, when I take a child to a specialist and am hit with a lot of information or options, it’s hard to retain everything to discuss with my spouse later. Recording the consult (with the doctor’s permission) or taking notes on my phone helps me process the information and make informed decisions. This is especially useful if I’m seeking a second opinion and want to compare perspectives.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;I hope this share brings you and your family the same benefits it’s brought mine. Wishing you a winter filled with health, happiness, and fewer unexpected doctor visits!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="cp-load-after-post"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Between Carpools</author><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 16:11:30 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMidkFVX3lxTE5ieW9QQ2F2UnN3cWMtVnJLeUUzUFJyWktUSEtnMFMtZzVxdy1pV3o5a0ZMTXQwOTI4eFZfV19YVHBzOThDYWU2bXlvRGZ5alNHeGxNRm9IMmVKbTZIel9UVmlVeWdsNmpodUpXZnlqLWhGM2tKMFE</guid></item><item><title>医院计划因疾病日益严重而限制访客-《代顿每日新闻》</title><link>https://www.daytondailynews.com/local/hospitals-plan-on-restricting-visitors-due-to-growing-illnesses/5LNXXDPQFZAY3PRTGXYNVXNVLY/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="c-contentElements" data-start-index="0"&gt;&lt;p class="story-text " data-index="1"&gt;“Our hospitals are taking proactive, temporary steps to protect patient safety and maintain access to care for our community,” said Sarah Hackenbracht,&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;GDAHA president and CEO. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="story-text " data-index="2"&gt;The restrictions will be: &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="list b-margin-bottom-d40-m20"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;No visitation by anyone who is ill with any respiratory symptoms including coughing, fever, chills, headache, vomiting, sore throat, muscle aches or diarrhea.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;No visitation by anyone under age 14 even if they have received the seasonal influenza vaccine or receive the appropriate vaccine when it becomes available. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="story-text " data-index="4"&gt;“We know how important it is for patients to have the support of loved ones, and these decisions are not made lightly. These measures help reduce the spread of illness and support our health care teams as they care for patients across the region,” Hackenbracht said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="story-subscription__placeholder subscription-promo b-margin-bottom-d40-m20"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="story-text " data-index="6"&gt;Area hospitals and ambulatory care sites are currently seeing higher-than-normal volumes of patients with positive cases of respiratory illnesses, including influenza, COVID-19 and other seasonal viruses, according to GDAHA. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="story-nativo_placeholder--moap b-clear-both is-deferred"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="story-text " data-index="8"&gt;Statewide, hospitalizations for respiratory illnesses have been slowly increasing since November, but the latest week showed 752 hospitalizations for the week ending Dec. 13, according to the most recent data available from the Ohio Department of Health. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="story-text " data-index="9"&gt;Of those hospitalizations, 327 were for COVID-19 cases, 318 were for the flu and 107 for respiratory syncytial virus (RSV), according ODH data. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="story-text " data-index="10"&gt;The local breakdown for the most recent week of data shows:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="list b-margin-bottom-d40-m20"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;In Butler County, 10 hospitalizations for COVID-19, 19 for the flu and eight for RSV&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;In Clark County, four hospitalizations for COVID-19, seven for the flu and none for RSV&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;In Montgomery County, 32 hospitalizations for COVID-19, 37 for the flu and 18 for RSV&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="story-text " data-index="12"&gt;Limiting visitors for hospital patients when there is a higher risk of spreading contagious illnesses like respiratory viruses is a standard infection prevention practice, according to GDAHA. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="story-text " data-index="15"&gt;Hospitals are asking community members to postpone visiting if they are feeling unwell, especially if experiencing symptoms such as fever, cough, sore throat or congestion. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="story-text " data-index="16"&gt;For visitors who are permitted into area hospitals, GDAHA is encouraging them to follow all hospital guidance, including hand hygiene and masking when requested.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="story-text " data-index="17"&gt;Visitor restrictions are temporary and will be reviewed regularly based on illness trends and hospital conditions. Exceptions may be made for pediatric patients, labor and delivery, end-of-life care and other special circumstances, according to GDAHA. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="story-text " data-index="18"&gt;GDAHA is a member-service organization representing 29 hospitals and health systems in the Dayton region. GDAHA collaborates with its members to improve the delivery of health care services in Auglaize, Butler, Darke, Champaign, Clark, Greene, Miami, Montgomery, Preble, Shelby, and Warren counties in West Central Ohio.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Dayton Daily News</author><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 16:01:01 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiyAFBVV95cUxOQm9naE54QkhhTXJIRG9CUjZBMzdmUFlBY1Vfa3R3MUhpYlBCOWltcGpydFgtamdleTQ1Y3lOREVNRVFzTzg5ZzJXN1g1bVhzUlVISUpTLUpKMlhWZEZGdHBXSWtsUGhGanZvaGc3Z3hNQll5d3NaOFc1RHFLc2VGcXNVM09uaVpJTmlpdlduS0FydUxmZ3c4ZFNkWjdwTzFBTzVLbzdPT00wMG9sNlhBeTBpdDBaWnRWZmRSUHh1cG91ZWJqRHhlXw</guid></item><item><title>卫生部召回血压药物--特立尼达和多巴哥新闻日报</title><link>https://newsday.co.tt/2025/12/24/health-ministry-recalls-blood-pressure-drug/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article class="article-content"&gt;


	&lt;a class="article-category" href="https://newsday.co.tt/category/news"&gt;News&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;header&gt;
	&lt;h1&gt;Health ministry recalls blood-pressure drug&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;/header&gt;



&lt;address class="article-author"&gt;
	&lt;a rel="author" href="https://newsday.co.tt/reporter/newsday_reporter"&gt;
		Newsday Reporter								
	&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/address&gt;



&lt;time class="date-time" pubdate datetime="2025-12-24" title="Wednesday 24 December 2025"&gt;2 Hrs Ago&lt;/time&gt;

&lt;figure id="article-featured-image" class="article-featured-image"&gt;&lt;img fetchpriority="high" src="https://newsday.co.tt/wp-content/uploads/2025/08/24251776-1024x754.jpg" alt="Health Minister Dr Lackram Bodoe "&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;Health Minister Dr Lackram Bodoe &lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The Ministry of Health, via its Chemistry, Food and Drug Division, has announced a voluntary recall affecting specific lots of bisoprolol fumarate and hydrochlorothiazide tablets, a generic medication used to treat hypertension.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The affected lots are 17232401 (expiring November 2025), 17232401 (expiring November 2025), 17232401 (expiring November 2025), 17240974 (expiring May 2026), 17240974 (expiring May 2026) and 17240974 (expiring May 2026).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The recall was initiated by Glenmark Pharmaceuticals Inc in coordination with the US Food and Drug Administration (FDA) after routine quality testing identified a potential cross-contamination issue. Trace amounts of another drug, ezetimibe, a medication used to treat high cholesterol, were detected in reserve samples of the product, which should not have been present in the blood-pressure medication.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A total of 11,136 bottles of these products have been affected by the recall.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While FDA’s classification of this recall is Class III, indicating that exposure to the trace contaminant is not likely to cause adverse health effects, the ministry is urging appropriate precaution.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="ad-manager-half-page-mobile-ad-300x600 ad-space-centered" id="div-gpt-ad-1550239531467-0"&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The ministry advised that people who may have purchased or are currently in possession of the affected products to discontinue use immediately and return the medication to the place of purchase.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It said anyone with health concerns should consult with their healthcare provider as patients should not abruptly stop antihypertensive medication without professional guidance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Additional information can be obtained by contacting the Office of the Director of the Chemistry, Food and Drugs Division via email at cfdd@health.gov.tt or phone at 217-4664 ext 13101.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/article&gt;



&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Trinidad and Tobago Newsday</author><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 15:44:37 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigwFBVV95cUxNT1NBTTM2Umg1WVl2eHotTUdYM2hrQUlkZUdHX3BfYWdzMW4yNlJDV25KRkNJYThrVTByeFl5QTNOUHU0YlJEd0dTZG9iQVNIN0tGdlQ3VTFUaFplcjhOME9qRFhSNDNkczR5eDdncm9pQVpPc013eWVpOS03ZGd5R2NYcw</guid></item><item><title>科学家逆转小鼠阿尔茨海默氏症并恢复记忆- ScienceDaily</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/12/251224032354.htm</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p id="first" class="lead"&gt;A study reveals that restoring the brain's energy balance may not just slow Alzheimer's -- but actually reverse it.&lt;/p&gt;

						&lt;div id="text"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;    &lt;li&gt;For more than a century, Alzheimer's disease has been widely viewed as permanent and untreatable once it begins. As a result, most research has focused on preventing the disease or slowing its progression rather than attempting to reverse it.&lt;/li&gt;    &lt;li&gt;By studying multiple mouse models of Alzheimer's alongside human Alzheimer's brain tissue, researchers identified a critical biological problem at the center of the disease. They found that the brain's inability to maintain healthy levels of a vital cellular energy molecule called NAD+ plays a major role in driving Alzheimer's.&lt;/li&gt;    &lt;li&gt;In animal models, maintaining normal brain NAD+ levels prevented Alzheimer's from developing. Even more striking, restoring NAD+ balance after the disease was already advanced allowed the brain to repair damage and fully restore cognitive function.&lt;/li&gt;    &lt;li&gt;These results suggest that treatments aimed at restoring the brain's energy balance could potentially move Alzheimer's therapy beyond slowing decline and toward meaningful recovery.&lt;/li&gt;    &lt;li&gt;The findings also open the door to further research, including the exploration of complementary strategies and carefully designed clinical trials to determine whether these results can translate to patients.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A Longstanding View of Alzheimer's Is Being Questioned&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For more than 100 years, Alzheimer's disease (AD) has been widely viewed as a condition that cannot be undone. Because of this belief, most scientific efforts have focused on preventing the disease or slowing its progression, rather than attempting to restore lost brain function. Even after decades of research and billions of dollars in investment, no drug trial for Alzheimer's has ever been designed with the goal of reversing the disease and recovering cognitive abilities.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That long-held assumption is now being challenged by researchers from University Hospitals, Case Western Reserve University, and the Louis Stokes Cleveland VA Medical Center. Their work set out to answer a bold question: can brains already damaged by advanced Alzheimer's recover?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;New Study Targets Brain Energy Failure&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The research was led by Kalyani Chaubey, PhD, of the Pieper Laboratory and published on December 22 in &lt;em&gt;Cell Reports Medicine&lt;/em&gt;. By examining both human Alzheimer's brain tissue and multiple preclinical mouse models, the team identified a key biological failure at the center of the disease. They found that the brain's inability to maintain normal levels of a critical cellular energy molecule called NAD+ plays a major role in driving Alzheimer's. Importantly, maintaining proper NAD+ balance was shown to not only prevent the disease but also reverse it in experimental models.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;NAD+ levels naturally decline throughout the body, including the brain, as people age. When NAD+ drops too low, cells lose the ability to carry out essential processes needed for normal function and survival. The researchers discovered that this decline is far more severe in the brains of people with Alzheimer's. The same pattern was seen in mouse models of the disease.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="insertion_middle"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How Alzheimer's Was Modeled in the Lab&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Although Alzheimer's occurs only in humans, scientists study it using specially engineered mice that carry genetic mutations known to cause the disease in people. In this study, researchers used two such models. One group of mice carried multiple human mutations affecting amyloid processing, while the other carried a human mutation in the tau protein.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Amyloid and tau abnormalities are among the earliest and most significant features of Alzheimer's. In both mouse models, these mutations led to widespread brain damage that closely mirrors the human disease. This included breakdown of the blood-brain barrier, damage to nerve fibers, chronic inflammation, reduced formation of new neurons in the hippocampus, weakened communication between brain cells, and extensive oxidative damage. The mice also developed severe memory and cognitive problems similar to those seen in people with Alzheimer's.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Testing Whether Alzheimer's Damage Could Be Reversed&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After confirming that NAD+ levels dropped sharply in both human and mouse Alzheimer's brains, the team explored two possibilities. They tested whether maintaining NAD+ balance before symptoms appeared could prevent Alzheimer's, and whether restoring that balance after the disease had already progressed could reverse it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This approach built on the group's earlier work published in Proceeding of the National Academy of Sciences USA, which showed that restoring NAD+ balance led to both structural and functional recovery after severe, long-lasting traumatic brain injury. In the current study, the researchers used a well-characterized pharmacologic compound called P7C3-A20, developed in the Pieper laboratory, to restore NAD+ balance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="insertion_bottom"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Full Cognitive Recovery Observed in Advanced Disease&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The results were striking. Preserving NAD+ balance protected mice from developing Alzheimer's, but even more surprising was what happened when treatment began after the disease was already advanced. In those cases, restoring NAD+ balance allowed the brain to repair the major pathological damage caused by the genetic mutations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Both mouse models showed complete recovery of cognitive function. This recovery was also reflected in blood tests, which showed normalized levels of phosphorylated tau 217, a recently approved clinical biomarker used to diagnose Alzheimer's in people. These findings provided strong evidence of disease reversal and highlighted a potential biomarker for future human trials.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Researchers Express Cautious Optimism&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"We were very excited and encouraged by our results," said Andrew A. Pieper, MD, PhD, senior author of the study and Director of the Brain Health Medicines Center, Harrington Discovery Institute at UH. "Restoring the brain's energy balance achieved pathological and functional recovery in both lines of mice with advanced Alzheimer's. Seeing this effect in two very different animal models, each driven by different genetic causes, strengthens the idea that restoring the brain's NAD+ balance might help patients recover from Alzheimer's."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dr. Pieper also holds the Morley-Mather Chair in Neuropsychiatry at UH and the CWRU Rebecca E. Barchas, MD, DLFAPA, University Professorship in Translational Psychiatry. He serves as Psychiatrist and Investigator in the Louis Stokes VA Geriatric Research Education and Clinical Center (GRECC).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A Shift in How Alzheimer's Is Viewed&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The findings suggest a fundamental change in how Alzheimer's could be approached in the future. "The key takeaway is a message of hope -- the effects of Alzheimer's disease may not be inevitably permanent," said Dr. Pieper. "The damaged brain can, under some conditions, repair itself and regain function."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dr. Chaubey added, "Through our study, we demonstrated one drug-based way to accomplish this in animal models, and also identified candidate proteins in the human AD brain that may relate to the ability to reverse AD."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why This Approach Differs From Supplements&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dr. Pieper cautioned against confusing this strategy with over the counter NAD+-precursors. He noted that such supplements have been shown in animal studies to raise NAD+ to dangerously high levels that promote cancer The method used in this research relies instead on P7C3-A20, a pharmacologic agent that helps cells maintain healthy NAD+ balance during extreme stress, without pushing levels beyond their normal range.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"This is important when considering patient care, and clinicians should consider the possibility that therapeutic strategies aimed at restoring brain energy balance might offer a path to disease recovery," said Dr. Pieper.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Next Steps Toward Human Trials&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The research also opens the door to additional studies and eventual testing in people. The technology is currently being commercialized by Glengary Brain Health, a Cleveland-based company co-founded by Dr. Pieper.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"This new therapeutic approach to recovery needs to be moved into carefully designed human clinical trials to determine whether the efficacy seen in animal models translates to human patients," Dr. Pieper explained. "Additional next steps for the laboratory research include pinpointing which aspects of brain energy balance are most important for recovery, identifying and evaluating complementary approaches to Alzheimer's reversal, and investigating whether this recovery approach is also effective in other forms of chronic, age-related neurodegenerative disease."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

					&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceDaily</author><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 15:15:25 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMib0FVX3lxTFBHa0hNTVpyWXRzR1lTTmpiSUtsdTg2M0tLb3daWGF4LUNFdWlvdlFrQlBYeXI4ekNpeFgzSkJfWTJxdHhYWGtPdmNMNmFfLUtVczRSNWxNVnRnV3lBSTVhaWdYRFF5cTN5Q3otek0tVQ</guid></item><item><title>专家说，圣诞节前流感病例下降-英国广播公司</title><link>https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/c3e0qpxzwe7o</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article&gt;&lt;p data-component="headline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 hNbOGD"&gt;&lt;h1 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 idLnWK"&gt;Flu cases falling ahead of Christmas, experts say&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="byline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="byline" class="sc-573fa0e8-0 bWRWzH"&gt;&lt;span data-testid="byline-contributors" class="sc-573fa0e8-11 cOQNNv"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="byline-contributors-contributor-0" class="sc-573fa0e8-5 gXJgDY"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="sc-573fa0e8-7 gqeTMs"&gt;Nick Triggle&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-testid="byline-contributors-contributor-0-role-location" class="sc-573fa0e8-8 bIfajQ"&gt;Health correspondent&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 eRlINq"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="hero-image" class="sc-5340b511-1 cMIbKV"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20251210-151139-37baf2dfdd-web-2.36.1-1/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 gUePlo hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/a145/live/7c53aff0-e0e4-11f0-a8dc-93c15fe68710.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/a145/live/7c53aff0-e0e4-11f0-a8dc-93c15fe68710.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/a145/live/7c53aff0-e0e4-11f0-a8dc-93c15fe68710.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/a145/live/7c53aff0-e0e4-11f0-a8dc-93c15fe68710.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/a145/live/7c53aff0-e0e4-11f0-a8dc-93c15fe68710.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/a145/live/7c53aff0-e0e4-11f0-a8dc-93c15fe68710.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/a145/live/7c53aff0-e0e4-11f0-a8dc-93c15fe68710.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/a145/live/7c53aff0-e0e4-11f0-a8dc-93c15fe68710.jpg.webp" loading="eager" alt="Getty Images A female doctor wearing a stethoscope standing in a hospital " class="sc-5340b511-0 hLdNfA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 jVqbAn"&gt;Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The amount of flu circulating has started to fall in England, &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.gov.uk/government/statistics/national-flu-and-covid-19-surveillance-reports-2025-to-2026-season/national-flu-and-covid-19-surveillance-report-24-december-2025-week-52" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;latest data suggests&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The UK Health Security Agency (UKHSA) said it was encouraging news heading into Christmas, but warned the virus could always bounce back in the new year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The UKHSA uses a range of different measures to monitor flu rates, including sample testing in hospitals and in GP practices.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The latest data covers last week up to Sunday with the UKHSA concluding the virus was circulating "at medium levels".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Similar trends are being seen elsewhere in the UK. Public Health Scotland said it had seen two weeks of cases decreasing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The fall in England comes after the agency said last week that the spread was stabilising after several weeks of rises.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;This year's flu season started early, driven by a mutated strain of the virus, which prompted concern about the pressure that could be placed on hospitals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;NHS England data for the total number of people in hospital is not being published this week.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;But there are signs in UKHSA's sample testing that the numbers being admitted to hospital are beginning to fall, suggesting the projections of record numbers of patients ending up in hospital with the virus over the festive period will not be realised.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="embed-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 djqsWD"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Dr Jamie Lopez-Bernal, an infectious diseases expert at UKHSA, said it was "encouraging news".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;But he added: "The virus is still very much with us and everyone, especially those most vulnerable to winter bugs, needs to take care to protect themselves or help not to spread these viruses to others.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"This is particularly important over Christmas as families come together to celebrate. So if you have any cold or flu-like symptoms you should try to minimise contact with others."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;He said there were simple steps we can all take to protect one another when mixing indoors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"Washing hands regularly and ensuring indoor spaces are well ventilated helps, and we advise those who have symptoms and need to go out, to consider wearing a face covering in indoor public spaces. These simple measures can help make a difference to reduce the spread.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"Flu is always unpredictable, is still circulating and could bounce back even further in the new year as we have seen in past years," he warned. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BBC</author><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 15:01:56 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiWkFVX3lxTE05WmROMjFHR2hpQkkxV3lDaGZfNGczNXdzUzN6YTA0RFE1VU1mTHo5WFlRS0RPZWRBQklZZktqdHJHZk9nNmVTQW5qRGU4LTBkc09RMkZrMVBiZ9IBX0FVX3lxTE9scVZ0YzhZTmpaSU4zZG9USmotTENaYmZGNk9jX0tOWXlWRjdUMmZvQUtjRWVXMFppOExqb2lNTktOQjlydmlrOEI5XzJtMV9ua1g4bWh2RWNNa1N6ci1j</guid></item><item><title>官员警告波士顿地区可能接触麻疹- WCVB</title><link>https://www.wcvb.com/article/measles-boston-westborough-massachusetts-texas-visitor/69857705</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-content--body-inner"&gt;
										&lt;div class="mobile"&gt;
													



																		&lt;div class="mobile"&gt;
							

&lt;section class="article-headline"&gt;
	
			&lt;p class="article-headline--title"&gt;Health officials warn about potential exposure to measles in Boston, Westborough&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;/section&gt;


							&lt;div class="article-branding"&gt;
						&lt;img data-src="https://kubrick.htvapps.com/htv-prod-media.s3.amazonaws.com/htv_default_image/site_branding/wcvb.png" class="lazyload lazyload-in-view branding" alt="WCVB logo"&gt;
								&lt;p class="article-headline--publish-date border-left"&gt;
			Updated: 11:17 AM EST Dec 24, 2025
		&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;a href="/article/hearst-television-news-policy-statements/14471973" class="editorial-standards border-left"&gt;Editorial Standards &lt;span class="info-icon"&gt;ⓘ&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;

							

&lt;p class="article-authors"&gt;
		&lt;/p&gt;


						&lt;/div&gt;
					&lt;/div&gt;
	
						
					&lt;p class="article-content--body-teaser"&gt;
						
					&lt;/p&gt;
	
					&lt;p class="article-content--body-text-raw"&gt;
						Massachusetts health officials issued a warning Wednesday about possible exposure to measles in locations visited by an infected tourist earlier this month. According to the Department of Public Health, a visitor from Texas arrived in the area on Dec. 11 on Airlines flight 2384, and departed on JetBlue flight 117 on Dec. 12. Potential exposures to the infected traveler may have occurred at:Logan Airport Terminal B, Boston, MA, 2:30 p.m.-4:45 p.m., Thursday, Dec. 11DoubleTree by Hilton Hotel Boston-Westborough, Westborough, MA, between 3:30 p.m., Thursday, Dec. 11, and 9 p.m., Friday, Dec. 12Logan Airport Terminal C, Boston, MA, 6 p.m.-11:30 p.m., Friday, Dec. 12Anyone who may have been exposed and begins to develop symptoms is advised to  call their healthcare provider before visiting an office, clinic, or emergency department."Measles is very contagious," DPH officials wrote in a statement. "However, the risk to most people in Massachusetts is low because the vaccination rate in the state is high. People who are not immune and visited any of the locations on the following dates and times may be at risk for developing measles."Video below: Expert 'On the Record' about vaccinesEarly symptoms may occur from one to three weeks after exposure and may resemble a cold. A skin rash follows a few days later. "This case is a reminder that everyone should be vaccinated against measles to protect themselves and others from this highly infectious disease. With multiple measles outbreaks across the country and increased travel around the holidays, now is an important time to ensure that you and your family are protected. Two doses of MMR vaccine are 97% effective at preventing measles and provides protection against mumps and rubella infection," said Dr. Bisola Ojikutu, Commissioner of Public Health for the City of Boston.
					&lt;/p&gt;
	
					&lt;div class="article-content--body-text"&gt;
						&lt;strong class="dateline"&gt;BOSTON —&lt;/strong&gt; 													&lt;p&gt;Massachusetts health officials issued a warning Wednesday about possible exposure to measles in locations visited by an infected tourist earlier this month. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to the Department of Public Health, a visitor from Texas arrived in the area on Dec. 11 on Airlines flight 2384, and departed on JetBlue flight 117 on Dec. 12. Potential exposures to the infected traveler may have occurred at:&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Logan Airport Terminal B, Boston, MA, 2:30 p.m.-4:45 p.m., Thursday, Dec. 11&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;DoubleTree by Hilton Hotel Boston-Westborough, Westborough, MA, between 3:30 p.m., Thursday, Dec. 11, and 9 p.m., Friday, Dec. 12&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Logan Airport Terminal C, Boston, MA, 6 p.m.-11:30 p.m., Friday, Dec. 12&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Anyone who may have been exposed and begins to develop symptoms is advised to  call their healthcare provider before visiting an office, clinic, or emergency department.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Measles is very contagious," DPH officials wrote in a statement. "However, the risk to most people in Massachusetts is low because the vaccination rate in the state is high. People who are not immune and visited any of the locations on the following dates and times may be at risk for developing measles."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Video below: Expert 'On the Record' about vaccines&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p id="cream-inline-rec" class="cream-inline hidden"&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Early symptoms may occur from one to three weeks after exposure and may resemble a cold. A skin rash follows a few days later. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"This case is a reminder that everyone should be vaccinated against measles to protect themselves and others from this highly infectious disease. With multiple measles outbreaks across the country and increased travel around the holidays, now is an important time to ensure that you and your family are protected. Two doses of MMR vaccine are 97% effective at preventing measles and provides protection against mumps and rubella infection," said Dr. Bisola Ojikutu, Commissioner of Public Health for the City of Boston.&lt;/p&gt;

							
											&lt;/div&gt;
	
	
						
						
														&lt;/div&gt;
	
																&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>WCVB</author><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilwFBVV95cUxNMW1IWEFDTU5xZE9QSGo3NEJhX2dYN09zUUMyUzNHdzFjbWIwVko4NWJZRGZINV9jZzA2eVRUcW1hdkVrbUhUcUFzTmtWWS1HMkVLaXUxakRiWDBfMko0WGpSUGxDWmZ0bHd6Ti1SV3ZsZXZqRTZzQWlKSF9HYWxRYnFTZEh5Z0pXTFdHU3pWcUpKYk94NWtz</guid></item><item><title>马萨诸塞州卫生官员警告可能在多个地点接触麻疹- NBC波士顿</title><link>https://www.nbcboston.com/news/local/measles-in-massachusetts-health-officials-warn-of-possible-exposure-in-boston-westborough/3867121/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-content rich-text"&gt;
									
					
&lt;p&gt;Health officials are issuing a warning about possible &lt;a href="https://www.mass.gov/info-details/measles"&gt;measles&lt;/a&gt; exposure in multiple locations in Massachusetts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The state Department of Public Health announced Wednesday that an out-of-state visitor who spent time in Boston and Westborough earlier this month was diagnosed with measles and visited multiple locations which could have resulted in other people being exposed to the virus.&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Health officials said the visitor arrived on Dec. 11 at 2:39 p.m. at Boston Logan International Airport on American Airlines flight 2384 from Dallas-Fort Worth, Texas. The visitor stayed at the DoubleTree by Hilton Hotel Boston-Westborough in Westborough and departed the state on Dec. 12 from Logan Airport at 9:19 p.m. on JetBlue flight 117 to Las Vegas, Nevada.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The state is now working with the U.S. Centers for Disease Control and Prevention and local partners to identify and notify anyone who might have been exposed to measles from this person.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Measles is a highly contagious, airborne disease, which has increased significantly in the United States because of the unfortunate decrease in vaccination rates. It is also a preventable disease,” said Robbie Goldstein, the state's public health commissioner. “This current situation serves as an important reminder of the critical role vaccination plays in protecting our communities. While Massachusetts has not had a measles case this year, 2025 saw the highest number of nationwide cases in more than a decade – nearly 2,000 in 44 jurisdictions, and sadly, three deaths. Fifteen years ago, measles had been considered eliminated in the United States, but that tremendous progress is at risk."&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Measles is very contagious. However, the risk to most people in Massachusetts is low because the vaccination rate in the state is high. People who are not immune and visited any of the locations on the following dates and times may be at risk for developing measles:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul class="wp-block-list"&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Logan Airport Terminal B, Boston, 2:30-4:45 p.m., on Thursday, Dec. 11&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;DoubleTree by Hilton Hotel Boston-Westborough, Westborough, between 3:30 p.m. on Thursday, Dec. 11 and 9 p.m. on Friday, Dec. 12&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;Logan Airport Terminal C, Boston, 6-11:30 p.m., on Friday Dec. 12&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Those who could have been exposed and begin to develop symptoms of measles should call their healthcare provider before visiting an office, clinic, or emergency department. Visiting a healthcare facility may put others at risk and should be avoided if possible. Anyone who has had measles in the past or has received two doses of the Measles, Mumps, and Rubella (MMR) vaccine is unlikely to develop measles even if exposed.&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;div class="recirc-module"&gt;
			&lt;h3 class="recirc__heading"&gt;Local&lt;/h3&gt;
			&lt;p class="recirc__subheading"&gt;In-depth news coverage of the Greater Boston and New England area.&lt;/p&gt;
											
											
					&lt;/div&gt;
	
&lt;p&gt;Early symptoms of measles occur seven to 21 days after exposure and may resemble a cold, with fever, cough, runny nose, and red eyes. A rash occurs on the skin two to four days after the initial symptoms develop. The rash usually appears first on the head and then moves downward. It typically lasts a few days and then disappears in the same order. People with measles could be contagious up to four days before the rash appears and for four days after the rash appears.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“This case is a reminder that everyone should be vaccinated against measles to protect themselves and others from this highly infectious disease. With multiple measles outbreaks across the country and increased travel around the holidays, now is an important time to ensure that you and your family are protected,” said Dr. Bisola Ojikutu, Boston's commissioner of public health.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Health care providers who suspect they might have measles are urged to call the Department of Public Health at 617-983-6800 for recommendations and testing guidance. Providers in Boston should call the Boston Public Health Commission at 617-534-5611.&lt;/p&gt;

									&lt;/div&gt;
												&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>NBC Boston</author><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 14:33:43 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi0AFBVV95cUxNcmVoVV9oRENIbHg4dDVLU1JwNlVMM3Rqa0hKZUZlVEJsandRaHBkQUN2ZGhlMTJ3alBIbVB6cTY5RE1RcXBUUy1CSUl1SnFyYmF4OFJVb3VaZzVKam1Cc284TkpqTXBkenRnOGIyRTVEeTUwU093aEFjYV9XNGc1OW9rWHZIU05OSjY5VTFYUUZMYk1VbDdQalIwMTQxNWlLWU5Fdm84TzIySTFhMWhaRmZaMWtWSzJhM0R1TERZbEl5Y1llZWZhVElIREdsZnpi0gHYAUFVX3lxTE9tMnFTUlBYNnQ3NHFmOUVYX0Y0dG51MXVnMDdsSzR1YWtWaENLS1k0QjFSV2dNcEcyLWhkLUpYcGNRV1pRV0J1NGtTUEZnenFwNWVBTjBUbkZhQWJoTld1VnZrRklJZGF1N3NORmJlQ3lXX3pORWFyemxZcGhaR0VfNllHMFJlVDBpYThHeWN3OThCUEVaMzgzbTdPZjhPX2tfbHlSVWFBcDNqYmZmZ2NaRmwtQktIMFphaVF4TFZqYzd0X3g1RVZvb200R1dCU0dfVTNFYUNFVg</guid></item><item><title>根据营养师的说法，最好的早晨水合饮料- EatingWell</title><link>https://www.eatingwell.com/best-morning-drink-for-hydration-11869995</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-page_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-page mntl-block structured-content" data-sc-sticky-offset="90" data-sc-ad-label-height="24" data-sc-ad-track-spacing="100" data-sc-min-track-height="250" data-sc-max-track-height="600" data-sc-breakpoint="50em" data-sc-load-immediate="4" data-sc-content-positions="[1, 1250, 1550, 1950, 2350, 2750, 3150, 3550, 3950]" data-bind-scroll-on-start="true"&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-block_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-callout--summary mntl-sc-block-universal-callout--tips mntl-sc-block-universal-callout theme-summary callout--bordered" data-text="Key Points" data-tracking-id="mntl-sc-block-callout" data-tracking-container="true"&gt;
&lt;div class="mntl-sc-block-universal-callout__body"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Dietitians say the best way to start your day for hydration is with plain water. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Hydration supports cognitive function, digestion and many other essential bodily functions.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;To stay hydrated all day, sip water, eat hydrating foods and monitor your hydration status.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_2-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Hydration can feel confusing—between electrolyte drinks, wellness shots and trending morning beverages, it’s hard to know what actually helps. Mornings are an especially important time for hydration, since we naturally lose fluid overnight. It may not be flashy, but the best morning drink is still &lt;strong&gt;plain water.&lt;/strong&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_3-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_4-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Drinking water first thing in the a.m. helps &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/what-to-do-tonight-if-you-didnt-drink-enough-water-11755822" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;rehydrate your body&lt;/a&gt;, restore balance and set you up for a more energized, clear-headed day. In this article, we break down why water is so effective in the morning and share other &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/9-best-foods-to-help-you-stay-hydrated-11764621" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;dietitian-approved ways to stay hydrated&lt;/a&gt; all day.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_5-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-why-water-works-so-well-in-the-morning"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_6-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Why Water Works So Well in the Morning &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_7-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Helps Boost Cognitive Function &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_8-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Rehydrating first thing in the morning can help &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/things-to-do-at-breakfast-to-keep-your-brain-sharp-11803856" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;support clearer thinking&lt;/a&gt; and better mood throughout the day. &lt;a href="https://pennsylvanianutritionservices.com/about/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="2" rel="nofollow"&gt;Alexandria Hardy, RDN, LDN&lt;/a&gt;, explains, “rehydration aids in cellular and metabolic function, can benefit our cardiovascular system and boosts mood and cognitive performance.”&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="1"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Hardy cites research that shows that hydration status plays an important role in attention, memory and overall mental functioning.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="2"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_9-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_10-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; A recent pilot study found that older adults with better hydration levels scored higher on several cognitive tests, including those measuring memory, learning ability and processing speed.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="3"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_11-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_12-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;a href="https://kellyjonesnutrition.com/about/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1" rel="nofollow"&gt;Kelly Jones, M.S., RD, CSSD&lt;/a&gt;, adds how this aligns with findings from observational studies, which have linked low daily water intake with a higher chance of experiencing anxiety or depressive symptoms in both adults and adolescents.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="4"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;,&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="5"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_13-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_15-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_16-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Can Support Digestion &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_17-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Water &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/7889310/drinks-for-better-digestion/" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;supports the digestive system&lt;/a&gt; by enhancing stomach motility and nutrient breakdown.&lt;span data-cite="6" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Morning hydration may also help counter constipation by improving stool consistency and promoting smoother movement through the gastrointestinal tract.&lt;span data-cite="7" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_18-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_19-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Supports Essential Body Functions &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_20-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Water makes up about 60% of the body and is required for nearly every physiological function.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="8"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Here are some examples of functions in the body that water helps support:
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_21-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_22-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;li&gt;Breakdown and transport of nutrients, making them usable to your cells&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Delivery of oxygen to cells, allowing them to function efficiently&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Regulation of internal temperature, so your body can cool itself&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Keeping tissues—like your mouth, eyes and nasal passages—hydrated&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Cushioning and protecting vital organs&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Providing lubrication for joints to support comfortable movement.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_23-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_24-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Can Help Prevent Dehydration &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_25-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Even if you don’t feel thirsty, you may be slightly dehydrated after several hours without fluid. As Hardy, explains, “We typically wake up &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/8064290/how-to-tell-if-you-are-dehydrated/" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;mildly dehydrated&lt;/a&gt;, thanks to overnight respiration, perspiration and urine production.”&lt;span data-cite="9" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Drinking water shortly after waking helps replenish these losses and potentially &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/8015851/sneaky-reasons-you-wake-up-feeling-tired/" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;prevent symptoms of fatigue and sluggishness&lt;/a&gt;. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_26-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_27-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Jones adds, “After a night of sleep without food and fluid, plain water offers the body what it needs to rehydrate and support optimal energy levels and digestion.” 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_28-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_29-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Helps Set the Tone for Healthy Hydration Habits &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_30-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Starting your morning with water can help you stay hydrated throughout the day. Hardy notes that one study found that the first six hours after waking are the prime time that people hydrate. For this reason, she suggests &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/7988280/should-you-be-drinking-water-first-thing-in-the-morning/" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;drinking a glass of water early in the morning&lt;/a&gt;, ideally before reaching for coffee.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="9"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_31-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_32-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Jones chimes in, “Because total daily fluid needs are individualized based on body weight, activity level, climate and other factors, there’s no one-size-fits-all for morning fluid recommendations.”
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_33-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_34-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; As a rule of thumb, most women should aim for about 11.5 cups per day and most men about 15.5 cups per day.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="10"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Research on the ideal water temperature for hydration is still limited, but one small study found that cool water around 60°F may support comfortable intake and optimal hydration after dehydration.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="11"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_35-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_37-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-other-dietitian-approved-ways-to-stay-hydrated"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_38-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Other Dietitian-Approved Ways to Stay Hydrated &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_39-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Flavor your water: &lt;/strong&gt;If plain water isn’t appealing, try adding lemon, cucumber, mint or berries for a boost of flavor without added sugar.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Enjoy hydrating foods: &lt;/strong&gt;Many fruits and vegetables, such as watermelon, cucumbers, oranges and tomatoes, are composed of over 85% water. Pairing water-rich foods with fluids can help meet hydration needs while also adding essential vitamins and minerals.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Replenish electrolytes when needed: &lt;/strong&gt;During intense workouts, hot weather or illness, extra electrolytes such as sodium and magnesium can help restore balance.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Stack habits together: &lt;/strong&gt;Jones suggests “stacking water intake with the habits you already have. If that’s a morning cup of coffee, drink water while it’s brewing. If you have a midmorning or afternoon snack packed for work, pair it with water in a reusable bottle.”&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Make it appealing:&lt;/strong&gt; Making hydration visually appealing can encourage you to drink more. “Don’t underestimate the power of a cute glass. Some research shows that the shape and fullness of a cup can impact how much and how quickly we drink.”&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="12"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Hardy likes to fill a 40-ounce cup each morning to make steady sipping easier.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-sc-block-adslot-inline"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Monitor your hydration status: &lt;/strong&gt;Use simple cues like thirst and urine color to track your hydration. Pale yellow pee typically indicates adequate hydration.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_40-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_42-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-our-expert-take"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_43-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Our Expert Take &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_44-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; When it comes to starting your day hydrated, plain water wins. It’s accessible, inexpensive and consistently supported by research for promoting digestion, cognitive function and overall fluid balance. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_45-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_46-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Starting your day with a glass sets a strong foundation, but hydration doesn’t stop there. Steady sipping throughout the day, along with water-rich foods, helps keep fluid levels stable so you feel your best all day long.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>EatingWell</author><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 13:16:22 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMid0FVX3lxTFAxeDhKU0pHU0EzWFZCU2tDYzY3NmhXUWtZeXFYWXVMbzJxZHB2WWpWVWlVcmExQV83bGx2OElkVzJWaW9PU0pSdlRibnI3NVRON1E1VlY0aXVCQ2liQ19kMmwyckhaVTlrUnVNNFJWTDFJelExcjFB</guid></item><item><title>茶或咖啡对骨骼有益吗？ -《华盛顿邮报》</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/wellness/2025/12/24/tea-coffee-bones-osteoporosis/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="FYE4SUEE6ZGADAZEGNJFJ6UEIE" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Both &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/wellness/interactive/2022/coffee-vs-tea-nutrition-health/" target="_blank"&gt;tea and coffee&lt;/a&gt; have various health benefits, but tea may come out slightly on top when it comes to the health of your bones, a recent study suggests. And too much coffee — five or more cups a day — might have a negative effect on your bone health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 12:31:50 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiAFBVV95cUxOV1dUVWVUNmtrX1FHUXlBSFpsV090Vndyc2NwT1hDT1FkR1ppRXg3S0hWdUxZanpSWFFqMV9fOHktcmJJVjZDcS1KVVFUWEZDd2RaT1ZGRkpoZFNHQklDajdGbVNGWWRRaFE1OXIxa1NCREV6UkdrNXBMcHVIWGdfV21EWTQwRGY3</guid></item><item><title>询问Eric ：当朋友得知我们要去巡游，但她没有被邀请时，她可能会感到不安- NJ.com</title><link>https://www.nj.com/advice/2025/12/asking-eric-a-friend-will-likely-be-upset-when-she-learns-were-going-on-a-cruise-and-she-wasnt-invited.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content   "&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="M6B66VGX7VBUJDDOFF6J5ELAUM"&gt;DEAR ERIC: Three friends and I are planning an eight-day cruise in January.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-1" data-gaid="inarticle-1"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="JGH7PHIAZRB5BGKXJJ2TRQSL7A"&gt;Two other people found out about the trip and are now coming as well. We are fine with that but are not looking to make it a larger group and I am definitely not looking to turn into the “cruise director” for the group as often seems to happen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-2" data-gaid="inarticle-2"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="IHFFPISC6ZE4TJXU5VR47BTTHY"&gt;There is one friend that we feel is going to be very upset when she finds out about the cruise and feel personally excluded. And to be honest she kind of was.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-3" data-gaid="inarticle-3"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="ELXBV4V5M5CM5JS43IF62NZLCE"&gt;While we have been careful not to talk about the trip in general so as not to encourage other people to say they want to come along, we have very specifically not mentioned the trip to this person because she tends to be very negative and those of us going on the trip can really only take her in small doses.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-4" data-gaid="inarticle-4"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="ZWOFFFB4YRHJBBR2RWR3CJD3CI"&gt;Sad to say, none of us really want to spend what should be a fun vacation with her bringing us down. She doesn’t see this behavior in herself but everyone else does.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-5" data-gaid="inarticle-5"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="GIA6E77QXZB6LDV3C2TJG2QQD4"&gt;I’m torn whether to mention this trip to her in advance or let her find out about it on her own, most likely from social media. And if I let the information drop, I’m not sure how to do it. I know she’s going to be upset either way. Any advice?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-6" data-gaid="inarticle-6"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="2N7SJ2ZRMRE4HPNKAFC6C3UUSA"&gt;– Anxious Cruiser&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-7" class="middleParagraph" data-gaid="inarticle-7"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="7GHBGVEISZG35PC4PYUP75KM6M"&gt;DEAR CRUISER: I’d be inclined to suggest you say nothing if it weren’t for the sticky issue of the truth. It’s perfectly fine for a subset of a friend group to decide to do something that doesn’t necessarily involve the rest of the group. Bruised feelings might occur, but this isn’t in and of itself a betrayal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-8" data-gaid="inarticle-8"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="KXGFXU5PB5FYTIOA2NSWKQSIEY"&gt;But you’ve purposefully been trying to exclude this one friend, something that she might correctly infer should she find out about the trip through social media.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-9" data-gaid="inarticle-9"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="6YTGXEDSHJH3LOSCI5QHWJQQOM"&gt;This is your right, of course, but you have to own your choices. To that end, think about what you personally desire from this friendship. It won’t help you to speak for the group – and hearing “we all think this…” never feels great. But you have an individual connection to this friend that may or may not be damaged by the group’s decision. Let that connection guide your actions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-10" data-gaid="inarticle-10"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="6HW6VNI3KRHZFCPQQACIAJLTBA"&gt;&lt;i&gt;(Send questions to R. Eric Thomas at &lt;/i&gt;&lt;a href="mailto:eric@askingeric.com"&gt;&lt;i&gt;eric@askingeric.com&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;i&gt; or P.O. Box 22474, Philadelphia, PA 19110. Follow him on &lt;/i&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/oureric"&gt;&lt;i&gt;Instagram&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;i&gt; and sign up for his weekly newsletter at &lt;/i&gt;&lt;a href="https://rericthomas.com/"&gt;&lt;i&gt;rericthomas.com&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;i&gt;.)&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-11" data-gaid="inarticle-11"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="XN2DGTJBOFCFVE6VUBLR3DNMOI"&gt;&lt;i&gt;©2025 Tribune Content Agency, LLC.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-12" data-gaid="inarticle-12"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-enter:4DY3ITAUBFEG3HB364CI7CT2ZM" data-fusion-component="4DY3ITAUBFEG3HB364CI7CT2ZM"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-exit:4DY3ITAUBFEG3HB364CI7CT2ZM" data-fusion-component="4DY3ITAUBFEG3HB364CI7CT2ZM"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-13" data-gaid="inarticle-13"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>NJ.com</author><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi2AFBVV95cUxNU05JUFlWYlY3YXhyZHNtNjhXaWFsTXJtdDBLaWdweTRsT2ZVTnRjNnBCaWdyV0RTb1NEWGFfdHp6aVNUYjk0em9ONzhKWnVkM012UzFUSmIyZ1VzNmUwaWZNeURvbFlNTDV4UllCTmlTOTRKVU05WTZiR052c0oxcTFVeEEtUEdIQTUtN3Zqd0dWRktFMkZpM1UzOHJvSEZGd1JEb2d1UDZtZkQ3Y2hFUE1iQ21fSTdQYlZCcS1jSWJabWlCMHNOVkZaN0phUDRuQ0l0YlZRdGnSAewBQVVfeXFMTUVJYmh3U3pQOFM0RU1HMVNQakRKMEFvTjY5Nkk1TzdzbWRoTGdVTEdJTUpCaklSWnI4Z2VnSXJ2TzVkSW5fX1VuVUJFaFhzYUNQNVh4QVd1dHhfaGNSdXRyd0duc3NrVXpJOS1scjdkRndISFh1VGJqdjVyVHJOOGhnMGhjWmlVcy0xV0locjhSWHNSOHJIUjBZN2VuWW4tVXJsUmgtU0Iwa0FzZlZtV09HOFkydHJfWWltRnFKOWhBWUVLT00wdDlQMm5kUVBObkJxSWlZVV9LdlJmeURiTE1kdGdCa0taTS1EbG4</guid></item><item><title>炒鸡蛋与燕麦片：哪种早餐更适合您的血糖？ - EatingWell</title><link>https://www.eatingwell.com/scrambled-eggs-vs-oatmeal-for-better-blood-sugar-11875765</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-page_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-page mntl-block structured-content" data-sc-sticky-offset="90" data-sc-ad-label-height="24" data-sc-ad-track-spacing="100" data-sc-min-track-height="250" data-sc-max-track-height="600" data-sc-breakpoint="50em" data-sc-load-immediate="4" data-sc-content-positions="[1, 1250, 1550, 1950, 2350, 2750, 3150, 3550, 3950]" data-bind-scroll-on-start="true"&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-block_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-callout--summary mntl-sc-block-universal-callout--tips mntl-sc-block-universal-callout theme-summary callout--bordered" data-text="Key Points" data-tracking-id="mntl-sc-block-callout" data-tracking-container="true"&gt;
&lt;div class="mntl-sc-block-universal-callout__body"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Scrambled eggs are high in protein and will have little impact on blood sugar response. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Oatmeal contains fiber and your blood sugar response may depend on the type of oats you choose. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Both are healthy breakfast options; pairings and mix-ins will impact how your body responds. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_2-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; If you’re trying to keep your blood sugar steady, what you choose for breakfast matters and two of the most popular options couldn’t be more different. Here, we’re putting Team Savory and Team Sweet in a head-to-head breakfast showdown. In one corner: scrambled eggs, the savory protein-packed powerhouse. In the other: oatmeal, the classic sweet staple. Next, dietitians break down how scrambled eggs and oatmeal impact blood sugar and which one might be the better pick for you. &lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_3-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-how-scrambled-eggs-affect-blood-sugar"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_4-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; How Scrambled Eggs Affect Blood Sugar &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_5-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Let’s start by cracking open eggs to see what’s inside. One-half a cup of whole scrambled eggs contains 164 calories, 12 g fat, 1.7 g of carbohydrates, 0 g fiber and 11 g protein.&lt;span data-cite="1" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_6-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_7-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; “Since scrambled eggs have very little carbohydrate and are made up mostly of protein and fat, they have very little impact on blood sugar on their own,” explains &lt;a href="https://www.jackietopol.com/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Jackie Topol, MS, RD&lt;/a&gt;, specializing in pre-diabetes. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_8-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_9-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; What you cook with your eggs can make a difference. “Cooking eggs with butter or oil will increase the fat content, which can slow digestion and slow the rise in blood sugar further. Adding in vegetables, which contain fiber, will also help slow down how quickly blood sugar rises”, she adds. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_10-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_11-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; What you pair with your eggs matters too. Eating them alongside a few slices of bread, cereal or a bowl of fruit may cause your blood sugar to rise. However, the protein and fat in eggs still helps slow digestion while also creating less of a rise in blood sugar levels and keeps you satiated longer too, explains &lt;a href="https://www.amysnutritionkitchen.com/about/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1" rel="nofollow"&gt;Amy Kimberlain, MS, RDN, CDCES,&lt;/a&gt; a diabetes educator. Ultimately, we’re keeping eggs in the running in this breakfast showdown. &lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_12-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_14-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_16-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-how-oatmeal-affects-blood-sugar"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_17-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; How Oatmeal Affects Blood Sugar &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_18-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Warm, comforting and filling, a bowl of oats is a blank canvas for sweet and savory toppings. When peering inside the barrel of oats, one cup of cooked oats provides 182 calories, 6 g of fat, 27 g of carbs, 4 g of dietary fiber and 5 g of protein.&lt;span data-cite="2" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_19-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_20-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; “Oatmeal contains carbohydrates and will impact blood sugar levels when consumed.  Additionally, the type of oat, how it’s cooked and what you eat it with will impact how quickly it can raise your blood sugar,” explains Kimberlain. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_21-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_22-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Topol breaks down the different varieties of oats: “Steel-cut oats are the least processed, highest in fiber and slowest to digest. They generally have the most gentle impact on blood sugar. Rolled oats are moderately processed and a good source of fiber; they typically provide a moderate rise in blood sugar. Instant oats are made up of ground oats, which are quickest to cook and also to digest, which can lead to a faster, sharper rise in blood glucose.”&lt;span data-cite="3" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-cite="4" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_23-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_24-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; However, it's important to note that all types of oats contain soluble fiber, which helps slow digestion and leads to fewer blood sugar spikes. Both experts emphasize that the portion size of oats and whether any added sugars are present will determine how much a person’s blood sugar may rise. Adding high-protein toppings like Greek yogurt or nuts, or extra fiber like berries or chia seeds, can help further slow down digestion and prevent blood sugar spikes, says Kimberlain.&lt;span data-cite="5" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_25-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-eggs-vs-oatmeal-which-is-better-for-blood-sugar"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_26-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Eggs vs. Oatmeal: Which Is Better for Blood Sugar? &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_27-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; So, when comparing the two head-to-head, what is the final verdict? The answer is: it depends. “Though eggs on their own may produce the smallest increase in blood sugar, without the addition of carbs, most people will be hungry pretty soon,” says Topol. That means you’ll likely pair eggs with something else for more sustenance - like toast, potatoes, fruits, veggies or a cup of juice - all of which can affect blood sugar. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_28-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_29-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Oatmeal, on the other hand, if prepared with both protein and fiber (ie. Greek-style yogurt and berries) and without added sugar, can provide sustained energy and lessen the blood sugar response, she adds. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_30-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_31-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; The ultimate verdict:  Aim for a breakfast that is balanced with protein, fiber and healthy fats, says Topol. Kimberlain agrees, and wants readers to remember: "Everyone's blood sugar response is different. Pay attention to how &lt;em&gt;your&lt;/em&gt; body responds to different foods, not just eggs or oatmeal. Checking your blood sugar after meals can help you understand your own patterns and make choices that work best for you.”&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_32-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-how-to-build-a-blood-sugar-friendly-version-of-each-breakfast"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_33-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; How to Build a Blood-Sugar-Friendly Version of Each Breakfast &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_34-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Here’s a guide on how to build a blood-sugar-friendly version of each breakfast that includes fiber-rich carbs, high-quality protein, healthy fats and plenty of produce. &lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_35-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_36-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Scrambled Eggs &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_37-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; When you break out your skillet - don’t forget to also include these items:
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_38-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_39-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Add Veggies&lt;/strong&gt;: Saute any type of veggies with your scrambled eggs, such as dark leafy greens, onions, bell peppers, mushrooms, broccoli or cauliflower.  &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Add Healthy Fat&lt;/strong&gt;: Include a source of healthy fat like avocado slices, a sprinkle of hemp seeds or a handful of walnuts.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Add Whole Grains or Starchy Veggies:&lt;/strong&gt; Enjoy your eggs with a slice or two of whole wheat or sprouted bread, or build your own breakfast bowl by adding eggs to cooked grains such as farro or buckwheat or starchy veggies like a sweet potato or yam.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Add Fruit:&lt;/strong&gt; Enjoy eggs with a bowl of cut fruit or berries. &lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_40-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_42-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_43-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Oatmeal &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_44-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Dress up your blank canvas of oats with a plethora of toppings and mix-ins.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_45-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_46-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Make with Milk: &lt;/strong&gt;Make oats with dairy or soy milk, as it will naturally increase the protein and add other nutrients like calcium and vitamin D to the mix. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Add Protein: &lt;/strong&gt;Mix in Greek-style yogurt or cottage cheese for more protein and to dial up the creaminess. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Add Nuts or Seeds: &lt;/strong&gt;Sprinkle or stir in seeds like chia, flax or hemp for omega-3 fats, fiber and protein. Or add nuts like walnuts or pistachios or drizzle on some almond or peanut butter.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Add Fruits: &lt;/strong&gt;Sweeten up your oats naturally by topping them with, or stirring in, any type of fruit. Kimberlain recommends raspberries or blackberries, which have the highest fiber and lowest sugar among fruits. &lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Make Savory Oats&lt;/strong&gt;: Whip up a batch of savory oats by topping it with eggs and veggies. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Choose Steel-Cut or Rolled Oats: &lt;/strong&gt;Topol recommends choosing steel-cut or rolled oats as your best option for the least blood sugar spiking oatmeal option.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_47-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_49-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-our-expert-take"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_50-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Our Expert Take &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_51-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; While there wasn’t a clear winner in our scrambled eggs versus oatmeal blood sugar showdown, our experts agree that the better breakfast depends on several factors. For eggs, what you cook them with and what you eat them alongside can influence blood sugar. For oats, the portion size, type of oats and mix-ins play a role. To build a blood-sugar-friendly breakfast bowl, dietitians recommend including a balance of protein, fruits, veggies, healthy fats and whole grains to each plate. 
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>EatingWell</author><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijAFBVV95cUxNUUdqM25neU1TeS1WOGZKZTdWMVpneHNSakxXVER1X2JENkYyVmRacm5keld1d1AxcUQ3ZWNULTRlcHA5RFpjam5HaGJmbGlaRGRIaUtvSi1oeTdpSDRoUDd1UE83b1ZRVGNZMzNETTM1ZnhXdlhUNTdhdVNhdG1kQy1iTmZObUJtVlV4VA</guid></item><item><title>多动症是“超级大国”吗？一项新研究对这种疾病的隐藏优势的看法-女性健康</title><link>https://www.womenshealthmag.com/health/a69811174/adhd-superpower-strengths-study/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div data-journey-body="standard-article" class="article-body-content article-body standard-body-content css-n3hm4j et2g3wt7"&gt;&lt;ul data-node-id="0" class="css-kw9lqy emevuu60"&gt;&lt;li data-node-id="0.0"&gt;&lt;em data-node-id="0.0.0"&gt;In a recent study, people with ADHD were more likely to strongly identify with 10 character strengths, including creativity and intuitiveness, over those without the condition.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-node-id="0.1"&gt;&lt;em data-node-id="0.1.0"&gt;People with ADHD were just as likely as those without the condition to recognize and apply those strengths in everyday life.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-node-id="0.2"&gt;&lt;em data-node-id="0.2.0"&gt;Researchers hope the findings will help people understand the strengths associated with ADHD.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;hr data-node-id="1" class="css-18pb4rg emevuu60"&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="2" class="css-6wxqfj emevuu60"&gt;When you have a condition like &lt;a href="https://www.womenshealthmag.com/health/a61015577/adhd-in-elite-athletes/" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.womenshealthmag.com/health/a61015577/adhd-in-elite-athletes/" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="attention-deficit/hyperactivity disorder" data-node-id="2.1" class="body-link css-7bauu1 emevuu60"&gt;attention-deficit/hyperactivity disorder&lt;/a&gt;, it can be easy to focus on the downsides. But new research suggests that having ADHD comes with some upsides too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="3" class="css-6wxqfj emevuu60"&gt;The study, which was published in &lt;em data-node-id="3.1"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cambridge.org/core/journals/psychological-medicine/article/role-of-psychological-strengths-in-positive-life-outcomes-in-adults-with-adhd/69B7CE4D4D9F370214929ABF53701567" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.cambridge.org/core/journals/psychological-medicine/article/role-of-psychological-strengths-in-positive-life-outcomes-in-adults-with-adhd/69B7CE4D4D9F370214929ABF53701567" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="Psychological Medicine" data-node-id="3.1.0" class="body-link css-7bauu1 emevuu60"&gt;Psychological Medicine&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;, discovered that people with ADHD were more likely to highlight certain character traits than those without the condition—and they were equally as likely to apply those strengths in their lives. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="4" class="css-6wxqfj emevuu60"&gt;The findings offer a more balanced way to think about an ADHD diagnosis. Here’s what the study found, and the key takeaways.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="6" class="body-tip css-mtq1aa emevuu60"&gt;&lt;strong data-node-id="6.0"&gt;Meet the experts&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;a href="https://www.radboudumc.nl/en/people/martine-hoogman" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.radboudumc.nl/en/people/martine-hoogman" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="Martine Hoogman, PhD" data-node-id="6.2" class="body-link css-7bauu1 emevuu60"&gt;Martine Hoogman, PhD&lt;/a&gt;, is the senior study author and assistant professor at Radboud University. Hillary Ammon, PsyD, is a clinical psychologist at the &lt;a href="https://cawewtherapy.com/" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-node-id="6.4" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://cawewtherapy.com/" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="Center for Anxiety &amp;amp; Women's Emotional Wellness" class="body-link css-7bauu1 emevuu60"&gt;Center for Anxiety &amp;amp; Women's Emotional Wellness&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;a href="https://researchportal.bath.ac.uk/en/persons/luca-hargitai/" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://researchportal.bath.ac.uk/en/persons/luca-hargitai/" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="Luca D Hargitai" data-node-id="6.6" class="body-link css-7bauu1 emevuu60"&gt;Luca D Hargitai&lt;/a&gt;, is the study co-author and post-graduate researcher at University of Bath.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="what-did-the-study-find" data-node-id="7" class="body-h2 css-1q3hln2 emevuu60"&gt;&lt;strong data-node-id="7.0"&gt;What did the study find?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="8" class="css-6wxqfj emevuu60"&gt;For the study, researchers asked 200 adults with ADHD and 200 adults without ADHD to examine how strongly they identify with 25 positive characteristics, like humor, creativity, and spontaneity. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="9" class="css-6wxqfj emevuu60"&gt;People with ADHD were more likely to strongly endorse 10 strengths they had over those without the condition. Those included:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-node-id="10" class="css-kw9lqy emevuu60"&gt;&lt;li data-node-id="10.0"&gt;       Hyperfocus (the ability to deeply concentrate on things that interested them)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-node-id="10.1"&gt;       Humor&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-node-id="10.2"&gt;       Creativity&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-node-id="10.3"&gt;       Spontaneity&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-node-id="10.4"&gt;       Intuitiveness&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="11" class="css-6wxqfj emevuu60"&gt;While having ADHD comes with potential challenges, the researchers discovered that people with the condition were just as likely as those without ADHD to recognize and apply their strengths in everyday life. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="12" class="css-6wxqfj emevuu60"&gt;“People with ADHD asked me to dive into this topic as a scientist,” says &lt;a href="https://www.radboudumc.nl/en/people/martine-hoogman" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.radboudumc.nl/en/people/martine-hoogman" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="Martine Hoogman, PhD" data-node-id="12.1" class="body-link css-7bauu1 emevuu60"&gt;Martine Hoogman, PhD&lt;/a&gt;, senior study author and assistant professor at Radboud University. “There are many claims about positive aspects, strengths—superpowers?—of ADHD on the web, but the scientific base is thin.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="13" class="css-6wxqfj emevuu60"&gt;There’s a growing push to look at the positive sides of ADHD, adds &lt;a href="https://researchportal.bath.ac.uk/en/persons/luca-hargitai/" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://researchportal.bath.ac.uk/en/persons/luca-hargitai/" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="Luca D Hargitai" data-node-id="13.1" class="body-link css-7bauu1 emevuu60"&gt;Luca D Hargitai&lt;/a&gt;, study co-author and post-graduate researcher at University of Bath. “People are recognizing that, while this neurodevelopmental condition is associated with difficulties in various domains, there may also be strengths associated with ADHD,” she says. “Much of the research in this area has focused on creativity and divergent thinking.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="why-does-this-matter" data-node-id="14" class="body-h2 css-1q3hln2 emevuu60"&gt;&lt;strong data-node-id="14.0"&gt;Why does this matter?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="15" class="css-6wxqfj emevuu60"&gt;This can help people with ADHD look at their diagnosis in a different way, says Hillary Ammon, PsyD, a clinical psychologist at the &lt;a href="https://cawewtherapy.com/" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-node-id="15.1" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://cawewtherapy.com/" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="Center for Anxiety &amp;amp; Women's Emotional Wellness" class="body-link css-7bauu1 emevuu60"&gt;Center for Anxiety &amp;amp; Women's Emotional Wellness&lt;/a&gt;. “For years, children and adults with ADHD were often encouraged to fit into a neurotypical ‘mold’ in school and in work settings,” she says. “As such, it likely worsened symptoms of depression or anxiety, as the ADHD brain is not wired the same way—it has different strengths and limitations.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="16" class="css-6wxqfj emevuu60"&gt;But the findings suggest that adults with ADHD who are aware of their strengths and actually use them have higher confidence and quality of life as a result, Ammon says. “This is novel and important research as clinicians working with children, teens, and adults with ADHD can start to increase the focus on the individuals’ strengths, some of which may be unique to individuals with ADHD, as opposed to only exploring how to compensate for their deficits associated with ADHD,” she says. “By doing so, I suspect this will aid in improving confidence in individuals with ADHD.”   &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="what-should-people-take-away-from-this" data-node-id="18" class="body-h2 css-1q3hln2 emevuu60"&gt;&lt;strong data-node-id="18.0"&gt;What should people take away from this?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="19" class="css-6wxqfj emevuu60"&gt;Hoogman says she hopes the findings will help people understand the strengths associated with ADHD. “My other studies show that adults with ADHD frequently, in addition to their deficits, also experience benefits from their ADHD characteristics,” she says. “If we take a more balanced approach towards ADHD, acknowledging challenges and benefits, this may lead to increased well-being for people with ADHD and lowering stigma related to ADHD in our society.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-journey-blur="partial" data-ad-exclude="true" class="css-19m4yzp e1jy25xv0"&gt;&lt;div class="css-sfzxfp ev8dhu59"&gt;&lt;span class="css-3mrz81 ev8dhu51"&gt;&lt;img src="https://hips.hearstapps.com/rover/profile_photos/ea27d1a6-ecd9-4da8-b2a7-049a03b4ab93_1528214135.file?fill=1:1&amp;amp;resize=120:*" alt="Headshot of Korin Miller" title="Headshot of Korin Miller" decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="css-o0wq4v ev8dhu53"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="css-1dsojn8 ev8dhu55"&gt;&lt;p class="css-1y37fga ev8dhu54"&gt;Korin Miller is a freelance writer specializing in general wellness, sexual health and relationships, and lifestyle trends, with work appearing in Men’s Health, Women’s Health, Self, Glamour, and more. She has a master’s degree from American University, lives by the beach, and hopes to own a teacup pig and taco truck one day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-ad-exclude="true" id="journey-inline" class="css-ciejky e1ye6jr30"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Women's Health</author><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiAFBVV95cUxObl84X2dVenRqY01vcHQyczMzYTlaamh1REZvMnRYaHZRbGZXZmhzaVRic0RyS0QyaGJXSXlWMWtiMXR4bjMwZXNNNEFxcmZ2eHhiMXhneGU0NHVNZndDR3lDRk95WFlBeWVqYUtEUms2ekg1RENjRk5uS2dJa3hWMlJiNUZ4N0Yx</guid></item><item><title>我女儿的朋友对我丈夫有好感。这让我们俩都非常不舒服。-石板</title><link>https://slate.com/advice/2025/12/parenting-advice-teenage-crush-husband.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article__content" itemprop="mainEntityOfPage"&gt;
          &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="16" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmigc3vzj000gqnkw5gcbt1iy@published"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Care and Feeding is Slate’s parenting advice column. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Have a question for Care and Feeding? &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://forms.gle/4BXEw8Wtcd7aAyXh9"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Submit it here&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="4" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmigc3vzj000hqnkwa93ze7lr@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dear Care and Feeding,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="72" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmiggpw0v001k3b788k2u0gvq@published"&gt;Our daughter and her friends are 16. One of her friends, “Callie,” has an innocent but obvious crush on my husband, “Josh.” Callie does a lot of clumsy teen flirting and he either ignores it or shuts it down politely. If she’s around, he makes himself scarce. Our daughter teases Callie about it and tells her it’s weird, but it hasn’t stopped. And there’s a particular reason that Josh is so uncomfortable.&lt;/p&gt;

    


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="50" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjei8htr001q3b7aa3o00t9m@published"&gt;He was abused by a trusted adult as a kid, and so he’s extra sensitive to stuff like this involving adults and children. Right now our approach is that I do all the supervising the girls, including carpool drives, pickups, and dropoffs, when Callie is involved, and Josh steers clear.&lt;/p&gt;

  

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="137" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjef213w000k3b7aa3tmge07@published"&gt;Josh came to me and told me it freaks him out so much he’s getting on a waitlist to go back to therapy to deal with flashbacks from his childhood. He’s worried about just the appearance of inappropriate behavior if she’s flirting with him. Josh begged me to help him deal with this situation. He suggested she not be allowed at our house anymore, and he wants to skip our daughter’s games for the rest of the season since Callie is also on the team. He suggested we talk to her parents. He suggested I (!!) talk to Callie about romantic safety and the risks to minors. This all seems like overkill, but maybe I’m just not taking this seriously enough? I want to keep everyone in this situation safe and well, but not go too far.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="2" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjef2160000l3b7a7qoate21@published"&gt;—Too Cautious?&lt;/p&gt;

  


  


  


  


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="2" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjef218j000m3b7avgq60ziv@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dear Too,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="196" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjef21al000n3b7ae2dzhftx@published"&gt;It may seem like “overkill,” but Callie’s behavior is triggering to your husband and it makes sense that he’s willing to do whatever it takes to avoid her. I would start with talking to her parents; while a talk from you could be helpful, it would be more appropriate for her own folks to have that discussion with her. For most teens, the humiliation of having her crush (and her behavior) shared with her parents should be enough to put a stop to her flirting. If she persists, then it would be fair to stop allowing her to come to the house; it’s not ideal for your husband to miss your daughter’s games, but if he needs to, try and be understanding—this situation has brought him back to one of the most traumatic times in his life. If you end up having to take one of these measures, you should talk to your daughter about what her dad experienced (he can decide how much he’d like to share) and the importance of behaving appropriately with adults. However, I suspect that Callie will get it together once her parents are made aware of how she’s been acting.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="1" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmigc3vzj000oqnkw6iercrzy@published"&gt;&lt;span class="slate-paragraph--tombstone"&gt;—Jamilah&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;h3 class="subhead subhead--none" data-uri="slate.com/_components/subhead/instances/cmigc3vzj000pqnkwbsk85c79@published"&gt;
&lt;p class="subhead__marker"&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
Classic Prudie

&lt;/h3&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="91" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmigc3vzj000qqnkw9ohkpdor@published"&gt;We have a vacation place in a popular tourist area. It’s pretty rural, there’s no cell coverage, and we had to go through a lot of engineering and effort to get ourselves workable internet service. My wife and I are both pretty strongly averse to social media. We’ve therefore blocked all the major social media services at our homes. We often invite friends to come stay with us—and we give a heads-up that there’s no Facebook et al. available. Some guests have seemed put out by this. &lt;a href="https://slate.com/life/2018/01/dear-prudence-we-block-access-to-social-media-in-our-vacation-home.html"&gt;Is it so unreasonable?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;section class="newsletter-signup   " data-list="Advice" data-uri="slate.com/_components/newsletter-signup/instances/cmigc3vzj000sqnkwx0sk44z7@published"&gt;


    &lt;p class="newsletter-signup__intro"&gt;
        &lt;svg class="newsletter-signup__arrow"&gt;
          &lt;use xlink:href="/media/components/newsletter-signup/sprite.svg#arrow"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;
        &lt;/svg&gt;
&lt;h1 class="newsletter-signup__headline"&gt;Never miss new Slate Advice columns&lt;/h1&gt;
      &lt;span class="newsletter-signup__description"&gt;Get the latest from Prudie and our columnists in your inbox each weekday, plus special bonus letters on Saturdays.&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;
    



&lt;/section&gt;

  

&lt;/div&gt;

      &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Slate</author><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiggFBVV95cUxQQlFwZzBnSXpGNlpFdEZad2NaWjNLMkdCMk9nRnppSklDNVdMdURkMjM3Z09jWXlOLUJmQW02OGdUWkxaSWdSRTY1Mzl5ZGtHTW9pQ3Exd0FOMVJWOThfY3B6UkxrQzZXWHpvczBuVXpiajN1VlNOaWIwdlppRXB5VWVB</guid></item><item><title>随着疫苗接种率下降，医生担心破伤风病例会上升- NBC新闻</title><link>https://www.nbcnews.com/health/kids-health/tetanus-cases-rise-vaccine-rates-down-dtap-children-shots-rcna244685</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body__content"&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-979779" class="body-graf"&gt;Doctors are worried about even a small uptick in the terrible infection, often called lockjaw. Symptoms, which can take &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/tetanus/hcp/clinical-overview/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;three to 21 days to appear&lt;/a&gt;, include muscle spasms that make it difficult to breathe. As the infection takes hold, a patient’s jaw clenches, forcing the face into what appears to be a wide smile, and the back muscles contort into a painful arch.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-6f7325" class="body-graf"&gt;“It looks terrible,” said Dr. Mobeen Rathore, chief of pediatric infectious diseases and immunology at the University of Florida College of Medicine-Jacksonville.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-5f8dc7" class="body-graf"&gt;Tetanus bacteria live in soil and manure. An infection can occur from a puncture wound, and the disease can persist through weeks of medical care.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-fae9cf" class="body-graf"&gt;Treatment can be arduous and costly. A 6-year-old &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/health/kids-health/unvaccinated-boy-almost-died-tetanus-hospital-bill-was-more-800-n981256" target="_blank"&gt;unvaccinated boy in Oregon&lt;/a&gt; racked up almost $1 million in medical bills after he contracted tetanus in 2019, according to a Centers for Disease Control and Prevention case report.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-eb11cd" class="body-graf"&gt;Rathore compared the cost of vaccines to the cost of intensive care.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-7f9aac" class="body-graf"&gt;“It’s not even pennies to dollars; it’s pennies to hundreds of thousands of dollars,” Rathore said. “It’s very expensive.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-74be7c" class="body-graf"&gt;When a 9-year-old unvaccinated patient came to Rathore with muscle spasm in Florida this year, he recognized the signs. He remembered the tetanus wards from his medical school days where patients were cared for in dark and silent isolation. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-fe29b0" class="body-graf"&gt;“The slightest noise would cause many of these patients to go into spasm,” Rathore said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-c55b43" class="body-graf"&gt;Tetanus spasms, which can also be triggered by light (known as “photophobia”), are extremely painful and can constrict the muscles around the airway.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-adb10b" class="body-graf"&gt;Amid the bright lights, loud noises and incessant beeping of the hospital’s intensive care unit, the options were limited for minimizing stimulation for Rathore's young patient. The 9-year-old was sedated, intubated and given tetanus immune globulin antibodies and the vaccine to reduce future risk of disease. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-7d45a0" class="body-graf"&gt;The child was hospitalized for 37 days.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-7013b7" class="body-graf"&gt;Dr. Matthew Davis, enterprise physician-in-chief and chief scientific officer at Nemours Children’s Health in Florida and Delaware, said that “it wasn’t until we had widespread vaccination that we saw a decline in cases of tetanus and thereby a reduction in the risk of mortality from it.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-9e939a" class="body-graf"&gt;John Johnson, a vaccination and epidemic response adviser at Doctors Without Borders, works in countries such as the Democratic Republic of the Congo (DRC) where tetanus remains a concern. Last year, there were 540 cases in the DRC, &lt;a href="https://immunizationdata.who.int/global/wiise-detail-page/tetanus-reported-cases-and-incidence?CODE=COD&amp;amp;DISEASE=TTETANUS&amp;amp;YEAR=" target="_blank"&gt;according to the World Health Organization&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-013172" class="body-graf"&gt;“It’s one of those things that’s so stupidly easy to prevent,” Johnson said. “If you see one case of tetanus in the U.S., it’s a shame. There’s no reason we should be seeing this disease anymore.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="anchor-93be9d" class="body-heading"&gt;'My jaw was completely locked shut'&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-db2b3f" class="body-graf"&gt;After the initial series in childhood, a booster dose is recommended every 10 years for adults, although many are unaware of the need. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-73689d" class="body-graf"&gt;Nikki Arellano, 42, hadn't had a tetanus shot since 2010 when she was injured while she was helping her friend set up for a wedding last month. An accident with a metal arch at the altar led to a minor cut on her leg. The following week, she found it difficult to chew during lunch at work because of pain in her jaw. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-8af84a" class="body-graf"&gt;Two days later, she couldn’t open her mouth.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-170eb8" class="body-graf"&gt;“My jaw was completely locked shut,” said Arellano, of Reno, Nevada. “I went to the ER, and they tried to give me a bunch of sedatives and pain medicine and muscle relaxers to get my jaw to open, and nothing was making it open.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-5a1d3d" class="body-graf"&gt;Arellano was diagnosed with tetanus and admitted to the hospital. She was connected to an intravenous pump so she could get antibiotics. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-9f7f34" class="body-graf"&gt;“Every time that it would run out, it was like a really, really loud beeping noise. When that started is when my muscle contractions would pop off,” she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-3b39f1" class="body-graf"&gt;Arellano said her spasms initially started in one arm, then progressed to both arms and then to full body spasms. “It would arch your back really bad, like, it was really, really painful muscle spasms.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-781b05" class="body-graf"&gt;Arellano began to have difficulty swallowing, prompting worries that her airway might become compromised. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-3c3539" class="body-graf"&gt;“It was very scary,” she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-09781e" class="body-graf"&gt;She was hospitalized for nearly a week and is still recovering.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="anchor-db35be" class="body-heading"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Heightened risk with climate change&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-a3a276" class="body-graf"&gt;Natural disasters such as hurricanes, tornadoes and floods are known risk factors for tetanus outbreaks. As people rummage through the wreckage, they are also likelier to be injured by loose nails or broken shards of glass.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-153105" class="body-graf"&gt;“As the Earth warms, there’s already a documented increase in the frequency, intensity and duration of many extreme weather and climate events,” said Kristie Ebi, an epidemiologist and professor of global health at the University of Washington who studies the health effects of climate change. “And as there are more flooding events, then fewer vaccinations for diseases like tetanus means that people would be at greater risk.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-15b0b6" class="body-graf"&gt;Some states that are at highest risk of significant natural disasters, including Florida, Texas and Kansas, are recording notable declines in tetanus vaccination, according to NBC News data. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>NBC News</author><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 10:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMisAFBVV95cUxQeDYwZHdfd0N6ZlFZdkI4QVJ2SEZESVo1U250Nl81QmdLVlV6YzBwM2xmWnBxNk9KaWcxWTg4V1RpbmlqZWF0OGRpV3RfRGxxNVBMTHBEaktpZzFzX1NEbE1xaXljNFR4Tng2T1p1SmRkRmRXWGx5TnBFT1RNSmZrbGoyeV9KTXcxN3A2WFJyVmZUemxuQUxiY3UtdjdkNmVIbjdueWZ1bkNaem5lYnJlU9IBVkFVX3lxTE1ZUHpsNXRJTHNVQXhOMUl0T1FpSGFMaThoLWJFbF92aGozWnA3a19VczFiRnBnSHhCNVV1am5IdlEzaGNJVXFWRmdTRDJtX2VDZThITlh3</guid></item><item><title>减肥药物结束了他们的性生活。它会反弹吗？ -《纽约时报》</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/12/24/well/weight-loss-drugs-ended-their-sex-life-could-it-bounce-back.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The New York Times</author><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 10:00:44 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipwFBVV95cUxOLTFncnVEUVFvZ0VJZ084ZHhLWVpOeWE1QWY0OTVSR3FkNDVJaFB2ZmhudVNQd1A5VTRKTkNEV2JvdG9NRkNEWDFwWEs3Nm9UOW5UWFZWOERxR19FdkRSNVp0TVNiTGVBaU9UNS0tMDV4TWRyX2dvdGNCTnRyVEhBSHZZYWNZaE5vMi1Gd3JBcm9BVTFaRnhjc0NfcmxQdllMOUNnNG05VQ</guid></item><item><title>是什么杀死了世界上最大的鳄鱼之一？对黑醋栗的尸检暗示了一个隐藏的杀手- IFLScience</title><link>https://www.iflscience.com/what-killed-one-of-the-worlds-biggest-crocs-a-necropsy-of-cassisus-suggests-a-hidden-killer-81983</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p data-pasted="true"&gt;Cassius the crocodile cheated death for more than a century until his wild life finally caught up with him last year in Australia. Now, experts dealing with his necroscopy have revealed what ultimately led to the giant's demise.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="piano-gate" id="piano-gate"&gt;&lt;p&gt;The 5.5-metre (nearly 18-foot) saltwater crocodile &lt;a href="https://www.iflscience.com/rip-cassius-worlds-largest-captive-crocodile-dies-at-approximately-110-years-old-76633" target="_blank"&gt;died in November 2024&lt;/a&gt; at the Marineland Melanesia wildlife park on Green Island off the coast of Cairns, where he had been housed for four decades. At the grand age of around 110-120, he was one of the &lt;a href="https://www.iflscience.com/at-123-years-old-henry-is-the-worlds-oldest-known-crocodile-and-hes-an-absolute-unit-76112" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;oldest known crocodiles&lt;/a&gt; in captivity. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Strangely enough, the world-famous reptile had been given the all-clear just a few weeks before his death by veterinarians, who noted he appeared "bright, alert and happy". Then, out of the blue, he passed away. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Speaking to &lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2025-12-12/world-record-crocodile-cassius-taxidermied-new-exhibit/106131178" target="_blank"&gt;ABC News&lt;/a&gt;, the Darwin-based Centre for Crocodile Research says its necropsy revealed that Cassius died of an infection related to an injury he had suffered in the wild more than 40 years ago.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The injury triggered an infection that became sealed inside a tough fibrous capsule, lying dormant for decades. Over time, that protective bubble broke down and eventually ruptured, allowing the infection to swarm through the crocodile’s body.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="trendmd-suggestions" data-pid-resource="RRUGNY3"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr Sally Isberg, Managing Director at the Centre for Crocodile Research, told the media outlet that while so-called fibriscesses are “well-documented” in crocodiles, Cassius’ case was extraordinary due to how long the infection was contained. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="piano-inline"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;With further snooping, the team concluded that the hidden infection may have been linked to an injury sustained in the 1980s when Cassius was struck by a boat propeller, resulting in the loss of his front left leg, part of his snout, and the end of his tail. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“What we didn't know was that the rib cage had also been damaged in that injury," said Dr Isberg.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The reason was that everything was perfectly healed — there were no signs of infection or recent scarring. Upon necropsy, his left rib was distended compared to his right one, so longer," she added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“This is a perfect example of the effect of old age — he was no longer able to continue that fibrous casing around that infection."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span contenteditable="false" draggable="true" class="fr-video fr-deletable fr-fvc fr-dvb fr-draggable"&gt;&lt;iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/-FTIeYNvQpQ?&amp;amp;wmode=opaque&amp;amp;rel=0" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="" class="fr-draggable"&gt;VIDEO&lt;span class="fr-mk"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="fr-mk"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="fr-mk"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="fr-mk"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="fr-mk"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="fr-mk"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="fr-mk"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="fr-mk"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="fr-mk"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="fr-mk"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="fr-mk"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="fr-mk"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="fr-mk"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="fr-mk"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="fr-mk"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cassius was captured in 1984 in the Finniss River near Darwin and transported by road and boat, eventually arriving at Marineland Melanesia in 1987. Owing to his size and power, he was named after Cassius Clay, the birth name of boxer Muhammad Ali.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He was recognized as the world’s largest captive crocodile for some time, according to &lt;a href="https://www.guinnessworldrecords.com/news/2023/8/largest-crocodile-cassius-went-from-terrifying-predator-to-dreamy-eyed-dad-756676" target="_blank"&gt;Guinness World Records&lt;/a&gt;, although the title was snatched by an &lt;a href="https://www.iflscience.com/at-62-meters-lolong-was-the-largest-crocodile-ever-recorded-and-captured-80905" target="_blank"&gt;even larger individual called Lolong&lt;/a&gt; in 2012. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But the legacy of Cassisu lives on. The taxidermied body of the Aussie beast (still missing its left leg and tail tip) has just arrived home to Marineland Melanesia, where it is now on display at a new exhibition.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>IFLScience</author><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 09:17:55 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiwgFBVV95cUxNaWkxWmJIcUVVeG41Yi1FSktvWGxNLUNTZWVnQlQteDJmUVVWcG1yU2hyOXYxYWdkQ042S0RHZmFuZ3piYTY5d2NGY3NCdzUxcWZiLXpHRVBXRVRTdlNQc0RIS0c5WElNRFQwZHhheTJvRzc1TlQweDYtVloyY2NoT2poU245bTlGVWVTMl90aWFVb1JzUVFqenpIWmg5Q0pwWVV4OGo2cmR2QkdEX0xrYmpoblJCS0xZWEdoS0l1YWFfUQ</guid></item><item><title>如果我感染HPV ，我是否更容易患宫颈癌？ -《独立报》</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/health-and-families/hpv-nhs-screening-b2890006.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="sc-jbiisr-0 gIQPHK sc-jbiisr-1" id="main"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="hydrate-root sc-10wlkbs-0" data-component="SupportNSCNative" data-loading="lazy" data-theme-name="base"&gt;&lt;aside class="sc-hez36s-0 dFpFuY"&gt;&lt;div class="sc-hez36s-1 iBibVd"&gt;&lt;h3 data-testid="support-nsc-title" class="sc-hez36s-2 jVZWGn"&gt;Your support helps us to tell the story&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;div class="sc-hez36s-8 juUDRT"&gt;&lt;div class="sc-hez36s-13 cqPbFA"&gt;&lt;div class="sc-aja53j-0 rAFIl sc-hez36s-16 jZSKtc"&gt;&lt;div class="sc-aja53j-6 PdmgT"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="dropdown-with-gradient-collapsed-content-container" class="sc-aja53j-5 eZqxmv"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div data-testid="dropdown-with-gradient-collapsed-content" class="sc-aja53j-4 tawua"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div data-testid="support-nsc-collapsed-content-tablet" class="sc-hez36s-7 gZmYS"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-1uza6dc-0 iCTyfe"&gt;From reproductive rights to climate change to Big Tech, The Independent is on the ground when the story is developing. Whether it's investigating the financials of Elon Musk's pro-Trump PAC or producing our latest documentary, 'The A Word', which shines a light on the American women fighting for reproductive rights, we know how important it is to parse out the facts from the messaging.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-1uza6dc-0 iCTyfe"&gt;At such a critical moment in US history, we need reporters on the ground. Your donation allows us to keep sending journalists to speak to both sides of the story.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-1uza6dc-0 iCTyfe"&gt;The Independent is trusted by Americans across the entire political spectrum. And unlike many other quality news outlets, we choose not to lock Americans out of our reporting and analysis with paywalls. We believe quality journalism should be available to everyone, paid for by those who can afford it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;strong class="sc-1uza6dc-1 cglitp"&gt;Your support makes all the difference.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;button class="sc-aja53j-1 keLMOw sc-aja53j-7 eMEmGu"&gt;&lt;span data-testid="dropdown-with-gradient-dropdown-tablet" class="sc-aja53j-3 dHXFkr"&gt;&lt;span data-action-type="Read more" class="sc-aja53j-2 dcYUYI"&gt;Read more&lt;/span&gt;&lt;svg class="sc-eaj12q-0 hUgQwJ sc-culv3z-0 eifaJK sc-a5wy94-0 hyKPon"&gt;&lt;use href="#ee6613da15642019"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Although most of us will be exposed human papillomavirus (HPV) at some point in our lives, it remains widely misunderstood.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Receiving a positive &lt;a href="/topic/hpv"&gt;HPV&lt;/a&gt; result can be worrying and confusing, yet the link between HPV and cervical cancer is more nuanced than many people realise.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We spoke to Miss Adeola Olaitan, consultant gynaecological oncologist at &lt;a rel="nofollow" target="_blank" href="https://www.hcahealthcare.co.uk/locations/hospitals/the-wellington-hospital"&gt;The Wellington Hospital&lt;/a&gt;, part of HCA Healthcare UK, who explained what HPV is, how it relates to cervical cancer and addressed some common myths around this topic.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="article-im-prompt"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What is HPV?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“HPV is a family of viruses that infect the skin and the mucosal tissue,” explains Olaitan. “There are different subtypes of HPV which are denoted by numbers.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="taboola-mid-article-thumbnails-ii" class="sc-looa6c-0 cPCVUJ"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You can get HPV from any skin-to-skin contact of the genital area, vaginal, anal or oral sex or through sharing sex toys, according to the &lt;a rel="nofollow" target="_blank" href="https://www.nhs.uk/conditions/human-papilloma-virus-hpv/"&gt;NHS website&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most of the time HPV does not cause any problems, highlights the gynaecological oncologist.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“In most cases, HPV is a transient, harmless condition, and most people clear it without even knowing that they had it,” says Olaitan. “It will usually clear naturally within two years.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What is the biggest misconception about HPV?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I think the biggest misconception about HPV is the stigma surrounding it,” says Olaitan. “Because it’s a sexually associated infection, people think it has connotations of promiscuity, which it doesn’t. You can have sex once and get HPV.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Which types of HPV can increase your risk of cervical cancer?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There are over 200 types of HPV, according to &lt;a rel="nofollow" target="_blank" href="https://eveappeal.org.uk/resource/hpv/"&gt;The Eve Appeal&lt;/a&gt;, and they are split into two groups: low-risk HPV and high-risk HPV.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Around 14 types of HPV are considered high risk for cervical cancer and two of these types (HPV 16 and HPV 18) cause about 70 out of 100 (70%) of all cervical cancer cases, according to &lt;a rel="nofollow" target="_blank" href="https://www.cancerresearchuk.org/about-cancer/cervical-cancer/risks-causes"&gt;Cancer Research UK&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“HPV 16 and HPV 18 can infect the cervix, and if the infection persists then they can increase the risk of cervical cancer,” explains Olaitan.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How can you find out if you have HPV?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“There are usually no symptoms of HPV, so if you don’t go to a cervical cancer screening, you won’t know you have it,” says Olaitan. “The knowledge of whether you have HPV or not is only important because it marks people out as having a greater risk of having abnormal cells, which if left undetected or untreated can increase the risk of cervical cancer.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Everyone with a cervix should be invited for screening by the &lt;a href="/topic/nhs"&gt;NHS&lt;/a&gt; every five years from the age 25 to 64, according to the &lt;a rel="nofollow" target="_blank" href="https://www.nhs.uk/tests-and-treatments/cervical-screening/what-is-cervical-screening/"&gt;NHS website&lt;/a&gt;. It also states that during the screening appointment, a small sample of cells is taken from your cervix and the sample is checked for high-risk HPV types that can cause changes to the cells of your cervix.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“If the initial screening finds high-risk HPV, a reflex cytology test would be conducted on the same sample to look for abnormal cells,” explains Olaitan. “If that finds no abnormal cells, you will be told to come back for a screening at a shorter interval. However, if abnormal cells are found you will be referred for a colposcopy to have a closer look at the cervix.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Can protect yourself against HPV?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The HPV vaccine is very effective at protecting people against HPV,” says Olaitan. “It’s typically given to children between the ages of 11 and 13 and is licensed to the age of 45, but it’s less effective the older you are.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“But you can have it even if you’ve been exposed to HPV or you have a current HPV infection, and it gives immunity that’s stronger and longer lasting than natural immunity alone. So, it’s still good to have it, but it’s better to have it when you’re young.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What are some symptoms of cervical cancer to look out for?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The most common symptoms of cervical cancer are bleeding after sex, bleeding in between periods, bleeding after the menopause, or an offensive, persistent vagina discharge,” highlights Olaitan. “Most of the time these symptoms are indicative of benign conditions, but it’s important that they’re not ignored and that you go and get them checked to exclude anything more serious going on.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="taboola-mid-article-thumbnails-iii" class="sc-looa6c-0 cPCVUJ"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What’s the most important thing people should know about HPV and cervical cancer?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Remember that cervical cancer is preventable, and people who go for regular screenings are unlikely to get cancer,” says Olaitan. “&lt;a href="/topic/screening"&gt;Screening&lt;/a&gt; and being vaccinated are two of the most important things you can do for your health.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Independent</author><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 09:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilwFBVV95cUxQT2RfMlZad0k0ejVuOVgyd2REanVRZ25wR0MwWmVJcm9MWW1EWTc4dlh5aEJQaGpMNVRpb0NsMVFHeXBnYklOUl9VdjQtZ2xZYlM1VG5nMHE2QlhSVnNobzUwM0VieWh4WTNZeGRtX25lZEZpOU1mZUQ5bThZdFRoSWpqbkxLNWU4NGdtMU5ER3RIcmotVThz</guid></item><item><title>询问Eric ：我们是否应该向消极的朋友坦白我们为什么不邀请她参加邮轮假期？ - OregonLive.com</title><link>https://www.oregonlive.com/advice/2025/12/asking-eric-do-we-owe-it-to-negative-friend-to-come-clean-about-why-we-didnt-invite-her-on-cruise-vacation.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content   "&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="CNI3I3G6MJG6RBRBMBUCZROQMQ"&gt;Dear Eric: Three friends and I are planning an eight-day cruise in January.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-1" data-gaid="inarticle-1"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="ARYGFESISNDALHRN4JBMV3UPLM"&gt;Two other people found out about the trip and are now coming as well. We are fine with that but are not looking to make it a larger group and I am definitely not looking to turn into the “cruise director” for the group as often seems to happen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-2" data-gaid="inarticle-2"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="HS722EYOERH3HN24CBEJB44YVA"&gt;There is one friend that we feel is going to be very upset when she finds out about the cruise and feel personally excluded. And to be honest she kind of was.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-3" data-gaid="inarticle-3"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="N7N2GZCHBRDW7KTS5ZL5A4OMBU"&gt;While we have been careful not to talk about the trip in general so as not to encourage other people to say they want to come along, we have very specifically not mentioned the trip to this person because she tends to be very negative and those of us going on the trip can really only take her in small doses.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-4" data-gaid="inarticle-4"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="DSS6UIUKMJHBNFCCG6TTAIRMLM"&gt;Sad to say, none of us really want to spend what should be a fun vacation with her bringing us down. She doesn’t see this behavior in herself but everyone else does.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-5" data-gaid="inarticle-5"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="XDBBFYYSNJHTPEYES4T6IUVLMI"&gt;I’m torn whether to mention this trip to her in advance or let her find out about it on her own, most likely from social media. And if I let the information drop, I’m not sure how to do it. I know she’s going to be upset either way. Any advice?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-6" class="middleParagraph" data-gaid="inarticle-6"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="NVNTGTED4RGPNJHE7LLCDCUIRU"&gt;– Anxious Cruiser&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-7" data-gaid="inarticle-7"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="ZTDXMCT5SNFTJCXFXGUK47GSFA"&gt;Dear Cruiser: I’d be inclined to suggest you say nothing if it weren’t for the sticky issue of the truth. It’s perfectly fine for a subset of a friend group to decide to do something that doesn’t necessarily involve the rest of the group. Bruised feelings might occur, but this isn’t in and of itself a betrayal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-8" data-gaid="inarticle-8"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="WQY42BG375APRLC3CIEHHQSNNU"&gt;But you’ve purposefully been trying to exclude this one friend, something that she might correctly infer should she find out about the trip through social media.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-9" data-gaid="inarticle-9"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="RFYZVSUBOFHOFFNRHDYHZTMP3Y"&gt;This is your right, of course, but you have to own your choices. To that end, think about what you personally desire from this friendship. It won’t help you to speak for the group – and hearing “we all think this…” never feels great. But you have an individual connection to this friend that may or may not be damaged by the group’s decision. Let that connection guide your actions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-10" data-gaid="inarticle-10"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-enter:ADCNGOTLAVGNHLEY2AEXIUJJY4" data-fusion-component="ADCNGOTLAVGNHLEY2AEXIUJJY4"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-exit:ADCNGOTLAVGNHLEY2AEXIUJJY4" data-fusion-component="ADCNGOTLAVGNHLEY2AEXIUJJY4"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-11" data-gaid="inarticle-11"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="5IHP6IFRNBEJZBVX5C7GIO562M"&gt;&lt;i&gt;Send questions to R. Eric Thomas at &lt;/i&gt;&lt;a href="mailto:eric@askingeric.com" rel="noopener noreferrer" title="mailto:eric@askingeric.com"&gt;&lt;i&gt;eric@askingeric.com&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;i&gt; or P.O. Box 22474, Philadelphia, PA 19110. Follow him on &lt;/i&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/oureric" rel="noopener noreferrer" title="https://www.instagram.com/oureric"&gt;&lt;i&gt;Instagram&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;i&gt; and sign up for his weekly newsletter at &lt;/i&gt;&lt;a href="https://rericthomas.com/" rel="noopener noreferrer" title="https://rericthomas.com/"&gt;&lt;i&gt;rericthomas.com&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;i&gt;.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-12" data-gaid="inarticle-12"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>OregonLive.com</author><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 08:04:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi6AFBVV95cUxQVi1oZHMydGxYdUxpLUctRnBUellWNXZyRE9rZDJQaDAzQ1lYbUMxUW9TUWVrdE1sSTF5ZFRpOFpUa042UkgwSlFsYUpZaXBWOGZkVlVObklBMEZvcDZFLUxTOVJuRGRaMVJyTUhhSmFaVlBUdGx4S1M4c2VvM0kycF82YVRqbE5zVW1nQVQycE9FOU00czVocTd5OVlqQ2U5S0kxeFZ3bEtNOVZZb244ZnJKZ0V4V2RhbWpoXzQ0X0pTQ0xIb2NweG8wSmJJcDR1RU5WOGtSaUE2QjA2dFRmSGxmMjk0c1V10gH8AUFVX3lxTE40R0UtanFaQUwyYVlMSmk2ZVUwYVVEbHJ6TXBDSnQ3QjdJclpXSTBHLVMyMjA2ZmY1ZTJPN0dVYUVKTEhZck5KcG9qcF8tM3FEZi0wMFZnT04tcE5BbV9zM1FQNnlocXJXNkhHbVFRRWJNamVWS2QtaFZkZVdRYUJJN0dRa0dSY3o4ZENNOGZjT3Z0YmpoVXlNMTl0MXR0eWFRT1M5OXQyZlJxWGFzdWR5TDhPemFiZjZWU0x4VnNhdTd1YmExTG9vVEZrUFFndF9POTV4S3UwQWFvMzRkamM2QTI4VFp2bHZPQzA4N0hXMWQwMm1pQUZUV0pWcg</guid></item><item><title>橙汁如何帮助支持心脏健康-今日医学新闻</title><link>https://www.medicalnewstoday.com/articles/orange-juice-could-help-support-heart-health</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div data-testid="tabbed-article-section" class="css-12va8w7"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;figure class="css-7j3c6j"&gt;&lt;span class="css-rwmw5v"&gt;&lt;span class="css-mjp0j9"&gt;&lt;picture class="css-16pk1is"&gt;&lt;source srcset="https://media.post.rvohealth.io/wp-content/uploads/sites/3/2025/12/sunlit-orange-juice-1296x728-header-1024x575.jpg 750w" media="(min-width: 1190px)"&gt;&lt;/source&gt;&lt;source srcset="https://media.post.rvohealth.io/wp-content/uploads/sites/3/2025/12/sunlit-orange-juice-1296x728-header-1024x575.jpg 750w" media="(min-width: 990px)"&gt;&lt;/source&gt;&lt;source srcset="https://media.post.rvohealth.io/wp-content/uploads/sites/3/2025/12/sunlit-orange-juice-1296x728-header-1024x575.jpg 879w" media="(min-width: 768px)"&gt;&lt;/source&gt;&lt;img loading="eager" src="https://media.post.rvohealth.io/wp-content/uploads/sites/3/2025/12/sunlit-orange-juice-1296x728-header-1024x575.jpg" alt="glass of orange juice" class="css-1jytyml"&gt;&lt;/picture&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;hl-share-overlay class="css-1mqo1cs"&gt;&lt;a class="icon-hl-pinterest css-11oz8gb" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer nofollow" data-event="Any Page|Image Pinterest Click|Icon Clicked" data-element-event="OPEN|CONTENTBLOCK|Any Page|Article Body|BUTTON|Image Widget Pinterest Click|" href="https://www.pinterest.com/pin/create/button/?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.medicalnewstoday.com%2Farticles%2Forange-juice-could-help-support-heart-health&amp;amp;media=https%3A%2F%2Fmedia.post.rvohealth.io%2Fwp-content%2Fuploads%2Fsites%2F3%2F2025%2F12%2Fsunlit-orange-juice-1296x728-header-1024x575.jpg&amp;amp;description=How%20orange%20juice%20could%20help%20support%20heart%20health" title="Share on Pinterest" data-pin-custom="true" data-share-url="https://media.post.rvohealth.io/wp-content/uploads/sites/3/2025/12/sunlit-orange-juice-1296x728-header-1024x575.jpg"&gt;&lt;span class="css-z1zfa"&gt;Share on Pinterest&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/hl-share-overlay&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;figcaption class="css-1nzy6lj css-whkgel"&gt;Orange juice could help keep your heart healthy, according to recent research. Image credit: Pepino de Mar studio/Stocksy&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Orange juice offers multiple benefits for heart health, according to a new study examining its impact on gene expression.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The study found that orange juice lowers blood pressure and systemic inflammation, and enhances fat metabolism.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This unique investigation into the physiological effects of orange juice offers a novel perspective on its potential value for heart health.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Orange juice delivers a full menu of good things for the heart, according to a new look at the popular beverage from a molecular point of view.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A recent study published in &lt;hl-trusted-source source="Wiley" rationale="Peer reviewed journal"&gt;&lt;a href="https://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/mnfr.70299" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;Molecular Nutrition &amp;amp; Food Research&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/hl-trusted-source&gt; found that orange juice broadly affected genes involved in physiological activity related to heart health, inhibiting unwanted processes and promoting beneficial ones.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;It did the same for inflammatory genes. Inflammation can lead to cardiac events by constricting and damaging blood vessels, as well as promoting the formation of dangerous plaque buildup.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;At the same time, orange juice upregulated – promoted – the activity of genes responsible for metabolizing fat, helping the body process and store it more efficiently.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study also found two body-type-dependent effects. Fat metabolism was particularly optimized by orange juice in people with overweight. People of normal weight saw a greater reduction in systemic inflammation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-testid="tabbed-article-section" class="css-1avyp1d"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study’s first author, &lt;a href="https://www.researchgate.net/profile/Layanne-Fraga" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;Layanne Nascimento Fraga&lt;/a&gt;, PhD, of the Food Research Center and School of Pharmaceutical Sciences, University of São Paulo in Brazil, explained the study’s novel perspective on orange juice to &lt;em&gt;Medical News Today&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;“What’s unique about our study,” said Nascimento Fraga, “is that we used the transcriptomic approach to evaluate the effects of orange juice on the entire metabolic system, allowing us to see how multiple pathways are modulated simultaneously.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;“We found that orange juice improves key cardiometabolic markers, including inflammation, oxidative stress, blood pressure, and lipid metabolism, showing that several mechanisms act together to produce its health benefits.”&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;After factoring for duplicates, the researchers found 1,705 differentially expressed genes affected by orange juice in this study, 98% of which were downregulated, according to Fraga.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="css-zya54r"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-testid="tabbed-article-section" class="css-1avyp1d"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://entirelynourished.com" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;Michelle Routhenstein&lt;/a&gt;, MS, RD, CDCES, CDN, a preventive cardiology dietitian at Entirely Nourished, who was not involved in this research, told &lt;em&gt;MNT&lt;/em&gt; that, prior to this study, “other &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC7987641/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;clinical trials&lt;/a&gt; and meta-analyses showed modest reductions in systolic and diastolic &lt;a href="https://www.medicalnewstoday.com/articles/327077" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;blood pressure&lt;/a&gt;, particularly in adults with pre- or stage 1 hypertension.“&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;“This is because orange juice, especially after meals, increases plasma hesperetin, which is a flavonoid that may improve endothelial function and microvascular reactivity,” Routhenstein explained.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.joinmidi.com/team/jayne-morgan" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;Jayne Morgan&lt;/a&gt;, MD, cardiologist and Vice President of Medical Affairs at Hello Heart, likewise not involved in this study, said that other foods hold promise for cardiovascular health, as well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Morgan advised that “anti-inflammatory spices and herbs — such as turmeric and garlic — chia, hemp seeds, beets, and beet juice” might also benefit from similar molecular investigations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;And &lt;a href="https://www.memorialcare.org/providers/cheng-han-chen" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;Cheng-Han Chen&lt;/a&gt;, MD, an interventional cardiologist and medical director of the Structural Heart Program at MemorialCare Saddleback Medical Center in Laguna Hills, CA, also not involved in this research, commented on the study’s investigative approach.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;“It’s interesting, but I’m more interested in how this connects to outcomes,” Chen told us.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;He expressed some doubt regarding the meaning of orange juice’s heart-health benefits when viewed from a molecular angle, since, “from a clinician’s perspective, it’s easy enough to measure blood pressure.“&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;“We can also measure lipids easily enough” in a clinical trial, he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-testid="tabbed-article-section" class="css-1avyp1d"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Everything in moderation, including orange juice,” Morgan advised people who may now feel tempted to up their orange juice intake.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;blockquote class="is-layout-flow wp-block-quote-is-layout-flow css-34gtoi"&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Orange juice likely has a U-shaped curve, wherein small–moderate amounts are likely helpful for improved endothelial function, decreased arterial stiffness, and mild-anti-inflammatory and antioxidant effects from the citrus flavonoid. And blood pressure health from the potassium. Most Americans are actually potassium-deficient, so orange juice is helpful.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;– Jayne Morgan, MD&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Morgan cautioned, however, that “larger amounts [of vitamin C] drive increased sugar loads and all of the risks inherent, such as insulin spikes, weight gain, and visceral fat, especially in perimenopausal and menopausal women.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I always recommend to my patients that they eat lots of fruit, including &lt;a href="https://www.medicalnewstoday.com/articles/272782" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;oranges&lt;/a&gt;, though I don’t say they should drink juices so much. When you extract juices, you leave behind things like fiber. Fiber helps even out the sudden release of sugar from juices,” Chen also advised.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I haven’t recommended orange juice specifically,” he added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Routhenstein suggested “further studying whole fruits, including the fiber-rich membranes and the white, spongy albedo, which is high in fiber and &lt;a href="https://www.medicalnewstoday.com/articles/flavanoids" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;flavonoids&lt;/a&gt;, could clarify how the fruit matrix influences bioavailability and gene responses compared with juice alone.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="css-zya54r"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-testid="tabbed-article-section" class="css-1avyp1d"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Many whole foods,” said Routhenstein, “provide similar multi-target cardiovascular support because they, too, deliver synergistic combinations of nutrients and bioactive compounds.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;“This would include &lt;a href="https://www.medicalnewstoday.com/articles/270272" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;chocolate&lt;/a&gt;,” noted Morgan, “as milk chocolate is actually the processed form of &lt;a href="https://www.medicalnewstoday.com/articles/dark-chocolate" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;dark chocolate&lt;/a&gt;.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;“&lt;a href="https://www.medicalnewstoday.com/articles/green-leafy-vegetables" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;Leafy greens&lt;/a&gt; supply nitrate, magnesium, and carotenoids that improve endothelial function and support healthy blood pressure,” added Routhenstein. “&lt;a href="https://www.medicalnewstoday.com/articles/what-are-legumes" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;Legumes&lt;/a&gt; provide viscous fiber, plant protein, potassium, and polyphenols that reduce &lt;a href="https://www.medicalnewstoday.com/articles/ldl-cholesterol" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;LDL cholesterol&lt;/a&gt;, stabilize blood sugar, and lower inflammation.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Foods high in &lt;a href="https://www.medicalnewstoday.com/articles/287212" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;potassium&lt;/a&gt;, said Morgan, “help keep your blood vessels and blood pressure healthy, such as oranges, bananas, spinach, beans, and potatoes.”&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Berries,” according to Routhenstein, “offer anthocyanins that enhance endothelial function and decrease oxidative stress, while nuts combine unsaturated fats, arginine, and polyphenols to improve lipid profiles and vascular tone.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Make plants the majority of your palate and use extra virgin olive oil, and foods rich in &lt;a href="https://www.medicalnewstoday.com/articles/325179" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;omega 3s&lt;/a&gt;,” said Morgan.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;She also recommended lean protein, especially in &lt;a href="https://www.medicalnewstoday.com/articles/perimenopause" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;perimenopause&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.medicalnewstoday.com/articles/317765" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;menopause&lt;/a&gt;, limiting both salt and alcohol, and avoiding canned soups, sauces, and deli meats when possible.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="css-zya54r"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Medical News Today</author><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 06:56:15 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijwFBVV95cUxORkRhcXoxZFdGeV9yQV9MVWJOTzMwOG85QVVrc0paTGZveFFHLVh4aVBUT0Y5c2tuU2xsajRuOHdxS1FVdGI5ZlEyMHdnVVBCRlVUX3JubndMTjN4RDI0dVZDN09adXpCVlY3aXJ4QXltVFRfOFhvMmI2V25RZ0hxM3RGQ00xNEpZY2dwN2RITQ</guid></item><item><title>专栏|询问Eric ：告诉朋友她没有被邀请参加团体旅行？还是让她知道？ -《华盛顿邮报》</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/advice/2025/12/24/asking-eric-cruise-excluding-friend/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="763I6PNCHVFMPEU53KTH3C7CB4" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dear Eric:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i&gt; Three friends and I are planning an eight-day cruise in January.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="WC5FGPYYCZBBRCVAIMKF3TPM3I" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;&lt;i&gt;Two other people found out about the trip and are now coming as well. We are fine with that but are not looking to make it a larger group and I am definitely not looking to turn into the “cruise director” for the group as often seems to happen.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 06:31:52 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijgFBVV95cUxOT3ZRc1RXTC1DZ0VJRUptdWVXMkFvamxOTFlYSHJOc1N5MXo3Qm03c1l0QlFpNUtEVmF5Zl9wSGJaSTdhUm1WZFlONkREX3g0cTB5MTlXbjRUWlVFNHRfb2NoSEFTdGtOZlIxSEdSdDlsSTg0alIzVEZWaldEbUNpdUpfb1hmM051cWR6Qm53</guid></item><item><title>以前未知的脑细胞功能可能改变脊髓损伤治疗- SciTechDaily</title><link>https://scitechdaily.com/previously-unknown-brain-cell-function-could-transform-spinal-cord-injury-treatment/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>SciTechDaily</author><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 06:15:48 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMirgFBVV95cUxPcW9IMGJOZUhhM0l6TzBLVjk1LWZuVGdyRFlTSmNiY1ZkUVl2QkYteUtZVEVjRGtYX0dXRzlubGVPWEFMdGNPTUNYc1dXYllXVV9WYVVrdzB0ejF2cFdoNnFlMjFIMXEycmNNTVBQQkwteDlXbEF5SHBJS00zal9hMkROd1JIOXhCUGFranJMM1ZEOWVZdlRlUllBUUItLVNUZ09ZQWxZSnI2VGd0Y0E</guid></item><item><title>简单的补充剂可显著减少透析患者的严重心脏并发症- SciTechDaily</title><link>https://scitechdaily.com/simple-supplement-dramatically-reduces-serious-heart-complications-in-dialysis-patients/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>SciTechDaily</author><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 05:40:54 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiswFBVV95cUxQMlVMOE1oSTV0UEt6ckpxdzNPd19hMUNMcG5UU3NDTjcyVGtKRTh5V2N1TlZfR2pyaUhnZ1VvSmh2UXN4NUMtQkxrWUpwZ3JUYktkcDNUcEtnR0JwWW9SYmcyME9zUURTcVZLRjdJV0diaVgzaWplTGFQYXk0MmZUUE82dW93dXdvSm1BRFFlQ3daa1o5eG14SDhvMC1JS0V0OExuWHdfZWdWUEE3eGlXYXRrZw</guid></item><item><title>随着假日聚会越来越近，流感在亚特兰大地铁达到“令人担忧”的水平- WSB-TV</title><link>https://www.wsbtv.com/news/local/north-fulton-county/flu-reaches-concerning-level-metro-atlanta-holiday-gatherings-get-closer/7XZ4N6FHWRHUBEIMWULUFRGLKA/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article class="default__ArticleBody-sc-tl066j-1 jPcFTl article-body-wrapper"&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 gJuxXh body-paragraph"&gt;ATLANTA — Doctors are warning families that flu hospitalizations have reached a concerning level this week.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 gJuxXh body-paragraph"&gt;According to the Georgia Department of Public Health, 153 people were hospitalized in metro Atlanta last week. The data also shows &lt;a href="https://influenzareport.s3.us-east-1.amazonaws.com/DPHFluReport_Week202550.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer" title="https://influenzareport.s3.us-east-1.amazonaws.com/DPHFluReport_Week202550.html"&gt;flu has left more than 500 people hospitalized&lt;/a&gt; since October.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 gJuxXh body-paragraph"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Channel 2’s Courtney Francisco&lt;/b&gt; was at the SmartMed Drive-Thru in Roswell on Tuesday where she said you could hear the coughing coming from cars lines up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 gJuxXh body-paragraph"&gt;&lt;b&gt;[DOWNLOAD: &lt;/b&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.wsbtv.com/smart-tv/" title=""&gt;&lt;b&gt;Free WSB-TV News app for alerts as news breaks&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;b&gt;]&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="taboola-read-more" class="taboola-read-more"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 gJuxXh body-paragraph"&gt;Jason Fritz brought his child through for treatment on Tuesday evening.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 gJuxXh body-paragraph"&gt;“She’s coughing like that and up all night long. So, we’re here to, hopefully, see if we can get her better,” said Fritz.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 gJuxXh body-paragraph"&gt;She’s one of 700 patients who’ve visited the clinic in the past six days, according to Dr. Luke Lathrop. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 gJuxXh body-paragraph"&gt;Staff use hospital-grade testing to diagnose patients as accurately as possible, and he said half are positive for influenza. Others are testing positive for COVID, RSV and strep.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="taboola-read-more-8" class="taboola-read-more-8"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 gJuxXh body-paragraph"&gt;“If you have a fever of 103, things like that, you can’t be around family. You’re going to get grandma sick or little baby sick, and we just can’t do that,” said Dr. Lathrop.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 gJuxXh body-paragraph"&gt;&lt;b&gt;RELATED STORIES:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 gJuxXh body-paragraph"&gt;Children’s Heathcare of Atlanta’s website said it’s &lt;a href="https://www.choa.org/waittimes" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer" title="https://www.choa.org/waittimes"&gt;managing a high number of very sick children and teenagers&lt;/a&gt; due to the flu.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 gJuxXh body-paragraph"&gt;Wait times at the Emergency Department were as long as 135 minutes Tuesday night.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 gJuxXh body-paragraph"&gt;“Pharmacies are running out of Tamiflu,” said Dr. Lathrop. “I know a few local schools had to close early last week because all the kids were sick.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 gJuxXh body-paragraph"&gt;His clinic will double the number of staff working Christmas Eve to treat as many people as possible, and doctors keep patients in their cars to reduce contact and slow the spread of the virus.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 gJuxXh body-paragraph"&gt;“I’d say it’s worse than last year because it came out of nowhere. Last year, there was a little bit of a ramp up, and then it hit the scene. But this year, it was just crazy,” said Dr. Lathrop&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 gJuxXh body-paragraph"&gt;&lt;b&gt;[SIGN UP: &lt;/b&gt;&lt;a href="https://membercenter.wsbtv.com/newsletters"&gt;&lt;b&gt;WSB-TV Daily Headlines Newsletter&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;b&gt;]&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 gJuxXh body-paragraph body-copyright"&gt;©2025 Cox Media Group&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>WSB-TV</author><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 05:11:44 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi6AFBVV95cUxNRGY1WW5oSzNzUkcySE90SWV2ejE0QzZhdGh5UW9iX3hsY1dSNVJ3WXhTSy1rRkhiS0F2aDRqLWF3ZFZEcTdFNmtJSkNnakVtTEV3VktGXzZRb090YTZCcXotMkJocnZldEE1SlJHNXgtek9CVzgwVnpyUUFXMzNPTC1lRmxtbDllRFNxRkduVVNpN284Y09sSmNHU2pkeVhtZm4yOVE3MDVhY3FaZl9xcnM3dDE3SEtteG1LNVY1eTZ3UFJvdWFZTVhXNHpDWnE5bDJWTlU3cjM5YkI5OXhNdlotbXg2LWRY0gH8AUFVX3lxTE5XWHlDQXNGd3IxZEhINGRQWE96NHhhVGdEWU9FTHIyTGhKUVZXNi1ZU2NJbURvMVVSNUliVzBoSE44SE9MeE01NGRCN2ZXT0U4MnlZVzYtdFp5UUpvajhzYV9oRW9LbFZpRWhmdlNzREJ1UVRfRE1ETlFEek5NZDVEbF9yZV9jUy12MkdfWFBBbGlhcjZpU253Qnl4dDFPS25VbVdkbmVndTBVMlJzaVdTQVpESm1BbENwemtna2lYUlk3cWxRNmpMUVhRSEVQUjBPOHRwZDB5ekFVa1FQNHN3WFVJa09ubDhUZ09WcDZBelctQUNkYjZCeDl6Ng</guid></item><item><title>斯坦福大学科学家发现为什么基于mRNA的COVID-19疫苗会导致心肌炎- SciTechDaily</title><link>https://scitechdaily.com/stanford-scientists-discover-why-mrna-based-covid-19-vaccines-can-cause-myocarditis/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>SciTechDaily</author><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 05:05:10 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMirgFBVV95cUxPdjA5QlJXclE4X3lGNXYzaDd5TGJmdE1HUFBudC04REVBaWQ4SVBsNFJ1NWowWEo2aG9tVy1MV3o0c25XbG4yYkdoQVEzcjlYTDZEa2ZleVRQS1BlQkZmdXRJMkluVGZOU1F2NFZPU051NlQ1X1d1c0oxYWVWbElpTmZJVjRwUkx0dW9FZnU0S01iV0VWRVVhRE0tQUZGXzB3b1pqNFhBSVhqUWprb2c</guid></item><item><title>随着呼吸道感染的增加，两人死亡- nationnews.com</title><link>https://nationnews.com/2025/12/24/two-die-as-respiratory-infections-rise/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="tdb-block-inner td-fix-index"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Two people, including a known asthmatic, were hospitalised and died as Barbados recorded a rise in respiratory illness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Those deaths were up to December 12, with the number of new infections ranging from 14 in one week to 24 and then 39.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While respiratory illness is not uncommon at this time of year, the Ministry of Health and Wellness is advising Barbadians to practise good hygiene, especially when interacting with the vulnerable, to reduce the transmission of these viruses.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The statement follows in full:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As is not uncommon at this time of the year, a growing rise in cases of respiratory illness has been noted, especially in adults in Barbados.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Over the past four weeks, numbers ranged from 14 to 24, up to 39 in the week ending December 12, 2025, some of whom have been hospitalised. Among the hospitalised, two acute deaths were recorded up to December 12, one is a known asthmatic.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Expected numbers would be no more than six to eight cases per week. The main causes identified have been the Influenzas (AH3N2 or H1N1 or Influenza B) and the respiratory syncytial virus, RSV. A few cases of COVID-19 and the common-cold virus were also identified.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Ministry of Health and Wellness advises that it is important for Barbadians to continue to practise good respiratory hygiene, especially when interacting with vulnerable persons, including the elderly, as this is the most effective way of reducing the transmission of respiratory viruses. Masks should be worn when visiting healthcare institutions. Masks may be worn by vulnerable persons in crowded areas.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These practices also include washing hands with soap and water for at least 20 seconds and drying them with disposable tissue. If soap and water are not available, the use of an alcohol-based hand sanitiser is recommended.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Health officials also advise people to keep unwashed hands away from the eyes, nose and mouth, and to generally avoid touching these areas as germs can enter the body this way.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Ministry also reminds the public to cover the nose and mouth with tissue when coughing or sneezing. Alternatively, persons should cough or sneeze into the inner side of the elbow. Used tissues should be discarded in a bin or a tied plastic bag.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Providers are being asked to check oxygen saturations in ill persons, especially those with asthma, and refer those with low saturations. Providers are also reminded to obtain Nasopharyngeal swabs to verify the infecting agent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As in prior years, persons at risk for severe illness from influenza illness (persons with asthma, diabetes, or other NCDs) are advised to take their maintenance medications as prescribed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>nationnews.com</author><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 04:27:52 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMifkFVX3lxTFAzaGlSNHpZSVkySmJGNkpFUk5YemNLQkZSaVdoQjdmR3hHT0o3VExyM0FMTFJyOEhKSVZEUEV4RG1kYncyV2tJb3ByQnRvOUtJdGt3Z3hHRkNERFg5czh6VVJSbWMtZ3BaMjBaVzJKUU44OF9fNjZSdjAyY0ZTZw</guid></item><item><title>生病的员工在家参加工作会议，但大老板因为没有打开摄像头而感到非常不安- TwistedSifter</title><link>https://twistedsifter.com/2025/12/sick-employee-joins-a-work-meeting-from-home-but-his-bosss-boss-is-really-upset-that-he-didnt-turn-his-camera-on/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article"&gt;
						
						&lt;div id="attachment_681148" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-681148" class="wp-image-681148" src="https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/plugins/lazy-load-0.7/images/1x1.trans.gif" alt="sick man working from home while blowing his nose" title="Sick Employee Joins A Work Meeting From Home, But The Big Boss Is Really Upset That He Didnt Turn His Camera On" data-lazy-src="https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Twisted-Sifter-2025-12-03T162014.302.png" data-lazy-srcset="https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Twisted-Sifter-2025-12-03T162014.302.png 1200w, https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Twisted-Sifter-2025-12-03T162014.302.png?resize=150,79 150w, https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Twisted-Sifter-2025-12-03T162014.302.png?resize=300,158 300w, https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Twisted-Sifter-2025-12-03T162014.302.png?resize=768,403 768w, https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Twisted-Sifter-2025-12-03T162014.302.png?resize=1024,538 1024w, https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Twisted-Sifter-2025-12-03T162014.302.png?resize=586,308 586w" data-lazy-sizes="(max-width: 800px) 100vw, 800px"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-681148" class="wp-image-681148" src="https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Twisted-Sifter-2025-12-03T162014.302.png" alt="sick man working from home while blowing his nose" srcset="https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Twisted-Sifter-2025-12-03T162014.302.png 1200w, https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Twisted-Sifter-2025-12-03T162014.302.png?resize=150,79 150w, https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Twisted-Sifter-2025-12-03T162014.302.png?resize=300,158 300w, https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Twisted-Sifter-2025-12-03T162014.302.png?resize=768,403 768w, https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Twisted-Sifter-2025-12-03T162014.302.png?resize=1024,538 1024w, https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Twisted-Sifter-2025-12-03T162014.302.png?resize=586,308 586w" sizes="(max-width: 800px) 100vw, 800px" title="Sick Employee Joins A Work Meeting From Home, But The Big Boss Is Really Upset That He Didnt Turn His Camera On"&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;p id="caption-attachment-681148" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Shutterstock/Reddit&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Imagine working from home when you’re not feeling well but feeling well enough to work.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="mm-player"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you had a mandatory Zoom meeting, would you keep your camera off even though you’re supposed to have it on, or would you turn it on even though you looked pretty bad since you were sick?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/antiwork/comments/1pbict8/okay_mr_manager_thanks_for_managing/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;In this story&lt;/a&gt;, one work from home employee is in this exact situation, and he chooses the second option. What really bothers him is how his boss didn’t stand up for him.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let’s read the whole story.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Okay Mr. Manager, thanks for managing!&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I just had a Weekly stand up with my manager Who, at the end of our meeting, let me know that I needed to have my camera on More frequently for work.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Except, that’s not quite how the conversation went. You see, I work remote and we are a very much a camera’s on culture. Every meeting You are expected to join with your camera on and be participating.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;However, for the back half of November, I have been violently ill on and off. I have taken seven sick days, which is unheard of For me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The last time I was sick was in 2021 when I had the rona. I have not taken a sick day since then.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This time he was so sick that he needed to take sick days.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;Quite simply because I just don’t get sick and If I have a doctor’s appointment, usually I’m able to scoot out undetected without having to officially log it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That being said, November has not been kind to me, and so I took the tim I’m allowed to take off off.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;However, because my illness was so sporadic, and some days I did feel up to the challenge of joining work, I would join but have my camera off.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He had good reasons for wanting to keep his camera off.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;At the end of the month prior to the holiday break we had an all staff meeting with about 60 people on the call, and I was one of very few who didn’t have their camera on.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Again, because while I was feeling up to the challenge of working lightly, I didn’t look that great. My nose was red, my nose was runny, I was coughing and sneezing. I just didn’t look great.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;More importantly, I did not have a voice, but I still felt compelled to show up to work And join the staff meeting where I was expected to contribute very little.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;His manager brought up something his boss wanted him to pass along.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fast forward to today, I meet with my boss. The meeting goes as planned and at the end of the meeting, he lets me know. “By the way, My boss wanted me to tell you That they didn’t appreciate that you didn’t have your camera on.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;During our all team meeting Last week. I recognize that you have been sick, But I just wanted to let you know I’m doing my job as a manager and letting you know that she was unhappy.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My immediate response was, “did you let her know that I was sick and without a voice, but I still participated in the meeting???”,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He stuttered and said. Like I said, I’m just doing my job as a manager and telling you I trust That you’ve been sick. I’m not worried about it, but my boss just felt it was a bit rude that a number of people haven’t been cameras on for the last few All staff meetings.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I again responded. “This is the first time I’ve not had my camera on in a meeting that your boss has been a part of. Thanks for letting me know, but I think we’re both in agreement that this is a non-issue for me.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He told me to have a good day, and we ended the call.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He has a pretty good guess at what really happened.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thanks for doing nothing. Mr manager!!! Not only did he not defend me, He dismissed the fact that I was still participating in the meeting, even though I was sick.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And here’s the worst part of all.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He didn’t join the meeting at all because he was also sick last week.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, what I’m guessing Happened was he got yelled at by his boss for not joining the meeting And his boss decided to also let him know that because of his absence, people from his team ( I.E me) were also slacking by not turning their cameras on.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He’s counting the many, many days until retirement.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;I really don’t know how to end this other than just to say even working remote presents its own unique and absolutely Bonkers challenges That frequently make me want to Chuck my laptop out the window and quit working all together.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am so far from retirement, but I think fondly of the day When I can just do what I want on my own time and no longer have to be beholden to the zoom camera Gods that are my managers and my managers boss.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It sounds like he needs to look for a different job that he doesn’t hate so much.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let’s see how Reddit reacted to this story.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here’s an interesting idea for next time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" class="alignnone wp-image-681149" src="https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/plugins/lazy-load-0.7/images/1x1.trans.gif" alt="Screenshot 2025 12 03 at 4.16.30 PM Sick Employee Joins A Work Meeting From Home, But The Big Boss Is Really Upset That He Didnt Turn His Camera On" title="Sick Employee Joins A Work Meeting From Home, But The Big Boss Is Really Upset That He Didnt Turn His Camera On" data-lazy-src="https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Screenshot-2025-12-03-at-4.16.30-PM.png" data-lazy-srcset="https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Screenshot-2025-12-03-at-4.16.30-PM.png 570w, https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Screenshot-2025-12-03-at-4.16.30-PM.png?resize=150,148 150w, https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Screenshot-2025-12-03-at-4.16.30-PM.png?resize=300,296 300w" data-lazy-sizes="(max-width: 800px) 100vw, 800px"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" class="alignnone wp-image-681149" src="https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Screenshot-2025-12-03-at-4.16.30-PM.png" alt="Screenshot 2025 12 03 at 4.16.30 PM Sick Employee Joins A Work Meeting From Home, But The Big Boss Is Really Upset That He Didnt Turn His Camera On" srcset="https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Screenshot-2025-12-03-at-4.16.30-PM.png 570w, https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Screenshot-2025-12-03-at-4.16.30-PM.png?resize=150,148 150w, https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Screenshot-2025-12-03-at-4.16.30-PM.png?resize=300,296 300w" sizes="(max-width: 800px) 100vw, 800px" title="Sick Employee Joins A Work Meeting From Home, But The Big Boss Is Really Upset That He Didnt Turn His Camera On"&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This person doesn’t think he should be mad at the manager.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" class="alignnone wp-image-681150" src="https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/plugins/lazy-load-0.7/images/1x1.trans.gif" alt="Screenshot 2025 12 03 at 4.17.02 PM Sick Employee Joins A Work Meeting From Home, But The Big Boss Is Really Upset That He Didnt Turn His Camera On" title="Sick Employee Joins A Work Meeting From Home, But The Big Boss Is Really Upset That He Didnt Turn His Camera On" data-lazy-src="https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Screenshot-2025-12-03-at-4.17.02-PM.png" data-lazy-srcset="https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Screenshot-2025-12-03-at-4.17.02-PM.png 584w, https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Screenshot-2025-12-03-at-4.17.02-PM.png?resize=83,150 83w, https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Screenshot-2025-12-03-at-4.17.02-PM.png?resize=167,300 167w, https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Screenshot-2025-12-03-at-4.17.02-PM.png?resize=568,1024 568w" data-lazy-sizes="(max-width: 800px) 100vw, 800px"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" class="alignnone wp-image-681150" src="https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Screenshot-2025-12-03-at-4.17.02-PM.png" alt="Screenshot 2025 12 03 at 4.17.02 PM Sick Employee Joins A Work Meeting From Home, But The Big Boss Is Really Upset That He Didnt Turn His Camera On" srcset="https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Screenshot-2025-12-03-at-4.17.02-PM.png 584w, https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Screenshot-2025-12-03-at-4.17.02-PM.png?resize=83,150 83w, https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Screenshot-2025-12-03-at-4.17.02-PM.png?resize=167,300 167w, https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Screenshot-2025-12-03-at-4.17.02-PM.png?resize=568,1024 568w" sizes="(max-width: 800px) 100vw, 800px" title="Sick Employee Joins A Work Meeting From Home, But The Big Boss Is Really Upset That He Didnt Turn His Camera On"&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here’s a picky comment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="alignnone wp-image-681151" src="https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/plugins/lazy-load-0.7/images/1x1.trans.gif" alt="Screenshot 2025 12 03 at 4.17.10 PM Sick Employee Joins A Work Meeting From Home, But The Big Boss Is Really Upset That He Didnt Turn His Camera On" title="Sick Employee Joins A Work Meeting From Home, But The Big Boss Is Really Upset That He Didnt Turn His Camera On" data-lazy-src="https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Screenshot-2025-12-03-at-4.17.10-PM.png" data-lazy-srcset="https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Screenshot-2025-12-03-at-4.17.10-PM.png 538w, https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Screenshot-2025-12-03-at-4.17.10-PM.png?resize=150,39 150w, https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Screenshot-2025-12-03-at-4.17.10-PM.png?resize=300,78 300w" data-lazy-sizes="auto, (max-width: 800px) 100vw, 800px"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="alignnone wp-image-681151" src="https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Screenshot-2025-12-03-at-4.17.10-PM.png" alt="Screenshot 2025 12 03 at 4.17.10 PM Sick Employee Joins A Work Meeting From Home, But The Big Boss Is Really Upset That He Didnt Turn His Camera On" srcset="https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Screenshot-2025-12-03-at-4.17.10-PM.png 538w, https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Screenshot-2025-12-03-at-4.17.10-PM.png?resize=150,39 150w, https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Screenshot-2025-12-03-at-4.17.10-PM.png?resize=300,78 300w" sizes="auto, (max-width: 800px) 100vw, 800px" title="Sick Employee Joins A Work Meeting From Home, But The Big Boss Is Really Upset That He Didnt Turn His Camera On"&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It would’ve been better not to join the meeting at all.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you liked this post, check out this story about &lt;a href="https://twistedsifter.com/2023/12/co-worker-keeps-scoring-call-center-employees-work-suspiciously-low-so-they-get-pro-revenge-my-supervisor-will-be-under-investigation/?utm_source=IN-ARTICLE&amp;amp;utm_medium=IN-ARTICLE&amp;amp;utm_campaign=IN-ARTICLE" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;an employee who got revenge on a co-worker who kept grading their work suspiciously low&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

						
						 	
						

						
												
						
						
						
					&lt;/div&gt;

					&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>TwistedSifter</author><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 04:17:57 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi4AFBVV95cUxPaFRLN1AxQmlrZE1YT1F3Yk5XT2V3eFdfN1hOelF5bmtJdmNWRDlqZGptbGl4ZUY3SngxdGg1M2pEQjdtR2V6d3MzMm5wWkhBdWExZXAzclZIZXZxZXRRNk5RbXFmLVA2dnNBR0o3c3h6STBneXRtRldzUWRUSHBXX2Uwd2ozSTB3RkpJTGRBbFU5WGM2NWV3bGF2ZEhPYkZoeGloVmEwY1NIdko3cWpqcXktZ3I0V0RtS0pnaDdiOUxuc1h5V2N5YkVtSVJuME5kWnNkOEhzSjlZQnFOT0h2Rw</guid></item><item><title>你的大脑年龄在五个不同的阶段，新的研究表明-华尔街日报</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/health/wellness/brain-stages-aging-five-study-nature-a015101e</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Wall Street Journal</author><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 04:00:23 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiAFBVV95cUxOTmczTV83LXBBRm1sTG1ZWl9OdjVRRkczR01MQVZEeF9PYW1UTG1zQ0ZqTWRSZzB1RmxQSG9KYTlMcWlFbGFRb3FDNnhvVXhLaU80X0pmaVZraWRKU25UeElWRjlWajBBazVuSnF3UTlJRnlfX19SbV9oYjI0SFdZZTRUTTk0d1Fw</guid></item><item><title>关于飙升的“冬季呕吐虫”及其传染性新变种- Axios的须知事项</title><link>https://www.axios.com/2025/12/24/norovirus-winter-vomiting-bug-variant-symptoms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Axios</author><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 02:03:26 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihgFBVV95cUxORWh2SllPS19RSTUzUHZ3UldrUUpWLTk2M1VNUTU2eTU5Vkl3UWRhMzFhemhTT21QQVRlM0M4blVoVE04NHNEVDBNNjc2X3dmN3RkVkZMSGkwVTdtM19fZlJTVDZpWWVTMldJWGZIUkVTUkwzNzUtNnZaMUw0VW5HNjJPR2Zudw</guid></item><item><title>新的流感变异袭击南加州，引起公共卫生专家的担忧- ABC7洛杉矶</title><link>https://abc7.com/post/new-flu-variant-hits-southern-california-raises-concerns-among-public-health-experts/18310392/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="xvlfx ZRifP TKoO eaKKC EcdEg bOdfO qXhdi NFNeu UyHES " data-testid="prism-article-body"&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao MvWXB TjIXL aGjvy ebVHC "&gt;&lt;span class="oyrPY qlwaB AGxeB  "&gt;LOS ANGELES (KABC) -- &lt;/span&gt;Holiday travel is in full swing and flu cases are ramping up. Some experts are pretty worried about a new flu variant making its way to Southern California.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;So now is the time to take the steps to protect you and your loved ones.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Many schools across the nation closed early for winter break because of an onslaught of illness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Mother of two, Audrey Garrett, says flu-like symptoms hit her family hard.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;"We actually are just coming back from being sick. He caught a fever. My daughter had that nasty cough, you know that honking cough at night," Garrett said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;"Last year was a pretty bad seasonal flu year for Los Angeles, so it is scary to hear that this year might be worse," Dr. Dawn Tereshita said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Dr. Tereshita monitors acute communicable disease at L.A. County's Department of Public Health. She warns of an emerging H3N2 flu variant that's difficult for our immune systems to recognize.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;"This subclade K is new," Dr. Tereshita said. "We don't know what's going to happen yet, but since it is circulating pretty widely, we are watching it very carefully."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;The new variant isn't a match for this season's flu vaccine, but experts believe a flu shot will still help reduce the risk of severe illness, including hospitalization and death.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;"Any reason to not go to the hospital is, in my mind, very worth it. There are also antivirals, which you can take if you get sick," Tereshita explained.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;These include Tamiflu and the new Xofluza. Talk to your doctor if you have a fever, sore throat, cough and body aches because these meds should be taken near the onset of symptoms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;"The main messages are wash your hands, stay home when you're sick, and if you have to go out, wear a mask," Dr. Tereshita said&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;While we are seeing a lot of respiratory illnesses, Dr. Terashita says flu activity in California remains low.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;But, now is the time to get a flu shot if you haven't because the flu usually peaks in January and February.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC eTIW sUzSN "&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="uvrxY zOGtW "&gt;Copyright © 2025 KABC Television, LLC. All rights reserved.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ABC7 Los Angeles</author><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 01:39:55 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMitwFBVV95cUxNWk9vcTBSNmtlcFhadGRwMkFRZVhrTW5fOTNJNGpkcGdHX0JiOWZaZkJIbUdhajg4MTRwVW1wVzdHU2VLalUzRVhVdHQySER2VS1zV1pXYlFMWkxyWkVhVGZPenliVTlrNTl2eDQ4cmNBc2RGVXRBRmJ0REcxLXBZZWRpSjR0bm1nVTdHR0NlMExyQjRVemxZbmNuZDNhMnpNNGo3Nzc2T1NDTHpyQ19zYlZSazdsdzjSAbwBQVVfeXFMT1dKSk84ZExtdm43REtkUWRKR0x3Yjc3WnFrTnVWSURWeHI2SjZFbHpRS1lwbnlxdHVXUXRoNV95R0ZQak1sNFNKaTZhR1plejJtakxtX2xHZ01qNHVSRm4ta1d3RG52YV9kcDdNTTlsU2F0eVQ4MU43akhnSEIxcjVMckFXSmZoSjNsR2RHWnhpbEFHc3o5S3hybDMtNjZ5LWlTaW9VX3VDa01fMHY2akN5Z2d0TnJnR3pGY3o</guid></item><item><title>拉什大学医学中心的Steven Flamm博士谈论酒精使用，肝脏疾病，新年前饮酒的影响- ABC7芝加哥</title><link>https://abc7chicago.com/post/rush-university-medical-centers-dr-steven-flamm-talks-alcohol-use-liver-disease-impact-drinking-ahead-new-year/18310620/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="xvlfx ZRifP TKoO eaKKC EcdEg bOdfO qXhdi NFNeu UyHES " data-testid="prism-article-body"&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao MvWXB TjIXL aGjvy ebVHC "&gt;&lt;span class="oyrPY qlwaB AGxeB  "&gt;CHICAGO (WLS) -- &lt;/span&gt;As a new year approaches, many people are rethinking their habits, including how much alcohol they're drinking.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Rush University Medical Center's Dr. Steven Flamm joined ABC7 on Tuesday night to talk about alcohol's impact on the body.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="shortcode-centertext EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Flamm talked about how much alcohol it takes to develop liver disease and how alcohol impacts men and women differently.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Flamm also weighed in on the Illinois Department of Public Health's &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://dph.illinois.gov/resource-center/news/2025/december/release-20251215.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;alcohol use survey&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="RxNCg ykkUm PvZ nIjPJ PMXYp LmsHF SfAHY mNgye lNbol LBPRq rBLIK "&gt;Facts about alcohol:&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;People who consume alcohol can have severe alcohol-related liver disease with as little as two drinks per day in women and three drinks per day in men.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;The liver-related toxicity for alcohol is double in women compared to men.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Alcohol-associated hepatitis is a severe and life-threatening condition that can develop in a matter of weeks. It frequently happens in young people, has no good medical therapies and has a high mortality.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;The only therapy for alcohol-related liver disease is alcohol abstinence.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC eTIW sUzSN "&gt;There has been a dramatic increase in alcohol associated liver disease in the U.S., including Illinois, since the start of the COVID-19 pandemic.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="uvrxY zOGtW "&gt;Copyright © 2025 WLS-TV. All Rights Reserved.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ABC7 Chicago</author><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 01:29:39 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi4wFBVV95cUxNY2NIZGo5MlE2QmdwcjJPVkxZa2pVU1RYZ09LNVhUMHhlaXk4bmFIcnRIRkFsQi1NTl9uV0E5SjlfNGtWMDFEbEwzZW1jNUNHeGJRWHFmaGtwNTNjSUVBY2RfTG9aRTlTSzZMNEhnWHlId3NzWHdBLS1fRV9WUEpjSWJ1SXJZNjdYd295RnZTc3dYZURiRWRIY2l6SjhMMlBVX0ViNUhVTHJ6dGtOdHlydnlvY2hXSThHaWR5MEtEUWJCV1VIRW1hREcwemp3TTljdkh5RXZiZXJ1M0NpNTd3SHI2SdIB6AFBVV95cUxQY3NJd3ZIM3JfTVdvU3lZc1c0MURScHZtcGdnNHV0bkhTaEpCUDdJTkFKaENKb1ZmN0o3bU81QmNvZUQxT1VGNHF6STY3V0Y3TWJIRGRibXk0UTdvX09lS3pKVGdQRDJMMHRlODNJMWFkenppZXJQQkhuOUYtaHJUdUdZMnQxaHBGbnJzcHdBNFZmVTdGbDI4Xy13YlA5Nzl2N0xFMGhMMWx6RFB1R3NRdGRRZ3VaZmR5azAtSFRRVVZEM09JZU55WGotdzB4MzFOTTFMSXZPTE9JczV0VWZDRTREaWNVQmsz</guid></item><item><title>科学家说，人类实际上可能有30多种感官- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/humans-may-actually-have-over-30-senses-scientists-say</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Stuck in front of our screens all day, we often ignore our senses beyond sound and vision. And yet they are always at work. When we're more alert, we feel the rough and smooth surfaces of objects, the stiffness in our shoulders, the softness of bread.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the morning, we may feel the tingle of toothpaste, hear and feel the running water in the shower, smell the shampoo, and later the aroma of freshly brewed  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/how-does-caffeine-wake-you-up" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73115" data-postid="186802" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;coffee&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aristotle told us there were &lt;a href="https://www.jstor.org/stable/2184311"&gt;five senses&lt;/a&gt;. But he also told us the world was made up &lt;a href="https://www.cabinet.ox.ac.uk/fifth-element-and-medieval-cosmology-2"&gt;of five elements&lt;/a&gt;, and we no longer believe that. And modern research is showing we may actually have dozens of senses.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/a-scientist-reveals-5-amazing-facts-about-your-sense-of-smell"&gt;A Scientist Reveals 5 Amazing Facts About Your Sense of Smell&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Almost all of our experience &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/topics/senses-1914"&gt;is multisensory&lt;/a&gt;. We don't see, hear, smell, and touch in separate parcels. They occur simultaneously in a unified experience of the world around us and of ourselves.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What we feel affects &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1163/22134808-bja10003"&gt;what we see&lt;/a&gt;, and what we see affects &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.3389/fpsyg.2014.00725"&gt;what we hear&lt;/a&gt;. Different odours in shampoo &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S0950329309000202"&gt;can affect how you&lt;/a&gt; perceive the texture of hair. The fragrance of roses makes hair seem silkier, for instance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Odours in low-fat yogurts can make them feel richer and thicker on the palate without adding more emulsifiers. Perception of odours &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S0304394006010020"&gt;in the mouth&lt;/a&gt;, rising to the nasal passage, is modified by the viscosity of the liquids we consume.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_186808" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-186808" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/12/child_eating_yoghurt_642.jpg" alt="child eating yoghurt" class="wp-image-186808 size-full" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/12/child_eating_yoghurt_642.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/12/child_eating_yoghurt_642-600x421.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-186808" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;The odours of liquids in our mouth affect how they feel. (&lt;a href="https://www.canva.com/photos/MAEEqTBRquA/"&gt;Antonio D'Albore/Getty Images Signature/Canva&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;My long-term collaborator, Professor Charles Spence from the Crossmodal Laboratory in Oxford, told me his neuroscience colleagues &lt;a href="https://www.sciculture.ac.uk/files/2014/07/AHRC-Rethinking-the-Senses-Case-Study.pdf"&gt;believe there are&lt;/a&gt; anywhere between 22 and &lt;a href="https://www.gla.ac.uk/research/az/cspe/projects/rethinking-the-senses/"&gt;33 senses&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These include &lt;a href="https://www.britannica.com/science/proprioception"&gt;proprioception&lt;/a&gt;, which enables us to know where our limbs are without looking at them. Our sense of balance draws on the &lt;a href="https://www.britannica.com/science/ear/The-physiology-of-balance-vestibular-function"&gt;vestibular system&lt;/a&gt; of ear canals as well as sight and proprioception.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another example is interoception, by which we sense changes in our own bodies, such as a slight increase in our heart rate and hunger. We also have a sense of agency when moving our limbs: a feeling that can go missing &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/nrn.2017.14"&gt;in stroke patients&lt;/a&gt; who sometimes even believe someone else is moving their arm.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There is the &lt;a href="https://academic.oup.com/brain/article/147/2/390/7319594"&gt;sense of ownership&lt;/a&gt;. Stroke patients sometimes feel their arm is not their own, for instance, even though they may still feel sensations in it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/newsletter?utm_source=promo_generic_health"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-642x273.jpg" alt="Subscribe to ScienceAlert's free fact-checked newsletter" class="alignnone wp-image-182810 size-medium" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-642x273.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-768x326.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-600x255.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final.jpg 850w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some of the traditional senses are combinations of several senses. Touch, for instance, involves pain, temperature, itch, and tactile sensations. When &lt;a href="http://www.nature.com/nature/journal/v486/n7403_supp/full/486S6a.html"&gt;we taste something&lt;/a&gt;, we are actually experiencing a combination of three senses: touch, smell, and taste – or gustation – which combine to produce the flavours we perceive in food and drinks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gustation covers sensations produced by receptors on the tongue that enable us to detect salt, sweet, sour, bitter, and umami (savoury). What about mint, mango, melon, strawberry, raspberry?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We don't have raspberry receptors on the tongue, nor is raspberry flavour some combination of sweet, sour, and bitter. There is no taste arithmetic for fruit flavours.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We perceive them through the &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/smell-triggers-the-same-brain-response-as-taste-does-even-if-you-havent-eaten-anything-264922"&gt;combined workings&lt;/a&gt; of the tongue and the nose. &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.3390/foods11121686"&gt;It is smell&lt;/a&gt; that contributes the lion's share to what we call tasting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is not inhaling odours from the environment, though. Odour compounds are released as we chew or sip, travelling from the mouth to the nose through the nasal pharynx at the back of the throat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://scholar.archive.org/work/sn5ora556nerbd2gwndzdut5t4"&gt;Touch plays its part too&lt;/a&gt;, binding tastes and smells together and fixing our preferences for runny or firm eggs, and the velvety, luxurious gooeyness of chocolate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sight is influenced by our vestibular system. When you are on board an aircraft on the ground, look down the cabin. Look again when you are in the climb.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It will "look" to you as though the front of the cabin is higher than you are, although optically, everything is in the same relation to you as it was on the ground. What you "see" is the combined effect of sight and your ear canals telling you that you are tilting backwards.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_186809" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-186809" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/12/aircraft_cabin_seats_642.jpg" alt="aircraft cabin" class="wp-image-186809 size-full" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/12/aircraft_cabin_seats_642.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/12/aircraft_cabin_seats_642-600x421.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-186809" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;The rise of the aisle in an aircraft cabin is determined by your vestibular system. (&lt;a href="https://www.canva.com/photos/MAGZKtbMSrc/"&gt;Jeffry S.S./Pexels/Canva&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;The senses offer a rich seam of research, and philosophers, neuroscientists, and psychologists work together at the Centre for the Study of the Senses at the University of London's School of Advanced Study.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In 2013, the centre launched its Rethinking the Senses project, directed by my colleague, the late Professor Sir Colin Blakemore. We discovered how modifying the sound of your own footsteps can make your body feel lighter or heavier.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We learned how audioguides in the Tate Britain art museum that address the listener as if the model in a portrait was speaking enable visitors to remember more visual details of the painting. We discovered how aircraft noise interferes with our perception of taste and why you should always drink tomato juice on a plane.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While our perception of salt, sweet, and sour is reduced in the presence of white noise, umami is not, and tomatoes and tomato juice are &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1186/2044-7248-3-2"&gt;rich in umami&lt;/a&gt;. This means the aircraft's noise will enhance the savoury flavour.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/scientists-think-theyve-identified-an-unknown-taste-in-human-cells"&gt;Scientists Think They've Identified an Unknown Taste in Human Cells&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At our latest interactive exhibition, &lt;a href="https://www.kingscross.co.uk/event/club-curling"&gt;Senses Unwrapped&lt;/a&gt; at Coal Drops Yard in London's King's Cross, people can discover for themselves how their senses work and why they don't work as we think they do.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For example, the size-weight illusion is illustrated by a set of small, medium, and large curling stones. People can lift each one and decide which is heaviest. The smallest one feels heaviest, but people can then place them on balancing scales and discover that they are all the same weight.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But there are always plenty of things around you to show how intricate your senses are, if you only pause for a moment to take it all in. So next time you walk outside or savour a meal, take a moment to appreciate how your senses are working together to help you feel all the sensations involved.&lt;img loading="lazy" decoding="async" src="https://counter.theconversation.com/content/270697/count.gif?distributor=republish-lightbox-basic" alt="The Conversation" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade"&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/profiles/barry-smith-128876"&gt;Barry Smith&lt;/a&gt;, Director of the Institute of Philosophy, &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/institutions/school-of-advanced-study-university-of-london-1058"&gt;School of Advanced Study, University of London&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This article is republished from &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com"&gt;The Conversation&lt;/a&gt; under a Creative Commons license. Read the &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/humans-could-have-as-many-as-33-senses-270697"&gt;original article&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 00:32:06 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiwFBVV95cUxQcGdUZTYyb25pQmtSYThyUm5GNm9Ybm84R2p2TFNuM0hZajdkT2dKN19xWHB1RXJUM3ZzNl9sanJHR1E4dVJ0NFN4STg0SGdBNUZlZjFnd1FfbUNIajI0TExNSENZM0ZWYmxLVVJVTHQzR3QzUXBOdnIzLXZ6UXlkMnVuX3ZibklsVWow</guid></item><item><title>心理健康护理：姐妹30年的斗争如何帮助兄弟对抗精神分裂症，启发了一部电影-印度快报</title><link>https://indianexpress.com/article/health-wellness/caregiving-for-mental-health-how-a-sisters-30-year-fight-helped-a-brother-battle-schizophrenia-inspired-a-film-10434485/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="pcl-full-content" class="story_details"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Surviving mental illness is a dual effort. Sometimes the strongest fighters are not just the ones who recover but also those who refuse to abandon them when they are at their lowest. Like Ila Basu who did not give up on her 67-year-old brother Tarun Das, who was diagnosed with schizophrenia, a severe, chronic brain disorder causing distorted perceptions of reality, which manifests as hallucinations and delusions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For three decades, Ila has looked after him and even undertaken crash courses in rehabilitation, inspiring the 2004 Marathi film Devrai. “My brother Tarun is the youngest child in a large and accomplished family. Our father N. M. Das, served in the Air Force and my mother Nilima Das devoted her life to raising seven children. My siblings are bright and talented, doctors, nurses, teachers – all of them high achievers. And then little Tarun, small and gentle for his age, followed them everywhere with innocence and admiration,” Ila, now settled in &lt;a rel="noamphtml" class="keywordtourl" href="https://indianexpress.com/section/cities/pune/"&gt;Pune&lt;/a&gt;, tells The &lt;a rel="noamphtml" class="keywordtourl" href="https://indianexpress.com/"&gt;Indian Express&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img class="lazyloading" decoding="async" src="https://indianexpress.com/wp-content/themes/indianexpress/images/default-ie.jpg" data-lazy-type="lazyloading-image" data-src="https://data.indianexpress.com/election2019/track_1x1.jpg" data-lazy-src="https://data.indianexpress.com/election2019/track_1x1.jpg" alt=""&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While their early years were spent in Mysuru, the children shifted schools. Recalling the time Tarun stepped into adolescence, Ila says, “It was like a silent storm had begun inside him. As this condition is closely associated with a loss of gray matter density in the brain, Tarun struggled with his studies. His body and mind developed much slower than his classmates and he lagged behind in development milestones.” Teachers misunderstood his difficulty and school after school closed their doors to him. He began to lose friends, confidence and eventually his connection with the world around him. “A boy who once loved cricket and laughter slowly slipped into isolation and confusion. His mind, still growing and trying to understand life, was overtaken by an illness, which nobody recognised at the time. His behaviour changed. Communication faded. He withdrew into silence. He became lost inside himself. Those days, there was no mental health awareness or a support system. Only frustration, fear and stigma,” says Ila.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As Tarun’s condition worsened, he got addicted to smoking and was later treated at NIMHANS (National Institute for Mental Health and neuro Sciences), &lt;a rel="noamphtml" class="keywordtourl" href="https://indianexpress.com/section/cities/bangalore/"&gt;Bengaluru&lt;/a&gt;, where for the first time his therapy was pivoted on structure, routine and care. “However, with my father passing away in the middle of his treatment, Tarun returned home. With no family support and understanding of his illness, he collapsed again — this time deeper than ever. He lost everything. A home, identity, routine, dignity… even his human rights. He became invisible to the world,” says Ila.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ev-engagement group-name="contentLogin"&gt;&lt;/ev-engagement&gt;&lt;ev-engagement group-name="myNotification"&gt;&lt;/ev-engagement&gt;&lt;div class="ev-meter-content ie-premium-content-block"&gt;&lt;p id="taboola-mid-article-personalisation"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Where others saw a problem, Ila saw her brother&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She decided to fight when others gave up. From 1996 onward, Ila and her family took responsibility for Tarun’s entire life: medical care, emotional care, ensuring dignity, compliance of daily routine and rehabilitation as well as protection from stigma and love without condition. By then, the family had shifted to Pune and Ila would encourage Tarun to paint. The familiar surroundings gave a sense of stability to Tarun that worked.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Once she took one of his paintings and went to Sassoon Hospital where she met psychiatrist Dr Neha Pandey. Moved by Ila’s commitment to her brother, the doctor offered her a job. Ila became part of the group therapy team, helping her brother as well as other patients live a life of dignity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;The science of caregiving for schizophrenia&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A decade later, Ila and her family have added meaning to Tarun’s life by filling his days with rituals like reading, writing, exercising, walking, watching television and teaching him to use the mobile phone. Thanks to technology, he could snap out of his imagined world and connect to reality. Tarun met his childhood friends through the internet as his best friend came to meet him in Pune.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="adboxtop adsizes"&gt;&lt;p class="ie-adtext"&gt;Story continues below this ad&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="gpt_ad_IE_ROS_ROTATE_1_300X250" class="ad-slot "&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;According to Ila, a caregiver’s job is a patient one. “The first step is to create a safe space for mutual communication by attempting to understand even the patient’s non-verbal cues,” she says. A caregiver often validates the patient’s feelings and experiences, opening a bridge of communication. If it’s a family member, then it is easier to understand a loved one’s reality without judgment and eases their sense of isolation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At the first step, a caregiver should not challenge delusions simply because it is pointless to reason with psychosis. The idea is to listen to the patient and gently redirect them to reality. Encourage them in doing things for themselves, which steers them closer to their immediate reality. Ila involved her brother in various activities and hobbies that would keep him grounded to reality and gently encouraged interaction with friends, family, and social outings to combat isolation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She learnt about schizophrenia to understand symptoms and behaviours so that she could deal with her brother’s anxieties better. In fact, becoming a caregiver-therapist helped her experience different manifestations of the disease and understand them better. Amid all this, Ila ensured that she stayed fit and alert. She watched her own sleep, diet, exercise and relaxation techniques to prevent burnout.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;What care-giving does: Low dose psychiatric medication, no relapse&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At BJ Government Medical College and Sassoon General Hospital in Pune, Ila coordinated with associate professor Dr Nishikant Thorat to supervise Tarun. He gradually reduced Tarun’s psychiatric medication and he did not have any bouts of relapse. “Ila has studied his silence, learnt his non-verbal language and built a world around his comfort and safety. She taught the family how to love him, not fear his illness. Alongside her stood her husband, son Tavish, and daughter-in-law, who gave up comfort, time and personal life to become Tarun’s protectors and support system. They gave him more than care, they gave him belonging,” Dr Thorat said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="adboxtop adsizes"&gt;&lt;p class="ie-adtext"&gt;Story continues below this ad&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="gpt_ad_IE_ROS_ROTATE_2_300X250" class="ad-slot "&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tarun’s struggle continues with age bringing in illnesses like kidney failure, cardiac issues, diabetes and other orthopaedic issues. Dialysis has become a part of his life. “Patients suffering from long standing psychiatric illnesses like schizophrenia pose a challenge. Psychotropic medications can sometimes have a negative impact on the kidneys. That’s why he requires regular dialysis thrice a week to manage his kidney issues. We are able to reduce his psychotropic medications to a bare minimum dose so as not to have any negative impact on his treatment for kidney failure. In fact, since the last three years, he is behaviourally stable, interactive and taking his dialysis sessions regularly,” says Dr Thorat.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tarun now lives a life of dignity. His mind may not match his age but his heart recognises love and finds joy in friendship, paintbrush, music and people who approach him with kindness.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p id="taboola-mid-article-personalisation-premium"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;												&lt;/div&gt;
												&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Indian Express</author><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 00:14:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi_wFBVV95cUxNaWlpQlAyZ1VzZVlidmZVOXdBMEFxMjhZY05IZkVjbm1YOHZDaHZLTDkxMDdiSlllbkRablc2NW51dURSOTduZW5RQlhzWkhEdkY5YzR1RUhXRzBSTEltSndXdnd1YXdvYk1PSVBZN1RjLWRwX0VDVmZmTHJzTzJnOGFiUjc3NHN0VzJEcjBqc2hueUdwNDdUdGJnazJrTmI1MXl1MVZNUXNKN3lWMzJoMEd6UnB0VVNFejNGRVdWWGxDWGZLRDhZZXNtamE4UmFKMnBDWUo3MkpCallGakpXT3lzQXFrVFdCejJxajJibzJYVUNUQ2Q4bmpVaV9OS2vSAYYCQVVfeXFMTXFHSW9OMEljTDBhaFpUeHFIeG1pRTRBY3lLUWQ1S2wzdnp6RWpZeldQVFNjNEhXanVFdnFITVlsN3RLVmxQUXFCSmZMX0pKSTJLdTY4NFFJLWRSVl9pTXl4U0NiMTlSR2xfX0ZQR2cwQnhpYnlOTjhqNXhTVzNmWlJqWmkwLU1QZEdaa1dVZU51NlhaeHdtRXdCY1Z1VXhZVFljdElibklGOHZCTGk3ZEZra05WTkFPQy1iaUdoLTVkVDgtSU9Tanp0QTZCel9hc21pZnFUV3gtUFp2bDlvYzJQMGh5V3ZNekZvbHBYUG5mOVVHdnd6bUx5UDZ1RU9ZSzlTNEtiUQ</guid></item><item><title>卫生官员警告DIA -科罗拉多州公共广播电台可能接触麻疹</title><link>https://www.cpr.org/2025/12/23/dia-potential-measles-exposure/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-content content"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Colorado health officials put out an alert Tuesday about a potential measles exposure at Denver International Airport earlier this month. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That exposure happened on Friday, December 12. An out-of-state traveler with a confirmed case of measles traveled through the airport while infectious, according to the Colorado Department of Public Health and Environment (CDPHE). &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The infected person arrived at gate B45 in the B Concourse at 7:24 p.m. on Friday, December 12. They departed from Gate B84 in the B Concourse at 9:41 p.m. Passengers exposed to the case on either flight will be notified directly by public health agencies. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p aria-hidden="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p aria-hidden="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a press release, CDPHE said the passenger is fully vaccinated and had mild symptoms — meaning the risk of transmission is lower, but still possible.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Measles cases are occurring throughout the country. As of December 23, 2025, a total of 2,012 confirmed measles cases &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/measles/data-research/index.html"&gt;were reported&lt;/a&gt; in the United States, according to the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention. That’s the most &lt;a href="https://publichealth.jhu.edu/ivac/2025/us-measles-cases-hit-highest-level-since-declared-eliminated-in-2000"&gt;in three decades&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The state health department says there's a higher likelihood of exposure in places where a lot of people gather, like an airport. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Measles is highly contagious. It can sometimes lead to serious health problems. But it is a preventable disease due to an effective vaccine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Measles symptoms start with fever, cough, runny nose, and red eyes. That’s followed by a rash that generally starts several days later on the face and spreads. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Getting vaccinated with the measles, mumps, and rubella (MMR) vaccine is the best way to protect yourself, your family, and your community, according to CDPHE.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p aria-hidden="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p aria-hidden="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Anyone who was at the part of the airport between 7 p.m. and 11:55 p.m. may have been exposed. If you were there, watch for symptoms for 21 days after exposure. In this case, that’s through Friday, Jan. 2. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If symptoms develop, the agency advises calling your health care provider, urgent care, or emergency department before going in. Tell them you may have been exposed to measles. This helps prevent further spread. Monitoring for symptoms is especially critical for people who have not been vaccinated with the MMR vaccine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Earlier this month, Colorado recorded three new measles cases, which increased the total for the year to 36, far surpassing totals from recent previous years. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Colorado's spike comes as the nation has seen a sharp increase in cases, and for the first time in a quarter century. &lt;a href="https://www.scientificamerican.com/article/canada-just-lost-its-measles-free-status-the-u-s-could-soon-follow/#:~:text=%E2%80%9CCanada%20can%20re%2Destablish%20its,misconduct%2C%20archaeology%20and%20the%20environment."&gt;The U.S. could lose its measles-free status&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For more information, visit the &lt;a href="https://cdphe.colorado.gov/dcphr/measles-information"&gt;CDPHE measles webpage&lt;/a&gt;, which includes information about symptoms, transmission, and vaccine recommendations as well as &lt;a href="https://cdphe.colorado.gov/diseases-a-to-z/measles/2025-case-information"&gt;2025 Colorado measles case information&lt;/a&gt; and a current list of &lt;a href="https://cdphe.colorado.gov/diseases-a-to-z/measles/colorado-exposure-location-information"&gt;exposure locations&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p aria-hidden="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Colorado Public Radio</author><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 23:33:12 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMib0FVX3lxTFBBUjRpbUd0ZG5XRFlzTHAzbVVGOGFUVUpWdnBrVXIyUkdkLS1OTkJna0hxUVV0TjFnOXJqcl8tbW9TbEUwYjNhZHRFdkZEUldlbHVXT2tMN2V3eXpLRndOSkNWQUFPSkUzWW9lc0djNA</guid></item><item><title>我是一名皮肤科医生—如何知道一个人长大后是否会皱纹更多- AOL.com</title><link>https://www.aol.com/articles/m-dermatologist-always-tell-person-110000964.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="caas-body"&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure align-caption-with-image"&gt;&lt;div class="no-margin"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="caption-wrapper"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption-collapse"&gt;Everyone gets wrinkles, but some people are more likely to have early lines and deeper grooves. Dr. Kseniya Kobets reveals three major tell-tale signs of accelerated aging.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Call ’em laugh lines, battle blemishes or experience etchings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wrinkles are a natural and universal part of aging. &lt;a href="https://nypost.com/2024/01/12/health/what-causes-wrinkles-groundbreaking-new-study-may-have-found-answer/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:These creases primarily form;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;These creases primarily form&lt;/a&gt; as the skin loses collagen and elastin, which provide structure, firmness and elasticity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Certain habits can accelerate this process, making lines and grooves appear earlier and deeper. Blame genetics, hormones, dehydration, insufficient sleep, poor diets, stress and repeated facial expressions such as squinting, smiling or frowning.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure align-caption-with-image"&gt;&lt;div class="no-margin"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="caption-wrapper"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption-collapse"&gt;Everyone gets wrinkles, but some people are more likely to have early lines and deeper grooves. Dr. Kseniya Kobets reveals three major tell-tale signs of accelerated aging. courtesy of Montefiore Einstein Advanced Care&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Stress has a lot to do with aging and reactive oxygen species,” &lt;a href="https://doctors.montefioreeinstein.org/providers/1912296674/kseniya-kobets" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Dr. Kseniya Kobets;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Dr. Kseniya Kobets&lt;/a&gt;, director of cosmetic dermatology at &lt;a href="https://montefioreeinsteinadvancedcare.org/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Montefiore Einstein Advanced Care;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Montefiore Einstein Advanced Care&lt;/a&gt;, told The Post.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Someone who doesn’t have a healthy lifestyle and doesn’t eat healthy vegetables or fruits once in a while is also more likely to have less healthy skin.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kobets reveals three major ways she can tell if someone is more likely to develop smile souvenirs as they age.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Steady sun-worshipping&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The sun is good for you — it helps your body make &lt;a href="https://nypost.com/2023/11/27/health/vitamin-d-recommended-levels-should-be-10x-higher-report/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:vitamin D;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;vitamin D&lt;/a&gt; for strong bones, enhances mood by boosting serotonin and regulates your body’s internal clock for better sleep.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But too many rays can be really bad for skin. Just ask New Jersey “tan mom” &lt;a href="https://nypost.com/2022/05/23/tan-mom-patricia-krentcil-im-a-totally-different-person/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Patricia Krentcil;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Patricia Krentcil&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure align-caption-with-image"&gt;&lt;div class="no-margin"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="caption-wrapper"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption-collapse"&gt;Sunscreen prevents wrinkles by protecting skin from UV rays, which break down collagen and elastin. verona_studio – stock.adobe.com&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kobets worries about fair-skinned people who live in sun-soaked areas or participate in outdoor activities like hiking, biking, skiing or vacationing in the tropics.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“They are more prone to developing wrinkles and especially other issues like sun damage and, God forbid, precancerous lesions and &lt;a href="https://nypost.com/2025/08/25/health/abcdes-of-skin-cancer-9-clues-you-shouldnt-ignore/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:skin cancers;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;skin cancers&lt;/a&gt;,” she explained.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;UV rays generate free radicals that destroy collagen and elastin, damage DNA, trigger inflammation and speed up skin aging.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;How much sun is OK is really dependent on your skin type and the daily UV index.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Everyone needs protection, including hats, &lt;a href="https://nypost.com/article/best-sunglasses-brands-men-women/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:sunglasses;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;sunglasses&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://nypost.com/2025/06/09/health/what-to-know-about-picking-sunscreen-including-2-key-ingredients/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:SPF 30+ sunscreen;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;SPF 30+ sunscreen&lt;/a&gt;, when the index reaches 3 or higher (moderate risk).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Rawdogging skincare&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sunscreen is the cornerstone of any good skincare regimen, which is key to fending off wrinkles.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“If someone doesn’t really have a consistent skin care routine, particularly one that includes daily sunscreen use, even if they’re not outdoors, they are more likely to develop wrinkles over time,” Kobets said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure align-caption-with-image"&gt;&lt;div class="no-margin"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="caption-wrapper"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption-collapse"&gt;A good skincare routine emphasizes sun protection, hydration (moisturizers, hyaluronic acid), retinoids for cell turnover and antioxidants like vitamin C. Rido – stock.adobe.com&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Besides &lt;a href="https://nypost.com/article/best-mineral-sunscreens-per-experts/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:mineral sunscreen;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;mineral sunscreen&lt;/a&gt;, which reflects and scatters UV rays, Kobets recommends topical and oral antioxidants.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That means consuming vitamin C, &lt;a href="https://nypost.com/2024/05/03/health/im-a-dietitian-eat-this-to-get-more-collagen/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:collagen;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;collagen&lt;/a&gt; and peptides, short amino acid chains that tell skin cells to pump out more collagen and elastin, and applying topical peptides and occasionally, a topical retinol.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“These are very important factors, not to mention wearing hats and staying in the shade, even if you are wearing sunscreen,” Kobets said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Puffing pores&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Baking in the sun is lousy for your skin, but smoking is often considered worse because it narrows blood vessels, breaks down collagen and elastin and amplifies sun damage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nicotine constricts blood vessels, limiting the flow of oxygen and essential nutrients to the skin.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“If the person is smoking — although there are a lot of genetic and environmental factors at play — they’re more likely to have thinner skin and wrinkles, especially around their mouth,” Kobets said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That’s a nice way to describe &lt;a href="https://nypost.com/2019/11/01/study-confirms-that-cigarettes-will-give-you-ugly-smokers-face/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:“smoker’s face,”;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;“smoker’s face,”&lt;/a&gt; a phenomenon characterized by deep wrinkles around the eyes and lips from the smoker constantly drawing on cigarettes and repeatedly squinting to keep smoke out of their eyes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Smokers also often suffer from sagging skin, a dull, yellowish-gray complexion and premature contours.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>AOL.com</author><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 23:31:37 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihAFBVV95cUxQNmFwQ0FpY2NGeW9ZVVluZUZtOVNHNF9QeHNLdnBLdTJvTTR2MjZadzF2aHR2Rzl5eGhNLUhsODZYb0tHTXBxaUxiY0k3TEtpZC1lcEZPMFdUMV9PSDIwUlBJTWtfdEJDSlZSMmtuUWNKU2o0RTlodEdFbkVjaGxvWFdpMmg</guid></item><item><title>每天只喝一杯与印度口腔癌风险增加50 ％有关- SciTechDaily</title><link>https://scitechdaily.com/just-one-drink-a-day-linked-to-50-higher-mouth-cancer-risk-in-india/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>SciTechDaily</author><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 23:30:38 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimAFBVV95cUxOanJ1UEEzU2RnbHQtYWtFSWNZY2NqbDZKVFBvMUFCWG5wX09GWE00S3I0V3ZUMV9fWWR2dUpXUVcwdjBlU21ZWjdNSjJzaWJOXy1LYjF4QXEtTTVkdF9TbkZEZVlORkdlM1FiWFpJOFh6UHRKeVoxQkwzaVgzeHJWR2lJMU9ZZHoyc1ZhbTgzV18tUTBkNG9EMw</guid></item></channel></rss>