<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>GNews Health</title><link>https://news.google.com/</link><description></description><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>专家称赞电子植入物在恢复视力方面取得了“非凡”的成功-卫报</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/science/2025/oct/20/experts-hail-remarkable-success-of-electronic-implant-in-restoring-sight</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body-commercial-selector article-body-viewer-selector dcr-11jq3zt"&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;An electronic eye implant half the thickness of a human hair has helped people with incurable sight loss to see again, opening up a potential “new era” in tackling blindness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Doctors who implanted the sim card-shaped prosthetic devices say they have helped many of the 38 elderly patients in the trial regain their ability to read letters, numbers and words.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="sign-in-gate"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“In the history of artificial vision, this represents a new era, said Mahi Muqit, a senior consultant at Moorfields eye hospital in London, one of the 17 sites involved.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“Blind patients are actually able to have meaningful central vision restoration, which has never been done before. Getting back the ability to read is a major improvement in their quality of life, lifts their mood and helps to restore their confidence and independence.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The trial found 84% of participants were once again able to read letters, numbers and words after being fitted with the implant, called the Prima device.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Eye specialists hailed the results as “remarkable” and said the device could help people with the “dry” form of age-related macular degeneration (AMD), the leading cause of sight loss in the over-50s.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Moorfields said: “The revolutionary new implant is the first ever device to enable people to read letters, numbers and words through an eye that had lost its sight.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The 38 patients all had geographic atrophy with dry AMD, which over time progressively deprives someone of their sight and for which there is no treatment. Most people with the condition lose some of their central vision and in some cases it progresses to full sight loss as the cells in the macula die and the central macula melts away.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;All had lost their central vision and had only limited peripheral vision before they had the device implanted in an operation lasting less then two hours. Five were treated at Moorfields and the others at hospitals in Germany, France, Italy and the Netherlands.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Sheila Wilson from Wiltshire, one of those who had the chip implanted at Moorfields, said: “Before receiving the implant it was like having two black discs in my eyes, with the outside distorted. I was an avid bookworm and I wanted that back. There was no pain during the operation but you’re still aware of what’s happening.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“It’s made a big difference. It’s a new way of looking through your eyes and it was dead exciting when I began seeing a letter. It’s not simple, learning to read again, but the more hours I put in, the more I pick up.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The Prima device, a super-thin microchip that is just 2mm by 2mm in size, is inserted under the centre of the eye’s retina in a procedure known as a vitrectomy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;To help them to see and write, patients were given augmented reality glasses containing a video camera connected to a small computer, which they attached to their waistband. It included a zoom feature to make text bigger and easier to read.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Patients can use the glasses to focus and scan the object in the projected image that they want to read. The glasses project the scenes as an infra-red beam across the chip, which activates the device. Artificial intelligence in the waistband computer processes the information and converts it into an electrical signal, which passes through the cells in the retina and optical nerve into the brain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Muqit stressed that patients had to undergo training and intensive rehabilitation of their eye in order to realise the benefits of the technology.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“It’s not like you’re popping a chip in the eye and then you can see again. You need to learn to use this type of vision,” he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The results of the trial are reported in the &lt;a href="https://www.nejm.org/doi/full/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;New England Journal of Medicine&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Guardian</author><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 12:29:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMivAFBVV95cUxQZWhCalptZS1PYUpfZU9oN0o3OWo4c3JOaFdlSnp2Y2RUZ25CYkk4cm56UWIycVRGaUxmdWpER09HZlpZVDdrR3Zncy1uV08tdGROYlhxZ3dKNGU4WmpVa2lNLTB5NHNHaUpHY3Zyd21haWMxZW1UVEpyQVQ1WFhHczNRdkFBcDFOVGE2RnUxLWpEQWdkS2dqNW1kQWVEdUcxSTBiSDk5U0lKZS1YakJseUlRVnhuVGZ3U0lsLQ</guid></item><item><title>根据新的饮食指南，每天吃2到3个猕猴桃可以缓解慢性便秘- CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2025/10/20/health/kiwi-health-benefits-relieve-constipation-wellness</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article__content" data-editable="content" itemprop="articleBody" data-reorderable="content"&gt;
                
    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgvczg59002x27pghmpndt2c@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Do you often experience difficulty defecating? If the answer is yes, newly released recommendations may help relieve your symptoms.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgvd8qeb000i3b6nw1r2hvlt@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Kiwifruit, rye bread and high mineral-content water can help alleviate chronic constipation, according to &lt;a href="https://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1111/jhn.70133" target="_blank"&gt;new dietary guidelines&lt;/a&gt; copublished October 13 by the Journal of Human Nutrition and Dietetics and Neurogastroenterology &amp;amp; Motility.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgvd8qeb000h3b6ncob49h9s@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            About &lt;a href="https://iffgd.org/gi-disorders/lower-gi-disorders/constipation/" target="_blank"&gt;1 out of every 6 to 7 people&lt;/a&gt; are affected by chronic constipation worldwide. In the United States, &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC7269025/" target="_blank"&gt;9% to 20% of adults&lt;/a&gt; have some form of chronic idiopathic constipation,&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;in which the cause of the condition&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;is unknown.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgvd8qeb000j3b6n54hkzesh@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Some &lt;a href="https://www.mayoclinic.org/diseases-conditions/constipation/symptoms-causes/syc-20354253" target="_blank"&gt;symptoms of chronic constipation&lt;/a&gt; include having a bowel movement fewer than three times a week, hard or lumpy stool, or straining or experiencing pain when pooping.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgvd8qeb000l3b6n3uiboa2j@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The guidelines “introduce foods and drinks (e.g., kiwifruit, prunes, rye bread, high mineral content water) and specific supplement interventions into clinical guidance, filling a long-standing gap between research and routine clinical advice,” lead study author Dr. Eirini Dimidi said in an email. “That will help clinicians give clearer, more targeted, and evidence-informed dietary advice, and will allow people to self-manage their symptoms more effectively.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgvd8qeb000m3b6nf4r7xob5@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The guidance applies to healthy adults with &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2013/08/28/health/gi-disorders-ibs-cic"&gt;chronic idiopathic constipation&lt;/a&gt; and “did not focus on constipation secondary to other conditions (e.g., neurological disease, pregnancy), so while some recommendations may be applicable, they should be used with caution in these groups, as well as in children,” said Dimidi, an associate professor in nutritional sciences at King’s College London.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgvd8qeb000n3b6ngxw8q3z0@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The guidelines did not include a general recommendation for increased fiber intake in a patient’s diet. Rather, they focused on specific foods that could be beneficial, Dimidi added.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgvd8qec000o3b6nks0tyjjn@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Certain &lt;a href="https://my.clevelandclinic.org/health/diseases/4059-constipation" target="_blank"&gt;lifestyle choices or situations&lt;/a&gt;, such as low fiber intake, dehydration, lack of exercise, or stress, can cause constipation. As a result, clinicians focus most treatment on dietary changes.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgvd8qec000p3b6nkiu9v0bf@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Previous dietary advice was broad, such as telling patients to eat more fiber. But these new guidelines, Dimidi said, suggest “incorporating evidence-based foods and drinks in your diet, such as consuming 2-3 kiwifruits a day.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgvd8qec000q3b6nyrl7zt33@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Unlike other recommended food such as prunes, kiwifruit is simple to incorporate into your diet.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgvd8qec000r3b6nhaw2jqlr@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “With kiwifruit, because it’s so well-tolerated, you usually can just step right into that dose, as opposed to prunes, for example, where you want to more gradually work up to that dose of six to eight prunes per day,” said Dr. William Chey, professor and chief of gastroenterology and hepatology at the University of Michigan. He was not involved in the new research.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgvd8qec000s3b6n5y2tb07c@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC6267416/" target="_blank"&gt;Kiwis can increase stool bulk&lt;/a&gt; and water content, enhance protein digestion, and smoothen the movement of food, fluids and waste in the digestive tract. The small fruits also improve the amount of time it takes for waste to pass through your intestine and have natural prebiotic effects, such as improved digestion and reduced gut inflammation.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgvd8qec000t3b6nmt66pxhb@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Kiwis are also palatable and soft, which makes them easy to eat, said Dr. Cuckoo Choudhary, the Dorrance H. Hamilton Professor of Medicine at Thomas Jefferson University Hospital in Philadelphia. She was not involved in the study.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgvd8qec000u3b6nh9jy0heg@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            You can also eat a kiwi’s skin or peel, which has extra fiber. But avoid heating a kiwi, since high temperatures destroy the enzyme that smoothens gut movement, Choudhary added.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgvd8qec000v3b6nmkmvq1n0@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Foods such as prunes, rye bread, flaxseeds, oranges, yogurt, beans and oatmeal &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2015/05/18/health/foods-for-constipation"&gt;can also help&lt;/a&gt; with chronic constipation.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgvd8qec000w3b6ncyd4t6et@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            For those who like dairy, you could “take a cup of yogurt, make it 8 ounces, any yogurt of your choice because all yogurts have probiotics, and take a heaped tablespoon full of crushed flaxseeds,” said Choudhary, an expert with the American Gastroenterological Association.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgvd8qec000x3b6n9ozxl3ub@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Other alternatives include dietary supplements, such as &lt;a href="https://my.clevelandclinic.org/health/drugs/18922-psyllium-powder-for-solution" target="_blank"&gt;psyllium&lt;/a&gt;, which helps your intestine move stool along and reduces your body’s cholesterol absorption from food.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgvd8qec000y3b6n2x0au123@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “That dosage is at least 10 grams of fiber per day. And again, the general rule is, start low and go slow. So start with 3 grams and gradually work your way up to 10 plus grams per day of psyllium to achieve the benefits,” said Chey, incoming president of the American College of Gastroenterology.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgvd8qec000z3b6nt9lvzh94@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC11583288/" target="_blank"&gt;Physical activity&lt;/a&gt; is also an important lifestyle change that patients with chronic constipation can incorporate.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgvd8qec00103b6n7ov5pipc@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Even something as simple as walking&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;increases the effectiveness of the digestive tract&lt;strong&gt;, &lt;/strong&gt;Choudhary said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgvd8qec00113b6npxjdgcii@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The new recommendations were based on findings of four systematic reviews and meta-analyses that looked at over 75 randomized controlled trials of dietary interventions for chronic constipation.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  
&lt;p data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/editor-note/instances/cmgz3up3r00023b6nszmosjaz@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="editor-note" class="editor-note-elevate vossi-editor-note inline-placeholder " data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
    Get inspired by a weekly roundup on living well, made simple. Sign up for &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/newsletters/life-but-better?source=nl-acq_article"&gt;CNN’s Life, But Better newsletter&lt;/a&gt; for information and tools designed to improve your well-being.
&lt;/p&gt;

              &lt;/div&gt;
                  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>CNN</author><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 11:25:51 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikgFBVV95cUxPR3F6LV8yQ1h4RzRUcUp2Y25lZGNPSFVGOHNubWQ0TUU2Sk5LVFJ5Z0dNRXhibHRhUXZKUjdycmw5TVVkNE5sTEVwalFfZU9xZk1PR0Fia0ZRQlRhdmFqRFNfZ1pkT29EcWN6R1l0cmdfcmVxU05zamlpZmREdnFfMjNyQ3hnQnJqb0dURHVaSmRLdw</guid></item><item><title>康涅狄格州的生活方式消失了。“一夜之间，它就完成了。结束了。” - Hartford Courant</title><link>https://www.courant.com/2025/10/20/a-connecticut-way-of-life-disappeared-overnight-it-was-done-it-was-ended/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="body-copy"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bart Mansi used to haul a thousand pounds of &lt;a href="https://www.courant.com/2025/05/14/the-days-of-connecticuts-booming-lobster-industry-are-long-gone-heres-what-changed/"&gt;lobster&lt;/a&gt; a day. Now he sets out just a couple dozen traps, out of curiosity — or force of habit — and he’s lucky to catch 10 lobsters.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I’ve been doing it all my life. I gotta see for myself,” he said. “But as far as trying to make a living, you can’t do it, not any more.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mansi converted his lobster wholesale facility on the dock in Guilford into a restaurant in the early 2000s. In the upstairs office on a sunny September morning, there are a few reminders of the life he used to lead: a “Captain’s Quarters” sign, framed photos from his lobstering heyday, the mast of his son’s fishing boat swaying gently out the window.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;His eyes lit up as he recalled the good days. “We saw a lot of lobsters, a real lot of lobsters,” Mansi said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="s2nPlayer k-iLgdKCFX" data-type="float" data-s2n-api="dfm_stn_player_script_id_iLgdKCFX"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure id="attachment_8871017" class="wp-caption alignnone size-article_inline"&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class=" lazyautosizes lazyload" src="https://i0.wp.com/www.courant.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/thc-l-lobsters-1025-01.jpg?fit=620%2C9999px&amp;amp;ssl=1" alt="Former lobsterman Bart Mansi sits in his office on the second story of the Guilford Lobster Pound on Sept. 3, 2025. (Dana Edwards / CT Mirror)" data-sizes="auto" data-src="https://i0.wp.com/www.courant.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/thc-l-lobsters-1025-01.jpg?fit=620%2C9999px&amp;amp;ssl=1" data-attachment-id="8871017" data-srcset="https://i0.wp.com/www.courant.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/thc-l-lobsters-1025-01.jpg?fit=620%2C9999px&amp;amp;ssl=1 620w,https://i0.wp.com/www.courant.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/thc-l-lobsters-1025-01.jpg?fit=780%2C9999px&amp;amp;ssl=1 780w,https://i0.wp.com/www.courant.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/thc-l-lobsters-1025-01.jpg?fit=810%2C9999px&amp;amp;ssl=1 810w,https://i0.wp.com/www.courant.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/thc-l-lobsters-1025-01.jpg?fit=1280%2C9999px&amp;amp;ssl=1 1280w,https://i0.wp.com/www.courant.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/thc-l-lobsters-1025-01.jpg?fit=1860%2C9999px&amp;amp;ssl=1 1860w"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Former lobsterman Bart Mansi sits in his office on the second story of the Guilford Lobster Pound on Sept. 3, 2025. (Dana Edwards / CT Mirror)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the 1980s and ’90s, &lt;a href="https://www.guilfordlobsterpound.com/"&gt;Mansi&lt;/a&gt; was making a killing, along with the roughly 1,200 commercial lobstermen on Long Island Sound. The Sound was the third most-productive lobster fishery in the country, with 10 million pounds of lobster landings at its peak in 1998, including 3.8 million pounds in Connecticut.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But in the fall of 1999, lobstermen pulled up traps filled with limp, sickly lobsters, and soon after, hardly any lobsters at all. It was an unprecedented mortality event, and the lobster population never recovered. Connecticut saw only 181,000 pounds of lobster landings in 2024, less than 5% of the 1998 peak. Now most seafood restaurants in the state — including Mansi’s — import lobster from Maine or Canada.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The catastrophic die-off is still an emotional subject for Mansi and so many former lobstermen. In addition to the painful memory of losing their livelihoods practically overnight, resentment lingers about how it happened. The scientific &lt;a href="https://portal.ct.gov/ceq/ar-23-gold/2023-ceq-annual-report-ebook/water-quality---rivers-lakes-and-estuaries/warming-and-rising-waters-of-long-island-sound"&gt;consensus is that warming waters,&lt;/a&gt; and an epidemic of a crustacean disease called paramoebiasis, were the primary culprits — and that pesticides used to combat West Nile virus may have had an additional effect.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But the &lt;a href="https://portal.ct.gov/deep/fishing/fisheries-management/lobster-assessment"&gt;catastrophe was complex and unprecedented&lt;/a&gt;, and not all scientists agree on which factors were the most significant. The lobstermen almost unanimously blame the pesticides, and they feel betrayed by the chemical manufacturers, the marine scientists, and the government — whose tightening regulations they resented and whose financial assistance they found inadequate.&lt;/p&gt;				
&lt;p&gt;In the early 2000s, as they fought for accountability and answers, the lobstermen had no choice but to adapt to the new reality. Some switched to fishing, clamming or catching conch, but most sold their boats and left the fishing docks behind entirely.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now there are no full-time commercial lobstermen left in Connecticut.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But there are still a few part-timers. In the southeasternmost corner of the state, the Stonington port is home to seven active lobster boats. Other than one boat in New London, Stonington is the last bastion of commercial lobstering in Connecticut. Roddy Grimshaw is one of the few in Stonington still at it, a man of 29 who goes lobstering with his dad and a small crew a few days a week.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It’s not just lobstering that’s in decline — all forms of commercial fishing are under threat as luxury development supplants the docks once home to a vibrant blue-collar fishing culture.&lt;/p&gt;				
&lt;p&gt;Grimshaw put it this way: “The way I see it, if we don’t stay active … this will become just another yacht club.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;The heyday&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mansi has fond memories of fishing with his family as a kid growing up in East Haven in the late 1960s.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I just loved being out on the water, the freedom,” he said. At that time, the Connecticut lobster industry was picking up steam after a decades-long lull around the turn of the century. His dad wasn’t a lobsterman, more of a recreational fisherman, but, eyeing the hauls of lobstermen down at the docks, he decided to give it a shot. He started working on a friend’s father’s lobster boat while he was in high school in the 1970s. Then, in 1983, he bought his own boat, the Jani M.— named after his wife — and went into business for himself. And business was good.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“When you left the dock, you knew you were gonna catch lobsters. It was exciting. You’re dying to pull that first trap to see what was in it. And, you know, they were almost always full,” he said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure id="attachment_8662036" class="wp-caption alignnone size-article_inline"&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class=" lazyautosizes lazyload" src="https://i0.wp.com/www.courant.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/05/thc-l-HC-EQ-LOBSTER-2_159358513.jpg?fit=620%2C9999px&amp;amp;ssl=1" alt="Lobsterman Bart Mansi III and his son, Bart Mansi IV, at left, load about 120 lobster pots onto his boat, the Erica Paige, at the Guilford Lobster Pound on June 25, 2008. Mansi was preparing to set the pots for the summer season early the next morning. (Bob MacDonnell/Hartford Courant file)" data-sizes="auto" data-src="https://i0.wp.com/www.courant.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/05/thc-l-HC-EQ-LOBSTER-2_159358513.jpg?fit=620%2C9999px&amp;amp;ssl=1" data-attachment-id="8662036" data-srcset="https://i0.wp.com/www.courant.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/05/thc-l-HC-EQ-LOBSTER-2_159358513.jpg?fit=620%2C9999px&amp;amp;ssl=1 620w,https://i0.wp.com/www.courant.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/05/thc-l-HC-EQ-LOBSTER-2_159358513.jpg?fit=780%2C9999px&amp;amp;ssl=1 780w,https://i0.wp.com/www.courant.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/05/thc-l-HC-EQ-LOBSTER-2_159358513.jpg?fit=810%2C9999px&amp;amp;ssl=1 810w,https://i0.wp.com/www.courant.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/05/thc-l-HC-EQ-LOBSTER-2_159358513.jpg?fit=1280%2C9999px&amp;amp;ssl=1 1280w,https://i0.wp.com/www.courant.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/05/thc-l-HC-EQ-LOBSTER-2_159358513.jpg?fit=1860%2C9999px&amp;amp;ssl=1 1860w"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Lobsterman Bart Mansi III and his son, Bart Mansi IV, at left, load about 120 lobster pots onto his boat, the Erica Paige, at the Guilford Lobster Pound on June 25, 2008. Mansi was preparing to set the pots for the summer season early the next morning. (Bob MacDonnell/Hartford Courant file)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the ’80s and ’90s, Mansi was landing up to 100,000 pounds per year on just his boat, over 50% of the state’s entire 2024 haul. At a market price of $3 per pound, he was making a killing. He also started the Guilford Lobster Pound, a wholesaler that bought lobster from other fishermen and sold it to Connecticut retailers and restaurants.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mansi described a vibrant waterfront community at the Guilford Marina and at fishing docks across the state. He pointed to a newspaper article framed on his wall, which told the story of a fellow Guilford lobsterman who suffered a heart attack.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“We got six lobstermen all together, and we ended up going out and pulling all his gear. We brought all his lobsters to the pound here, we sold his lobsters, and we gave him a check. We all stuck together,” he said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mansi wasn’t the only one to turn a high school lobstering job into a lucrative career in those years. Some 30 miles down the Sound in Norwalk, Gary Whetmore grew up lobstering with his dad.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“My father lobstered on a very small scale, and then I got into it on a much bigger scale,” Whetmore said. “I remember swapping lobsters with a gym teacher to get out of classes.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Gary Whetmore stands for a portrait on his boat in Norwalk on Aug. 19, 2025. Credit: Dana Edwards / CT Mirror&lt;br&gt;
“It was fun. It wasn’t work. The money was great, but it was the freedom of it. You could make as much or as little as you wanted to make. And if you worked hard enough, you could have anything you want in the world,” he said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One might think that the accelerating lobster hauls in those days — a roughly six-fold increase in Connecticut from the 1970s to the 1990s — risked depleting the lobster population. Counterintuitively, the reverse was true.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“There were a lot of lobsters,” Whetmore continued, “but it wasn’t natural.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Connecticut lobstermen from that era describe their work not as catching lobsters but, rather, “farming”  them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class=" size-article_inline lazyautosizes lazyload" src="https://i0.wp.com/www.courant.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/LOBSTER-0925-DE-183-768x509aaaa.jpg?fit=620%2C9999px&amp;amp;ssl=1" alt="Gary Whetmore stands for a portrait on his boat in Norwalk on Aug. 19, 2025. Credit: Dana Edwards / CT Mirror" data-sizes="auto" data-src="https://i0.wp.com/www.courant.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/LOBSTER-0925-DE-183-768x509aaaa.jpg?fit=620%2C9999px&amp;amp;ssl=1" data-attachment-id="8871021" data-srcset="https://i0.wp.com/www.courant.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/LOBSTER-0925-DE-183-768x509aaaa.jpg?fit=620%2C9999px&amp;amp;ssl=1 620w,https://i0.wp.com/www.courant.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/LOBSTER-0925-DE-183-768x509aaaa.jpg?fit=780%2C9999px&amp;amp;ssl=1 780w,https://i0.wp.com/www.courant.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/LOBSTER-0925-DE-183-768x509aaaa.jpg?fit=810%2C9999px&amp;amp;ssl=1 810w,https://i0.wp.com/www.courant.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/LOBSTER-0925-DE-183-768x509aaaa.jpg?fit=1280%2C9999px&amp;amp;ssl=1 1280w,https://i0.wp.com/www.courant.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/LOBSTER-0925-DE-183-768x509aaaa.jpg?fit=1860%2C9999px&amp;amp;ssl=1 1860w"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“We were feeding them and letting them go,” Whetmore said. Indeed, in the ’80s and ’90s, lobstermen were stuffing millions of pounds of bait fish — pogy, mackerel, and others — into tens of thousands of traps in Long Island Sound.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The influx of bait represented a huge supplement to the lobsters’ natural food sources, artificially increasing the population to levels never before seen in the Sound. It was great for business, but scientists say the crowded crustacean conditions on the seafloor, combined with the unnaturally young population — lobstermen harvested them as soon as they reached the minimum size required by regulation — likely left them more vulnerable to the disease that decimated the population in the late ’90s. It was the boom before the bust.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It was not sustainable. Something was going to give,” Whetmore said. “There were no big lobsters here. As soon as they were legal, we harvested them. We’re feeding them, we’re growing them, and we’re harvesting, and whoever worked the hardest harvested the most. And that’s as simple as it was.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It was really, really good, and when it ended, it ended,” Whetmore said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mansi spoke of the sudden die-off with a similar sense of finality. “You go out there one day, and that’s it. Overnight, it was done. It was ended,” he said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;The die-off&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the years leading up to the widespread die-off in the fall of 1999, there were early signs of trouble. Two localized lobster mortality events occurred in the &lt;a href="https://www.researchgate.net/publication/287002284_The_1999_Long_Island_Sound_Lobster_mortality_event_Findings_of_the_Comprehensive_Research_Initiative"&gt;western Sound, f&lt;/a&gt;rom Norwalk to Greenwich, in 1997 and 1998.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Whetmore, just a few miles further east, took heed of those early warnings. “I heard about the die-off getting as far up as Greenwich in ’98. And I told my guys that were working for me: If it happens next year, and it comes this way, we’re done. And sure enough, it got here,” he said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In August 1999, dead lobsters started washing up on beaches along the Sound. On Sept. 16, Tropical Storm Floyd hit the region, dumping up to 12 inches of rain into the Sound in just two days.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By the following week, Long Island Sound’s lobster industry practically collapsed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“A week after the storm, when I went out, the lobsters in the pots were nothing but goo. It smelled. It was nothing but lobster parts,” said Tony Carlo, a Darien lobsterman.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href="https://www.researchgate.net/publication/287002284_The_1999_Long_Island_Sound_Lobster_mortality_event_Findings_of_the_Comprehensive_Research_Initiative"&gt;Western Sound was hit the hardest,&lt;/a&gt; that fall experiencing a 99% reduction in lobster landings compared to the previous year. Ports in the east of the Sound saw reductions of 64% to 91%.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At first, neither the lobstermen nor marine scientists had a clear understanding of the cause. A New York Times headline on Oct. 18, 1999, read, “Scientists Are Mystified by Deaths Of Lobsters in Long Island.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But there was a suspicious coincidence. In August, just a month before the storm, the government began applying pesticides, including resmethrin and methoprene, across Connecticut and New York to curb the spread of West Nile Virus. Because lobsters are related to insects, which the pesticides were designed to kill, many suspected that the runoff from the storm poisoned the lobsters.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In January 2000, a “commercial fishery failure” was declared in the Sound, and the federal government authorized $13.9 million to provide economic relief for the lobstermen and to fund research into the causes of the disaster. Over 20 research projects across a slew of institutions and agencies were approved.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When the studies concluded by 2004, a clearer picture emerged. A parasitic amoeba, &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC8145359/"&gt;Neoparamoeba pemaquidensis,&lt;/a&gt; had infected and killed the lobsters. But it wasn’t just the disease. Researchers referred to a &lt;a href="https://www.courant.com/2017/03/16/proposals-aim-to-restore-lobsters-to-long-island-sound/"&gt;“perfect storm” of contributing factors.&lt;/a&gt; Years of above-average water temperatures weakened the immune systems of the lobsters, which are extremely sensitive to temperature increases. The storm may have accelerated the die-off by churning up the waters, bringing warmer temperatures to the already sick lobsters. Furthermore, the unnaturally high and primarily juvenile population was particularly vulnerable to infection.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“When you have a bunch of young animals all together, just like a cold in a classroom at school, the disease spreads through them pretty quickly,” said biologist Nancy Balcom, associate director of Connecticut Sea Grant, who was involved in research after the die-off and published several articles summarizing the findings.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the decades since 1999, the lobster population would appear to rebound in some years with a new crop of juvenile lobsters.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“But then a few years later, you didn’t see the adults,” Balcom said. This is consistent with the finding that the water is just getting too warm for the lobsters to tolerate, even though the paramoebiosis epidemic has passed. Long Island Sound has historically been the southernmost tip of the inshore range of the American lobster. With global warming, that map is being redrawn, and their range may soon terminate in Massachusetts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;The pesticides&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The role of the pesticides loomed large immediately after the die-off. Toxicology testing and several modeling exercises were conducted, but even the “worst case scenario” model indicated that the concentration of the chemicals never reached lethal levels for the lobsters. The scientific consensus is that the pesticides were not the primary cause of the die-off.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That consensus, however, is not ironclad, and most of the lobstermen don’t buy it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“The pesticides are what killed them,” Mansi said. “We actually see what’s going on. We were there, and we’re telling you what we saw. They [the scientists] have never been on the water, they just sit in a lab and they make up these models that we have to adhere to.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The timing of the pesticide application and the storm runoff was uncanny, and the lobstermen observed strange, hyperactive behavior in some living lobsters they caught after the die-off, as well as in certain species of crabs. Mansi helped recruit a biologist the lobstermen considered one of their own, Dr. Robert Bayer of Maine’s Lobster Institute. Bayer came down to Connecticut, performed his own tests, and concluded that the lobsters hauled alive during the 1999 event “showed the behaviors, classic behaviors, of pesticide poisoning — which is hyperactivity.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the months and years that followed, while the government-funded studies were still underway, the lobstermen initiated a class action lawsuit against Cheminova and other pesticide makers, eventually receiving two settlements, for $12.5 million and $3.75 million. The lobstermen see the settlement as a vindication of their hypothesis, while Balcom says the pesticide makers never admitted to causing the die-off and merely settled to make the lawsuit go away.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“If the pesticides were the primary cause of death, they would have received probably lots more money,” she said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tarsila Seara, a social scientist who studies fishing communities, views the science as less settled, and she understands the animosity Mansi and many other lobstermen still feel towards the biologists, the pesticide companies and the government. In 2019, while a professor at the University of New Haven, she interviewed 20 former lobstermen and published two papers about the social impacts of the die-off.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“There was a dismissal of their experience and the knowledge that the fishermen were trying to bring to the table,” Seara said. “It should have been dealt with differently.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“The reality is that it was a very complex combination of factors, and the lobstermen really wanted to find the one thing that they could blame, and they were naturally upset because there was no backing of that one culprit,” she said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tony Carlo and Roger Frate, cousins who started lobstering in the 1970s in central Connecticut, were active in the fight against the pesticide companies in the early 2000s. Frate now runs the &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/darienseafood/"&gt;Darien Seafood Market&lt;/a&gt; with Carlo’s help. Alongside tanks with live lobsters (now imported from Maine or Canada), the store has multiple display cases with newspaper articles documenting the die-off and ensuing legal battles.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The two cousins are still angry at the chemical makers, politicians and marine scientists they see as responsible for causing — or failing to address — the destruction of their livelihood.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“We lost everything within a three-week period,” Carlo said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“We fought in Washington, Hartford, Boston … we fought against some big people at the chemical companies. We kept going for years and years,” Frate said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Frate and Carlo see the government’s regulatory response in the 2000s — mandating an increase in “gauge” size (a device used to measure the minimum-sized lobsters legal to catch), as well as a 90-day moratorium imposed on lobstering from early September to early December — as harmful and misguided.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“From beginning to end, it seemed like they were always against us, to slow us down one way or another,” Carlo said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They argued for years that the real culprit was toxicity from the pesticides, as well as an accumulation of other pollutants from decades of runoff into the Sound. They asked for money to “clean up” the Sound and more financial support for the struggling lobstermen. But their pleas fell on deaf ears.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Frate and Carlo hold a litany of grudges against the Connecticut and New York politicians of that era.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Schumer would never call us back … Blumenthal’s telling lies … Chris Shays, that piece of shit. You got your money. The state got their money. Now the fisheries’ money’s not there,” Frate said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Frate and Carlo did eventually collect checks from the pesticide maker settlements. “But it wasn’t about the money,” Carlo said. “We’d give it all back to them if they could give us back Long Island Sound. We want our lobster back.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;A difficult adjustment&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Seara, the social scientist, understands the animosity towards the government in the years following the die-off.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“They were not being supported when they were going through something that was very impactful, very traumatic,” she said. “Some of the programs the government put in place were not well received. They didn’t seem to make sense to a lot of the fishermen.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Over the years, there were some experiments with lobster trap buyback programs, which paid lobstermen to recover the thousands of abandoned pots littering the seafloor. In September, these programs received a $1.8 million boost of federal funding.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Other programs included various job retraining efforts, which lobstermen like Mansi scoff at to this day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“They said, ‘We’ll train you.’ Well, there’s no retraining. You don’t take a guy that’s been fishing on the water all his life and retrain him to go work in an office. It’s something that you can’t do,” Mansi said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What made the prospect of retraining particularly unappealing is that, for so many lobstermen, lobstering is not just a job but a deeply held identity and beloved lifestyle. Seara, along with her mentor, Professor Richard Pollnac, have studied fishing communities across the world, and they’ve found that self-employed fishermen experience some of the highest levels of job satisfaction of any workers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It’s the freedom, being out in the water, being close to nature, and some aspects that are thrilling. It’s a gamble, right? You’re out there, you don’t know what you’re going to get. Every day is different. You have encounters with nature, whales, and beautiful sunsets, and, on top of it, this adventure and this challenge, and this camaraderie,” Seara said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“A fisherman once put it to me like this: ‘What other profession in the world do you know that people pay to do over the weekend?’” she said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Each lobsterman took their own path after the die-off. Some turned to clamming or catching conch, but most couldn’t find a way to support themselves on the water. Many struggled.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“We had a lot of guys who became alcoholics or drug addicts,” Mansi said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“We had to move on,” Mansi said. “I am still bitter about what happened, because not only did they wipe out an industry, they wiped out a way of life,” he said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mansi turned his lobster pound on the docks in Guilford into a seasonal restaurant. He considers himself lucky, as he’s still able to work down by the water, and his son runs a fishing boat out of the same port.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Carlo initially got a job doing manual labor down at the docks in Norwalk for $10 an hour, “just to do something and stay near the water,” but it didn’t pay the bills. He was forced to find a new career, so he started a landscaping business, which he still runs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Landscaping, being on land … I hated it. Hated it. I hate it to this day,” Carlo said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One of the few who seemed to transition smoothly was Whetmore. Immediately after the die-off, he got into marine construction, and he now runs a successful business out of Norwalk, G&amp;amp;C Marine, which primarily builds residential docks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Whetmore was included in Seara’s 2019 study; notably, he was the sole lobsterman out of the 20 interviewed who said they believe that warming waters and the disease were to blame for the die-off. Even his own son insists it was the pesticides.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You can’t argue the numbers. You know, the bottom temperature, it’s there,” Whetmore said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He attributes his ability to adapt — and his acceptance of immovable forces like global warming — to a feeling that he is lucky to be alive. In the last two decades, he’s had two kidney transplants, cancer and multiple heart attacks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Stonington’s working docks smell like diesel and bait.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On a sunny September afternoon, a flock of gulls circled the docks as the Lady Lynn cruised into the harbor — 42 feet of scuffed fiberglass, stacked with crusty lobster traps. The Lady Lynn is one of seven lobster boats still operating out of Stonington, the last commercial lobster fleet in Connecticut.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Roddy Grimshaw was on deck with his crew, Ian Crimm and Bubba Dolith, his 10-month-old puppy, Bailey, who ran back and forth excitedly, and his dad, Mike, who bought the Lady Lynn back in the ’70s. They were in a rush to haul out all their traps before Sept. 7, when the season closed for 90 days.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After unloading all the traps into massive stacks on the dock, Grimshaw took a breather.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“When I’m on the boat, I’m always active, doing something like hauling lobsters, driving the boat, hauling the gear, seeing interesting things. I just, I love it, and I love to tan,” he said, laughing. Grimshaw showed off a new tattoo of a lobster on his very tan forearm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It’s been a good year,” he said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Grimshaw was averaging 160 lobsters (totaling about 200 pounds) each time he pulled traps. Though it’s a far cry from the quadruple digits his dad used to haul back in the ’90s, it’s an improvement from last year.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It’s not a coincidence that the last remnants of the state’s lobster industry are located in Stonington. Just outside of Long Island Sound, only a few miles from the Rhode Island border, the area has somewhat cooler water, and its fishery wasn’t hit as hard by the die-off in the ’90s.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These days, Grimshaw lobsters two to three days per week and the rest of the week goes out “dragging” for fish — flounder, whiting, sea bass and others. But lobstering is his true love, and he’d like to dedicate himself to it full-time, though he says the catch is just too variable to rely on. His eyes lit up when he considered the possibility. “It’s a big, big idea, and it would be so great,” he said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One of his other struggles is fetching a reasonable price for the lobsters he lands. Lobster imported from Maine and Canada for roughly $3 per pound dominate the market, which just isn’t enough to cover his costs. So he sells directly to the public on the docks in addition to selling to wholesalers who are willing to pay about $7 per pound, this year’s going rate for Connecticut lobsters.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;His crew members, Crimm, 18 and Dolith, 19, kidded around as they fixed up the engine and organized tools. They’re new to working with Grimshaw, who recently had to replace his entire crew after he discovered that one was drinking on the job, and the other was a registered sex offender.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Crimm and Dolith love the work, even though Grimshaw can give them a hard time. Neither of them has had what they’d consider a “normal” job — they’ve bounced between farming and other forms of manual labor — and they want to keep working on the Lady Lynn as long as there are lobster to be caught.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It’s not a normal 9-to-5, which I hate. I can’t do them,” Dolith said while pulling up lobster pots hanging off the side of the Lady Lynn in the harbor.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Their boss, Grimshaw, plans to take over his dad’s lobstering license in January. At 29, as the youngest active commercial lobster captain in the state, he’ll represent both the next generation and the last of the line.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Grimshaw understands the weight of his position.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“There’s not many other people here that does it, that wants to do it,” Grimshaw said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He pointed to a seafood restaurant and yacht club visible in the distance. “If this harbor wasn’t here, it wouldn’t make a difference to the tourists and out-of-town people. And I just don’t want to see that,” he said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I want to continue,” he said. “I don’t see myself doing something different.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Whetmore expressed a similar unease with the luxury development and tourism taking over the waterfront that used to be home to so many fishing and working docks. While walking around his construction yard in Norwalk one August afternoon, he pointed to the neighboring lots.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“There were oil tankers on this river. There were fishermen going down the river. Now it’s condos and rowing clubs. It’s definitely changing. It’s been very gentrified.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Norwalk Planning &amp;amp; Zoning Commission just approved a 59-unit mixed-use complex, with luxury apartments and a boardwalk, on the property adjacent to Whetmore’s construction yard. He said the town government has applied enormous pressure on him to move his business.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In town after town along the Sound, the working waterfront is giving way to luxury housing and recreation. A 2022 mid-Atlantic fisheries briefing flagged “persistent trends toward gentrification of working waterfronts,” noting that the loss of maritime space can upend the cultural identity of fishing communities.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“They don’t want equipment like this. They need us when we build their docks, their yacht clubs, their rowing clubs, and they love us when we’re building them, but they don’t want to see us,” Whetmore said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“There was a community, a waterfront community, and that’s gone,” he said. “That way of life is gone.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dana Edwards of Columbia University is a Photojournalism Fellow  for The Connecticut Mirror (https://ctmirror.org/ ). Copyright 2025 © The Connecticut Mirror..&lt;/p&gt;

			&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Hartford Courant</author><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 09:01:49 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMirAFBVV95cUxNTXRqdF80YWltLTZ3Ym1Gb2Q3azNyUDVzNTVCY28xQ1Vfc1Z1a3ZqSFQyWVBiVGNIRldfc3Flek9XQThJQTdIUkJHQTVIck9yOVAyZVZmMURWTmFEenFxWDJMS2JjdFpudmh1VUxhVEtSWVpBa1JPcEthSVQ0dTJENVBEOGhTS0w0RGxGbk9YQUxqcnFZdjFVZDdJcnRwNkt2aUZHeEVUdUJBY09P</guid></item><item><title>美国有线电视新闻网首播：市卫生官员敦促接种疫苗，批评联邦政府的信息传递-美国有线电视新闻网</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2025/10/20/health/vaccines-city-health-officials</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article__content" data-editable="content" itemprop="articleBody" data-reorderable="content"&gt;
                
    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgy3bwy8004x26p33s686c16@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The Big Cities Health Coalition is the latest group to take a strong public stand in support of vaccination as a direct response to concerns that the federal government is limiting access and raising doubts.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgy3cb4h00043b6nbu1oeq9v@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “We are united behind a simple message: get vaccinated,” the group wrote in a &lt;a href="https://www.bigcitieshealth.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/VaxMemberStatement.October2025.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;statement&lt;/a&gt; that was published Monday. It was signed by two dozen public health leaders from some of the nation’s largest cities, in both Democrat- and Republican-led states.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgy3cb4h00053b6nl9ia75m4@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Vaccination has saved millions of lives, they wrote, but falling vaccination rates across the country have led to more frequent outbreaks of devastating diseases such as measles and polio. They also referenced the “rapidly approaching” respiratory virus season, which brings a heavy wave of Covid-19 and flu infections.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgy3cb4h00063b6n692ikxoo@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “We are deeply troubled by the repeated false claims about vaccines from too many federal officials, which have contributed directly to these trends,” the public health leaders wrote. “We are equally concerned about recent changes to the recommended childhood and adult immunization schedules that unnecessarily limit access to vaccines.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgy3cb4h00073b6nf1v8b1x9@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Vaccine advisers to the US Centers for Disease Control and Prevention &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2025/09/18/health/cdc-vaccine-panel-acip-mmrv-hepatitis"&gt;voted&lt;/a&gt; last month to recommend against the combined measles, mumps, rubella and varicella (MMRV) vaccine for children younger than 4, and a new working group will convene to more broadly assess the safety, effectiveness and timing of the shots children and adolescents get, as well as whether &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2025/10/09/health/cdc-acip-vaccine-working-group"&gt;the schedule should be changed&lt;/a&gt;.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgy3cb4h00083b6nws1wzadu@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            And at a recent Cabinet meeting, President Donald Trump made &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2025/10/09/politics/fact-check-trump-cabinet-meeting"&gt;numerous false claims&lt;/a&gt; about vaccines given to children, including about the size of vaccine doses and that babies get 82 vaccines in a single shot.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgy3cb4h00093b6ni88031zx@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            As vaccination becomes increasingly politicized, city health officials say, they felt a need to speak up to protect their communities.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgy3cb4h000a3b6nkcrasbhy@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “We have to make our public health decisions based on data and not on political ideology,” said Dr. Phil Huang, director of the Dallas County Health and Human Services Department. “We have to be the voices for that science and reason.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgy3cb4h000b3b6nz8gc5wnq@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Multiple major medical organizations – including the &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2025/08/19/health/covid-vaccine-recommendation-aap"&gt;American Academy of Pediatrics&lt;/a&gt; and the &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2025/08/22/health/covid-vaccine-pregnancy-acog-recommendations"&gt;American College of Obstetricians and Gynecologists&lt;/a&gt; – have broken from the CDC on vaccine guidance. And new &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2025/09/03/health/west-coast-states-health-guidance"&gt;public health organizations have formed&lt;/a&gt; in recent months with an aim to safeguard public health amid turmoil at the federal level.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgy3cb4h000c3b6nei209twu@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The Big Cities Health Coalition, with members representing about a fifth of the US population, has been working together to exchange ideas and address public health threats for more than two decades.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgy3cb4h000d3b6ntp7e7jrx@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            But the “threats are growing and becoming more complicated,” said Dr. Raynard Washington, director of public health for Mecklenburg County, North Carolina – including from the federal government.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgy3cb4h000e3b6nbyrgn33k@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “There’s a lot of conversation happening about how, in the absence of a strong federal public health system, we are able to navigate and ensure that we continue to protect public safety,” he said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgy3cb4h000f3b6nc0d3srv7@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Consistency is important in public health, and the federal structure helped facilitate that, he said. But in the absence of that, coordination becomes key.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgy3cb4h000g3b6neg1xv8cc@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            A measles outbreak is growing quickly in the upstate region of South Carolina, just about 100 miles from Charlotte.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgy3cb4h000h3b6n4uaazu5o@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “I don’t have any walls to put up to keep folks from Mecklenburg going into South Carolina, or people from South Carolina going into Mecklenburg County,” Washington said. “So as a country, our local public health system is only as strong as the weakest county or jurisdiction. There is an importance of ensuring that we work collaboratively, because the boundaries that we actually exist in are only administrative.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgy3cb4h000i3b6nddo8hb7b@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            More than 100 unvaccinated students in South Carolina are in quarantine because of a &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2025/10/10/health/measles-outbreaks-utah-arizona-south-carolina"&gt;measles&lt;/a&gt; exposure in school – one of the many reasons why Big Cities Health Coalition emphasizes the importance of vaccination.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgy3cb4h000j3b6n5jwp5t09@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Vaccines “keep classrooms safe and schools open. They allow children to spend time with friends and enjoy their favorite activities. They help parents and caregivers work to support their families,” the organizations wrote in the new letter.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgy3cb4h000k3b6n2x7kd6j3@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Trust also plays a key role in public health, experts say, and city health leaders want to provide reassurance to their communities.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgy3cb4h000l3b6ndhg188u9@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “CDC has been the pinnacle of our public health science up until now. Now it seems more driven by political ideology than actual data and science, so it undermines the trust,” Huang said. “We’re all having to band together and provide that credible data- and science-driven messaging.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgy3cb4h000m3b6nognbjc47@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            A recent &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2025/10/09/health/rfk-approval-cdc-trust-vaccines-kff"&gt;KFF poll&lt;/a&gt; found that public trust in the CDC is the lowest it’s been since the Covid-19 pandemic began. Only half of adults in the US say they trust the agency to provide reliable vaccine information, down from 57% in July and 63% in September 2024.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgy3cb4h000n3b6ntx0ezq96@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “Despite all the chaos and mixed messages, we remain steadfast in our commitment to the health of our communities and making sure the message is clear on the importance of vaccination,” Huang said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

              &lt;/div&gt;
                  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>CNN</author><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 09:00:51 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMid0FVX3lxTE85NXlIbl9vUnlTOGV5dGtPWk92b1NYcEJialdTRVRjWTVaZkZKWndsQm1oMTdSUXM1XzQwR3VCTnVtdnZBc1dweHZSb3dGTHl3azRqNzdlM1ZXQUswX0Z1LWJjV0tzWG9UMWF5QWN3TDEwMldnTGlB</guid></item><item><title>胶原蛋白补充剂能改善皮肤吗？以下是研究显示的情况-美国国家公共广播电台</title><link>https://www.npr.org/2025/10/20/nx-s1-5560956/collagen-supplements-skin-joints</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="storytext" class="storytext storylocation linkLocation"&gt;
      &lt;div id="resg-s1-94018" class="bucketwrap image large"&gt;
            
&lt;div class="credit-caption"&gt;
    &lt;div class="caption-wrap"&gt;
        &lt;div class="caption" aria-label="Image caption"&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;
                Collagen is the most abundant protein in our bodies. It helps keep our skin firm and elastic. But as we age, the amount and quality of that collagen declines. And some people turn to supplements.
                &lt;b class="credit" aria-label="Image credit"&gt;
                    
                    Luis Echeverri Urrea/iStockphoto/Getty Images
                    
                &lt;/b&gt;
                &lt;b class="hide-caption"&gt;&lt;b&gt;hide caption&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;
            &lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;


            &lt;b class="toggle-caption"&gt;&lt;b&gt;toggle caption&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;

    &lt;span class="credit" aria-label="Image credit"&gt;
        
        Luis Echeverri Urrea/iStockphoto/Getty Images
        
    &lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;The explorer Ponce de Leon famously went to Florida in search of the fountain of youth. But if you listen to social media influencers, he should probably have headed to the &lt;a href="https://www.npr.org/2025/09/04/nx-s1-5526053/are-creatine-supplements-all-that-theyre-pumped-up-to-be" target="_blank"&gt;supplement aisle &lt;/a&gt;to pick up some collagen.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"I'm in my 40s and if I shave, I look like I'm in my mid-20s," a Tiktok creator who goes by Shop By Jake claims &lt;a href="https://www.tiktok.com/@shopbyjake/video/7423801980809760043?q=collagen&amp;amp;t=1760564499655" target="_blank"&gt; in one paid promotion&lt;/a&gt;. "People ask me all the time, what do you do for your skin? I take collagen," he says.&lt;/p&gt;   
   
   

   &lt;p&gt;Claims about the health and beauty benefits of collagen supplements are commonplace these days, especially online. But does the evidence back the hype?&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;h3 class="edTag"&gt;The claim&lt;/h3&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Collagen supplements can promote healthier skin, hair and nails, and stronger joints.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;h3 class="edTag"&gt;The theory&lt;/h3&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Collagen is the most &lt;a href="https://my.clevelandclinic.org/health/articles/23089-collagen" target="_blank"&gt;abundant protein in the body&lt;/a&gt;. It's found in skin, hair, nails, tendons, ligaments, cartilage and bones. It helps maintain our skin's elasticity and volume. It's a structural protein, so it gives strength and integrity to our tissues and keeps joints strong, among other things. But starting in our 20s, the amount and quality of the collagen our bodies produce declines.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Factors lik&lt;a href="https://www.npr.org/sections/shots-health-news/2024/06/17/nx-s1-5002030/sunscreen-tiktok-misinformation-melanoma" target="_blank"&gt;e UV radiation, &lt;/a&gt;smoking and exposure to&lt;a href="https://www.npr.org/sections/shots-health-news/2025/06/18/nx-s1-5436960/maha-rfk-toxic-chemicals-trump-hhs-epa" target="_blank"&gt; environmental pollutants &lt;/a&gt;can speed up that decline. But it's going to happen with age regardless, which is why lots of people turn to collagen supplements.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Collagen supplements generally come in two main forms.&lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC8944283/" target="_blank"&gt; Hydrolyzed collagen peptides&lt;/a&gt; are basically collagen that's been broken down into smaller chains of amino acids to make them easier to absorb. They're derived from animal sources, such as fish, cattle, pigs or chicken. That's typically what's used in supplements aimed at improving skin and hair, as well as joint health.  &lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"The theory is that if you ingest [a collagen supplement,] it goes through the GI tract and gets absorbed and then it theoretically goes to places to support or increase collagen production," says &lt;a href="https://www.nm.org/doctors/1720366636/lauren-taglia-md-phd" target="_blank"&gt;Dr. Lauren Taglia&lt;/a&gt;, a board-certified dermatologist with Northwestern Medicine in Naperville, Ill.&lt;/p&gt;   
   &lt;p&gt;The second main form of supplement is &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC10058045/#:~:text=Native%20type%20II%20collagen%20has,tissues%20and%20exert%20chondroprotective%20effects." target="_blank"&gt;undenatured, or native, type II collagen&lt;/a&gt;, which hasn't been broken down. It's derived from chickens. Most of the collagen found in cartilage is type II. These kinds of supplements are thought to promote joint health by triggering the immune system to produce chemical messengers that tamp down inflammation.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;So what does the research say?&lt;/p&gt;   
   

   &lt;h3 class="edTag"&gt;The evidence&lt;/h3&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Let's start with skin.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;When it comes to skin health, there are studies that suggest collagen supplements work.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"There have been randomized controlled trials that have shown that after 8 to 12 weeks of collagen supplementation, things like depth of wrinkles, skin elasticity, dermal thickness seem to be improved," says&lt;a href="https://connects.catalyst.harvard.edu/Profiles/display/Person/10176" target="_blank"&gt; Dr. Maryanne Makredes Senna&lt;/a&gt;, an assistant professor of dermatology at Harvard Medical School.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;One &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/33742704/" target="_blank"&gt;meta-analysis of 19 studies published in 2021&lt;/a&gt; found that, compared with a placebo, people taking collagen supplements had better skin hydration, elasticity and improvements in wrinkles.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;A &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40324552/" target="_blank"&gt;second meta-analysis &lt;/a&gt;was published this year. It looked at 23 randomized controlled trials with more than 1,400 patients who took collagen supplements for skin issues, and it also found significant improvements in those same areas after 90 days.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;But Senna says those findings came with a big caveat: The studies that found the biggest improvements were lower-quality and were funded by the supplement industry, she says.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"High-quality studies and studies not funded by industry did not show a significant association rate," Senna says.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Given that, the state of the evidence when it comes to collagen supplements for skin is mixed at best, says dermatologist Lauren Taglia. "As physician-scientists, we would love to see studies done on a large scale and done independently," she says.&lt;/p&gt;   
   

   &lt;p&gt;It's a similar story when it comes to collagen supplements for joint health. Studies have shown benefits — such as in &lt;a href="https://bjsm.bmj.com/content/52/3/167" target="_blank"&gt;reducing pain from osteoarthritis&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;But again, much of the research is industry funded, so it can be hard to disentangle potential bias, says &lt;a href="https://www.bumc.bu.edu/camed/profile/david-felson/" target="_blank"&gt;Dr. David Felson&lt;/a&gt;, an osteoarthritis researcher and professor at Boston University.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;One &lt;a href="https://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/abs/10.1111/1756-185X.14382" target="_blank"&gt;systematic review &lt;/a&gt;found that most of the studies of collagen supplements for rheumatoid arthritis and osteoarthritis were too low quality to determine whether they really helped. Some studies included in that review reported adverse effects, such as an exacerbation of symptoms.&lt;/p&gt;   
   &lt;p&gt;"With respect to collagen, I don't know what the right answer is," Felson says. It could potentially help, but "there are no large scale studies here and there need to be," he says.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;h3 class="edTag"&gt;The bottom line&lt;/h3&gt;   &lt;p&gt;If it's healthier skin you're after, collagen supplements "could be helpful, but there's not a ton of strong evidence to support them at this point," Taglia says.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Your best bet is to focus on things that do have robust evidence behind them, says &lt;a href="https://wexnermedical.osu.edu/find-a-doctor/maya-jonas-md-121877" target="_blank"&gt;Dr. Maya Jonas&lt;/a&gt;, an assistant professor of dermatology at the Ohio State University. That includes&lt;a href="https://www.npr.org/sections/health-shots/2023/06/04/1179542293/picking-the-right-sunscreen-isnt-as-important-as-avoiding-these-6-mistakes" target="_blank"&gt; wearing sunscreen and other sun protection&lt;/a&gt; and using &lt;a href="https://health.osu.edu/health/skin-and-body/what-retinoids-can-do-for-skin" target="_blank"&gt;vitamin A-based products like retinol&lt;/a&gt;, which have been clinically proven to stimulate collagen production. Keeping your skin moisturized is also important.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Lifestyle factors matter too, Jonas says. She recommends a diet rich in fruits and vegetables, which provide antioxidants like vitamin C, and nuts and seeds, which are good sources of zinc and copper and help support collagen production.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"We always talk about diet, making sure patients are eating a healthy Mediterranean diet that's well-balanced, avoiding alcohol, not smoking and avoiding secondhand smoke," Jonas says.&lt;/p&gt;   
   

   &lt;p&gt;And &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC10979338/" target="_blank"&gt;get plenty of sleep and exercise&lt;/a&gt;, adds Senna. Poor sleep and stress can &lt;a href="https://www.jstage.jst.go.jp/article/jnsv/63/1/63_15/_article" target="_blank"&gt;take a toll on skin&lt;/a&gt;, while exercise can improve blood flow to the skin and may &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41598-023-37207-9" target="_blank"&gt;help counteract the loss of elasticity and dermal thickness&lt;/a&gt; that comes with aging.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;That's not just good for skin, but overall health, too.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>NPR</author><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 09:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigwFBVV95cUxNRUc2RTJBNDNwdi1hdm1hdGJEMEllYXFJV2UyRHh4OXcxS2Z4dHVjWFRkWUFCZTBKSkUwN2R3bnRlQ0N3WWhGdVUzR3dzWUVJVlR4VkFuTi1LbjJHQ01kb09nSE5MdkNkaWhaX0VuVlpPaXZJU1pNRWhlN2RZM0Jya2QzZw</guid></item><item><title>研究发现，由于2015年具有里程碑意义的建议，约有6万名儿童避免了花生过敏-哥伦比亚广播公司新闻</title><link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/peanut-allergies-60000-kids-avoided-2015-advice/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;section class="content__body"&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;A decade after a landmark study proved that feeding peanut products to young babies could prevent development of life-threatening allergies, new research finds the change has made a big difference in the real world. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;About 60,000 children have avoided developing peanut allergies after guidance first issued in 2015 upended medical practice by recommending introducing the allergen to infants starting as early as 4 months. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"That's a remarkable thing, right?" said Dr. David Hill, an allergist and researcher at Children's Hospital of Philadelphia, and author of a study published Monday in the medical journal Pediatrics. Hill and colleagues analyzed electronic health records from dozens of pediatric practices to track diagnoses of food allergies in young children before, during and after the guidelines were issued. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I can actually come to you today and say there are less kids with food allergy today than there would have been if we hadn't implemented this public health effort," he added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Our findings have relevance from those of us who treat patients to those caring for infants, and more awareness, education and advocacy could further increase the positive results we observed in this study," he continued. "Future studies could potentially explore specific feeding practices that help us better understand the timing, frequency and dose of foods that optimize protection against food allergies."&lt;/p&gt;

    
&lt;p id="mpu-plus-outstream-middle" data-ad="mpu-plus-outstream-middle" class="ad-mpu-plus-outstream-middle ad-wrapper " data-ad-unit='"mpu-plus-outstream-middle"'&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The researchers found that peanut allergies in children ages 0 to 3 declined by more than 27% after guidance for high-risk kids was first issued in 2015 and by more than 40% after the recommendations were expanded in 2017. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The effort hasn't yet reduced an overall increase in food allergies in the U.S. in recent years. About 8% of children are affected, including more than 2% with a peanut allergy. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Peanut allergy is caused when the body's immune system mistakenly identifies proteins in peanuts as harmful and releases chemicals that trigger allergic symptoms, including hives, respiratory symptoms and, sometimes, life-threatening anaphylaxis. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For decades, doctors had recommended delaying feeding children peanuts and other foods likely to trigger allergies until age 3. But in 2015, Gideon Lack at King's College London published the groundbreaking Learning Early About Peanut Allergy, or LEAP, trial.  &lt;/p&gt;

    
    
&lt;p id="mpu-flex-inc3" data-ad="mpu-flex-inc" class="ad-mpu-flex-inc ad-wrapper " data-ad-unit='["mpu-flex-inc",3]'&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lack and colleagues showed that introducing peanut products in infancy reduced the future risk of developing food allergies by more than 80%. Later analysis showed that the protection persisted in about 70% of kids into adolescence.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study immediately sparked new guidelines urging early introduction of peanuts — but putting them into practice has been slow. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Only about 29% of pediatricians and 65% of allergists reported following the expanded guidance issued in 2017, surveys found. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Confusion and uncertainty about the best way to introduce peanuts early in life led to the lag, according to a commentary that accompanied the study. Early on, medical experts and parents alike questioned whether the practice could be adopted outside of tightly controlled clinical settings.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The data for the analysis came from a subset of participating practice sites and may not represent the entire U.S. pediatric population, noted the commentary, led by Dr. Ruchi Gupta, a child allergy expert at Northwestern University.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, the new research offers "promising evidence that early allergen introduction is not only being adopted but may be making a measurable impact," the authors concluded.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Advocates for the 33 million people in the U.S. with food allergies welcomed signs that early introduction of peanut products is catching on. &lt;/p&gt;

    
    
&lt;p id="mpu-flex-inc4" data-ad="mpu-flex-inc" class="ad-mpu-flex-inc ad-wrapper " data-ad-unit='["mpu-flex-inc",4]'&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"This research reinforces what we already know and underscores a meaningful opportunity to reduce the incidence and prevalence of peanut allergy nationwide," said Sung Poblete, chief executive of the nonprofit group Food Allergy Research &amp;amp; Education, or FARE.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The new study emphasizes the current guidance, updated in 2021, which calls for introducing peanuts and other major food allergens between four and six months, without prior screening or testing, Hill said. Parents should consult their pediatricians about any questions.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It doesn't have to be a lot of the food, but little tastes of peanut butter, milk-based yogurt, soy-based yogurts and tree butters," he said. "These are really good ways to allow the immune system exposure to these allergenic foods in a safe way." &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tiffany Leon, 36, a Maryland registered dietician and director at FARE, introduced peanuts and other allergens early to her own sons, James, 4, and Cameron, 2. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At first, Leon's own mother was shocked at the advice to feed babies such foods before the age of 3, she said. But Leon explained how the science had changed. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"As a dietician, I practice evidence-based recommendations," she said. "So when someone told me, 'This is how it's done now, these are the new guidelines,' I just thought, 'OK, well, this is what we're going to do.'"&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/section&gt;

  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>CBS News</author><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 08:43:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigwFBVV95cUxPZXJFSkZJYVdZR1ZzQ2VEX25GTTVRelY5U0JfbWNRd2dGbDFmaWt1RU9WbjY4OEpyQWVSajgzVS1vRVJEZFlmRDhtLWhFelhLUjBiRFNCRXVwZ1ZYdTQ3QWFGdnBjUGVtcWEtOWc4NkQtdDRORFlRakY5dHJEaW9PREh4QdIBiAFBVV95cUxPX2xoRlFacjRGR1B0NV92Ylgzc1AxUnlTSWxJR3ppMUFxbm12RGh0aS1wX2FIMS1PNWNYRmlEbnA5NjVmQnFPT1dnYUNGQ0NYZjg0R2NVajFhX0xRQTFNMGM1QkpuejhtNlREdVEwek1BQzRwUjZaQ28ycmFoQWJwMndReU41TUhL</guid></item><item><title>研究发现，尽早喂养婴儿花生并经常帮助6万名儿童避免过敏的建议-美联社新闻</title><link>https://apnews.com/article/peanut-allergy-children-infants-anaphylaxis-9a6df6377a622d05e47c340c5a9cffc8</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="LeaderBoardAd-Mobile "&gt;
                                    
                                        
                                            
                                        
                                    
                                &lt;/p&gt;
                            
                            
                                
                                
                                    &lt;div class="RichTextStoryBody RichTextBody"&gt;
                                        &lt;p&gt;A decade after a landmark study proved that feeding peanut products to young babies could &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gLhHL8pjYRc" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;prevent development&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; of life-threatening allergies, new research finds the change has made a big difference in the real world.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;About 60,000 children have avoided developing peanut allergies after guidance first issued in 2015 upended medical practice by recommending introducing the allergen to infants starting as early as 4 months.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“That’s a remarkable thing, right?” said Dr. David Hill, an allergist and researcher at Children’s Hospital of Philadelphia, and author of a study &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://publications.aap.org/pediatrics/online-first?autologincheck=redirected" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;published Monday&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; in the medical journal Pediatrics. Hill and colleagues analyzed electronic health records from dozens of pediatric practices to track diagnoses of food allergies in young children before, during and after the guidelines were issued.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I can actually come to you today and say there are less kids with food allergy today than there would have been if we hadn’t implemented this public health effort,” he added. &lt;/p&gt;
    
&lt;p&gt;The researchers found that peanut allergies in children ages 0 to 3 declined by more than 27% after guidance for high-risk kids was first issued in 2015 and by more than 40% after the recommendations were expanded in 2017.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The effort hasn’t yet reduced an overall increase in food allergies in the U.S. in recent years. About 8% of children are affected, including more than 2% with a peanut allergy.&lt;/p&gt;
    
    
    
&lt;p&gt;Peanut allergy is caused when the body’s immune system mistakenly identifies proteins in peanuts as harmful and releases chemicals that trigger allergic symptoms, including hives, respiratory symptoms and, sometimes, life-threatening anaphylaxis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For decades, doctors had recommended delaying feeding children peanuts and other foods likely to trigger allergies until age 3. But in 2015, Gideon Lack at King’s College London, published the groundbreaking &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://www.nejm.org/doi/full/10.1056/NEJMoa1414850" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Learning Early About Peanut Allergy,&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; or LEAP, trial. &lt;/p&gt;
    
&lt;p&gt;Lack and colleagues showed that introducing peanut products in infancy reduced the future risk of developing food allergies by more than 80%. Later analysis showed that the protection persisted in about 70% of kids into adolescence. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study immediately sparked new guidelines urging early introduction of peanuts — but putting them into practice has been slow.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Only about 29% of pediatricians and 65% of allergists reported following the expanded guidance issued in 2017, surveys found.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Confusion and uncertainty about the best way to introduce peanuts early in life led to the lag, according to a commentary that accompanied the study. Early on, medical experts and parents alike questioned whether the practice could be adopted outside of tightly controlled clinical settings. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The data for the analysis came from a subset of participating practice sites and may not represent the entire U.S. pediatric population, noted the commentary, led by Dr. Ruchi Gupta, a child allergy expert at Northwestern University. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, the new research offers “promising evidence that early allergen introduction is not only being adopted but may be making a measurable impact,” the authors concluded. &lt;/p&gt;
    
&lt;p&gt;Advocates for the 33 million people in the U.S. with food allergies welcomed signs that early introduction of peanut products is catching on.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“This research reinforces what we already know and underscores a meaningful opportunity to reduce the incidence and prevalence of peanut allergy nationwide,” said Sung Poblete, chief executive of the nonprofit group Food Allergy Research &amp;amp; Education, or FARE. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The new study emphasizes the current guidance, updated in 2021, which calls for introducing peanuts and other major food allergens between four and six months, without prior screening or testing, Hill said. Parents should consult their pediatricians about any questions. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“It doesn’t have to be a lot of the food, but little tastes of peanut butter, milk-based yogurt, soy-based yogurts and tree butters,” he said. “These are really good ways to allow the immune system exposure to these allergenic foods in a safe way.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tiffany Leon, 36, a Maryland registered dietician and director at FARE, introduced peanuts and other allergens early to her own sons, James, 4, and Cameron, 2.&lt;/p&gt;
    
&lt;p&gt;At first, Leon’s own mother was shocked at the advice to feed babies such foods before the age of 3, she said. But Leon explained how the science had changed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“As a dietician, I practice evidence-based recommendations,” she said. “So when someone told me, ‘This is how it’s done now, these are the new guidelines,’ I just though, OK, well, this is what we’re going to do.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;——-&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="optimizelyHubpeekId" class="optimizelyHubpeekClass"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Associated Press Health and Science Department receives support from the Howard Hughes Medical Institute’s Department of Science Education and the Robert Wood Johnson Foundation. The AP is solely responsible for all content.&lt;/p&gt;
                                    &lt;/div&gt;
                                
                            

                            
                    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>AP News</author><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 04:05:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipgFBVV95cUxPSFhJMFRDS1FwNU5KbHRMeWVud2J1bEFBT2lzLTVCYlBjTkh6aWRBejR2VnBxU3dweGxFclI0SWhVZmhvVlNTWHZNV1pkR0o5Q253djVCUHc1Vzk4QVhfM2VFejRpTDZ4eUhYS0x0MEI1SDBfR25tbGpvVTNrQlUyckEzR0hYQmJ6M25MVWI0WXJRT0wwLURPTUZHWWdyVDV1UFl2cWhn</guid></item><item><title>研究表明，儿童对花生过敏的人数急剧下降-《纽约时报》</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/10/20/well/peanut-allergy-drop.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The New York Times</author><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 04:01:05 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMickFVX3lxTE5LQkhHdWxJT3F1MVFmLTNzYzBMbjVXN2ZlRnVaWDhfcDloaEQyVDAxYi0tQXE3Q0dEVTZLaldCZkpIYjdEM1pTQjVzeFZ3c2JUN1pHaW5kanRjNjVaWGNndzRkNnhvd2hDWlVNQ1JXWXlZdw</guid></item><item><title>英国大脑监测初创公司从青少年创意发展到1亿美元的资金$ -英国《金融时报》</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/1f41a613-c97a-4725-8715-5dd3090f5287</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="o-grid-row details-section o3-type-body-base css-pmzbjb"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;FT Digital Edition: today’s FT, cover to cover on any device. This subscription does not include access to ft.com or the FT App.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Financial Times</author><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 04:00:39 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMicEFVX3lxTE5NOUFBZEdLT0xMM2JJaEVGb3lOWVZscEdrZTVvWHNtMHZrNGpyTnY2Y2kzN1RLWVJUVFVQaXJxM3g3NjRLbVdaRURrdTNXNHJ3UWNRVjhPMW90RG5uMlkydzM2S1Z2UVNuazNCTkZZNzc</guid></item><item><title>当我了解到我们的家人接触过麻疹时，我的儿子只有1天大。接下来会发生什么。- Yahoo News UK</title><link>https://uk.news.yahoo.com/son-1-day-old-learned-023106819.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="" data-article-body="true"&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The author's 16-month-old during her hospital stay where she may have been exposed to measles.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;I’m at the hospital when I get the call. It’s a Thursday morning, not even 24 hours since my C-section. I’m watching my newborn son nap in his bassinet and trying to enjoy my first meal since surgery.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The caller ID says CHKD Children’s Hospital, so I answer. My 16-month-old daughter was just released from that hospital earlier in the week following a severe bacterial infection that caused her lymph nodes to swell an extraordinary amount.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“Hello?” I say, worried that they uncovered something concerning in her bloodwork.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“Hello, I’m a pediatrician at Norfolk Children’s Hospital. I’m calling to check on Camille, and to let you know that she may have been exposed to the measles during her stay with us.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;My heart dropped, and the post-surgery nausea that had nearly subsided suddenly returned.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The doctor proceeded to tell me that she was reading from a script, and that they (under the advisement of the &lt;a href="https://www.vdh.virginia.gov/news/2025-news-releases/virginia-health-officials-confirm-measles-case-in-eastern-region/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Virginia Department of Health;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Virginia Department of Health&lt;/a&gt;) were recommending that all young children exposed receive their second measles vaccine as soon as possible. She then asked me about the vaccination status of everyone else who visited my daughter at the hospital, including myself, my parents, my husband and my almost-3-year-old.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Thankfully, both of my daughters had their first measles shot, which grants immunity in &lt;a href="https://med.stanford.edu/news/insights/2025/05/measles-risk-vaccination-young-old.html" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:up to 95% of individuals;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;up to 95% of individuals&lt;/a&gt;. However, I now have a vulnerable infant to consider, and even a small chance of exposing him to this virus with no protection is too big of a risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;So, under the advice of our pediatrician, I decided to give both of my daughters their second measles-mumps-rubella vaccine early. I didn’t feel entirely comfortable with this decision — especially with my 16-month-old just recovering from an infection and borderline immunocompromised. But it was the best decision available to me.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;And because of parents who opt out of vaccinating their kids, I was put in the position to make it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The recent measles scare in Virginia came from a student at a local elementary school. Though the individual’s vaccination status was not directly stated in a &lt;a href="https://drive.google.com/file/d/1tKGC4YZAa4g6Vsua0qVEmN-zgZ3AxuJ6/view" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:letter;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;letter&lt;/a&gt; from the Virginia Beach Department of Health or in an &lt;a href="https://www.wtkr.com/news/virginia-department-of-health-reports-measles-case-in-hampton-roads" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:interview;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;interview&lt;/a&gt; with officials, several local outlets have taken this opportunity to advocate for the safety and continued necessity of childhood vaccinations. Of the 1,491 confirmed cases of measles in the U.S. this year, &lt;a href="https://www.nfid.org/infectious-disease/measles/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:92% occurred in individuals;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;92% occurred in individuals&lt;/a&gt; who were unvaccinated (or who had an unknown vaccination status).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;In fact, &lt;a href="https://publichealth.jhu.edu/ivac/2025/us-measles-cases-hit-highest-level-since-declared-eliminated-in-2000" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:2025;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;2025&lt;/a&gt; boasts more measles cases since the disease was considered eliminated in 2000 — and more than any other year in the past three decades.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.uchicago.edu/big-brains-podcast-why-measles-resurging-and-rise-vaccine-hesitancy" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Low vaccination rates;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Low vaccination rates&lt;/a&gt; caused by vaccine hesitancy and anti-vaccine movements are largely to blame.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;In other words, parents who choose not to vaccinate their children play a major role in these outbreaks ― which will continue to rise if nothing changes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="relative mb-4"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="relative text-sm mt-1 pr-2.5"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; Photo Courtesy Of Lauren Gumpert&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The author's two daughters visiting their newest sibling at the hospital.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;As parents, we make hundreds of decisions on a daily basis — some inconsequential, others less so. We’re constantly weighing pros and cons, risks and benefits. In a world that feels more disconnected than ever — when we can bury our heads into our phones and surround ourselves with an echo chamber of conspiratorial ideas — it’s easy to lose sight of the bigger picture.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;So let’s zoom out for a minute. In 1900, infectious diseases (such as pneumonia, influenza and measles) &lt;a href="https://www.vox.com/health/402687/measles-outbreak-vaccine-kids-children-history" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:killed about 18% of children;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;killed about 18% of children&lt;/a&gt;. Before vaccines and other public health measures, 1 in 5 children did not live to see their first birthday.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Compare that reality to today, when &lt;a href="https://www.vox.com/health/402687/measles-outbreak-vaccine-kids-children-history" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:less than 1%;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;less than 1%&lt;/a&gt; of children die before their fifth birthday.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Back then, childhood was inherently dangerous. Even if they lived, those who became infected with a virus such as measles often suffered &lt;a href="https://ourworldindata.org/measles-increases-disease-risk" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:long-term side effects;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;long-term side effects&lt;/a&gt; such as brain damage and a permanently weakened immune system.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The success of public health measures such as vaccines has given people a &lt;a href="https://www.vaccinestoday.eu/stories/the-public-health-paradox-vaccines-are-a-victim-of-their-own-success/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:false sense of security;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;false sense of security&lt;/a&gt;, leading many to conclude that once-tragic diseases are no longer a threat. But it’s only thanks to science that illness and death among children is no longer commonplace.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Nowadays, it’s easy to take our health for granted — especially with &lt;a href="https://www.statnews.com/2024/11/18/rfk-jr-anti-vaxxer-vaccine-skeptic/#:~:text=Kennedy%20likes%20to%20say%20that,of%20how%20they%20describe%20themselves." rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:anti-vaccine conspiracy theorist Robert F. Kennedy Jr.;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;anti-vaccine conspiracy theorist Robert F. Kennedy Jr.&lt;/a&gt; steering the narrative at the helm of the Department of Health and Human Services. We have the luxury of arguing over genetically modified organisms and artificial food colors and doubting the effectiveness of the very things that have kept us safe for the past half-century.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;I won’t pretend to understand the various circumstances that might lead a parent not to vaccinate their child.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;But I do know that as parents (and human beings), we have a responsibility to protect all children. I’m reminded of a quote by author and activist &lt;a href="https://www.goodreads.com/quotes/10931895-there-s-no-such-thing-as-other-people-s-children" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Glennon Doyle;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Glennon Doyle&lt;/a&gt; who said, “There’s no such thing as other people’s children.” We have an obligation to protect those who cannot opt to protect themselves. This is why I keep my kids home when they’re sick, why I advocate for stricter gun laws and — yes — why I vaccinate my kids.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Because measles is an airborne disease, one infected person can easily pass it on to &lt;a href="https://www.gavi.org/vaccineswork/story-measles-five-charts" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:18 other people;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;18 other people&lt;/a&gt;. To achieve herd immunity, 95% of the population must be fully vaccinated. Unfortunately, vaccination rates among children have continued to decline since the COVID-19 pandemic, with &lt;a href="https://publichealth.jhu.edu/ivac/2025/across-the-us-childhood-vaccination-rates-continue-to-decline#:~:text=During%20the%202024%2D25%20school,prevent%20transmission%20of%20measles%20virus." rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:only 92.5% of kindergartners;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;only 92.5% of kindergartners&lt;/a&gt; in the U.S. reportedly vaccinated against measles last year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Just this week, &lt;a href="http://publichealth.lacounty.gov/phcommon/public/media/mediapubhpdetail.cfm?prid=5135#:~:text=Public%20Health%20Reminds%20Residents%20About,years%20after%20the%20initial%20diagnosis." rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:a school-aged child in California died;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;a school-aged child in California died&lt;/a&gt; due to a delayed measles-related complication known as subacute sclerosing panencephalitis (SSPE). The child contracted the disease in infancy before they were eligible for vaccination. If infected, my newborn son could suffer the same fate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;I don’t want my kids — or anyone else’s — to become another preventable casualty.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;So, both of my daughters received their second MMR vaccine ahead of schedule. However, we still aren’t out of the woods, because measles &lt;a href="https://www.vdh.virginia.gov/measles/#:~:text=If%20you%20think%20you%20might,discuss%20post%2Dexposure%20treatment%20options." rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:symptoms can appear as late as 21 days after exposure;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;symptoms can appear as late as 21 days after exposure&lt;/a&gt;. Additionally, &lt;a href="https://www.babycenter.com/health/doctor-visits-and-vaccines/my-child-developed-a-rash-about-a-week-after-receiving-the-m_1471851" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:about 5% of children;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;about 5% of children&lt;/a&gt; who receive their second vaccine develop a measles-like rash and fever, so it can be difficult to determine whether they have the disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Now I’m left to wonder and stress about every little bump that surfaces on my daughters’ skin. And if one of them does develop symptoms, I’ll have to contact the &lt;a href="https://www.vdh.virginia.gov/news/2025-news-releases/virginia-health-officials-confirm-measles-case-in-eastern-region/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Virginia Department of Health;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Virginia Department of Health&lt;/a&gt; to get them tested, because I can’t bring them to the pediatrician and risk exposing other vulnerable children.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;I understand why many parents have grown to distrust medical institutions. I’ve also had my fair share of negative experiences that sometimes make me doubt doctors’ recommendations and interventions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;But overall, I believe that people in helping professions (like medicine) have good intentions. The millions of doctors and organizations supporting and promoting vaccine use would not intentionally harm children. RFK, on the other hand, seems to change his opinion often &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2025/04/12/politics/rfk-jrs-long-complicated-history-with-the-measles-vaccines" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:to suit his political agenda;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;to suit his political agenda&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Despite the fact that a link between vaccines and autism has been disproven &lt;a href="https://www.aap.org/en/news-room/fact-checked/fact-checked-vaccines-safe-and-effect-no-link-to-autism/#:~:text=%E2%80%9CMultiple%20studies%20from%20around%20the,living%20rich%2C%20fulfilling%20lives.%E2%80%9D" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:over and over;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;over and over&lt;/a&gt;, RFK Jr. continues to spread lies and misinformation. He promised Americans that he would find a cause for the &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2025/04/10/health/kennedy-autism-causes" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:“autism epidemic”;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;“autism epidemic”&lt;/a&gt; — a pursuit that won him support among many parents. However, with no formal medical or public health training, the secretary of health continues to undermine the scientific process by hiring incompetent individuals and misappropriating resources to maintain his base of support. For example, he recently employed a known &lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2025/03/27/health/rfk-jr-autism-vaccines.html" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:pseudoscientist;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;pseudoscientist&lt;/a&gt; to uncover a link between vaccines and autism (which, as previously stated, studies have found &lt;a href="https://www.acpjournals.org/doi/10.7326/M18-2101?utm_source=substack&amp;amp;utm_medium=email" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:does not exist;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;does not exist&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;In light of &lt;a href="https://www.npr.org/2025/09/18/nx-s1-5542082/cdc-acip-vaccine-hepatitis-b-mmrv" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:recent threats;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;recent threats&lt;/a&gt; to vaccine access, 34 scientific and medical organizations including the American Association of Immunologists and the American College of Physicians have come together to produce a &lt;a href="https://www.acponline.org/acp-newsroom/leading-organizations-unite-to-affirm-vaccine-safety-amid-rising-misinformation-and-declining-trust" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:statement;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;statement&lt;/a&gt; reaffirming the safety and effectiveness of vaccines.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;With so many conspiracy theories circulating on the internet, it can be difficult to know who to trust. As a result, many parents fail to recognize the far-reaching implications of their choices. A once-standard public health measure has become politicized and exploited — and our children will suffer because of it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Mother Teresa said: “If we have no peace, it is because we have forgotten that we belong to each other.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The consequences of a decision like not vaccinating your child are not hypothetical. By now, hundreds of families in Virginia Beach like mine have been affected by one family’s choices. None of us live on an island, and our actions continue to ripple outward and affect others in unexpected ways.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;In this life, we have no choice but to rely on each other. As parents, we have the power to end preventable deaths by vaccinating our children. I hope the vaccine skeptics among us will find the strength to do what’s necessary to keep all of our children safe.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;em&gt;This article originally appeared on &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/entry/measles-exposure-anti-vaccine-movement_n_68d1bba8e4b03c190c21c872" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:HuffPost;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;HuffPost&lt;/a&gt; in September 2025.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Yahoo News UK</author><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 02:31:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMib0FVX3lxTE9sNjdMVzRXbFZCRlpxNGhRdU51ZDVmbnFNZ3BheXJFOW8yVFY0YzFRbFRfdTRKLTNWVEZCMkVCWWU3eDdiS1c4Tl9nQmJVY2hQSHc2SUNERVpyczB4WHVSLWxZRFJxUllkY18wdG1SUQ</guid></item><item><title>一种甜美的水果，还可以控制血糖水平。研究声称它降低了糖尿病患者的风险-《经济时报》</title><link>https://m.economictimes.com/magazines/panache/a-fruit-that-is-sweet-and-can-also-control-blood-sugar-levels-study-claims-it-lowers-diabetics-risk/articleshow/124570023.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div data-brcount="28" class="artText"&gt;&lt;p&gt;It may sound surprising, but research suggests that eating mangoes—a fruit known for its natural sweetness—can actually help manage &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a ref="dofollow" data-ga-onclick="Inarticle articleshow link click#Magazines#href" href="/topic/blood-sugar-levels" target="_blank"&gt;blood sugar levels&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;. A study conducted by researchers at &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a ref="dofollow" data-ga-onclick="Inarticle articleshow link click#Magazines#href" href="/topic/george-mason-university" target="_blank"&gt;George Mason University&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; revealed that individuals who consumed mango daily had better blood sugar control and reduced body fat compared to those who opted for low-sugar snacks. The study’s findings, published in Foods in August 2025 under the title “Daily Mango Intake Improves Glycemic and Body Composition Outcomes in Adults with Prediabetes: A Randomized Controlled Study,” emphasize that the nutritional context of sugar within whole foods plays a more crucial role than the sugar content alone.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;The Science Behind Mango’s Benefits&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;In an interview with&lt;/p&gt;&lt;em&gt; Science Daily&lt;/em&gt;&lt;p&gt;, Raedeh Basiri, Assistant Professor in George Mason’s Department of Nutrition and Food Studies, explained that it’s not simply about how much sugar food contains, but about the overall nutritional makeup. Mangoes, for instance, offer a unique balance—while they contain natural sugars, these are accompanied by fiber, antioxidants, and essential vitamins. This combination helps slow sugar absorption, keeping blood glucose levels stable.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-mid-newpos-mgid="mgid_124570023" id="div-mgid-mid-newpos-124570023"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p id="E_3" class="etoro"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In contrast, foods that contain added sugars—such as processed cereals or packaged low-sugar snacks—lack this natural balance and can actually heighten the risk of developing diabetes. The fiber in mangoes supports digestion and promotes satiety, helping control appetite and preventing overeating, which further aids weight management.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Glycemic Index and Safe Consumption Tips&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mangoes fall within a moderate range on the glycemic index (GI), scoring between 51 and 56, a range comparable to orange juice. According to the &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a ref="dofollow" data-ga-onclick="Inarticle articleshow link click#Magazines#href" href="/topic/american-diabetes-association" target="_blank"&gt;American Diabetes Association&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; (ADA), this places mangoes in the low-to-medium GI category, making them suitable for moderate consumption. The ADA recommends choosing fruits that are fresh, frozen, or canned without added sugars.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-mid-vdoai="vdoai_124570023" id="div-vdoai-mid-124570023"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A typical serving of fruit should provide around 15 grams of carbohydrates, which roughly equals two-thirds of a cup of mango. The ADA also notes that fresh fruit tends to be more satisfying than dried varieties, as the portion size of dried fruit is smaller and can lead to excessive intake of sugars.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-size="[[300, 250], [600, 250], [600, 300]]" data-adsslot="/7176/Economictimes/ET_News/ET_News_ROS/ET_News_ROS_MID_INTL_300" data-loc="100" id="div-gpt-ad-858478126-1-124570023" class="country_specAD"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p data-size="[[300, 250], [600, 250], [600, 300]]" data-adsslot="/7176/Economictimes/ET_News/ET_News_ROS/ET_News_ROS_MID1_INTL_300" data-loc="2" id="div-gpt-ad-858478132-1-124570023" class="country_specAD2nd"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-size="[[300, 250], [600, 250], [600, 300]]" data-adsslot="/7176/Economictimes/ET_News/ET_News_ROS/ET_News_ROS_MID1_INTL_300" data-loc="5" id="div-gpt-ad-858478132-1-124570023" class="country_specAD2nd"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-size="[[300, 250], [600, 250], [600, 300]]" data-adsslot="/7176/Economictimes/ET_News/ET_News_ROS/ET_News_ROS_MID1_INTL_300" data-loc="3" id="div-gpt-ad-858478132-1-124570023" class="country_specAD2nd"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Additional Health Perks&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Beyond controlling blood sugar, mangoes may also improve cholesterol levels. A study published in the British Journal of Nutrition in 2011 observed that mice fed a high-fat diet supplemented with freeze-dried mango exhibited lower body fat, reduced cholesterol, and improved glucose levels compared to those treated with lipid- or sugar-lowering drugs like fenofibrate and rosiglitazone.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The research underscores that incorporating whole fruits like mangoes into one’s diet not only satisfies sweet cravings naturally but also supports metabolic health, making this tropical fruit a surprisingly smart choice for balanced living.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h3&gt;Signs Of High Blood Sugar&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;As per a Cleveland Clinic report, early signs of high blood sugar, also known as hyperglycemia, often appear gradually and may include excessive thirst or hunger, frequent urination, headaches, and blurred vision. These symptoms occur as the body struggles to manage rising glucose levels. If left unchecked for a longer period, chronic hyperglycemia can lead to more serious issues such as persistent fatigue, unexplained weight loss, recurring vaginal yeast or skin infections, and slow-healing cuts or sores. Recognizing these warning signals early is crucial, as timely lifestyle changes and medical intervention can help prevent severe complications like nerve damage or diabetes-related disorders.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;How To Keep Blood Sugar In Check?&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;To maintain healthy blood sugar levels, focus on a balanced diet rich in fiber, whole grains, lean proteins, and non-starchy vegetables. Limit refined sugars, processed foods, and sweetened beverages. Eat smaller, regular meals to prevent spikes and dips in glucose. Stay active with at least 30 minutes of daily exercise, such as brisk walking or yoga. Manage stress through meditation or deep breathing, as stress hormones can raise blood sugar. Get enough sleep and stay hydrated. Regularly monitor blood glucose levels, and follow your doctor’s advice to keep your sugar within a healthy range.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;meta content="cms.article3" name="cmsei-article3"&gt;&lt;div class="inSideInd"&gt;&lt;div data-ga-action="Preference Banner InArticle Widget" data-ga-impression="Preference Banner InArticle Widget#Impressions | Preference Banner | Articleshow#url" class="Pbanner"&gt;&lt;div class="Pbannertext"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Add &lt;/p&gt;&lt;img alt="ET Logo" src="https://img.etimg.com/photo/123467569.cms"&gt;&lt;p&gt; as a Reliable and Trusted News Source&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Economic Times</author><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 01:26:34 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigAJBVV95cUxQNkQzYUE3YktFWHNVSHpSYzZrVWtrY083WWthSEhacWprS20wR01OUjc2ZlpVSFRnWUdVbVRhZEpPNER1LWFlWEtRNFVZU3RPR2g2dkJWRi1QNlNDNHpTY3o0MGItYTF6N2pZOEl6UWlDMV8tOWNTaHdjSS1qTF9ZX2cwUXhoaklrQ1NlSkZzQkpwSWVVT1lLNS1adjlrUnpGSTZndzNoM1RqOEdmUndQSU84VkJKQ0JYaTlZVkhpT3dVdnBVd2NUYkwtZmJNbGJFU2F2V1VCdmw5TGxaTHlvNVA3TU01NERjdGpzbm50eVB3VEREM1pnN3pTc2xDMkVm</guid></item><item><title>最后一名埃博拉患者在刚果民主共和国出院，世卫组织表示-半岛电视台</title><link>https://www.aljazeera.com/news/2025/10/19/last-ebola-patient-discharged-from-dr-congo-who</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;header class="article-header"&gt;&lt;h1&gt;Last Ebola patient discharged in DR Congo, WHO says&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;p class="article__subhead"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Barring new cases, the patient’s recovery kicks off a 42-day countdown to declaring the country’s 16th outbreak over.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/header&gt;&lt;div class="article-info m--t-20 m--desktop-b-30 m--b-mobile-20"&gt;&lt;div class="article-dates"&gt;&lt;p class="date-simple"&gt;&lt;span class="screen-reader-text"&gt;Published On 19 Oct 2025&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span aria-hidden="true"&gt;19 Oct 2025&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="rich-share" data-testid="rich-share"&gt;&lt;div class="rich-share__wrapper"&gt;&lt;div class="rich-share__button-wrapper"&gt;&lt;button class="rich-share__button row" aria-expanded="false"&gt;&lt;p class="screen-reader-text"&gt;Click here to share on social media&lt;/p&gt;&lt;svg class="icon icon--share2 icon--primary icon--16 " viewbox="0 0 20 16" version="1.1" aria-hidden="true"&gt;&lt;title&gt;share2&lt;/title&gt;&lt;path fill="#000" fill-rule="evenodd" d="M11.688 9.048c-.659 0-1.252.282-1.673.733l-4.92-2.45c.016-.115.028-.232.028-.352 0-.117-.011-.23-.027-.343l4.913-2.423a2.285 2.285 0 0 0 1.68.739C12.964 4.952 14 3.899 14 2.6 14 1.302 12.965.25 11.688.25S9.377 1.302 9.377 2.601c0 .117.01.23.027.343L4.49 5.367a2.285 2.285 0 0 0-1.68-.739C1.536 4.628.5 5.681.5 6.979c0 1.299 1.035 2.35 2.312 2.35.659 0 1.252-.281 1.673-.731l4.92 2.45a2.357 2.357 0 0 0-.029.351c0 1.299 1.035 2.351 2.312 2.351S14 12.698 14 11.399s-1.035-2.35-2.312-2.35Z" clip-rule="evenodd"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/button&gt;&lt;p class="rich-share__social-text"&gt;Share&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wysiwyg wysiwyg--all-content" aria-live="polite" aria-atomic="true"&gt;&lt;p&gt;The last Ebola patient in the Democratic Republic of the Congo (DRC) has been released from a treatment centre in Kasai province, according to the United Nations health agency.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The patient is the 19th to recover out of 64 total cases recorded since the &lt;a href="/news/2025/9/4/dr-congo-announces-new-ebola-outbreak"&gt;outbreak was declared&lt;/a&gt; in September, the World Health Organization (WHO) said in a statement on Sunday.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;section class="more-on"&gt;&lt;h2 class="more-on__heading"&gt;Recommended Stories &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;span class="screen-reader-text"&gt;list of 3 items&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="screen-reader-text"&gt;end of list&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;p&gt;If no new cases are discovered in the next 42 days, the outbreak will be declared over.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mohamed Janabi, the WHO’s director for Africa, said the recovery was a “remarkable achievement”, given the outbreak began just six weeks ago.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The country’s robust response, with support from WHO and partners, was pivotal to this achievement,” he added in a social media post.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="p1"&gt;In a video alongside the post on X, health workers were seen celebrating as the final patient exited the treatment centre in Bulape.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The outbreak, which is the DRC’s 16th to date, was declared on September 4 as Ebola cases appeared in the Bulape and Mweka areas of the Kasai province in the country’s southwest.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Since then, the WHO has tallied 53 confirmed and 11 probable cases, with patients showing typical Ebola symptoms such as fever, vomiting, diarrhoea and haemorrhaging. Forty-five people have died.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The remote Kasai province has proven challenging to reach, even as it may have helped to prevent the spread of the virus, health officials have said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="article-newsletter-slot" data-testid="article-newsletter-slot"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Still, the WHO deployed response teams and set up a 32-bed treatment centre for the first time “outside a simulation exercise” in the region, the organisation said. More than 35,000 people have received vaccinations in the Bulape area.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;No new cases have been identified since September 25.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ebola was first identified in 1976 after an outbreak in what is now the DRC. Without treatment, up to 90 percent of cases are fatal, according to the US Centers for Disease Control and Prevention.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The largest outbreak occurred from 2014 to 2016 in West Africa, ultimately infecting 28,600 and killing 11,325 people, with the disease also spreading to Europe and the United States.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The DRC’s most recent outbreak occurred in 2022 and involved just one &lt;a href="/news/2022/9/27/dr-congo-declares-end-latest-ebola-virus-outbreak"&gt;recorded case&lt;/a&gt; of the virus.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Al Jazeera</author><pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 21:43:56 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikwFBVV95cUxORGtKRkZXYlJ3ckRtWW1fS2oxQ1ZIbU16V00zeXNZeHFhVGkxdWdMazBzT1RYWGEybU5wRXE0NTZmZFJHUldqYkJhWExjbXI0SDBYcGRZcDdQU3lqQlBLbVlvM21UMHRQUDNmY2lRWmZLUTVlbTFnVDNRZ3g5M0FiM3pQQU1Kd0lNdmNCWnliU3hrNmvSAZgBQVVfeXFMT0RrNmh4X0pYZlY5bGJkWnhwd3hhaFV0aEdXQXg1bUZGTHdiTUhIQlhTc3VLQ2xnaHJEd1VKaWdaMnNBRVMyTmVoS2FiRGZsMmJYeEFuUUhfZkNYcmxhSkdiSHNOUDNiN3BIbHNqdkVGTkpYbmFBSTI5NmdyMlZZTi1iNldVMW5tb2R6bmhqQjEtQUx1TjlTQW8</guid></item><item><title>根据传染病医生的说法，如果您生病了，要避免的“健康”活动- AOL.com</title><link>https://www.aol.com/articles/healthy-activity-avoid-sick-according-182500780.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="caas-body"&gt;&lt;p&gt;No one wants to get sick. As a kid, at least coming down with a virus meant spending a day on the couch watching TV instead of going to school. But as an adult, life’s demands don’t just stop when you’re not feeling well. There are still deadlines to meet and kids’ lunches to pack.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;With so much going on (why is it that there’s never a good time to get sick?), it’s tempting to push through an illness instead of rest, trying to keep with your normal routine as much as possible. &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC2947637/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:According to one scientific study;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;According to one scientific study&lt;/a&gt;, 94% of surveyed ill employees went to work while sick and 8% vomited while at work. (As if you needed another reminder to &lt;a href="https://parade.com/health/flumist-at-home-review" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:get your flu shot;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;get your flu shot&lt;/a&gt;, right?)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s worth emphasizing that if you’re feeling sick, &lt;a href="https://parade.com/living/phrases-to-use-for-sick-day-email-according-to-hr-expert" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:you should rest at home;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;you should rest at home&lt;/a&gt; instead of going to work. This will prevent others from getting sick and help you heal faster. But there’s something else an infectious disease doctor wants people to never do when they’re starting to get sick.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://emojipedia.org/stethoscope" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:🩺;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;🩺&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="https://parade.com/newsletters/healthy-now" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:SIGN UP for tips to stay healthy &amp;amp; fit with the top moves, clean eats, health trends &amp;amp; more delivered right to your inbox twice a week;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SIGN UP for tips to stay healthy &amp;amp; fit with the top moves, clean eats, health trends &amp;amp; more delivered right to your inbox twice a week&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="https://emojipedia.org/pill" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:💊;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;💊&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure align-caption-with-image"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;h2&gt;The Activity an Infectious Disease Doctor Says To Avoid When You’re Sick&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;When you’re feeling under the weather, one question you may ask yourself is &lt;a href="https://parade.com/health/working-out-while-sick" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:whether or not you should still work out.;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;whether or not you should still work out.&lt;/a&gt; On the one hand, &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC7387807/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:exercise has been shown;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;exercise has been shown&lt;/a&gt; to boost immunity and help the body fight infection. On the other hand, you probably feel more fatigued and weak than you normally do.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to &lt;a href="https://www.unlv.edu/people/brian-labus" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Dr. Brian Labus, PhD, MPH, REHS;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dr. Brian Labus, PhD, MPH, REHS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;,&lt;/strong&gt; an infectious disease epidemiologist and professor at the University of Nevada, Las Vegas, whether or not you should work out when you’re sick depends on the type of illness you have. If it’s just a slight head cold, he says that working out probably won’t do much harm. But if it’s a stomach virus or upper respiratory infection, he warns against it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://parade.com/health/habit-to-break-to-avoid-getting-sick-according-to-doctors" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:The One Habit Doctors Are Begging You To Break ASAP if You Don't Want To Get Sick This Fall;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;The One Habit Doctors Are Begging You To Break ASAP if You Don't Want To Get Sick This Fall &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“If you have a serious respiratory illness, you’re going to have trouble breathing to begin with. Even if it’s just a cough, something is happening that’s hurting your lungs. Working out on top of that can be very taxing on the body and &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC11282332/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:make it harder to recover from the illness;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;make it harder to recover from the illness&lt;/a&gt;,” Dr. Labus says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In addition to taxing the body, he explains that working out leads to losing fluid through sweat, which is the opposite of what the body needs when you’re sick. This is another reason it can take longer to bounce back if you push through a hard workout when you’re feeling under the weather. He emphasizes that it’s an absolute myth that you can “sweat out an illness.” &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;“The virus or bacteria that’s making you sick doesn’t care about sweating,” he says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://parade.com/health/one-food-to-shorten-a-cold-according-to-registered-dietitians" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:The One Food Nutritionists Say Can Help Shorten a Cold;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;The One Food Nutritionists Say Can Help Shorten a Cold&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Not only does working out when you have an upper respiratory infection (such as COVID, the flu, RSV, strep throat or the common cold), mean it will likely take you longer to recover, it also puts others around you at risk. “When you’re working out, you’re breathing heavily. Breathing heavily puts a lot more of the virus into the air, which puts others at risk,” Dr. Labus says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you absolutely must work out even though you’re sick, he recommends exerting yourself less than you normally do and to work out outside, away from other people. This can look like going for a walk around the block or moving through a gentle yoga flow in your yard.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://parade.com/health/gym-habits-that-can-make-you-sick-according-to-doctors" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Headed Back to the Gym? Doctors Are Urging You To Avoid These Gross Habits;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Headed Back to the Gym? Doctors Are Urging You To Avoid These Gross Habits&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;How To Know When You Can Start Working Out Again&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Instead of trying to work or work out when you’re sick, Dr. Labus recommends focusing on resting and hydrating. This, he says, is the best way to take care of your immune system.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In terms of how to know when you’ve recovered from your illness enough that you can start working out again, Dr. Labus stresses that it depends on the type of illness you have and how severe your symptoms are. “A head cold typically lasts a couple of days, but the flu can last up to a week,” he explains.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He adds that there isn’t one hard and fast rule about when to start working out again after being sick. “Every person is unique and every [illness] is unique,” he tells &lt;em&gt;Parade&lt;/em&gt;. For example, an adult who is young or middle-aged and in good health may recover faster than an elderly adult or someone with an underlying illness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Since everyone is different, Dr. Labus recommends listening to your body and acting accordingly. When you do feel ready to work out again, he recommends easing into it instead of doing an intense workout on your first day back.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Working out regularly is a great habit to have and benefits the body in a myriad of ways, but that doesn’t mean you should push through when you’re sick. Taking a few days off will help you recover faster and is the best way to care for your body.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Up Next:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://parade.com/health/how-to-keep-this-bathroom-staple-bacteria-free" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Related: This Bathroom Staple Could Be Making You Sick—Here’s How To Keep It Bacteria-Free;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Related: This Bathroom Staple Could Be Making You Sick—Here’s How To Keep It Bacteria-Free&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Sources:&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;This story was originally reported by &lt;a href="https://parade.com/health/what-to-avoid-when-you-start-feeling-sick" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Parade;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Parade&lt;/a&gt; on Oct 19, 2025, where it first appeared in the &lt;a href="https://parade.com/health" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Health &amp;amp; Wellness;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Health &amp;amp; Wellness&lt;/a&gt; section. Add Parade as a &lt;a href="https://google.com/preferences/source?q=parade.com" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Preferred Source by clicking here.;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Preferred Source by clicking here.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>AOL.com</author><pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 21:28:51 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiAFBVV95cUxNdmRnem96ekFGODVyLUpMU0ZqMVg4ZkdzQXozNTBNMjBuaUlHUzZhNGtnWGFZYm1nWWZsaVBkZU90SDVQck5rMUtJNkU2MFlWdm9BSWhuX2ZNaDdZbEtsXzU2NVBCV3JXUmxOczJMY0dlaGs2RUlHbThvOTNnREFjVTlYcU8taDJO</guid></item><item><title>美国男性突然精子数量极低。现在，专家们知道原因了--《每日邮报》</title><link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-15202593/American-men-lower-sperm-count-RFK-Jr.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div itemprop="articleBody"&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;a target="_self" href="/news/rfk-jr/index.html" id="mol-3b3392c0-ad2b-11f0-a063-adc1283ccd93"&gt;Robert F Kennedy Jr&lt;/a&gt; has issued a dire warning about the state of the nation's &lt;a target="_self" href="/health/fertility/index.html" id="mol-a2445110-ab8d-11f0-a84b-2965f463c46a"&gt;fertility&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In the Oval Office on Thursday, the Health and Human Services Secretary said&lt;span&gt;: 'Today, the average teenager in this country has 50 percent of the sperm count, 50 percent of the testosterone as a 65-year-old man.'&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The 71-year-old continued: 'Our girls are hitting puberty six years earlier, and that's bad, but also our parents aren't having children.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Now, the Daily Mail has spoken to three experts who say Kennedy is bringing important attention to an issue they have been worried about for decades.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;However, they added it did not appear his claims were completely true, and they were unaware of any data showing teenagers had testosterone levels half as high as 65-year-old men.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;It wasn't clear if the secretary was comparing sperm counts in today's teens and seniors or sperm counts when today's seniors were teens several decades ago.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But the experts warned studies do suggest sperm counts appear to be trending downward across the generations, which may be driven by higher obesity rates and sedentary lifestyles, as well as exposure to environmental pollutants like plastics.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;On girls entering puberty earlier, they also said that while they were not aware of evidence that showed it was happening six years earlier, studies do show that the age for a first period is also trending to earlier in life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Robert F Kennedy Junior, the Health and Human Services Secretary, is pictured above with Donald Trump at the press conference yesterday&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    
    
    &lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Dr Stephen Lazarou, a reproductive endocrinologist at Boston IVF, told the Daily Mail: 'I think there is a general sense that testosterone levels may, indeed, be declining across the [male] generations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'There is some evidence, or some speculation, that there may be contributing environmental or lifestyle factors, and we believe that that might be secondary to more sedentary lifestyles or increasing obesity rates.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Dr David Shusterman, a urologist who runs a men's fertility clinic in New York City, added: 'I have seen that testosterone levels are on the decline in my clinic, especially even for younger men, and that may be what Kennedy is trying to draw attention to.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'In some cases, these men appear otherwise normal, you know, they are not overweight or have other factors that would put them at higher risk.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;RFK Jr made the comments at a press conference hosted by President Donald Trump Thursday but had also mad&lt;span&gt;e the same claims in April, telling Fox News that a teenager today has less testosterone than a 68-year-old man and a sperm count that is 'down 50 percent.'&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;A spokesperson for the Department of Health and Human Services said: 'Secretary Kennedy is sounding the alarm on a public health issue others are too timid, or too politically cautious, to confront.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'A growing body of peer-reviewed research shows significant declines in sperm counts over the past decades, and pretending this isn't a serious trend is irresponsible.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;They pointed to two studies from 2017 and 2022, which both warned that sperm counts had dipped 52 percent among men from 1973 to 2011. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Testosterone is the male sex hormone and is behind secondary male characteristics such as a deeper voice and facial hair.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;It peaks in men in the early 20s before gradually declining by about one to two percent per year, which researchers say is a natural part of aging.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Experts told the Daily Mail that symptoms of low testosterone include low sex drive, fatigue, decreased muscle mass, depression, and weak bones, among others&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;It is also linked to sperm counts, with normal levels signaling for sperm production while lower levels can lead the body to produce less sperm.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;High testosterone levels, as a result of supplements or testosterone injections, can also slash sperm counts, however, by interfering with the other hormonal signals needed for sperm production.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In&lt;a class="" rel="nofollow noreferrer noopener" target="_blank" href="https://academic.oup.com/humupd/article/23/6/646/4035689?login=false"&gt; a 2017 study&lt;/a&gt; published in the journal &lt;a class="" rel="nofollow noreferrer noopener" target="_blank" href="https://academic.oup.com/humupd/article/23/6/646/4035689?login=false"&gt;Human Reproduction Update&lt;/a&gt;, and indicated by HHS, scientists surveyed sperm counts from 185 studies involving nearly 43,000 men conducted between 1973 and 2011.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;They found that sperm counts had declined 52 percent over this period in &lt;span&gt;North America, Europe, Australia and New Zealand.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In 2022, the same researcher, environmental medicine expert Dr Shanna Swan at Mount Sinai in New York, &lt;a class="" rel="nofollow noreferrer noopener" target="_blank" href="https://academic.oup.com/humupd/article/29/2/157/6824414?login=false"&gt;published a second follow-up analysis&lt;/a&gt;, also cited by HHS, with Dr Swan telling &lt;a class="" rel="noreferrer noopener" target="_blank" href="https://www.theguardian.com/society/2021/mar/28/shanna-swan-fertility-reproduction-count-down"&gt;The Guardian &lt;/a&gt;her work suggested that the median sperm count could reach zero by 2045.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Some experts have raised concerns over the paper, saying it compared semen samples where different methods were used to count sperm, which may make the results unreliable.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But another paper from&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a class="" rel="noreferrer noopener" target="_blank" href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/39128669/"&gt;January 2025&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; similarly found that, after surveying samples from 11,700 men from between 1970 and 2018, there had been a 'modest decline' in sperm counts, although researchers added it would not affect fertility.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Many experts have been raising the alarm over declining fertility in men for decades, with the cause being unclear, although it has previously been linked to environmental toxins affecting the testicles, as well as poor diets and exercise.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Experts say a healthy man has a testosterone level between 300 and 1,000 nanograms per deciliter (ng/dL), with a man with levels below this considered to have low testosterone.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;It is not clear how many men have low testosterone, although symptoms of the condition include erectile dysfunction, loss of muscle mass, increased body fat and mood changes such as irritability or depression.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Testosterone levels peak in young adulthood, around age 20, but decline by about 1 percent annually after age 30. This data is from a University of Wisconsin study &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Studies have also found evidence that young girls are now starting puberty earlier than ever before, but not the six years earlier that RFK Jr claims. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;One paper published in JAMA in &lt;a class="" rel="nofollow noreferrer noopener" target="_blank" href="https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jamanetworkopen/fullarticle/2819141?utm_source=chatgpt.com"&gt;May last year&lt;/a&gt; found that while women born between 1950 and 1969 started their periods at 12.5 years old on average, for those born between 2000 and 2005, the average age was 11.9 years old.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The researchers also found that the proportion of girls starting their puberty before the age of 11 had risen from 8.6 to 15.5 percent. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;And while the proportion starting their periods before the age of nine was still small, it had more than doubled during the same time frame from 0.6 to 1.4 percent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Researchers have said childhood obesity could be behind the shift, as well as diet, psychological stress and environmental factors such as toxins that disrupt hormones.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But it has alarmed officials, who say the change could be behind a higher risk of heart disease, cancer, miscarriages and even premature death.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Not all the experts agreed with RFK Jr, however, with Dr Jeff Singer, a senior fellow at the Cato Institute in the Department of Health Policy Studies, telling this website: 'What I CAN say is that Secretary Kennedy has taken a couple of real studies and turned them into a sensational sound bite.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'There's some evidence of modest downward trends across generations, likely tied to lifestyle and health factors, but nothing close to Kennedy's doomsday framing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'His claim badly distorts the data, confusing normal aging with supposed generational collapse.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
            

            
            
            
            
            &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Daily Mail</author><pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 20:46:47 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimgFBVV95cUxQX1JWNmNSZWZfbi1jeS0wUHVYb2FkOFZ5d2NvM3ExX3A0RmJOZzVMMHkzdHVwMWI5dEUxajBhNlBRcEg2cXFZc0o1LWc1NDJKMG5PX1VGemlyRWdFR096Y1k1Nm1XZ2JEb1hpWDFvVTU0Um1WQklXakVlS2dDbmc4UGpWbHFuZ1NIU19CdEdkWUZreHZrSm9WSV9R</guid></item><item><title>人质个人康复时间表-《耶路撒冷邮报》</title><link>https://www.jpost.com/health-and-wellness/article-870977</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Jerusalem Post</author><pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 20:46:21 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiZ0FVX3lxTE1HNWtzYjN0amZCeG5tLXhrY3FKZlZwT2hEZjJvS2tQcDV2cTFnbmNBeTVibHpERXVZT0g3TzVfclR2TUkxOUdKVFlNbVBmNDlsYk1lbWxlVDI0UHhBemFSVVUwTjk2eWs</guid></item><item><title>水下视频显示船舶锚和链条对南极海底的可怕破坏- Earth.com</title><link>https://www.earth.com/news/underwater-video-shows-destruction-of-antarctic-seabed-by-ship-anchors-chains/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="page_content__AwOj6"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Antarctica’s bays look calm from the surface. Down below, that calm hides scars. When large vessels stop in shallow Antarctic waters, many of them still drop heavy anchors attached to long chains. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wind and currents nudge a ship around, and the chain drags arcs across the bottom. A new study documented what that looks like in Antarctic waters and why it matters for life on the seafloor.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;More ships now reach coves along the &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/image/the-antarctic-peninsula-covered-in-ice/"&gt;Antarctic Peninsula&lt;/a&gt; and nearby islands during the austral summer. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sea ice retreats earlier and returns later, so cruise ships, research vessels, and a few private boats visit anchorages that stayed locked in ice in past decades. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That traffic brings people closer to wildlife and science sites, but it also raises a practical question: what happens when anchors and chains meet a slow-growing, cold-water marine community? Short answer: it’s not good.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-anchor-damage-on-antarctic-seafloor"&gt;Anchor damage on Antarctic seafloor&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Researchers turned ordinary stops into a survey. They lowered a high-definition camera to hover about 3.3 feet above the seabed. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Over dozens of dives in multiple regions, including well-known locations where ships drop anchor in the icy &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/warming-waters-are-dramatically-changing-microbial-life-in-antarctica/"&gt;Antarctic waters&lt;/a&gt;, they recorded hours of footage that showed crisp grooves matching the sweep of an anchor chain. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The lens caught bare patches where the top layer of fine sediment had been scraped away and plumes of silt hanging in the water.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the strongest clips, crushed sponge skeletons and toppled sea fans sat within those chain-swept tracks, while nearby undisturbed patches still supported dense, living communities. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The contrast was clear and immediate: intact habitat next to scraped corridors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wp-block-image"&gt;&lt;figure class="aligncenter size-full"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=epeVg6QndWo" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" decoding="async" src="https://cff2.earth.com/uploads/2025/10/19140830/antarctica-seafloor_anchor-chain-damage_crushed-sponges_KOLOSSAL_1s-1.webp" alt="Striations, grooves, and mud deposits from anchor retrieval were visible in the substrate of the ocean floor. The researchers observed crushed sponge colonies. Credit: Matt Mulrennan / KOLOSSAL" class="wp-image-1991521" srcset="https://cff2.earth.com/uploads/2025/10/19140830/antarctica-seafloor_anchor-chain-damage_crushed-sponges_KOLOSSAL_1s-1.webp 300w, https://cff2.earth.com/uploads/2025/10/19140830/antarctica-seafloor_anchor-chain-damage_crushed-sponges_KOLOSSAL_1s-1-150x150.webp 150w, https://cff2.earth.com/uploads/2025/10/19140830/antarctica-seafloor_anchor-chain-damage_crushed-sponges_KOLOSSAL_1s-1-32x32.webp 32w" sizes="(max-width: 300px) 100vw, 300px"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;figcaption class="wp-element-caption"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Striations, grooves, and mud deposits from anchor retrieval were visible in the substrate of the Antarctic ocean floor. The researchers observed crushed sponge colonies. Credit: Matt Mulrennan / KOLOSSAL. Click image to watch video footage.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-seafloor-damage-recovery-is-slow"&gt;Seafloor damage recovery is slow&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Antarctic seafloors host animals that grow slowly in cold, stable water. Many are “sessile,” meaning they stay fixed in place. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Those sponges, fans, and mats of filter feeders add three-dimensional structures that shelter fish and invertebrates and increase &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/acidity-levels-of-antarctic-waters-will-soon-double-harming-life/"&gt;local diversity&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Because growth is slow, wounds last. In some temperate seas, anchor scars remain visible for a decade; in &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/why-antarctic-waters-are-cooling-in-a-warming-world/"&gt;Antarctica’s chill&lt;/a&gt;, recovery could take far longer. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Flattening these structures does more than change the view. It reduces filtering capacity, shifts which creatures can live there, and lowers the ability of the community to bounce back. These communities also store carbon in tissue and skeletons, so damage can reduce that storage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-ship-tracks-tell-the-story"&gt;Ship tracks tell the story&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/antarctic-sea-ice-collapse-linked-to-a-sudden-surge-in-ocean-salt/"&gt;Icebergs&lt;/a&gt; can rake the bottom too, so the team checked that possibility. At several sites, the marks curved and repeated in patterns that fit a swinging chain, not a drifting block of ice. The scars appeared at depths iceberg keels rarely reach. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Small ridges of redeposited mud and smashed but still recognizable sponge structures pointed to recent mechanical scraping. The evidence lined up with anchoring as the cause.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To estimate how often this happens, the team analyzed automatic identification system (&lt;a href="https://www.navcen.uscg.gov/automatic-identification-system-overview" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;AIS&lt;/a&gt;) signals – data that ships broadcast to report location and speed – coming from the location of Antarctic anchor drops and chain damage&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Clusters of vessels sitting at very low speeds inside sheltered bays strongly suggested anchoring. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a single busy month at a &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/safeguarding-antarctica-from-human-activity-crucial-sites-identified/"&gt;popular harbor&lt;/a&gt;, multiple passenger vessels lingered in depths where standard practice would require paying out five times the water depth in chain. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even conservative math adds up to hundreds of feet of heavy chain lying on the bottom per ship, with extra sweep as wind and currents shift. Repeated visits concentrate disturbance in the same limited areas.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wp-block-image"&gt;&lt;figure class="aligncenter size-full"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FC22gO_I_zE" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" decoding="async" src="https://cff2.earth.com/uploads/2025/10/19140812/antarctica-seafloor_anchor-chain-damage_Antarctic-Sun-Star_KOLOSSAL_1s-1.webp" alt="The researchers recorded giant volcano sponges, Antarctic sun stars, giant Antarctic octopus, sea spiders, and a variety of fish at anchor depths. Credit: Matt Mulrennan / KOLOSSAL" class="wp-image-1991519" srcset="https://cff2.earth.com/uploads/2025/10/19140812/antarctica-seafloor_anchor-chain-damage_Antarctic-Sun-Star_KOLOSSAL_1s-1.webp 300w, https://cff2.earth.com/uploads/2025/10/19140812/antarctica-seafloor_anchor-chain-damage_Antarctic-Sun-Star_KOLOSSAL_1s-1-150x150.webp 150w, https://cff2.earth.com/uploads/2025/10/19140812/antarctica-seafloor_anchor-chain-damage_Antarctic-Sun-Star_KOLOSSAL_1s-1-32x32.webp 32w" sizes="(max-width: 300px) 100vw, 300px"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;figcaption class="wp-element-caption"&gt;&lt;em&gt;The researchers recorded giant volcano sponges, Antarctic sun stars, giant Antarctic octopus, sea spiders, and a variety of fish at anchor depths. Click image to watch video footage.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-study-scope-and-limits"&gt;Study scope and limits&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Working in Antarctica means trade-offs. The researchers collected observational evidence rather than running a controlled experiment. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They did not take sediment cores or use laser scales to measure exact dimensions, so they avoided claims about the precise depth of disturbance or the size of damaged organisms. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The combination of high-quality imagery and the behavioral signal from ship movements painted a consistent picture: anchoring in sensitive Antarctic sites is actively harming seafloor life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-antarctic-seafloor-anchor-solutions"&gt;Antarctic seafloor anchor solutions&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Solutions to combat this problem already exist. Many modern ships can hold position with &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Dynamic_positioning" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;dynamic positioning&lt;/a&gt; – computer-guided thrusters that maintain location without dropping an anchor. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Where anchoring remains necessary, managers can install hardened moorings: permanent anchors connected to floating buoys so vessels can tie off without dragging gear across living habitat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Harbors can mark “no-anchor” zones around fragile communities and require operators to log and share where they anchor and for how long. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Small choices like these can make a big difference. If a stop will be brief, avoid anchoring. If weather allows, select deeper or less sensitive areas where scouring is less likely to touch vulnerable organisms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-why-does-any-of-this-matter"&gt;Why does any of this matter?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Those sponge gardens and fan forests filter large volumes of water, trap particles, and create shelter and feeding surfaces for fish, sea stars, brittle stars, sea spiders, and many smaller creatures. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They contribute to local food webs that draw wildlife to the same coves where ships like to pause. When anchors clear-cut living structures, the habitat flattens and becomes less diverse. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mud suspended by the chain can clog feeding structures, which slows recovery. Glass sponges in these waters can live for centuries to millennia. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A single swing of chain can knock down individuals that took lifetimes to build skeletons. The cost lands on an ecosystem that heals on timescales far longer than a port call.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study shows vividly what is at stake and how choices at the surface echo across the seafloor. The lesson isn’t “no ships in Antarctica.” The simple solution is “no unnecessary anchors in the wrong places.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-video is-provider-youtube wp-block-embed-youtube wp-embed-aspect-16-9 wp-has-aspect-ratio"&gt;&lt;p class="wp-block-embed__wrapper"&gt;&lt;iframe loading="lazy" title="Anchor and chain damage to seafloor habitats in Antarctica" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/ZZt8AUpXip4?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen&gt;VIDEO&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figcaption class="wp-element-caption"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Underwater recording of the scientists’ observations. Credit: Matt Mulrennan / KOLOSSAL&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;The full study was published in the journal &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.frontiersin.org/news/2025/06/09/protected-antarctic-oceanic-life-threatened-ships-anchoring" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Frontiers in Conservation Science&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;—–&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Like what you read? &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/subscribe/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Subscribe to our newsletter&lt;/a&gt; for engaging articles, exclusive content, and the latest updates.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Check us out on &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/earthsnap/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;EarthSnap&lt;/a&gt;, a free app brought to you by &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/author/eralls/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Eric Ralls&lt;/a&gt; and Earth.com.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;—–&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Earth.com</author><pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 20:44:55 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiqAFBVV95cUxOVHhsVXpSTzJGQjlNNjdlSW9hcjBuZWRMYjl1RFFoSmszcF83X3NualBRUHZjN2NTNWtVVGVJVkxEb2dLNV9xcFppU0hGeVdjOE5jcXBPWlVRYzFPaUoybC1iVXZTanlCZndzYWphalJlSTJacVBMVzE5bXdaOUp6QnA1VGlOQ0xqb3B2Y0h2cWQ1Q0dFamVtbFhITUhKRUl5QmZwLUpLMkE</guid></item><item><title>由营养师创建的健康衰老7天糖尿病膳食计划- EatingWell</title><link>https://www.eatingwell.com/7-day-healthy-aging-meal-plan-for-diabetes-11830086</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="mntl-sc-block-universal-table__table-wrapper"&gt;
&lt;table class="mntl-sc-block-universal-table__table"&gt;
&lt;colgroup span="1"&gt;&lt;/colgroup&gt;
&lt;colgroup span="1"&gt;&lt;/colgroup&gt;
&lt;colgroup span="1"&gt;&lt;/colgroup&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th colspan="3" class="mntl-sc-block-universal-table__title"&gt;Meal Plan at a Glance&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Breakfast/ A.M. Snack&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Lunch/ P.M. Snack&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Dinner/ Evening Snack&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;
&lt;tbody data-check="0"&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;French toast &amp;amp; berries/ Mixed nuts&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Tuna rice bowl/ Cocoa chia pudding&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Sweet chili salmon bowl&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Vanilla-cranberry overnight oats/ Yogurt parfait&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Chickpea salad lunch box/ Cocoa chia pudding&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Balsamic chicken with arugula salad/ Crunchy chickpeas&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Vanilla-cranberry overnight oats/ Edamame&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Chickpea salad lunch box/ Cocoa chia pudding&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Mojo chicken with veggies/ Crunchy chickpeas&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Vanilla-cranberry overnight oats/ Mixed nuts&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Chickpea salad/ Edamame&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Creamy pesto shrimp &amp;amp; gnocchi/ Yogurt parfait&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Yogurt parfait/ Mixed nuts&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Chickpea salad/ Cottage cheese snack jar&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Spicy chicken &amp;amp; cabbage stir-fry/ Apple &amp;amp; nut butter&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Yogurt parfait/ Edamame&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Chicken &amp;amp; feta wrap/ Cottage cheese snack jar&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Chicken with rice &amp;amp; green beans/ Apple &amp;amp; nut butter&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Yogurt parfait/ Edamame&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Chicken &amp;amp; feta wrap/ Cottage cheese snack jar&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;High-protein pasta with peas/ Yogurt parfait&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_5-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-day-1"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_6-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Day 1  &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure id="mntl-sc-block_7-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image--no-theme no-theme figure-square figure-high-res"&gt; 
&lt;figcaption id="mntl-figure-caption_1-0" class="comp mntl-figure-caption text-utility-100 figure-article-caption"&gt; &lt;span class="figure-article-caption-text"&gt;Air-Fryer French Toast Sticks.&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class="figure-article-caption-owner"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jason Donnelly&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_8-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Breakfast (403 Calories)  &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_10-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_11-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Morning Snack (199 Calories)  &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_12-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;li&gt;¼ cup unsalted dry-roasted mixed nuts &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_13-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_14-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Lunch (394 calories)  &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_16-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_17-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Afternoon Snack (222 Calories)  &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_19-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_20-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Dinner (604 Calories)  &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_22-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_23-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Daily totals&lt;/strong&gt;: 1,822 calories, 88 g fat, 93 g protein, 168 g carbohydrates, 34 g fiber, 1,724 mg sodium&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_24-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_25-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;To make it 1,500 calories&lt;/strong&gt;: Omit morning snack and omit avocado from dinner.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_26-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_27-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;To make it 2,000 calories&lt;/strong&gt;: Add ¼ cup hummus with 1 cup cucumbers as an evening snack. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_28-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-day-2"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_29-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Day 2 &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure id="mntl-sc-block_30-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image--no-theme no-theme figure-square figure-high-res"&gt; 
&lt;figcaption id="mntl-figure-caption_2-0" class="comp mntl-figure-caption text-utility-100 figure-article-caption"&gt; &lt;span class="figure-article-caption-text"&gt;Easy Chickpea Salad Lunch Box.&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class="figure-article-caption-owner"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ali Redmond&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_31-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Breakfast (422 Calories)  &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_33-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_34-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Morning Snack (125 Calories)  &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_35-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;li&gt;½ cup low-fat plain strained (Greek-style) yogurt&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;½ cup fresh blueberries&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_36-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_37-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Lunch (422 calories)  &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_39-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_40-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Afternoon Snack (222 Calories)  &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_42-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_43-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Dinner (485 Calories)  &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_45-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_46-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Evening Snack (100 Calories)  &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_48-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_49-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Daily totals&lt;/strong&gt;: 1,776 calories, 81 g fat, 90 g protein, 190 g carbohydrates, 44 g fiber, 1,399 mg sodium&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_50-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_51-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;To make it 1,500 calories&lt;/strong&gt;: Omit blueberries from morning snack and omit afternoon snack. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_52-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_53-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;To make it 2,000 calories&lt;/strong&gt;: Increase morning snack to 1 cup low-fat plain strained (Greek-style) yogurt with 1 cup blueberries and add ½ cup low-fat plain strained (Greek-style) yogurt and ¼ cup cucumbers to evening snack to make a savory yogurt bowl.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_54-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-day-3"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_55-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Day 3 &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure id="mntl-sc-block_56-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image--no-theme no-theme figure-square figure-high-res"&gt; 
&lt;figcaption id="mntl-figure-caption_3-0" class="comp mntl-figure-caption text-utility-100 figure-article-caption"&gt; &lt;span class="figure-article-caption-text"&gt;Sheet-Pan Mojo Chicken with Green Beans &amp;amp; Potatoes.&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class="figure-article-caption-owner"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Photographer: Jake Sternquist, Food Stylist: Shannon Goforth, Prop Stylist: Breanna Ghazali.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_57-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Breakfast (422 Calories)  &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_59-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_60-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Morning Snack (129 Calories)  &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_61-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;li&gt;1 cup edamame, in pods (microwaved from frozen) &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_62-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_63-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Lunch (505 calories)  &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_65-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_66-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Afternoon Snack (222 Calories)  &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_68-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_69-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Dinner (413 Calories)  &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_71-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_72-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Evening Snack (100 Calories)  &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_74-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_75-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Daily totals&lt;/strong&gt;: 1,790 calories, 85 g fat, 94 g protein, 181 g carbohydrates, 49 g fiber, 1,422 mg sodium&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_76-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_77-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;To make it 1,500 calories&lt;/strong&gt;: Omit yogurt from lunch and omit afternoon snack. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_78-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_79-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;To make it 2,000 calories&lt;/strong&gt;: Add ⅓ avocado to dinner and add ½ cup low-fat plain strained (Greek-style) yogurt and ¼ cup cucumbers to evening snack to make a savory yogurt bowl.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_80-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-day-4"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_81-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Day 4 &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure id="mntl-sc-block_82-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image--no-theme no-theme figure-square figure-high-res"&gt; 
&lt;figcaption id="mntl-figure-caption_4-0" class="comp mntl-figure-caption text-utility-100 figure-article-caption"&gt; &lt;span class="figure-article-caption-text"&gt;Creamy Pesto Shrimp with Gnocchi &amp;amp; Peas.&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class="figure-article-caption-owner"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Photographer: Greg DuPree, Prop stylist: Shell Royster, Food stylist: Emily Hall&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_83-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Breakfast (422 Calories)  &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_85-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_86-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Morning Snack (199 Calories)  &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_87-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;li&gt;¼ cup unsalted dry-roasted mixed nuts &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_88-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_89-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Lunch (422 calories)  &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_91-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_92-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Afternoon Snack (129 Calories)  &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_93-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;li&gt;1 cup edamame, in pods (microwaved from frozen) &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_94-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_95-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Dinner (409 Calories)  &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_97-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_98-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Evening Snack (250 Calories)  &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_99-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;li&gt;1 cup low-fat plain strained (Greek-style) yogurt&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;1 cup blueberries &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_100-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_101-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Daily totals&lt;/strong&gt;: 1,830 calories, 86 g fat, 87 g protein, 192 g carbohydrates, 37 g fiber, 1,222 mg sodium&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_102-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_103-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;To make it 1,500 calories&lt;/strong&gt;: Omit morning and afternoon snacks. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_104-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_105-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;To make it 2,000 calories&lt;/strong&gt;: Add ¼ cup hummus with 1 cup cucumbers to afternoon snack.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_106-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-day-5"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_107-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Day 5 &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure id="mntl-sc-block_108-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image--no-theme no-theme figure-square figure-high-res"&gt; 
&lt;figcaption id="mntl-figure-caption_5-0" class="comp mntl-figure-caption text-utility-100 figure-article-caption"&gt; &lt;span class="figure-article-caption-text"&gt;Everything Bagel Cottage Cheese Snack Jar with Bell Peppers and Chickpeas.&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class="figure-article-caption-owner"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Photographer: Jen Causey, Food Stylist: Chelsea Zimmer, Prop Stylist: Claire Spollen&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_109-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Breakfast (381 Calories)  &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_111-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_112-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Morning Snack (199 Calories)  &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_113-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;li&gt;¼ cup unsalted dry-roasted mixed nuts &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_114-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_115-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Lunch (422 calories)  &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_117-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_118-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Afternoon Snack (195 Calories)  &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_120-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_121-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Dinner (392 Calories)  &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_123-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_124-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Evening Snack (190 Calories)  &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_125-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;li&gt;1 medium apple&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;1 Tbsp. natural peanut butter&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_126-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_127-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Daily totals&lt;/strong&gt;: 1,779 calories, 81 g fat, 93 g protein, 173 g carbohydrates, 34 g fiber, 1,406 mg sodium&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_128-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_129-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;To make it 1,500 calories&lt;/strong&gt;: Omit walnuts from breakfast and omit evening snack . 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_130-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_131-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;To make it 2,000 calories&lt;/strong&gt;: Add 1 Tbsp. chia seeds to breakfast, add ½ cup blueberries to morning snack, and add 1 cup edamame, in pods (microwaved from frozen) to dinner.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_132-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-day-6"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_133-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Day 6  &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure id="mntl-sc-block_134-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image--no-theme no-theme figure-landscape figure-high-res"&gt; 
&lt;figcaption id="mntl-figure-caption_6-0" class="comp mntl-figure-caption text-utility-100 figure-article-caption"&gt; &lt;span class="figure-article-caption-text"&gt;Chicken, Spinach &amp;amp; Feta Wrap.&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class="figure-article-caption-owner"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Photographer: Grant Webster, Food Stylist: Addelyn Evans, Prop Stylist: Gabe Greco&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_135-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Breakfast (381 Calories)  &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_137-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_138-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Morning Snack (129 Calories)  &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_139-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;li&gt;1 cup edamame, in pods (microwaved from frozen) &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_140-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_141-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Lunch (457 calories)  &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_143-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_144-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Afternoon Snack (195 Calories)  &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_146-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_147-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Dinner (459 Calories)  &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_149-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_150-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Evening Snack (190 Calories)  &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_151-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;li&gt;1 medium apple&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;1 Tbsp. natural peanut butter &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_152-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_153-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Daily totals&lt;/strong&gt;: 1,810 calories, 78 g fat, 124 g protein, 160 g carbohydrates, 36 g fiber, 1,547 mg sodium&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_154-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_155-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;To make it 1,500 calories&lt;/strong&gt;: Omit morning and evening snacks. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_156-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_157-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;To make it 2,000 calories&lt;/strong&gt;: Add 1 Tbsp. chia seeds to breakfast, add ½ cup blueberries to morning snack, and add ⅓ avocado to lunch wrap.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_158-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-day-7"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_159-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Day 7  &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure id="mntl-sc-block_160-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image--no-theme no-theme figure-square figure-high-res"&gt; 
&lt;figcaption id="mntl-figure-caption_7-0" class="comp mntl-figure-caption text-utility-100 figure-article-caption"&gt; &lt;span class="figure-article-caption-text"&gt;High-Protein Pasta with Peas.&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class="figure-article-caption-owner"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Photographer: Morgan Hunt Glaze, Prop Stylist: Claire Spollen, Food Stylist: Chelsea Zimmer&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_161-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Breakfast (381 Calories)  &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_163-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_164-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Morning Snack (129 Calories)  &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_165-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;li&gt;1 cup edamame, in pods (microwaved from frozen)  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_166-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_167-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Lunch (457 calories)  &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_169-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_170-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Afternoon Snack (195 Calories)  &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_172-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_173-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Dinner (414 Calories)  &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_175-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_176-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Evening Snack (250 Calories)  &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_177-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;li&gt;1 cup low-fat plain strained (Greek-style) yogurt&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;1 cup blueberries &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_178-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_179-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Daily totals&lt;/strong&gt;: 1,825 calories, 71 g fat, 119 g protein, 181 g carbohydrates, 35 g fiber, 1,369 mg sodium&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_180-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_181-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;To make it 1,500 calories&lt;/strong&gt;: Omit morning and afternoon snacks. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_182-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_183-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;To make it 2,000 calories&lt;/strong&gt;: Add 1 Tbsp. chia seeds to breakfast and add ⅓ avocado to lunch wrap.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_184-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div id="mntl-sc-block_186-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-faq mntl-sc-block-universal-faq"&gt;&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-faqs-bef0fa37-757c-4570-81e8-6f9ad1218e59"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;h2 class="mntl-sc-block-universal-faq__title"&gt;Frequently Asked Questions&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;noscript id="universal-faq-noscript_1-0" class="comp universal-faq-noscript mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block-universal-faq__content_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block-universal-faq__content mntl-accordion js-accordion"&gt;
&lt;li class="accordion__item js-accordion-item " data-ordinal="1"&gt;
&lt;p tabindex="0" class="accordion__header js-accordion-trigger" id="mntl-accordion__item_1-0-section-0"&gt;
&lt;svg class="icon icon-chevron accordion__icon"&gt;
&lt;use xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xlink:href="#icon-chevron" href="#icon-chevron"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;
&lt;/svg&gt;
&lt;span class="accordion__title"&gt;Is it OK to mix and match meals if there’s one I don’t like?&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="accordion__body"&gt;
&lt;div id="mntl-accordion__content_1-0" class="comp mntl-accordion__content"&gt; &lt;div class="faq-accordion__item-answer"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yes! This meal plan is meant to serve as inspiration. It doesn’t need to be followed exactly to reap the benefits. When choosing recipes, we made sure to check the calories, fiber, protein and sodium to align with the parameters of this plan and be within our sodium limits. If you’re making a recipe swap, it may be helpful to choose a recipe with similar calories, fiber, protein and sodium levels. For more inspiration, check out these delicious &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/recipes/17899/health-condition/diabetic/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;diabetes-friendly recipes.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="accordion__item js-accordion-item " data-ordinal="2"&gt;
&lt;p tabindex="0" class="accordion__header js-accordion-trigger" id="mntl-accordion__item_2-0-section-1"&gt;
&lt;svg class="icon icon-chevron accordion__icon"&gt;
&lt;use xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xlink:href="#icon-chevron" href="#icon-chevron"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;
&lt;/svg&gt;
&lt;span class="accordion__title"&gt;Can I eat the same breakfast or lunch every day?&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="accordion__body"&gt;
&lt;div id="mntl-accordion__content_2-0" class="comp mntl-accordion__content"&gt; &lt;div class="faq-accordion__item-answer"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Definitely, it’s fine to eat the same breakfast or lunch every day. The breakfasts range from 381 to 422 calories, while the lunches span 394 to 505 calories. These ranges are fairly close, though if you’re closely monitoring your calories or other nutrients, like protein, you may want to adjust a snack or two.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="accordion__item js-accordion-item " data-ordinal="3"&gt;
&lt;p tabindex="0" class="accordion__header js-accordion-trigger" id="mntl-accordion__item_3-0-section-2"&gt;
&lt;svg class="icon icon-chevron accordion__icon"&gt;
&lt;use xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xlink:href="#icon-chevron" href="#icon-chevron"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;
&lt;/svg&gt;
&lt;span class="accordion__title"&gt;Why is there not a 1,200-calorie modification?&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="accordion__body"&gt;
&lt;div id="mntl-accordion__content_3-0" class="comp mntl-accordion__content"&gt; &lt;div class="faq-accordion__item-answer"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We no longer provide modifications for 1,200-calorie days in our meal plans. The 2020-2025 Dietary Guidelines for Americans suggests that limiting calories to 1,200 per day is too low for most people to meet their nutritional needs, plus it’s unsustainable for long-term health and well-being.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="5"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;noscript id="accordion-noscript_1-0" class="comp accordion-noscript mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_187-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-other-tips-for-healthy-aging"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_188-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Other Tips for Healthy Aging &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_189-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Besides eating a well-rounded diet with plenty of fruits, veggies, whole grains, lean proteins and healthy fats, there are a few other lifestyle changes you can make for healthy aging. For one, try to stay active through a mix of aerobic activity, muscle-strengthening and balance work. This promotes &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/small-habits-for-heart-health-11796620" link-destination-recommendation="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;heart health&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/best-habit-to-break-for-better-metabolic-health-8751700" link-destination-recommendation="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;metabolic health&lt;/a&gt; and helps prevent falls. It also helps combat age-related losses in muscle mass and bone density.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="3"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_190-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_191-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Also, don’t underestimate the importance of a good night’s sleep. This is when your body and brain slow down to rest and recover from the wear-and-tear of the day. Studies show that not getting enough quality sleep is linked with higher rates of depression, dementia, falls and cognitive decline. Other things that support healthy aging include keeping up with regular checkups with your health care providers, minimizing your alcohol intake, quitting smoking, regularly socializing and keeping your mind active through reading, writing or games.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="4"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_192-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="mntl-sc-block_193-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-callout mntl-sc-block-universal-callout theme-generic" data-tracking-id="mntl-sc-block-callout" data-tracking-container="true"&gt; &lt;h3 class="mntl-sc-block-universal-callout__heading"&gt;How We Create Meal Plans&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;div class="mntl-sc-block-universal-callout__body"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Registered dietitians thoughtfully create EatingWell’s meal plans to be easy-to-follow and delicious. Each meal plan meets specific parameters depending on the health condition and/or lifestyle goal it is targeting and is analyzed for accuracy using the nutrition database, ESHA Food Processor. As nutritional needs differ from person to person, we encourage you to use these plans as inspiration and adjust as you see fit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>EatingWell</author><pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 19:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihAFBVV95cUxQMXlOWFE1Y2RkbWwxZGEyOGMyN3k5R3lWY3E5anNrN0tpUjRodzAzbTJNaklrZjdqRGJUMXpiSUdUZDk1WUtyMGNwN3dFNkRyUGVZQ3VDa2ZqNlVoUUQ2T2lKUGlxTjVIQnQzemhfZ3pUa2hUTmJ3MmhPUUIyemtoU2o1YkY</guid></item><item><title>纽约市在公园推出狂犬病疫苗诱饵- Boro Park 24</title><link>https://www.boropark24.com/news/nyc-rolls-out-rabies-vaccine-baits-in-parks</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="single-blog-wrapper"&gt;

						
						&lt;h2 class="axil-post-title hover-line"&gt;NYC Rolls Out Rabies Vaccine Baits in Parks&lt;/h2&gt;
						
						&lt;figure&gt;
							&lt;img src="https://d2hznbomsf2d97.cloudfront.net/news/31539315-176071658668f26729eb5b01760716585964.jpeg" alt="NYC Rolls Out Rabies Vaccine Baits in Parks"&gt;						&lt;/figure&gt;
						

						&lt;p&gt;By Y.M. Lowy &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Brooklyn parks are part of the city’s fall campaign to vaccinate raccoons against rabies using fish-scented bait packets. The Health Department is distributing the oral vaccines in areas of Brooklyn, Queens, and Manhattan where raccoons are common.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So far this year, 18 raccoons, one cat, and one bat in the city have tested positive for rabies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The bait packets are small, brown, and fish-scented, containing a pink liquid vaccine that immunizes animals when chewed. Officials are placing them in wooded parks and green spaces in coordination with the U.S. Department of Agriculture and the city’s Parks Department. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Rabies is a serious disease that can be fatal,” said Acting Health Commissioner Dr. Michelle Morse. “New Yorkers can help by keeping pets up to date on rabies vaccinations and maintaining distance from wildlife. If you see an animal behaving erratically, please call 311.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Officials emphasized that the baits do not pose a risk to people or pets, though the liquid inside can cause a rash if touched. Anyone who comes into contact with it should wash their hands with soap and water or use hand sanitizer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;photo: Shutterstock&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

						&lt;p class="gallery_section"&gt;

													&lt;/p&gt;
						




					&lt;/div&gt;
					
				&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Boro Park 24</author><pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 18:54:44 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigAFBVV95cUxQamxFc1lkRXlyU3VpMWdZT1BmUTh4OWFNZUVRZWNJYUdWbkd5bmtLTVl5MnBkZk92aUFYVjFSYmFRM0VtdVU3cVFPRm5CUXQzc1NmcWVzX3ZyVVNwTVIzR1c4YlFmV1g5Ykl4ZGhhbHlLZHpGWVVTNFJTc1NVS0owWQ</guid></item><item><title>Cowboy State Daily罕见的10万分之一Piebald牛麋鹿在Cody附近被发现</title><link>https://cowboystatedaily.com/2025/10/19/1-in-100-000-white-elk-spotted-near-cody/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;section class="_1sy4yg80 _1t01cac0"&gt;&lt;p class="_1uhbe1z1 _1uhbe1z0"&gt;When Powell resident Michael Moore ventured up the South Fork of the Shoshone River, east of Cody, he was looking for elk. Fall’s the best time of year to catch them acting up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="_1uhbe1z1 _1uhbe1z0"&gt;“Every year, there's always a bunch of elk on the J Bar 9 Ranch, right off the highway,” Moore told Cowboy State Daily. “I always like to look at the elk when they're in the rut.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="_1uhbe1z1 _1uhbe1z0"&gt;Moore found a herd of elk right where he expected them to be, but they weren’t doing much of anything. That’s when he noticed “the one elk that stood out.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="_1uhbe1z1 _1uhbe1z0"&gt;“It was far above the others,” he said. “I took a look at it, got it closer with my zoom lens, and saw that it was one of those piebald elk.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="_1uhbe1z1 _1uhbe1z0"&gt;Instead of the usual brown, this cow elk’s entire body was covered in white hair. Moore had seen pictures of piebald elk, but in his many years of hunting and wildlife photography, he’d never encountered one in the wild.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="_1uhbe1z1 _1uhbe1z0"&gt;“It was definitely worth the drive,” he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="_1uhbe1z3 _1uhbe1z2 _1uhbe1z0"&gt;&lt;figure class="n1n9p21"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="p8ohjc5 p8ohjc0 n1n9p22 _10mr6051 vbxqml4 _10mr60539"&gt;The piebald elk cow along the South Fork of the Shoshone River near Cody. Most piebald elk don't make it to adulthood, but this extremely rare cow appeared to be young and healthy. (Courtesy Michael Moore)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h2 class="_1uhbe1z1 _1uhbe1z0"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Standing Out In A Crowd&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="_1uhbe1z1 _1uhbe1z0"&gt;Piebaldism is the result of a genetic recessive trait, a lack of melanin in the skin and hair of animals, that rarely manifests in nature. Both parents of an animal must have the same recessive trait to produce a piebald offspring, which has blotches of white covering its body.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="_1uhbe1z1 _1uhbe1z0"&gt;When a piebald elk was spotted in Estes Park, Colorado, earlier this year, Colorado Parks and Wildlife said the trait only appears in “&lt;a class="OWAAutoLink" href="https://www.facebook.com/CoParksWildlife/posts/a-glimpse-of-a-rare-elkthis-piebald-female-cow-elk-in-estes-park-has-been-catchi/1117374513762978/" title="https://www.facebook.com/CoParksWildlife/posts/a-glimpse-of-a-rare-elkthis-piebald-female-cow-elk-in-estes-park-has-been-catchi/1117374513762978/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;1 out of every 100,000 elk.&lt;/a&gt;”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="_1uhbe1z1 _1uhbe1z0"&gt;Karie Decker, director of Wildlife and Habitat for the Rocky Mountain Elk Foundation, can verify that statistic, but there’s no denying that piebald elk are a rare sight.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="_1uhbe1z1 _1uhbe1z0"&gt;“We generally say it's less than 1% of the population,” she said. “It's hard to pin down because a lot of fawns that are born with this condition don't live very long, so you don't actually see them in the wild.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="_1uhbe1z1 _1uhbe1z0"&gt;Decker said there haven’t been any studies specifically on piebald elk, except for the fact that both parents must have the same recessive gene for the trait to manifest in their offspring. One out of two isn’t good enough, and a piebald parent isn’t guaranteed to produce a matching calf.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="_1uhbe1z1 _1uhbe1z0"&gt;“It's possible for a piebald doe to produce completely normal-looking calves,” she said. “It’s just a mix of white and brown hair and skin, but it depends on how the female’s gene shows up and combines with the male gene.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="_1uhbe1z1 _1uhbe1z0"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Piebald Problems&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="_1uhbe1z1 _1uhbe1z0"&gt;Piebald elk could be more common than biologists realize, but evidence suggests that most elk calves born with the recessive gene don’t survive to adulthood. Decker said being piebald can come with a host of genetic issues that can cripple or kill a calf not long after its birth.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="_1uhbe1z1 _1uhbe1z0"&gt;“There are other physical traits that piebald deer, elk, and other animals can experience,” she said. “A lot of calves have skeletal deformities, which can be fairly mild or fairly severe, that don't allow them to live very long. The coloration isn’t causing the deformities, but the group of recessive genes that cause them can come along with (piebaldism).”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="_1uhbe1z1 _1uhbe1z0"&gt;A skeletal deformity, especially in the long bones of the legs, can be a death sentence for a calf before it’s born. They’ll usually die of natural causes or be more easily picked off by a predator shortly after birth.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="_1uhbe1z1 _1uhbe1z0"&gt;Seeing a piebald elk in adulthood means it was born without any skeletal deformities, or it’s managed to thrive despite any genetic setbacks. According to Moore, the piebald elk he spotted was young, healthy, and thriving in the Greater Yellowstone Ecosystem.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="_1uhbe1z1 _1uhbe1z0"&gt;“I've heard older cow elk can get grayed up, but I’ve never seen one,” he said. “People who’ve seen my pictures have said this one was actually a pretty young cow, and she seemed to be doing just fine.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="_1uhbe1z1 _1uhbe1z0"&gt;Even Decker hasn’t seen a piebald elk in the wild. When someone with the Rocky Mountain Elk Foundation hasn’t seen one, you know it’s special.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="_1uhbe1z1 _1uhbe1z0"&gt;“It’s definitely rare,” she said. “It’s nothing, something that we’re going to see in the landscape often.”  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="_1uhbe1z3 _1uhbe1z2 _1uhbe1z0"&gt;&lt;figure class="n1n9p21"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="p8ohjc5 p8ohjc0 n1n9p22 _10mr6051 vbxqml4 _10mr60539"&gt;The piebald elk cow along the South Fork of the Shoshone River near Cody. Most piebald elk don't make it to adulthood, but this extremely rare cow appeared to be young and healthy. (Courtesy Michael Moore)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h2 class="_1uhbe1z1 _1uhbe1z0"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;White Meat?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="_1uhbe1z1 _1uhbe1z0"&gt;Assuming this piebald elk survives the winter, she could go on to produce healthy calves. Some of them could even be piebald, but only if she finds and mates with a bull elk carrying that specific recessive gene.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="_1uhbe1z1 _1uhbe1z0"&gt;A piebald cow elk is rare enough, but nearly all of those spotted have been cows. A piebald bull could be the Holy Grail of elk for lucky photographers and hunters, if there are any out there.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="_1uhbe1z1 _1uhbe1z0"&gt;Since piebaldism affects the skin and hair of animals, could it also affect their meat? Would a piebald elk taste differently from a normal elk?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="_1uhbe1z1 _1uhbe1z0"&gt;“I don't suspect it would,” Decker said. “The genetic mutation is primarily focused on the skin and hair, so I can't imagine that it would affect the meat, but I can’t say I’ve ever eaten a piebald elk.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="_1uhbe1z1 _1uhbe1z0"&gt;Moore got a few shots of the piebald elk before it lay down in a less-than-optimal position for photography. He didn’t get the fall rut he was hoping for that day, but a 1-in-100,000 elk wasn’t a bad consolation prize.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="_1uhbe1z1 _1uhbe1z0"&gt;“There's nothing quite like getting up there when the bulls are acting pretty aggressive and you can hear them bugling,” he said. “I got a few photos of the piebald elk before she lay down with her back to me. Not a lot of great photos, but still worth seeing.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="_1uhbe1z1 _1uhbe1z0"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Andrew Rossi can be reached at &lt;a href="mailto:arossi@cowboystatedaily.com" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;arossi@cowboystatedaily.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Cowboy State Daily</author><pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 17:34:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiAFBVV95cUxNOFpFLVY2ZjhmZldCODU2cy1raF9Kd0Jad0YtWjE3X2ZSWWdSdHJ1UW1BeUlrbEpSQXlwZUNacTJNcXQ1dFlhb2JDcU14cVV6NzdYTTc2YjNzY1otS21FU2pGdVlNRkRKa25Ya0FiZGRWSU4xZkNCdmliSVprQ3FyX2NOZlRXd2Rj</guid></item><item><title>专家说，「日式」间歇步行是健身的简单方法- WQOW</title><link>https://www.wqow.com/health-watch/japanese-interval-walking-is-an-easy-way-to-become-fit-experts-say/article_c30dfa69-c57e-5aa0-b7c2-ec1c1b836cd5.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="article-body" itemprop="articleBody" class="asset-content  subscriber-premium" false&gt;
                                &lt;meta itemprop="isAccessibleForFree" content="true"&gt;
                                
                                
                                &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;(CNN) —&lt;/strong&gt; One of the latest fitness fads trending on social media is “Japanese walking,” a 30-minute exercise regimen in which you alternate walking at a normal pace with &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2025/08/11/health/walking-fast-benefits-study-wellness"&gt;bursts of speed&lt;/a&gt;. It’s easy to see the appeal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Japanese walking is a relatively short, accessible workout that doesn’t require a gym membership or special equipment. All you have to do is walk out the door.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“What I like about Japanese walking is that anyone can do it,” said Dr. Irvin Sulapas, a sports medicine physician and associate professor at UTHealth Houston. “You don’t need to do super high-intensity workouts, where you’re sore and tired, to gain improvements to your health.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="tncms-region-article_instory_top" class="tncms-region hidden-print"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Japanese researchers developed this exercise regimen — hence the moniker Japanese walking — more than 20 years ago. The goal was to increase physical fitness among middle-aged and older adults, plus help this group prevent &lt;a href="https://www.un.org/en/chronicle/article/lifestyle-diseases-economic-burden-health-services"&gt;lifestyle-related diseases&lt;/a&gt; such as diabetes and obesity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;High-intensity interval walking may protect older people from higher blood pressure, the researchers found. The activity may also help combat decreased thigh muscle strength and diminished peak aerobic capacity, according to the &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/17605959/"&gt;July 2007 study&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This same research team found in a related &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/19752116/"&gt;2009 review&lt;/a&gt; that five months of interval walking training increased participants’ physical fitness and improved their indices of lifestyle-related diseases by an average of 10% to 20%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;More recently, older adults who practiced Japanese walking for five months showed improvements in resting blood pressure, lower-limb muscle strength and &lt;a href="https://www.health.harvard.edu/staying-healthy/vo2-max-what-is-it-and-how-can-you-improve-it"&gt;VO2 max&lt;/a&gt;, a key indicator of cardiovascular fitness and aerobic endurance, according to a &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40582858/"&gt;2025 study&lt;/a&gt; by a different group of scientists. This latest research may have sparked Japanese walking’s current popularity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;High-intensity interval walking — and other forms of exercise — are definitely good for your heart health and well-being, said Dr. Sergiu Darabant, a medical cardiologist at Miami Cardiac &amp;amp; Vascular Institute, part of Baptist Health South Florida.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“But Japanese walking is intriguing to many because it offers an entry to exercise from a sedentary lifestyle,” Darabant said. “It’s not intimidating.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;How to get started&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the 2007 study, researchers instructed participants to alternate three minutes of fast walking at 70% peak aerobic capacity — a moderate- to high-intensity pace — with three minutes of slower walking at 40% peak aerobic capacity, a low-intensity exercise level, for at least 30 minutes on four days per week.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That’s generally the same advice experts give today, although Darabant suggested upping the walk to five days per week. If you do so, you’ll be getting 150 minutes of moderate-intensity exercise every week, the exact recommendation for aerobic activity from the &lt;a href="https://www.heart.org/en/healthy-living/fitness/fitness-basics/aha-recs-for-physical-activity-in-adults"&gt;American Heart Association&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;How do you know if you’re walking fast enough during your speedy minutes? Walk as fast as you can without breaking into a jog, Darabant said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Generally, a brisk walk is considered around 4 miles per hour, although everyone’s different,” Sulapas said. Four miles per hour equates to a 15-minute-per-mile pace.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="tncms-region-article_instory_middle" class="tncms-region hidden-print"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As with any exercise, safety is key. Before rushing outside to try Japanese walking, consult your doctor, and stop immediately if you experience pain. Keep in mind you can also practice Japanese walking indoors on a treadmill, especially if your streets aren’t well-paved, it’s icy out, or you don’t have a safe place to walk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“If you’re using a treadmill, set the incline at 1% to 2%,” Sulapas said, as this incline best mimics the resistance the average person gets from walking outside.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But if you do have the option of performing this workout alfresco, especially in a natural setting, that’s the best option, Darabant said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Engaging with the outdoors is 100% better,” he said. “It not only helps your overall physique, but it helps &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2022/04/22/health/forest-bathing-wellness"&gt;engage your mind, reduces anxiety&lt;/a&gt; and connects you with nature.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Transitioning to other forms of exercise&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Once you’re a pro at Japanese walking, you may want to consider advancing to jogging or walking with a weighted vest.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The more intense the level, the better outcomes you’ll see,” Darabant said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yet in the end, committing to your exercise regimen is most important.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I don’t mean this as a pun, but exercise is a marathon, not a sprint,” Darabant said. “We should all aim for consistency and a clear lifestyle change. Embarking on an exercise journey should be done gradually.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sulapas agreed. “Interval walking is a great start to someone’s fitness journey,” he said. “As you become more fit, you can always up the intensity. But there are definitely health benefits, even if you stick with interval walking.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Which, incidentally, both physicians practice. Sulapas employs Japanese walking toward the end of the half-marathons he runs. “By then,” he said, “I’m kind of hurting!”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Darabant turns to Japanese walking whenever he’s short on time and energy. “It’s always my go-to backup,” he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The-CNN-Wire&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;™ &amp;amp; © 2025 Cable News Network, Inc., a Warner Bros. Discovery Company. All rights reserved.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="tncms-region-article_instory_bottom" class="tncms-region hidden-print"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
                                
                                
                            &lt;/div&gt;

                            

                            
    


                            
    


                            
                                &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>WQOW</author><pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi5AFBVV95cUxPQWZ5bUZjT2syMjV1VXcxXzUtVGdkNFBMVmNYT08xbnF5a3ZUMUh4N3ExZ1lZRi1IUFF5MXFwZ0s0ZVFvVWVHRV84SkRJYWl5aWVMYjh6a05CaFpCVmVRa3hhb01XY3RMWEVHdUFTS1F5eEREUzZTMFcwVVRCd0luekdUaGVfR3hlR2JJOHFiNDBkV1JMV1hGMGRueDJxWVd2Z1FQb1FEZzJKa1NGTzliYXFfdkJrdHBPT1Jld2J1N3NGUTJHMnFjYXpYR2l6UnNDemprMDc1MERYVFYtX1NVZlRwb1k</guid></item><item><title>椰子水对空腹的7种健康益处- NDTV</title><link>https://www.ndtv.com/webstories/feature/7-health-benefits-of-coconut-water-on-empty-stomach-48257</link><description>&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt; &lt;amp-story standalone class="ms-ObwsjcNKm_Ene56B0cj" poster-portrait-src="https://c.ndtvimg.com/gws/ms/7-health-benefits-of-coconut-water/assets/19.jpeg?1760885283" publisher-logo-src="https://c.ndtvimg.com/gws/2128/assets/15.png" publisher="NDTV" title="7 Health Benefits Of Coconut Water On Empty Stomach"&gt; &lt;amp-story-page id="orpxclzgug" class="orpxclzgug ms-st-pg"&gt; &lt;amp-story-grid-layer template="fill" class="pbaejagp"&gt; &lt;amp-img layout="responsive" class="pbaejag" id="orpxclzgug-bg" src="https://c.ndtvimg.com/gws/ms/7-health-benefits-of-coconut-water/assets/2.jpeg?1760885283" alt="7 Health Benefits Of Coconut Water On Empty Stomach"&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt; &lt;/amp-story-grid-layer&gt; &lt;amp-story-grid-layer template="vertical" id="wdjwf" class="scrim"&gt;&lt;div class="letterbox"&gt;  &lt;h1 class="ttpqj pa ttpqj-a"&gt;&lt;span&gt;7 Health Benefits Of Coconut Water On Empty Stomach&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h1&gt; &lt;p class="aiecb pa aiecb-a"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Image credit: Unsplash&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p class="zomof pa svg-el"&gt;&lt;svg preserveaspectratio="none" viewbox="0 0 100 100" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"&gt; &lt;ellipse cx="50" cy="50" rx="50" ry="50" fill="rgba(0,0,0,1)"&gt;&lt;/ellipse&gt; &lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;h2 class="ozgkr pa"&gt;19 October 2025&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/amp-story-grid-layer&gt; &lt;amp-story-animation layout="nodisplay" trigger="visibility"&gt;  &lt;/amp-story-animation&gt; &lt;/amp-story-page&gt; &lt;amp-story-page id="zkmrglwebp" class="zkmrglwebp ms-st-pg"&gt; &lt;amp-story-grid-layer template="fill" class="pbijlcip"&gt; &lt;amp-img layout="responsive" class="pbijlci" id="zkmrglwebp-bg" src="https://c.ndtvimg.com/gws/ms/7-health-benefits-of-coconut-water/assets/4.jpeg?1760885283" alt="7 Health Benefits Of Coconut Water On Empty Stomach"&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt; &lt;/amp-story-grid-layer&gt; &lt;amp-story-grid-layer template="vertical" id="kozls" class="scrim"&gt;&lt;div class="letterbox"&gt; &lt;h2 class="qzcum pa qzcum-a"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Nariyal &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;pani&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;, or coconut water, is a refreshing and nutritious beverage that offers several benefits when consumed on an empty stomach&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;    &lt;p class="assgo pa assgo-a"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Image credit: Unsplash&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/amp-story-grid-layer&gt; &lt;amp-story-animation layout="nodisplay" trigger="visibility"&gt;  &lt;/amp-story-animation&gt; &lt;/amp-story-page&gt; &lt;amp-story-page id="eizzxurglw" class="eizzxurglw ms-st-pg"&gt; &lt;amp-story-grid-layer template="fill" class="pbwpwfdp"&gt; &lt;amp-img layout="responsive" class="pbwpwfd" id="eizzxurglw-bg" src="https://c.ndtvimg.com/gws/ms/7-health-benefits-of-coconut-water/assets/7.jpeg?1760885283" alt="7 Health Benefits Of Coconut Water On Empty Stomach"&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt; &lt;/amp-story-grid-layer&gt; &lt;amp-story-grid-layer template="vertical" id="fizas" class="scrim"&gt;&lt;div class="letterbox"&gt; &lt;h2 class="nsela pa nsela-a"&gt;&lt;span&gt;1. Hydration: It is a natural, electrolyte-rich drink that replenishes fluids and electrolytes. An amazing rehydrating drink, especially after a night of sleep&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;    &lt;p class="oqndn pa oqndn-a"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Image credit: Unsplash&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/amp-story-grid-layer&gt; &lt;amp-story-animation layout="nodisplay" trigger="visibility"&gt;  &lt;/amp-story-animation&gt; &lt;/amp-story-page&gt; &lt;amp-story-page id="bzxyvaedmo" class="bzxyvaedmo ms-st-pg"&gt; &lt;amp-story-grid-layer template="fill" class="pbcgaxup"&gt; &lt;amp-img layout="responsive" class="pbcgaxu" id="bzxyvaedmo-bg" src="https://c.ndtvimg.com/gws/ms/7-health-benefits-of-coconut-water/assets/8.jpeg?1760885283" alt="7 Health Benefits Of Coconut Water On Empty Stomach"&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt; &lt;/amp-story-grid-layer&gt; &lt;amp-story-grid-layer template="vertical" id="lqfis" class="scrim"&gt;&lt;div class="letterbox"&gt; &lt;h2 class="lbkmj pa lbkmj-a"&gt;&lt;span&gt;2. Energy Booster: The natural sugars and electrolytes in coconut water provide a quick energy boost, helping you feel more alert and focused&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;    &lt;p class="gdnln pa gdnln-a"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Image credit: Unsplash&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/amp-story-grid-layer&gt; &lt;amp-story-animation layout="nodisplay" trigger="visibility"&gt;  &lt;/amp-story-animation&gt; &lt;/amp-story-page&gt; &lt;amp-story-page id="nlkeevbhsb" class="nlkeevbhsb ms-st-pg"&gt; &lt;amp-story-grid-layer template="fill" class="pblkjupp"&gt; &lt;amp-img layout="responsive" class="pblkjup" id="nlkeevbhsb-bg" src="https://c.ndtvimg.com/gws/ms/7-health-benefits-of-coconut-water/assets/9.jpeg?1760885283" alt="7 Health Benefits Of Coconut Water On Empty Stomach"&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt; &lt;/amp-story-grid-layer&gt; &lt;amp-story-grid-layer template="vertical" id="lzkte" class="scrim"&gt;&lt;div class="letterbox"&gt; &lt;h2 class="sfjcw pa sfjcw-a"&gt;&lt;span&gt;3. Digestion: Coconut water has antimicrobial properties that help maintain gut health and prevent digestive issues like bloating and constipation&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;    &lt;p class="zdsri pa zdsri-a"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Image credit: Unsplash&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/amp-story-grid-layer&gt; &lt;amp-story-animation layout="nodisplay" trigger="visibility"&gt;  &lt;/amp-story-animation&gt; &lt;/amp-story-page&gt; &lt;amp-story-page id="eqxfjccwnl" class="eqxfjccwnl ms-st-pg"&gt; &lt;amp-story-grid-layer template="fill" class="pbzqgaip"&gt; &lt;amp-img layout="responsive" class="pbzqgai" id="eqxfjccwnl-bg" src="https://c.ndtvimg.com/gws/ms/7-health-benefits-of-coconut-water/assets/10.jpeg?1760885283" alt="7 Health Benefits Of Coconut Water On Empty Stomach"&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt; &lt;/amp-story-grid-layer&gt; &lt;amp-story-grid-layer template="vertical" id="xttcw" class="scrim"&gt;&lt;div class="letterbox"&gt; &lt;h2 class="bxxrc pa bxxrc-a"&gt;&lt;span&gt;4. Blood Pressure: Regular consumption of coconut water may help lower blood pressure due to its potassium content, which counteracts the effects of sodium&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;    &lt;p class="gzfal pa gzfal-a"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Image credit: Unsplash&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/amp-story-grid-layer&gt; &lt;amp-story-animation layout="nodisplay" trigger="visibility"&gt;  &lt;/amp-story-animation&gt; &lt;/amp-story-page&gt; &lt;amp-story-page id="zizouythcr" class="zizouythcr ms-st-pg"&gt; &lt;amp-story-grid-layer template="fill" class="pbqdorcp"&gt; &lt;amp-img layout="responsive" class="pbqdorc" id="zizouythcr-bg" src="https://c.ndtvimg.com/gws/ms/7-health-benefits-of-coconut-water/assets/11.jpeg?1760885283" alt="7 Health Benefits Of Coconut Water On Empty Stomach"&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt; &lt;/amp-story-grid-layer&gt; &lt;amp-story-grid-layer template="vertical" id="ikeqr" class="scrim"&gt;&lt;div class="letterbox"&gt; &lt;h2 class="ceqlb pa ceqlb-a"&gt;&lt;span&gt;5. Weight Loss: It is low in calories and high in fibre, making it a great addition to a weight loss diet. It also helps reduce bloating and improve metabolism&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;    &lt;p class="jwrqw pa jwrqw-a"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Image credit: Unsplash&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/amp-story-grid-layer&gt; &lt;amp-story-animation layout="nodisplay" trigger="visibility"&gt;  &lt;/amp-story-animation&gt; &lt;/amp-story-page&gt; &lt;amp-story-page id="spobjjvcyh" class="spobjjvcyh ms-st-pg"&gt; &lt;amp-story-grid-layer template="fill" class="pbfcqubp"&gt; &lt;amp-img layout="responsive" class="pbfcqub" id="spobjjvcyh-bg" src="https://c.ndtvimg.com/gws/ms/7-health-benefits-of-coconut-water/assets/12.jpeg?1760885283" alt="7 Health Benefits Of Coconut Water On Empty Stomach"&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt; &lt;/amp-story-grid-layer&gt; &lt;amp-story-grid-layer template="vertical" id="kalms" class="scrim"&gt;&lt;div class="letterbox"&gt; &lt;h2 class="bzlmx pa bzlmx-a"&gt;&lt;span&gt;6. Alkalises Body: Coconut water has an alkalising effect on the body, helping to balance pH levels and reduce acidity&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;    &lt;p class="brcbi pa brcbi-a"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Image credit: Unsplash&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/amp-story-grid-layer&gt; &lt;amp-story-animation layout="nodisplay" trigger="visibility"&gt;  &lt;/amp-story-animation&gt; &lt;/amp-story-page&gt; &lt;amp-story-page id="lriliupltt" class="lriliupltt ms-st-pg"&gt; &lt;amp-story-grid-layer template="fill" class="pbjociqp"&gt; &lt;amp-img layout="responsive" class="pbjociq" id="lriliupltt-bg" src="https://c.ndtvimg.com/gws/ms/7-health-benefits-of-coconut-water/assets/13.jpeg?1760885283" alt="7 Health Benefits Of Coconut Water On Empty Stomach"&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt; &lt;/amp-story-grid-layer&gt; &lt;amp-story-grid-layer template="vertical" id="xfdcs" class="scrim"&gt;&lt;div class="letterbox"&gt; &lt;h2 class="zrnjb pa zrnjb-a"&gt;&lt;span&gt;7. Kidney Health: Coconut water may help dissolve kidney stones and prevent urinary tract infections due to its high water content and electrolytes&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;   &lt;p class="nsukg pa nsukg-a"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Image credit: Unsplash&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/amp-story-grid-layer&gt; &lt;amp-story-animation layout="nodisplay" trigger="visibility"&gt;  &lt;/amp-story-animation&gt; &lt;/amp-story-page&gt; &lt;amp-story-page id="enqronzeyq" class="enqronzeyq ms-st-pg"&gt; &lt;amp-story-grid-layer template="fill" class="pbtzqbnp"&gt; &lt;amp-img layout="responsive" class="pbtzqbn" id="enqronzeyq-bg" src="https://c.ndtvimg.com/gws/ms/7-health-benefits-of-coconut-water/assets/14.jpeg?1760885283" alt="7 Health Benefits Of Coconut Water On Empty Stomach"&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt; &lt;/amp-story-grid-layer&gt; &lt;amp-story-grid-layer template="vertical" id="erled" class="scrim"&gt;&lt;div class="letterbox"&gt; &lt;h2 class="emqoo pa emqoo-a"&gt;NOTE: Always consult a doctor before starting to take it for a particular condition &lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;    &lt;p class="azgmb pa azgmb-a"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Image credit: Unsplash&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/amp-story-grid-layer&gt; &lt;amp-story-animation layout="nodisplay" trigger="visibility"&gt;  &lt;/amp-story-animation&gt; &lt;/amp-story-page&gt; &lt;amp-story-page id="odxaxrasym" class="odxaxrasym ms-st-pg"&gt; &lt;amp-story-grid-layer template="fill" class="pbxfpoip"&gt; &lt;amp-img layout="responsive" class="pbxfpoi" id="odxaxrasym-bg" src="https://c.ndtvimg.com/gws/ms/7-health-benefits-of-coconut-water/assets/15.jpeg?1760885283" alt="7 Health Benefits Of Coconut Water On Empty Stomach"&gt;&lt;/amp-img&gt; &lt;/amp-story-grid-layer&gt; &lt;amp-story-grid-layer template="vertical" id="rrxwz" class="scrim"&gt;&lt;div class="letterbox"&gt;  &lt;h1 class="bnpog pa bnpog-a"&gt;Check More Stories&lt;br&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h1&gt; &lt;p class="gppuf pa gppuf-a"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Image: Reuters&lt;/span&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p class="ajfzf pa ajfzf-a"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Image: Unsplash&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/amp-story-grid-layer&gt; &lt;amp-story-animation layout="nodisplay" trigger="visibility"&gt;  &lt;/amp-story-animation&gt;&lt;amp-story-page-outlink layout="nodisplay" theme="dark"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.ndtv.com/" class="cta-a"&gt;&lt;span&gt;ndtv.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/amp-story-page-outlink&gt; &lt;/amp-story-page&gt; &lt;amp-story-auto-ads&gt;&lt;/amp-story-auto-ads&gt;&lt;amp-analytics type="chartbeat"&gt; &lt;/amp-analytics&gt;&lt;amp-analytics type="taboola" id="taboola"&gt;&lt;/amp-analytics&gt;&lt;amp-analytics type="comscore"&gt; &lt;/amp-analytics&gt;&lt;amp-analytics type="gtag" data-credentials="include"&gt;&lt;/amp-analytics&gt;&lt;amp-analytics type="gtag" data-credentials="include"&gt;&lt;/amp-analytics&gt;&lt;amp-story-bookend layout="nodisplay"&gt;&lt;/amp-story-bookend&gt; &lt;/amp-story&gt; &lt;/body&gt; </description><author>NDTV</author><pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 16:56:40 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMingFBVV95cUxQbWFaZ0c5WXEzYlo0ZGpIeHQ3dnlPTTFvQXZwd0xhajljcUxveUpyc1VJcm04UDQxSHg4MkJLZ2JTbS14ZFNiQi1ZNWhsYVpiR1QzSmhfWWFFTUczQlRJazEzek1FWElma3lQT3NhNnlaVEI0U25HR210TnE2NTc2QkNiVlpINFhIaGxhb2VsWVcyelZXaUJoN204cE5qZ9IBngFBVV95cUxQbWFaZ0c5WXEzYlo0ZGpIeHQ3dnlPTTFvQXZwd0xhajljcUxveUpyc1VJcm04UDQxSHg4MkJLZ2JTbS14ZFNiQi1ZNWhsYVpiR1QzSmhfWWFFTUczQlRJazEzek1FWElma3lQT3NhNnlaVEI0U25HR210TnE2NTc2QkNiVlpINFhIaGxhb2VsWVcyelZXaUJoN204cE5qZw</guid></item><item><title>接种新冠疫苗的癌症患者寿命更长-《科学日报》</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/10/251019120503.htm</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p id="first" class="lead"&gt;People with advanced lung or skin cancer who received a COVID-19 mRNA vaccine within 100 days of beginning immunotherapy lived considerably longer than those who did not, according to new research.&lt;/p&gt;

						&lt;div id="text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Scientists from the University of Florida and the University of Texas MD Anderson Cancer Center describe this as a milestone in more than a decade of work developing mRNA-based treatments that activate the body's immune defenses against cancer. Building on an earlier UF study, the results represent an important step toward creating a universal cancer vaccine capable of enhancing the effects of immunotherapy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The analysis, which examined medical records from over 1,000 MD Anderson patients, is still preliminary. However, if upcoming randomized clinical trials confirm these results, the impact on cancer care could be profound.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"The implications are extraordinary -- this could revolutionize the entire field of oncologic care," said senior researcher Elias Sayour, M.D., Ph.D., a UF Health pediatric oncologist and the Stop Children's Cancer/Bonnie R. Freeman Professor for Pediatric Oncology Research. "We could design an even better nonspecific vaccine to mobilize and reset the immune response, in a way that could essentially be a universal, off-the-shelf cancer vaccine for all cancer patients."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jeff Coller, Ph.D., a leading mRNA expert at Johns Hopkins University, noted that the findings highlight yet another way Operation Warp Speed (the U.S. government's rapid COVID-19 vaccine initiative) continues to benefit lives in "unique and unexpected ways."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"The results from this study demonstrate how powerful mRNA medicines truly are and that they are revolutionizing our treatment of cancer," Coller said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Presented today (October 19) at the 2025 European Society for Medical Oncology Congress in Berlin, the study builds on eight years of Sayour's research combining lipid nanoparticles with mRNA. Messenger RNA, or mRNA, is present in every cell and carries the instructions for making proteins.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="insertion_middle"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In July, Sayour's laboratory made an unexpected discovery: to trigger a strong immune attack on cancer, it was not necessary to target a specific tumor protein. Instead, they could simply stimulate the immune system to respond as if it were fighting a viral infection.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By pairing their experimental "nonspecific" mRNA vaccine with immune checkpoint inhibitors -- common cancer drugs that help the immune system recognize and destroy tumors -- the researchers observed a powerful antitumor response in mice. This experimental vaccine was not specific to COVID or any other virus or cancer but used similar technology to COVID-19 vaccines.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That breakthrough inspired former UF researcher and current MD Anderson scientist Adam Grippin, M.D., Ph.D., to ask a key question: Could the COVID-19 mRNA vaccine have a similar immune-boosting effect in cancer patients?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To explore that idea, the team analyzed data from patients with Stage 3 and 4 non-small cell lung cancer and metastatic melanoma treated at MD Anderson between 2019 and 2023.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Their findings showed that patients who received a COVID mRNA vaccine within 100 days of starting immunotherapy survived significantly longer than those who did not.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;According to Sayour, the most striking improvements occurred in patients who, based on tumor biology and other factors, were not expected to respond strongly to immunotherapy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="insertion_bottom"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Although these results are from an observational study and require confirmation through a randomized clinical trial, researchers emphasize their potential importance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Despite the need for further validation, Sayour described the discovery as pivotal for the future of cancer treatment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Although not yet proven to be causal, this is the type of treatment benefit that we strive for and hope to see with therapeutic interventions -- but rarely do," said Duane Mitchell, M.D., Ph.D., Grippin's doctoral mentor and director of the UF Clinical and Translational Science Institute. "I think the urgency and importance of doing the confirmatory work can't be overstated."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In lung and skin cancers, doctors commonly engage the immune system with drugs designed to "release the brakes" and recognize and attack cancer cells more effectively. In advanced disease stages, however, most patients don't respond well and often have exhausted other treatment options like radiation, surgery and chemotherapy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The new study involved records of 180 advanced lung cancer patients who received a COVID vaccine within a 100-day period before or after starting immunotherapy drugs and 704 treated with the same drugs who did not receive the vaccine. Getting the vaccine was associated with a near doubling of median survival, from 20.6 months to 37.3 months.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Of the metastatic melanoma patients, 43 received a vaccine within 100 days of initiating immunotherapy, while 167 patients did not receive a vaccine. With the vaccine, median survival increased from 26.7 months to a range of 30 to 40 months; at the time the data were collected, some patients were still alive, meaning the vaccine effect could be even stronger.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Receiving non-mRNA pneumonia or flu vaccines resulted in no changes in longevity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To back their findings, UF researchers then used mouse models to pair immunotherapy drugs with an mRNA vaccine targeted specifically at COVID spike protein. Those experiments showed they could turn unresponsive cancers into responsive ones, thwarting tumor growth.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"One of the mechanisms for how this works is when you give an mRNA vaccine, that acts as a flare that starts moving all of these immune cells from bad areas like the tumor to good areas like the lymph nodes," Sayour said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The next step is to launch a large clinical trial through the UF-led OneFlorida+ Clinical Research Network, a consortium of hospitals, health centers and clinics in Florida, Alabama, Georgia, Arkansas, California and Minnesota.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"One of our key motivations at OneFlorida is to move discoveries from academic settings out into the real world and the places where patients get care," said Betsy Shenkman, Ph.D., who leads the consortium.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If confirmed, the new findings unlock numerous possibilities, and the researchers said an even better nonspecific universal vaccine could be designed. For patients with advanced cancers, the increased survival from such a universal vaccine could provide a priceless benefit: more time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"If this can double what we're achieving currently, or even incrementally -- 5%, 10% -- that means a lot to those patients, especially if this can be leveraged across different cancers for different patients," said Sayour, an investigator with UF's McKnight Brain Institute.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The study was funded by the National Cancer Institute and multiple foundations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sayour, Grippin and Mitchell hold patents related to UF-developed mRNA vaccines that are licensed by iOncologi Inc., a biotech company born as a "spinout" from UF in which Mitchell holds interest.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

					&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Science Daily</author><pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 16:45:56 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMib0FVX3lxTE9OLUM5NzU5Qmt1WXlRRGpfRTJpWXpRSk9yWGtBbFZkNXVTaHNiQ2pYY2NFVldpdmVURWhaaS0wUXdkNHJqZlFKcFk0dXF1NHZMQmdiakhlN3J2TXRWdjVrN0VfWWt3VmRIMGxZVk00WQ</guid></item><item><title>肝癌现在也会影响健康：这是医生说人们应该注意的-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/liver-cancer-now-strikes-the-healthy-too-heres-what-doctors-say-people-should-watch-for/articleshow/124688171.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Do you sometimes feel constantly tired, no matter how much rest you get? Or experience a lingering, mild pain on the upper right side of your abdomen? You may even notice a faint yellow tinge in your skin or eyes - signs we often brush off as stress or just a hectic lifestyle.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="2"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The liver’s role is vital, quietly performing its essential metabolic and detoxification functions and supporting overall health. Yet liver cancer remains a serious concern, often slipping under the radar until its late stages. In 2022, over 759,000 lives were lost to liver cancer worldwide. It is now ranked as the third leading cause of cancer related deaths globally, and as overall cancer fatalities are projected to cross 10 million by 2025 making early awareness and intervention crucial.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="5"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Not Just a Drinker’s Disease&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="7"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="8"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;For decades, liver cancer was closely linked to heavy alcohol consumption and hepatitis infections. However, recent trends show a worrying rise in cases among non-drinkers. The culprit is often MASLD (Metabolic Dysfunction Associated Steatotic Liver Disease) and its severe form, MASH (Metabolic Dysfunction Associated Steatohepatitis). In these conditions, excess fat accumulates in the liver, causing long-term inflammation and scarring that can eventually lead to cancer even without the traditional causes like alcohol or viral hepatitis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="11"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lifestyle factors such as obesity, type 2 diabetes, high cholesterol, sedentary habits and poor dietary choices play a significant role, making even young adults susceptible. The challenge is that early symptoms are vague or non-existent, so many people remain unaware of their risk until the disease is advanced.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="13"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;The Importance of Early Detection&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="15"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="16"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Early detection saves lives. I recommend routine liver screenings, especially for individuals with diabetes or a family history of liver disease. Liver function tests and abdominal ultrasounds can detect early changes in the liver before cancer develops or worsens. Unfortunately, many avoid check-ups until symptoms become severe, missing a critical therapeutic window.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="20"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Exploring Modern Treatment Options&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="22"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="23"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Liver cancer treatment varies widely based on the stage of the disease and patient’s overall health. Surgery, including liver resection or transplantation, offers the best chance for a cure but isn’t always feasible, especially in late-stage cancer. Other options include ablation therapies, systemic treatments like chemotherapy or targeted drugs, and radiation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="27"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;One increasingly important treatment is Transarterial Chemoembolization, or TACE. This minimally invasive technique delivers chemotherapy directly to the tumor while cutting off its blood supply, limiting tumor growth. It’s generally palliative but can significantly improve symptoms and quality of life when surgery is not an option. Globally, TACE has become a standard of care for many patients, slowing disease progression and reducing complications.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="31"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Not long ago, a 21-year-old gym enthusiast came to us with severe abdominal pain and exhaustion. Despite regular exercise and a clean diet, he was diagnosed with primary liver cancer. The tumor was too large and located unfavourable for surgery, so TACE was chosen. This helped control the tumor and alleviate symptoms, enabling him to maintain a good quality of life while continuing treatment. This case reflects growing global trends - liver cancer no longer follows old patterns, necessitating vigilance across all age groups.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="35"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Lifestyle and Prevention&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="37"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="38"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;While liver cancer presents a serious challenge, many risks can be minimized through lifestyle modifications. A balanced diet rich in fruits, vegetables, and whole grains supports liver health, as does staying well-hydrated and engaging in regular physical activity - aiming for at least 150 minutes per week through walking, cycling, swimming, or any similar activities. Avoiding alcohol consumption, smoking, and environmental toxins also lowers risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="42"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Vaccination against hepatitis B is critical in many regions, and maintaining safe practices to prevent hepatitis C infection rounds out preventive care. Regular health check-ups enable early problem detection and timely intervention, which can be lifesaving.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="44"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;This Liver Cancer Awareness Month, the message is clear: liver cancer is a silent threat that can affect anyone. Increased awareness, proactive lifestyle choices, and timely medical screening can help detect problems early and improve outcomes, offering hope against a rising global health challenge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="46"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;(Dr Rajesh V. Helavar, Consultant - Interventional and Diagnostic Radiology, Manipal Hospitals, Yeshwanthpur)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 16:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilgJBVV95cUxPc2dpdHpvSmx4X2twTDNBUXlNVUF3aV9VaFVzQndHM3RUekEzREFLdzRyUThpRzQyY2xnRVNqQXQ4UUM2b0xXbWVXbGlHX050SWVqLVVpZGNKLUdGeWZ2RFZZT0RyMVIzVlVzN2VIY0FQMWMyU1l2UXc2XzRVZE0tWDZFeE1ORVJmYkk4cWVHQ004bVV5RFNpMndnY1Y1RFhLeGVQU0lOZlVtRm81ajIyX2xJN2FzN0RWOEstQ1l4N1VTYTc3c18zOHhMcVRkVldwY2Y1d0tnMGJRVGM1N1RVRE9ac3VXUk9QRFBEOVZGeXROeDBhZEJtSUx6RGNHZzlUS0NGNlV0OGUzMWxiUEU2YXoxenJQUdIBmwJBVV95cUxNSEFuWmFjbzhNdDBJczNrdHc3bUFuUmVxUk1TTlRrY29tTDlLSFQzaTVtYXVHdnJaYTBXRk0wbU10ZExScURBOTlPeTd6ZVdMT3Nkc29hRVM1T2xadFVOdUV3RWZsU08yYWk3eVBFMlllWURFYUZJZ2R4ZHhxTmVjNDhCcWFtLUY5S3ZtYko2dXVoN2FGV3Ryc2RENy1BU3BUTkVfaWNEbGpja0N0YVhRQTN5cTJwb295WWdwekl6Y0FPcS1qNDhwNXBBc0tzelI5aGZUZjdxMnp5dnE4RUNCcFltR2swUnFNcV9fclYtZHRYM2JRUFZWME9xeXhsNTVLZTdfOHRFQWN0SmRyLTRrYmZ2a2lJc3FKTEpz</guid></item><item><title>危险或挽救生命？为什么阻止疾病的药物计划受到抨击。-《华盛顿邮报》</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/health/interactive/2025/needle-exchanges-disappearing-harm-reduction/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="story relative"&gt;&lt;div class="PJLV"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="noscript-warning"&gt;Warning: This graphic requires JavaScript. Please enable JavaScript for the best experience.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="Text" data-file="custom-template-components/src/Text/Text.js" data-style="stitches" id="EZTCDA4YTNAD7PKLNY2H4QTVGQ" data-contentid="EZTCDA4YTNAD7PKLNY2H4QTVGQ" class="wpds-c-foYyTm wpds-c-foYyTm-idAgRsb-css"&gt;EVANSVILLE, Ind. — Lavender Timmons popped the trunk of her weather-beaten 2007 Ford Focus parked near the city’s homeless shelter. Regulars gathered around, including one drug user who in the past bought sterile syringes from the illicit market.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-component="Text" data-file="custom-template-components/src/Text/Text.js" data-style="stitches" id="D2O6BG3I25CEPBFC3SZRDJ7N2I" data-contentid="D2O6BG3I25CEPBFC3SZRDJ7N2I" class="wpds-c-foYyTm wpds-c-foYyTm-idAgRsb-css"&gt;Timmons, executive director of Evansville Recovery Alliance, wanted to offer them new needles to keep them from contracting HIV, hepatitis C or other infections. But a police car idled a couple blocks away.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-component="Text" data-file="custom-template-components/src/Text/Text.js" data-style="stitches" id="NEWFA6PMZNDYZFUYXWYKHT5IBE" data-contentid="NEWFA6PMZNDYZFUYXWYKHT5IBE" class="wpds-c-foYyTm wpds-c-foYyTm-idAgRsb-css"&gt;“The cops are watching us,” Timmons said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="Ad" data-file="custom-template-components/src/Ad/Ad.js" data-style="stitches" class="wpds-c-PJLV"&gt;&lt;div class="PJLV PJLV-icAbLfl-css"&gt;&lt;div aria-hidden="true" class="hide-for-print relative flex justify-center content-box items-center b bh mb-lg mt-lg pt-md pb-md"&gt;&lt;div class="center absolute w-100 border-box"&gt;&lt;p class="dib flex divider gray-dark pl-xs pr-xs font-sans-serif light font-xxxxs lh-md"&gt;Story continues below advertisement&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="Text" data-file="custom-template-components/src/Text/Text.js" data-style="stitches" id="ZYALB24JJNGEBDTVCT5JFWKUQE" data-contentid="ZYALB24JJNGEBDTVCT5JFWKUQE" class="wpds-c-foYyTm wpds-c-foYyTm-idAgRsb-css"&gt;A decade after users injecting prescription painkillers sparked a historic HIV outbreak in a southern Indiana county, programs providing sterile needles that contained the crisis are fading. They may disappear completely next year — and nationwide, they are also in peril. The Trump administration has &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/health/2025/08/06/opioid-crisis-harm-reduction-funding/?itid=lk_inline_enhanced-template" target="_blank"&gt;declared that no federal funding&lt;/a&gt; can go toward supplies that “promote or facilitate drug use” — even though decades of &lt;a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/books/NBK598959/?itid=lk_inline_enhanced-template"&gt;research&lt;/a&gt; has shown that syringe programs reduce disease transmission rates and do not appear to increase injection frequency or neighborhood crime rates.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="Image" data-file="components/Image/Image.js" data-style="stitches" class="wpds-c-bTCZLY wpds-c-bTCZLY-idZwvW-type-default"&gt;&lt;figure id="image-3NOMDAU2FVGIMINWR3M5NNPXQI" class="wpds-c-PJLV wpds-c-PJLV-XgEPk-type-large"&gt;&lt;img alt="" loading="lazy" decoding="async" data-nimg="1" srcset="https://img.washingtonpost.com/wp-apps/imrs.php?src=https://arc-anglerfish-washpost-prod-washpost.s3.amazonaws.com/public/3NOMDAU2FVGIMINWR3M5NNPXQI_size-normalized.JPG&amp;amp;high_res=true&amp;amp;w=2048 1x" src="https://img.washingtonpost.com/wp-apps/imrs.php?src=https://arc-anglerfish-washpost-prod-washpost.s3.amazonaws.com/public/3NOMDAU2FVGIMINWR3M5NNPXQI_size-normalized.JPG&amp;amp;high_res=true&amp;amp;w=2048"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="wpds-c-kaVXjn wpds-c-kaVXjn-fTrHqK-type-large"&gt;Timmons delivers pizza and other supplies to people in the city's impoverished Boxtown neighborhood.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="Text" data-file="custom-template-components/src/Text/Text.js" data-style="stitches" id="7TRKWKEJN5B63LE23G34QAEFPI" data-contentid="7TRKWKEJN5B63LE23G34QAEFPI" class="wpds-c-foYyTm wpds-c-foYyTm-idAgRsb-css"&gt;Evansville has never authorized needle exchanges. Advocates, such as Timmons, who have lobbied for needle exchanges are losing hope — even as fentanyl and methamphetamine users continue to inject with used needles. Under state law, a county health officer must first declare an HIV or hepatitis C emergency — and there is not enough testing to quantify the need, Timmons said, despite some support from local officials.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-component="Text" data-file="custom-template-components/src/Text/Text.js" data-style="stitches" id="AB3HHWRQR5CWHHFDUCP7LL4Q3M" data-contentid="AB3HHWRQR5CWHHFDUCP7LL4Q3M" class="wpds-c-foYyTm wpds-c-foYyTm-idAgRsb-css"&gt;In Indiana, possessing a syringe without a prescription constitutes a low-level felony. On the recent weekday outside the homeless shelter, Timmons, 42, left donated packs of new syringes in her trunk. She handed out opioid overdose reversal medication, hygiene kits, fentanyl testing kits and snacks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-component="Text" data-file="custom-template-components/src/Text/Text.js" data-style="stitches" id="TQRWGCE3JZF6TC6NA5SWYOUNJI" data-contentid="TQRWGCE3JZF6TC6NA5SWYOUNJI" class="wpds-c-foYyTm wpds-c-foYyTm-idAgRsb-css"&gt;“I don’t want to give them anything that’s going to get them in trouble,” she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 data-component="Heading" data-contentid="HGTWVOMVFBCVRNENRAC2UMNHRI" data-file="custom-template-components/src/Heading/Heading.js" data-style="stitches" id="HGTWVOMVFBCVRNENRAC2UMNHRI" class="wpds-c-iFKWRt wpds-c-iFKWRt-jirhpe-level-2 wpds-c-iFKWRt-iiCGobN-css"&gt;A historic outbreak&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;div data-component="Image" data-file="components/Image/Image.js" data-style="stitches" class="wpds-c-bTCZLY wpds-c-bTCZLY-idZwvW-type-default"&gt;&lt;figure id="image-K3JBL3BXAJA33DUZLUMCPQ56BY" class="wpds-c-PJLV wpds-c-PJLV-XgEPk-type-large"&gt;&lt;img alt="" loading="lazy" decoding="async" data-nimg="1" srcset="https://img.washingtonpost.com/wp-apps/imrs.php?src=https://arc-anglerfish-washpost-prod-washpost.s3.amazonaws.com/public/K3JBL3BXAJA33DUZLUMCPQ56BY.JPG&amp;amp;high_res=true&amp;amp;w=2048 1x" src="https://img.washingtonpost.com/wp-apps/imrs.php?src=https://arc-anglerfish-washpost-prod-washpost.s3.amazonaws.com/public/K3JBL3BXAJA33DUZLUMCPQ56BY.JPG&amp;amp;high_res=true&amp;amp;w=2048"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="wpds-c-kaVXjn wpds-c-kaVXjn-fTrHqK-type-large"&gt;Becky Wells, a peer support specialist for the Holding Space Recovery Project, visits a relative's home in Austin, Indiana, on Aug. 21. Wells used to inject drugs but stayed disease-free because of a syringe service program in Scott County a decade ago that has since closed.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="Text" data-file="custom-template-components/src/Text/Text.js" data-style="stitches" id="JJULTQEO4VECPMIFIXUQLYRILA" data-contentid="JJULTQEO4VECPMIFIXUQLYRILA" class="wpds-c-foYyTm wpds-c-foYyTm-idAgRsb-css"&gt;Underground syringe service programs emerged in the United States during the HIV/AIDS epidemic of the 1980s as experts realized that shared needles helped transmit the disease. Cities and states soon began legalizing programs. As the opioid crisis surged in subsequent decades — driven first by painkillers, then illicit fentanyl — the absence of syringe programs &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/news/to-your-health/wp/2016/11/29/white-rural-drug-users-lack-needle-exchange-programs-to-prevent-hiv-infections/?itid=lk_inline_enhanced-template"&gt;proved catastrophic&lt;/a&gt;, particularly in rural White communities.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-component="Text" data-file="custom-template-components/src/Text/Text.js" data-style="stitches" id="J2AULXYWTBGXTO57IIUDGHA7AA" data-contentid="J2AULXYWTBGXTO57IIUDGHA7AA" class="wpds-c-foYyTm wpds-c-foYyTm-idAgRsb-css"&gt;In rural Scott County, Indiana, less than an hour’s drive to Louisville, the HIV outbreak infected 235 people in 2015. Media flocked to the county, as did federal health officials who tracked the spread and helped testing and outreach.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-component="Text" data-file="custom-template-components/src/Text/Text.js" data-style="stitches" id="SXFMFTWETJGADMT4RBATUF6AO4" data-contentid="SXFMFTWETJGADMT4RBATUF6AO4" class="wpds-c-foYyTm wpds-c-foYyTm-idAgRsb-css"&gt;Critics at the time ripped the governor, Mike Pence (R), for waiting two months to declare a state of emergency. Researchers later concluded the outbreak could have been prevented had officials acted faster.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="Image" data-file="components/Image/Image.js" data-style="stitches" class="wpds-c-bTCZLY wpds-c-bTCZLY-idZwvW-type-default"&gt;&lt;figure id="image-MRFDL5LMAZDG5LERHVW4ODIDJA" class="wpds-c-PJLV wpds-c-PJLV-XgEPk-type-large"&gt;&lt;img alt="" loading="lazy" decoding="async" data-nimg="1" srcset="https://img.washingtonpost.com/wp-apps/imrs.php?src=https://arc-anglerfish-washpost-prod-washpost.s3.amazonaws.com/public/MRFDL5LMAZDG5LERHVW4ODIDJA_size-normalized.JPG&amp;amp;high_res=true&amp;amp;w=2048 1x" src="https://img.washingtonpost.com/wp-apps/imrs.php?src=https://arc-anglerfish-washpost-prod-washpost.s3.amazonaws.com/public/MRFDL5LMAZDG5LERHVW4ODIDJA_size-normalized.JPG&amp;amp;high_res=true&amp;amp;w=2048"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="wpds-c-kaVXjn wpds-c-kaVXjn-fTrHqK-type-large"&gt;People ride motorcycles in Austin, Indiana, during an Aug. 23 fundraiser for Holding Space Recovery Project, a program that helps drug users stay healthy and connects them with treatment.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="Text" data-file="custom-template-components/src/Text/Text.js" data-style="stitches" id="JHZL2I25MRAU5ADZSLLSSK6QDU" data-contentid="JHZL2I25MRAU5ADZSLLSSK6QDU" class="wpds-c-foYyTm wpds-c-foYyTm-idAgRsb-css"&gt;Pence opposed the creation of syringe service programs in Indiana, although he eventually established an emergency one in Scott County; lawmakers later authorized them under certain conditions, including that an outbreak needed to be certified first&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;by a local health official.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-component="Text" data-file="custom-template-components/src/Text/Text.js" data-style="stitches" id="NOVU7SYUSZAAZPTVY3HYNOLRQM" data-contentid="NOVU7SYUSZAAZPTVY3HYNOLRQM" class="wpds-c-foYyTm wpds-c-foYyTm-idAgRsb-css"&gt;“I was lucky enough not to catch HIV” because of the program, said Becky Wells, 34, before a group gathered for a motorcycle fundraiser in Austin, Indiana. She started injecting drugs during the HIV outbreak after her father died.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="Ad" data-file="custom-template-components/src/Ad/Ad.js" data-style="stitches" class="wpds-c-PJLV"&gt;&lt;div class="PJLV PJLV-icAbLfl-css"&gt;&lt;div aria-hidden="true" class="hide-for-print relative flex justify-center content-box items-center b bh mb-lg mt-lg pt-md pb-md"&gt;&lt;div class="center absolute w-100 border-box"&gt;&lt;p class="dib flex divider gray-dark pl-xs pr-xs font-sans-serif light font-xxxxs lh-md"&gt;Story continues below advertisement&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="Text" data-file="custom-template-components/src/Text/Text.js" data-style="stitches" id="5YHALI7P2NFFHGJUXXTPGRYLRA" data-contentid="5YHALI7P2NFFHGJUXXTPGRYLRA" class="wpds-c-foYyTm wpds-c-foYyTm-idAgRsb-css"&gt;A program staffer who had delivered new needles to Wells’s home drove her to rehab in 2020. Wells, a mother of three, remains sober and&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;now works at Holding Space Recovery Project, a harm reduction nonprofit that deploys teams to connect users with recovery coaches as well as HIV and hepatitis C testing and supplies. In Austin, hundreds of people — all touched by the opioid and HIV crisis — gathered under a fierce August sun to raise money for the group, founded by former syringe program employees Kelly Hans and Lisa Webster.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-component="Text" data-file="custom-template-components/src/Text/Text.js" data-style="stitches" id="7FFP2BM3OBESXDPNKO2SXOR3WY" data-contentid="7FFP2BM3OBESXDPNKO2SXOR3WY" class="wpds-c-foYyTm wpds-c-foYyTm-idAgRsb-css"&gt;They celebrated the many victories: Open drug use on the streets has disappeared, and many former users are thriving in recovery.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div id="71f35b87-012c-4567-bac1-6b1581caec60" class="wpds-c-dVLvml wpds-c-dVLvml-eOmIMU-type-imageGrid image-package-71f35b87-012c-4567-bac1-6b1581caec60"&gt;&lt;figure class="wpds-c-PJLV wpds-c-PJLV-iPJLV-css image-1"&gt;&lt;img alt="" loading="lazy" decoding="async" data-nimg="1" srcset="https://img.washingtonpost.com/wp-apps/imrs.php?src=https://arc-anglerfish-washpost-prod-washpost.s3.amazonaws.com/public/BXGNHJ7SH5Q2GUMZ73QAQSNEPE_size-normalized.JPG&amp;amp;high_res=true&amp;amp;w=2048 1x" src="https://img.washingtonpost.com/wp-apps/imrs.php?src=https://arc-anglerfish-washpost-prod-washpost.s3.amazonaws.com/public/BXGNHJ7SH5Q2GUMZ73QAQSNEPE_size-normalized.JPG&amp;amp;high_res=true&amp;amp;w=2048"&gt;&lt;figcaption type="imageGrid" class="wpds-c-iAKjhe"&gt;Sarah Davis rides with her sister, Nikki Spicer, during the fundraising event for Holding Space Recovery Project. &lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figure class="wpds-c-PJLV wpds-c-PJLV-iPJLV-css image-2"&gt;&lt;img alt="" loading="lazy" decoding="async" data-nimg="1" srcset="https://img.washingtonpost.com/wp-apps/imrs.php?src=https://arc-anglerfish-washpost-prod-washpost.s3.amazonaws.com/public/BSXETZ4UM2C2LAY5NZTLLMNCZU_size-normalized.JPG&amp;amp;high_res=true&amp;amp;w=2048 1x" src="https://img.washingtonpost.com/wp-apps/imrs.php?src=https://arc-anglerfish-washpost-prod-washpost.s3.amazonaws.com/public/BSXETZ4UM2C2LAY5NZTLLMNCZU_size-normalized.JPG&amp;amp;high_res=true&amp;amp;w=2048"&gt;&lt;figcaption type="imageGrid" class="wpds-c-iAKjhe"&gt;Wells, center, joins hands with other riders to pray over her boyfriend’s motorcycle after the fundraising ride. &lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV wpds-c-PJLV-ilcLoLw-css image-3"&gt;&lt;figcaption type="imageGrid" class="wpds-c-iAKjhe"&gt;Scott County residents participate in a fundraiser for Holding Space Recovery Project in Austin, Indiana, on Aug. 23. (David Ovalle/The Washington Post) (David Ovalle/TWP)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="Text" data-file="custom-template-components/src/Text/Text.js" data-style="stitches" id="EDFIWBIGQFAE7CWEDS4PRS3BAU" data-contentid="EDFIWBIGQFAE7CWEDS4PRS3BAU" class="wpds-c-foYyTm wpds-c-foYyTm-idAgRsb-css"&gt;But needle drug use has not disappeared — and workers can no longer distribute clean syringes. In 2021, Scott County commissioners &lt;a href="https://www.npr.org/sections/health-shots/2021/06/01/1001278712/indiana-needle-exchange-that-helped-contain-an-hiv-outbreak-may-be-forced-to-clo?itid=lk_inline_enhanced-template"&gt;closed&lt;/a&gt; the syringe program. “I know people that are alcoholics, and I don’t buy him a bottle of whiskey,” one commissioner remarked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-component="Text" data-file="custom-template-components/src/Text/Text.js" data-style="stitches" id="PNNACWX5T5DPRPLGJRZ3KWRPEM" data-contentid="PNNACWX5T5DPRPLGJRZ3KWRPEM" class="wpds-c-foYyTm wpds-c-foYyTm-idAgRsb-css"&gt;But people mired in addiction will use drugs anyway and need the additional services these programs provide, said Jerrica Hall, 35, who contracted HIV a decade ago.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-component="Text" data-file="custom-template-components/src/Text/Text.js" data-style="stitches" id="QM5I6VREFRGUFCTW3DR7PVWKBQ" data-contentid="QM5I6VREFRGUFCTW3DR7PVWKBQ" class="wpds-c-foYyTm wpds-c-foYyTm-idAgRsb-css"&gt;The Scott County syringe program helped her secure health insurance, which paid for HIV medications. Today, she is sober and married to a partner without HIV. “I never thought back then that I could find love. I have three beautiful children that are HIV negative,” said Hall, who is president of the board for Holding Space.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="Image" data-file="components/Image/Image.js" data-style="stitches" class="wpds-c-bTCZLY wpds-c-bTCZLY-idZwvW-type-default"&gt;&lt;figure id="image-ZVNILQTI3TQNTHQLB7ZDJZALQU" class="wpds-c-PJLV wpds-c-PJLV-XgEPk-type-large"&gt;&lt;img alt="" loading="lazy" decoding="async" data-nimg="1" srcset="https://img.washingtonpost.com/wp-apps/imrs.php?src=https://arc-anglerfish-washpost-prod-washpost.s3.amazonaws.com/public/ZVNILQTI3TQNTHQLB7ZDJZALQU_size-normalized.JPG&amp;amp;high_res=true&amp;amp;w=2048 1x" src="https://img.washingtonpost.com/wp-apps/imrs.php?src=https://arc-anglerfish-washpost-prod-washpost.s3.amazonaws.com/public/ZVNILQTI3TQNTHQLB7ZDJZALQU_size-normalized.JPG&amp;amp;high_res=true&amp;amp;w=2048"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="wpds-c-kaVXjn wpds-c-kaVXjn-fTrHqK-type-large"&gt;Jerrica Hall, president of the Holding Space Recovery Project board, plays with her children after church on Aug. 23.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="Text" data-file="custom-template-components/src/Text/Text.js" data-style="stitches" id="4ASUSETVPJCKPEUGKBK6L5A6X4" data-contentid="4ASUSETVPJCKPEUGKBK6L5A6X4" class="wpds-c-foYyTm wpds-c-foYyTm-idAgRsb-css"&gt;Research &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC7407057/?itid=lk_inline_enhanced-template"&gt;cited&lt;/a&gt; by former Indiana health commissioner &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/opinions/2025/10/07/surgeons-general-rfk-jr-robert-kennedy/?itid=lk_inline_enhanced-template" target="_blank"&gt;Jerome Adams&lt;/a&gt;, who served as U.S. surgeon general during President Donald Trump’s first term, noted that new syringe program users are five times as likely to enter drug treatment compared to those who did not use them. Centers for Disease Control and Prevention researchers later reported that the number of participants who reported sharing injection equipment dropped dramatically. By 2018, Scott County saw a 96 percent reduction in new HIV infections and a 76 percent drop in new hepatitis C infections.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-component="Text" data-file="custom-template-components/src/Text/Text.js" data-style="stitches" id="C4K5XXF4ZVGM5PPRUOXRTCA26M" data-contentid="C4K5XXF4ZVGM5PPRUOXRTCA26M" class="wpds-c-foYyTm wpds-c-foYyTm-idAgRsb-css"&gt;Some who escaped HIV still paid a steep price. When the program shut down, Matthew Colwell could no longer get sterile syringes and turned to dull discarded needles, sometimes injecting fentanyl every 20 minutes. Colwell, 24, beat his addiction but contracted endocarditis, heart inflammation caused by bacteria from contaminated needles.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-component="Text" data-file="custom-template-components/src/Text/Text.js" data-style="stitches" id="MWCXUIC5ONDGFK4WUBUAMAVI3A" data-contentid="MWCXUIC5ONDGFK4WUBUAMAVI3A" class="wpds-c-foYyTm wpds-c-foYyTm-idAgRsb-css"&gt;He spent nearly a month in the hospital. Today, even moderate exercise prompts his heart to race abnormally. “My heart is still messed up to this day,” Colwell said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 data-component="Heading" data-contentid="V5OY5AKW7BC7RKQWFYEES4QIPY" data-file="custom-template-components/src/Heading/Heading.js" data-style="stitches" id="V5OY5AKW7BC7RKQWFYEES4QIPY" class="wpds-c-iFKWRt wpds-c-iFKWRt-jirhpe-level-2 wpds-c-iFKWRt-iiCGobN-css"&gt;Changing approaches&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;div data-component="Image" data-file="components/Image/Image.js" data-style="stitches" class="wpds-c-bTCZLY wpds-c-bTCZLY-idZwvW-type-default"&gt;&lt;figure id="image-I7AJBXMFWLTM34MXCJ5JTSGLWY" class="wpds-c-PJLV wpds-c-PJLV-iossVB-type-medium"&gt;&lt;img alt="" loading="lazy" decoding="async" data-nimg="1" srcset="https://img.washingtonpost.com/wp-apps/imrs.php?src=https://arc-anglerfish-washpost-prod-washpost.s3.amazonaws.com/public/I7AJBXMFWLTM34MXCJ5JTSGLWY_size-normalized.JPG&amp;amp;high_res=true&amp;amp;w=2048 1x" src="https://img.washingtonpost.com/wp-apps/imrs.php?src=https://arc-anglerfish-washpost-prod-washpost.s3.amazonaws.com/public/I7AJBXMFWLTM34MXCJ5JTSGLWY_size-normalized.JPG&amp;amp;high_res=true&amp;amp;w=2048"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="wpds-c-kaVXjn wpds-c-kaVXjn-jBafdS-type-notLarge"&gt;Timmons hopes to one day use this van, donated by the Chicago Recovery Alliance, to distribute sterile syringes to keep users disease-free.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="Text" data-file="custom-template-components/src/Text/Text.js" data-style="stitches" id="FVJ4ZONYN5AK5B3COEMMR3AEOY" data-contentid="FVJ4ZONYN5AK5B3COEMMR3AEOY" class="wpds-c-foYyTm wpds-c-foYyTm-idAgRsb-css"&gt;Data on the number of syringe programs nationwide is imprecise because many are not sanctioned and do not advertise to avoid crackdowns. In the five years after Indiana started its syringe exchange, the number of known programs roughly doubled, according to the &lt;a href="https://nasen.org/?itid=lk_inline_enhanced-template"&gt;North American Syringe Exchange Network&lt;/a&gt;, a harm reduction group.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-component="Text" data-file="custom-template-components/src/Text/Text.js" data-style="stitches" id="SJCA3KIC7ZB4XBH2C6JBPHRLRI" data-contentid="SJCA3KIC7ZB4XBH2C6JBPHRLRI" class="wpds-c-foYyTm wpds-c-foYyTm-idAgRsb-css"&gt;The Biden administration supported syringe programs, although federal funding by law could not be used to purchase the needles themselves.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-component="Text" data-file="custom-template-components/src/Text/Text.js" data-style="stitches" id="GGWOWYKTLFCDPOSOUYHJB7MH5Q" data-contentid="GGWOWYKTLFCDPOSOUYHJB7MH5Q" class="wpds-c-foYyTm wpds-c-foYyTm-idAgRsb-css"&gt;HIV diagnoses increased 5 percent among people who inject drugs between 2018 and 2022, according to the CDC. But communities across the country are now pushing back against needle exchange programs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="Ad" data-file="custom-template-components/src/Ad/Ad.js" data-style="stitches" class="wpds-c-PJLV"&gt;&lt;div class="PJLV PJLV-icAbLfl-css"&gt;&lt;div aria-hidden="true" class="hide-for-print relative flex justify-center content-box items-center b bh mb-lg mt-lg pt-md pb-md"&gt;&lt;div class="center absolute w-100 border-box"&gt;&lt;p class="dib flex divider gray-dark pl-xs pr-xs font-sans-serif light font-xxxxs lh-md"&gt;Story continues below advertisement&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="Text" data-file="custom-template-components/src/Text/Text.js" data-style="stitches" id="6E4C2JAE45E7BHJIS5PX6IILPY" data-contentid="6E4C2JAE45E7BHJIS5PX6IILPY" class="wpds-c-foYyTm wpds-c-foYyTm-idAgRsb-css"&gt;Health officials in Bangor, Maine, have recorded a &lt;a href="https://www.pressherald.com/2025/07/23/how-a-cluster-of-hiv-cases-in-penobscot-county-became-one-of-maines-largest-outbreaks/?itid=lk_inline_enhanced-template#read-free"&gt;spike in HIV cases&lt;/a&gt; among injection drugs users since 2023. The city stopped a newly authorized program from distributing sterile needles at parks and &lt;a href="https://www.wabi.tv/2025/07/29/needlepoint-sanctuary-loses-office-five-days-after-opening-per-bangor-code-enforcement/?itid=lk_inline_enhanced-template"&gt;closed a new facility&lt;/a&gt; in July because it was not zoned properly. In rural Lewis County, Washington, the American Civil Liberties Union &lt;a href="https://www.aclu.org/press-releases/church-challenges-lewis-county-washington-ordinance-targeting-harm-reduction-programs?itid=lk_inline_enhanced-template"&gt;filed a federal lawsuit&lt;/a&gt; in September aimed at overturning an ordinance that barred a ministry from handing out sterile syringes and other supplies. West Virginia — a Republican state hit hard by the opioid crisis and HIV infections — has continued to &lt;a href="https://www.healthbeat.org/2025/01/03/hiv-syringe-west-virginia-exchange-fears/?utm_source=chatgpt.com&amp;amp;itid=lk_inline_enhanced-template"&gt;impose restrictions&lt;/a&gt; on syringe exchanges.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-component="Text" data-file="custom-template-components/src/Text/Text.js" data-style="stitches" id="NSV4ZOGOCFHRTHMXZAQI3NWTK4" data-contentid="NSV4ZOGOCFHRTHMXZAQI3NWTK4" class="wpds-c-foYyTm wpds-c-foYyTm-idAgRsb-css"&gt;Last year, Nebraska Gov. Jim Pillen (R) vetoed a bipartisan bill that would have green-lit syringe exchanges, saying they would re-create the “failed policies of drug-infested cities like San Francisco here.” Even San Francisco &lt;a href="https://www.latimes.com/california/story/2025-04-02/san-francisco-ties-clean-syringe-distribution-for-drug-users-to-treatment-counseling?itid=lk_inline_enhanced-template"&gt;scaled back&lt;/a&gt; syringe programs in April, tying clean needles to treatment or other services.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="Image" data-file="components/Image/Image.js" data-style="stitches" class="wpds-c-bTCZLY wpds-c-bTCZLY-idZwvW-type-default"&gt;&lt;figure id="image-OQ3UZNK7UPHBP7B4CRWE523KCE" class="wpds-c-PJLV wpds-c-PJLV-XgEPk-type-large"&gt;&lt;img alt="" loading="lazy" decoding="async" data-nimg="1" srcset="https://img.washingtonpost.com/wp-apps/imrs.php?src=https://arc-anglerfish-washpost-prod-washpost.s3.amazonaws.com/public/OQ3UZNK7UPHBP7B4CRWE523KCE_size-normalized.JPG&amp;amp;high_res=true&amp;amp;w=2048 1x" src="https://img.washingtonpost.com/wp-apps/imrs.php?src=https://arc-anglerfish-washpost-prod-washpost.s3.amazonaws.com/public/OQ3UZNK7UPHBP7B4CRWE523KCE_size-normalized.JPG&amp;amp;high_res=true&amp;amp;w=2048"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="wpds-c-kaVXjn wpds-c-kaVXjn-fTrHqK-type-large"&gt;Timmons provides food, naloxone and other supplies to unhoused people near the city's downtown homeless shelter.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="Text" data-file="custom-template-components/src/Text/Text.js" data-style="stitches" id="SQHQT3GWVFHMBIYFSRLP3C5YWY" data-contentid="SQHQT3GWVFHMBIYFSRLP3C5YWY" class="wpds-c-foYyTm wpds-c-foYyTm-idAgRsb-css"&gt;The Trump administration has taken aim at these programs, &lt;a href="https://www.whitehouse.gov/wp-content/uploads/2025/05/Fiscal-Year-2026-Discretionary-Budget-Request.pdf?itid=lk_inline_enhanced-template"&gt;blasting its predecessor’s backing&lt;/a&gt; of the programs as “dangerous.” In a July 29 letter, the Substance Abuse and Mental Health Administration, which administers billions in grants to states, prohibited the use of grants to purchase needles, sterile water, saline, vitamin C or any other supplies “to promote or facilitate drug use” — or support such services.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-component="Text" data-file="custom-template-components/src/Text/Text.js" data-style="stitches" id="TJMBJTNJEFA7BP7OSKOACCYPRI" data-contentid="TJMBJTNJEFA7BP7OSKOACCYPRI" class="wpds-c-foYyTm wpds-c-foYyTm-idAgRsb-css"&gt;The stance comes as Health and Human Services Secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr., who has acknowledged publicly contracting hepatitis C through injection drug use years ago, had pledged $100 million &lt;a href="https://www.hhs.gov/press-room/hhs-100m-hepatitis-c-elimination-funding-opportunity.html?itid=lk_inline_enhanced-template"&gt;to fund&lt;/a&gt; local and state programs to prevent, test, treat and cure the virus. About half of all acute hepatitis C infections &lt;a href="https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jama/fullarticle/2838798?itid=lk_inline_enhanced-template" target="_blank"&gt;result from injection drug use&lt;/a&gt;, according to a Sept. 10 JAMA Network article.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="Ad" data-file="custom-template-components/src/Ad/Ad.js" data-style="stitches" class="wpds-c-PJLV"&gt;&lt;div class="PJLV PJLV-icAbLfl-css"&gt;&lt;div aria-hidden="true" class="hide-for-print relative flex justify-center content-box items-center b bh mb-lg mt-lg pt-md pb-md"&gt;&lt;div class="center absolute w-100 border-box"&gt;&lt;p class="dib flex divider gray-dark pl-xs pr-xs font-sans-serif light font-xxxxs lh-md"&gt;Story continues below advertisement&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="Text" data-file="custom-template-components/src/Text/Text.js" data-style="stitches" id="42JM4CCLQ5C7JKJ7TJLHTJRKDM" data-contentid="42JM4CCLQ5C7JKJ7TJLHTJRKDM" class="wpds-c-foYyTm wpds-c-foYyTm-idAgRsb-css"&gt;It remains unclear whether federal grants can be used to pay staff salaries or other operations for organizations that offer syringes among other services. The agency said it will ensure grants “are aligned with both the administration’s priorities and sound clinical practice” and recently removed a &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/syringe-services-programs/php/index.html?itid=lk_inline_enhanced-template"&gt;CDC webpage&lt;/a&gt; that touted benefits of syringe programs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-component="Text" data-file="custom-template-components/src/Text/Text.js" data-style="stitches" id="UCXTFDKKZFDTVAKKWYYEKQRB3Y" data-contentid="UCXTFDKKZFDTVAKKWYYEKQRB3Y" class="wpds-c-foYyTm wpds-c-foYyTm-idAgRsb-css"&gt;Organizations or states may shut down their programs for fear of losing other funding, said Beth Meyerson, director of the University of Arizona’s Harm Reduction Research Lab. “States that weren’t supportive in the first place will use this as their shield” from criticism if they shut down needle exchanges, Meyerson said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 data-component="Heading" data-contentid="JYOLJGFMZNDGFCCWDDICAUJH2E" data-file="custom-template-components/src/Heading/Heading.js" data-style="stitches" id="JYOLJGFMZNDGFCCWDDICAUJH2E" class="wpds-c-iFKWRt wpds-c-iFKWRt-jirhpe-level-2 wpds-c-iFKWRt-iiCGobN-css"&gt;An uphill battle&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;div data-component="Image" data-file="components/Image/Image.js" data-style="stitches" class="wpds-c-bTCZLY wpds-c-bTCZLY-idZwvW-type-default"&gt;&lt;figure id="image-4ZNNDEGKAULMQXQCQCO34KUYKM" class="wpds-c-PJLV wpds-c-PJLV-XgEPk-type-large"&gt;&lt;img alt="" loading="lazy" decoding="async" data-nimg="1" srcset="https://img.washingtonpost.com/wp-apps/imrs.php?src=https://arc-anglerfish-washpost-prod-washpost.s3.amazonaws.com/public/4ZNNDEGKAULMQXQCQCO34KUYKM_size-normalized.JPG&amp;amp;high_res=true&amp;amp;w=2048 1x" src="https://img.washingtonpost.com/wp-apps/imrs.php?src=https://arc-anglerfish-washpost-prod-washpost.s3.amazonaws.com/public/4ZNNDEGKAULMQXQCQCO34KUYKM_size-normalized.JPG&amp;amp;high_res=true&amp;amp;w=2048"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="wpds-c-kaVXjn wpds-c-kaVXjn-fTrHqK-type-large"&gt;A woman embraces Timmons after receiving food and other supplies.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="Text" data-file="custom-template-components/src/Text/Text.js" data-style="stitches" id="MPIDB5B3PZABLNQ7SENP5MVKA4" data-contentid="MPIDB5B3PZABLNQ7SENP5MVKA4" class="wpds-c-foYyTm wpds-c-foYyTm-idAgRsb-css"&gt;In Indiana, after the SAMHSA letter was published, the health department ordered groups that get state funding to destroy “safer use” supplies commonly given to injection users such as cookers, cottons, tourniquets and sterile water.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-component="Text" data-file="custom-template-components/src/Text/Text.js" data-style="stitches" id="67EQX7OCRFDA7HVAIETTT3Y2JI" data-contentid="67EQX7OCRFDA7HVAIETTT3Y2JI" class="wpds-c-foYyTm wpds-c-foYyTm-idAgRsb-css"&gt;At least 11 of Indiana’s 92 counties have operated syringe programs, though three have closed in recent years. The remaining eight serve many of the most populous regions and&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;may close next summer if lawmakers don’t renew a state law, said Indiana state Rep. Ed Clere, a moderate Republican who supports the programs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-component="Text" data-file="custom-template-components/src/Text/Text.js" data-style="stitches" id="LNQUHJPK2ZFIJNF6NSMQVQEXKM" data-contentid="LNQUHJPK2ZFIJNF6NSMQVQEXKM" class="wpds-c-foYyTm wpds-c-foYyTm-idAgRsb-css"&gt;He cited state data that between 2020 and the start of 2024, the programs distributed more than 161,600 doses of naloxone, the opioid reversal medication. “Sterile syringes are a way to get people in the door,” Clere said. He added that he plans to fight for the law’s renewal but admitted that the administration’s stance makes a “steep hill even steeper.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="Image" data-file="components/Image/Image.js" data-style="stitches" class="wpds-c-bTCZLY wpds-c-bTCZLY-idZwvW-type-default"&gt;&lt;figure id="image-VABSAAQEXYTDJF77ELEILVDYS4" class="wpds-c-PJLV wpds-c-PJLV-iossVB-type-medium"&gt;&lt;img alt="" loading="lazy" decoding="async" data-nimg="1" srcset="https://img.washingtonpost.com/wp-apps/imrs.php?src=https://arc-anglerfish-washpost-prod-washpost.s3.amazonaws.com/public/VABSAAQEXYTDJF77ELEILVDYS4_size-normalized.JPG&amp;amp;high_res=true&amp;amp;w=2048 1x" src="https://img.washingtonpost.com/wp-apps/imrs.php?src=https://arc-anglerfish-washpost-prod-washpost.s3.amazonaws.com/public/VABSAAQEXYTDJF77ELEILVDYS4_size-normalized.JPG&amp;amp;high_res=true&amp;amp;w=2048"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="wpds-c-kaVXjn wpds-c-kaVXjn-jBafdS-type-notLarge"&gt;Timmons stores many of the outreach supplies she distributes in her home.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="Text" data-file="custom-template-components/src/Text/Text.js" data-style="stitches" id="VES2QGVIRZGXDIJSXRNYXQMZBQ" data-contentid="VES2QGVIRZGXDIJSXRNYXQMZBQ" class="wpds-c-foYyTm wpds-c-foYyTm-idAgRsb-css"&gt;The office of Indiana Gov. Mike Braun (R) did not reply to requests for comment, but his chief health policy aide emailed Clere in August saying that Braun does not believe syringe programs “align with the administration’s priorities or long-term approach to addressing addiction in Indiana.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-component="Text" data-file="custom-template-components/src/Text/Text.js" data-style="stitches" id="DSNJWSZUGZCBBFK3T6EC5K6U4M" data-contentid="DSNJWSZUGZCBBFK3T6EC5K6U4M" class="wpds-c-foYyTm wpds-c-foYyTm-idAgRsb-css"&gt;In Clark County, just outside Louisville, health officials warn that ending the syringe program could trigger more needle-sharing and infectious disease because it collects used syringes from users and drop boxes. “We actually take more off the street than we give out,” said Eric Yazel, the county health officer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div id="61b7c6c4-781c-4a15-b400-d93762acc371" class="wpds-c-dVLvml wpds-c-dVLvml-eOmIMU-type-imageGrid image-package-61b7c6c4-781c-4a15-b400-d93762acc371"&gt;&lt;figure class="wpds-c-PJLV wpds-c-PJLV-iPJLV-css image-1"&gt;&lt;img alt="" loading="lazy" decoding="async" data-nimg="1" srcset="https://img.washingtonpost.com/wp-apps/imrs.php?src=https://arc-anglerfish-washpost-prod-washpost.s3.amazonaws.com/public/TQF6O4DGSMNUQLOQ234MXO4MPM_size-normalized.JPG&amp;amp;high_res=true&amp;amp;w=2048 1x" src="https://img.washingtonpost.com/wp-apps/imrs.php?src=https://arc-anglerfish-washpost-prod-washpost.s3.amazonaws.com/public/TQF6O4DGSMNUQLOQ234MXO4MPM_size-normalized.JPG&amp;amp;high_res=true&amp;amp;w=2048"&gt;&lt;figcaption type="imageGrid" class="wpds-c-iAKjhe"&gt;Timmons collects used syringes to dispose of. &lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figure class="wpds-c-PJLV wpds-c-PJLV-iPJLV-css image-2"&gt;&lt;img alt="" loading="lazy" decoding="async" data-nimg="1" srcset="https://img.washingtonpost.com/wp-apps/imrs.php?src=https://arc-anglerfish-washpost-prod-washpost.s3.amazonaws.com/public/ZUPY5QK3JDOJOJWGLYCSP2J2TY_size-normalized.JPG&amp;amp;high_res=true&amp;amp;w=2048 1x" src="https://img.washingtonpost.com/wp-apps/imrs.php?src=https://arc-anglerfish-washpost-prod-washpost.s3.amazonaws.com/public/ZUPY5QK3JDOJOJWGLYCSP2J2TY_size-normalized.JPG&amp;amp;high_res=true&amp;amp;w=2048"&gt;&lt;figcaption type="imageGrid" class="wpds-c-iAKjhe"&gt;Timmons picks up a discarded syringe. &lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV wpds-c-PJLV-ilcLoLw-css image-3"&gt;&lt;figcaption type="imageGrid" class="wpds-c-iAKjhe"&gt;Lavender Timmons, founder of the Evansville Recovery Alliance, searches for used needles to dispose of. (David Ovalle/The Washington Post) (David Ovalle/TWP)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="Text" data-file="custom-template-components/src/Text/Text.js" data-style="stitches" id="HUQYLHYSBRBIXLH54I4RT35IBA" data-contentid="HUQYLHYSBRBIXLH54I4RT35IBA" class="wpds-c-foYyTm wpds-c-foYyTm-idAgRsb-css"&gt;Back in Evansville, Timmons pulled a wheeled cart down a concrete path to a plaza on a bend of the Ohio River. Armed with a trash picker, she scoured the ground for orange-tipped syringes. Every day, Timmons fans out across Evansville — Indiana’s third-largest city — to gather syringes. Most are handed over by users who trust her.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-component="Text" data-file="custom-template-components/src/Text/Text.js" data-style="stitches" id="NDOPW2FYKZBFNNJIQJYZHVWZAQ" data-contentid="NDOPW2FYKZBFNNJIQJYZHVWZAQ" class="wpds-c-foYyTm wpds-c-foYyTm-idAgRsb-css"&gt;Her efforts underscore another vexing problem posed by the lack of a syringe program: People have nowhere to legally dispose of used needles.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-component="Text" data-file="custom-template-components/src/Text/Text.js" data-style="stitches" id="UPIXZ5CF55BTPBRO6XWPGO5EHY" data-contentid="UPIXZ5CF55BTPBRO6XWPGO5EHY" class="wpds-c-foYyTm wpds-c-foYyTm-idAgRsb-css"&gt;The homeless often camp on this scenic stretch in Evansville’s downtown overlooking Kentucky, discarding needles that pose a danger to children. Sometimes, people try to sharpen discarded needles by rubbing them on concrete to reuse them or rigging them with safety pins, leading to infections.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="Image" data-file="components/Image/Image.js" data-style="stitches" class="wpds-c-bTCZLY wpds-c-bTCZLY-idZwvW-type-default"&gt;&lt;figure id="image-2AD6WV6L4DP4Z5B7G4TZNXWONY" class="wpds-c-PJLV wpds-c-PJLV-XgEPk-type-large"&gt;&lt;img alt="" loading="lazy" decoding="async" data-nimg="1" srcset="https://img.washingtonpost.com/wp-apps/imrs.php?src=https://arc-anglerfish-washpost-prod-washpost.s3.amazonaws.com/public/2AD6WV6L4DP4Z5B7G4TZNXWONY_size-normalized.JPG&amp;amp;high_res=true&amp;amp;w=2048 1x" src="https://img.washingtonpost.com/wp-apps/imrs.php?src=https://arc-anglerfish-washpost-prod-washpost.s3.amazonaws.com/public/2AD6WV6L4DP4Z5B7G4TZNXWONY_size-normalized.JPG&amp;amp;high_res=true&amp;amp;w=2048"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="wpds-c-kaVXjn wpds-c-kaVXjn-fTrHqK-type-large"&gt;Timmons enters a wooded area to collect used needles from a homeless encampment.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="Text" data-file="custom-template-components/src/Text/Text.js" data-style="stitches" id="XL2OBTF5TZCKLMLSCGVQI6J27I" data-contentid="XL2OBTF5TZCKLMLSCGVQI6J27I" class="wpds-c-foYyTm wpds-c-foYyTm-idAgRsb-css"&gt;The work is personal for Timmons. She experienced a chaotic childhood in Evansville. Her mother used drugs, and they were often homeless. In her 20s, Timmons battled her own addiction, wandering the country by hopping trains.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-component="Text" data-file="custom-template-components/src/Text/Text.js" data-style="stitches" id="J3KEKM2AWZEDNDFKIK36WU4GZA" data-contentid="J3KEKM2AWZEDNDFKIK36WU4GZA" class="wpds-c-foYyTm wpds-c-foYyTm-idAgRsb-css"&gt;She now runs the alliance on a shoestring budget, relying solely on private donations of supplies. Another harm reduction group recently donated a chrome-colored van that she hopes to use as a mobile syringe center if her group can ramp up testing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-component="Text" data-file="custom-template-components/src/Text/Text.js" data-style="stitches" id="Y74QIUXTFBBVPBMWHUISOTXZAQ" data-contentid="Y74QIUXTFBBVPBMWHUISOTXZAQ" class="wpds-c-foYyTm wpds-c-foYyTm-idAgRsb-css"&gt;She makes her rounds to homes, encampments along the railroad tracks and the run-down motels lining Evansville’s Fares Avenue strip. Then each week, she or another volunteer drive two hours to dispose of used needles at a state-designated site in Bloomington.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-component="Text" data-file="custom-template-components/src/Text/Text.js" data-style="stitches" id="36BJO2A5HNFGLJYNXGWCZFF2DQ" data-contentid="36BJO2A5HNFGLJYNXGWCZFF2DQ" class="wpds-c-foYyTm wpds-c-foYyTm-idAgRsb-css"&gt;“I’ve seen people injecting themselves with a lot of rigged-up sharp things,” Timmons said, adding that one user she knows developed wounds from this approach and recently died of sepsis. “It doesn’t work.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 16:00:42 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiogFBVV95cUxPbkQ2V19IWkg5WXc0ZXlkejYxN2NjeEt4WDlxMFk0emZfOTFLdWhmRUIyY01qbXBVNzhkbFI3MEU1RkNGYUt0NGlMeG5sRWRBckNwVE1IT2NDU2N6MGtfSXkycENDX01JZXdpTUp2Skh2UTVoNHQza2lJN2hKblp1ZG5DeGtGWE9lYXZoUFZ2bXFlY3NBQmpOeEZwQ0dDejBYT3c</guid></item><item><title>医生刚刚发现了一些有趣的东西，当你在Ozempic上喝酒时会发生什么-未来主义</title><link>https://futurism.com/health-medicine/doctors-drinking-ozempic</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;figure class="article-featured-image-figure"&gt;
			
			
	&lt;p class="article-featured-image-caption-container"&gt;
		&lt;figcaption class="article-featured-image-caption"&gt;
			Illustration by Tag Hartman-Simkins / Futurism. Source: Getty Images
 		&lt;/figcaption&gt;
	&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/figure&gt;
	
	
	
	
	
	&lt;div class="content-wrapper" data-toc-container&gt;
		
&lt;p class="pw-incontent-excluded article-paragraph skip"&gt;GLP-1 drugs like semaglutide, the active ingredient in Novo Nordisk’s Ozempic and Wegovy, were originally intended to treat diabetes — and didn’t become blockbuster prescriptions until doctors realized that they were also potent weight loss aids that seem to re-wire patients’ relationship to food and satiety. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;Since then, it’s slowly been emerging that they have another surprising effect: many users report less of a desire to throw back as many drinks as they did before starting the injections. Indeed, several small studies have found promising&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;evidence that the drugs indeed curb&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://people.com/ozempic-lowers-alcohol-craving-semaglutide-study-11678702" rel="noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;cravings for alcohol&lt;strong&gt;, &lt;/strong&gt;cigarettes&lt;/a&gt;, and even &lt;a href="https://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1111/add.16679" rel="nofollow noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;opioids&lt;/a&gt;, meaning they also hold promise to treat a range of addiction disorders.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;Exactly why remains hazy, though. It’s &lt;a href="https://med.stanford.edu/news/insights/2025/04/ozempic-addiction-glp-1s-mounjaro-lembke.html" rel="nofollow noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;generally established&lt;/a&gt; that GLP-1s target the brain’s dopamine reward system, but scientists are still working to understand the exact mechanism.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;Adding&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;to the complexity is that the drugs make other changes to the body’s functioning that could interact with substance use in complex ways. Take  a &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41598-025-17927-w" rel="nofollow noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;new paper&lt;/a&gt; published in the journal&lt;em&gt; Scientific Reports&lt;/em&gt; by Virginia Tech researchers this week, for instance, which found that GLP-1s appear to physically change the way our bodies process alcohol.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;In the study, participants drank&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;three alcoholic drinks over the course of&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;an hour while researchers tracked their&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;blood alcohol, glucose, and vital signs. Compared to non-users, the&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;the participants on GLP-1s reported feeling less drunk overall — and had the readings to prove it: their&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;blood alcohol level rose more slowly, meaning the buzz was delayed and less significant.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;It’s not hard to imagine why. GLP-1s are known to slow gastric emptying of the stomach, which could likely result in alcohol reaching the bloodstream more slowly. But it once again shows how nuanced these drugs’ effects on our bodies and minds is: it may well be that an injection like semaglutide is both changing the neurological reward associated with alcohol, while simultaneously changing the way your stomach and gut processes a drink. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;Exactly how the latest finding affects doctors’ understanding of GLP-1 as a tool to fight addiction is hard to say — and the test group was small, at only 20 subjects, so further research is needed — but a sharper picture is slowly coming into focus.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;“Why would this matter? Faster-acting drugs have a higher abuse potential,” said Alex DiFeliceantonio, a Virginia Tech neuroscientist who worked on the study, in a &lt;a href="https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-10-glp-drugs-delay-alcohol-effects.html" rel="nofollow noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;blurb about the research&lt;/a&gt;. “They have a different impact on the brain. So if GLP-1s slow alcohol entering the bloodstream, they could reduce the effects of alcohol and help people drink less.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;More on Ozempic: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://futurism.com/neoscope/ozempic-anti-aging"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Scientists Find Evidence That Ozempic Can Reverse Aging&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Futurism</author><pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMibkFVX3lxTE5xUVVmVlY3NElKd295VnBKN1ZrNldQOEpjQ1duYkRwaUZ4WkdxZDRmQ2JxdnBGc1laUEI2bEUzRE82eTNZb3pkalVCWERZUlNXaGZzdHZ6QUY4TllCNmJhbGRqSUpsSzhQM3pTME9R</guid></item><item><title>前老大哥参赛者在现场洗碗后因残疾提起诉讼- Ynetnews</title><link>https://www.ynetnews.com/culture/article/ry8vzfmcgg</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="ArticleHeaderComponent" class="ArticleHeaderEngComponent1280 selectableShareable for-print" role="header" aria-label="article header"&gt;&lt;p class="mainTitleWrapper"&gt;&lt;h1 class="mainTitle"&gt;Former Big Brother contestant sues for disability after washing dishes on set&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="subTitleWrapper"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;span disabled class="subTitle" contenteditable="false"&gt;Shilo Shalom claims lasting damage from hand injury during 2024 season; lawsuit argues he was a salaried employee entitled to benefits, while National Insurance rejects claim over lack of employer-employee relationship&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Ynetnews</author><pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 15:36:43 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiYEFVX3lxTE9kX25SNGlNZWZYb3hoSmRleVF5N2RLRm9JRTJZNDhCWWtqVkd1OTM1Y29fNnRhLXB1UDllTm9xaDNlcVpLUTY5VURrRnk4VktvNnJRODA5ZTMwWUNNVmVqdQ</guid></item></channel></rss>