<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>GNews Health</title><link>https://news.google.com/</link><description></description><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>疫苗试验被称为“不道德”和“独特”的机会。开启还是关闭？ - NPR</title><link>https://www.npr.org/2026/01/22/g-s1-106571/vaccine-trial-hepatitis-b-guinea-bissau</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="storytext" class="storytext storylocation linkLocation"&gt;
      &lt;div id="resg-s1-106802" class="bucketwrap image large"&gt;
            
&lt;div class="credit-caption"&gt;
    &lt;div class="caption-wrap"&gt;
        &lt;div class="caption" aria-label="Image caption"&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;
                A medical worker prepares a hepatitis B vaccine.
                &lt;b class="credit" aria-label="Image credit"&gt;
                    
                    Nicholas Kajoba/Xinhua/via Getty Images
                    
                &lt;/b&gt;
                &lt;b class="hide-caption"&gt;&lt;b&gt;hide caption&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;
            &lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;


            &lt;b class="toggle-caption"&gt;&lt;b&gt;toggle caption&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;

    &lt;span class="credit" aria-label="Image credit"&gt;
        
        Nicholas Kajoba/Xinhua/via Getty Images
        
    &lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;This past week has brought a dizzying back-and-forth about a U.S.-funded medical research trial.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Many public health experts call the study unethical and unnecessary, likening it to the infamous Tuskegee Experiment, while the Trump Administration has promoted it as a rare opportunity to study the potential negative effects of a vaccine.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;The randomized controlled trial — funded partly with $1.6 million from the U.S. Centers for Disease Control and Prevention — would study the general health effects of the hepatitis B vaccine given at birth in the west African country of Guinea-Bissau.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;For a relatively small study in a relatively remote place, there has been outsized attention, and the rumor mill has been spinning. There have been contradictory reports that the trial has already started, that it has been canceled and that it's proceeding as planned.&lt;/p&gt;   
   &lt;p&gt;This morning at a press conference, the Minister of Public Health in Guinea-Bissau, Quinhin Nantote, finally weighed in, saying the study is suspended pending review.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"We decided to suspend or even cancel the above mentioned study," said Nantote, who was speaking in Portuguese, through an interpreter. He said a local ethics committee that had approved the study did not have the "required technical resources" and did not coordinate with the necessary other medical authorities in the country. The country experienced a military coup in November last year and many high level officials changed in the process.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Nantote said the ethics review was the "consequence of misinformation, weak social communication means and a lack of international communication, leading to inappropriate interpretations of our national health policies regarding immunization and health studies." He added that there has "been no sufficient coordination in order to take a final decision regarding that study."&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Africa CDC, the health agency of the African Union, says it is sending a team to Guinea-Bissau to help the country evaluate the study. It says that local officials have the final authority.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"It's not a foreign country that will come and say this one will take place. It's the sovereignty of the country," says Dr. Jean Kaseya, director-general of Africa CDC.&lt;/p&gt;   
   &lt;p&gt;Immediately following the Thursday press conference, speaking on the condition of anonymity, an official with the U.S. Department of Health and Human Services sent an email to NPR that contradicted Nantote and Kasaya, asserting that the study has not been suspended.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Here's a look at why this trial has garnered so much attention.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;h3 class="edTag"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This study is happening as U.S. vaccine policy changes&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;   &lt;p&gt;For more than 30 years, giving the &lt;a href="https://www.npr.org/sections/shots-health-news/2025/12/04/nx-s1-5629168/hepatitis-b-vaccine-kids-health" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;u&gt;hepatitis B&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; vaccine to all newborns in the U.S. has been standard practice. It's also &lt;a href="https://www.who.int/news-room/fact-sheets/detail/hepatitis-b" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;u&gt;the recommendation&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; of the World Health Organization.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;The vaccine helps prevent infants from getting the hepatitis B virus from their mothers during delivery. The virus attacks the liver and can, years later, lead to cirrhosis, liver cancer and death. There's no known cure.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;However, on December 5, CDC advisers &lt;a href="https://www.npr.org/sections/shots-health-news/2025/12/05/nx-s1-5634004/cdc-hepatitis-b-vaccine-acip-meeting" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;u&gt;voted to overturn&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; the U.S. policy.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;The advisers — hand-picked by vaccine-skeptic and Health and Human Services Secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr. — worried the vaccine might cause some harm. However, outside medical groups point to numerous &lt;a href="https://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/abs/10.1002/ebch.120" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;u&gt;studies&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; showing that it's safe and that rates of pediatric hepatitis B virus have &lt;a href="https://www.cidrap.umn.edu/sites/default/files/searchable-download/Universal%20Hepatitis%20B%20Vaccination%20at%20Birth%202Dec2025.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;u&gt;dropped by 99%&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; since 1991 and the &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/hepatitis/statistics/2020surveillance/hepatitis-b/table-2.4.htm" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;u&gt;CDC reported&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; that in 2020 only 10 children in the U.S. got hepatitis B from exposure at birth.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Less than two weeks after the vote, a &lt;a href="https://public-inspection.federalregister.gov/2025-23245.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;u&gt;document emerged&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; detailing that the CDC would fund a study to look into the hepatitis B vaccine in Guinea-Bissau, where nearly one in five adults are infected with hepatitis B virus. That rate is much higher than elsewhere in sub-Saharan Africa where the prevalence is just around 6%, according to the Africa CDC.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;h3 class="edTag"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The basics of the study&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Guinea-Bissau does not currently give the hepatitis B vaccine to newborns per the WHO recommendation but plans to start doing so in 2028, according to Guinea-Bissau's Nantote.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Danish researchers say on &lt;a href="https://www.bandim.org/hepatitis-b-vaccine-at-birth/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;u&gt;their website&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; that they want to study 14,500 newborns during this "unique window of opportunity" before the birth vaccination starts. Half of newborns will get the hepatitis B vaccine at birth, while the other half would get the inoculation later as part of other routine vaccinations given at 6, 10 and 14 weeks old.&lt;/p&gt;   
   &lt;p&gt;The idea is not to test whether the hepatitis B vaccine works against hepatitis B. Instead, the researchers are looking for other health effects of the vaccine. Do the newborns who get the vaccine develop other severe illnesses in the first few weeks of life? Do they get eczema in the first two years of life? Or perhaps they show neurological differences before they turn 5?&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;h3 class="edTag"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The ethics: unethical and unnecessary? &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Not long after the study surfaced physicians and medical ethicists called for its cancellation.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"[The Guinea-Bissau study] is highly unethical and cruel and frankly dishonest," says &lt;a href="https://www.chop.edu/doctors/offit-paul-a" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Dr. Paul Offit&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, director of the Vaccine Education Center at the Children's Hospital of Philadelphia and formerly a member of the CDC's Advisory Committee on Immunization Practices.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;He's one of a number of physicians who have compared this study to the notorious &lt;a href="https://www.npr.org/2021/02/16/967011614/in-tuskegee-painful-history-shadows-efforts-to-vaccinate-african-americans" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Tuskegee Experiment&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, which started in the 1930s and, for decades, denied treatment to poor African Americans with syphilis so that researchers could see how the disease progresses. More than 100 died as a result.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"The 7,000 group that's not getting the vaccine till six weeks of age are now being exposed to substandard care — substandard care that is being paid for by American tax dollars," Offit says, noting that with such a high rate of hepatitis B virus in the population many of those youngers could be infected by their mothers before 6 weeks of age.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://med.emory.edu/departments/medicine/divisions/infectious-diseases/studies-programs/bircwh/scholars/boghuma-titanji.html" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Dr. Boghuma Titanji&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, an infectious disease physician at Emory University, agrees with the Tuskegee analogy and worries the study could be the "initial trigger that then leads to communities being distrustful of medical intervention and vaccines." She says that distrust can last decades and even be passed down from generation to generation.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;The researchers behind the study counter that, currently, newborns in Guinea-Bissau are not getting the vaccine at birth.&lt;/p&gt;   
   &lt;p&gt;"No newborn in Guinea-Bissau will receive fewer vaccines because of this study," they wrote on &lt;a href="https://www.bandim.org/hepatitis-b-vaccine-at-birth/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;u&gt;their website&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, defending their study. They foresee that "vaccination coverage will increase" explaining "trial vaccination teams will operate every day of the year, including weekends and holidays. This is expected to increase timely vaccination coverage compared with routine services." The researcher did not respond to NPR's multiple requests for comment about the ethical questions and whether the study has been canceled.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Some bioethicists say there's a more fundamental issue: "The first and important consideration in making a study ethical is: The study has to answer a valuable question," says Christine Grady, former chief of the Department of Bioethics at the National Institutes of Health Clinical Center. "In this case, I think that's perhaps the biggest problem with this study," she says, noting that the vaccine has long been known to be safe and effective.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;The researchers argue on their website that the results "will contribute to the global scientific understanding of how vaccination affects overall child health" and that "this is an important trial which can impact future vaccine policies in the region and worldwide."&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;h3 class="edTag"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The politics: Non-competitive, questionable researchers&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Another major point of contention: who is doing the research and how they were selected.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;The Danish researchers at the helm — including Dr. Christine Stabell Benn — are highly controversial. They are affiliated with the University of Southern Denmark and lead the Bandim Health Project, which has done research in Guinea-Bissau for decades.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;While work by Stabell Benn's team has been published in reputable scientific journals, their statistical work has been questioned. For example, last month, in the journal &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S0264410X25012344" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;u&gt;Vaccine&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, outside biostatisticians evaluated the studies coming out of Bandim Health. What they found was that the group has "systematically over-interpreted the findings from their randomized trials," meaning the conclusions have been overstated and often aren't backed up by the data&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;when there was "proper statistical handling." That's according to a &lt;a href="https://health.au.dk/en/display/artikel/randomized-trials-show-no-evidence-of-non-specific-vaccine-effects" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;u&gt;press release&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; accompanying the article.&lt;/p&gt;   
   &lt;p&gt;"I was surprised by some quite strong claims," explains &lt;a href="https://www.au.dk/en/stovring@biomed.au.dk/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Henrik Støvring&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, a professor of pharmacometrics and statistics at Denmark's Aarhus University and lead author on the article. "But whenever I looked at a randomized trial — the primary outcomes I could find — it did not show statistical significance."&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Stabell Benn's team has pushed back against this conclusion and requested the review be retracted by the journal. The request is being reviewed.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Still, RFK Jr. is a fan of Stabell Benn's team.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;He cited a widely-criticized study on vaccine safety by Stabell Benn and others when he &lt;a href="https://www.npr.org/sections/goats-and-soda/2025/07/01/g-s1-74752/rfk-jr-vaccines-safety-gavi" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;u&gt;pulled more than a billion dollars&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; in U.S. funding for Gavi, the Vaccine Alliance. That money would have helped fund childhood vaccinations in many low-resources settings. The anti-vaccine organization RFK Jr. chaired — &lt;a href="https://www.npr.org/2024/12/03/nx-s1-5198506/rfk-jr-anti-vaccine-chd-lawsuits" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Children's Health Defense&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; — also &lt;a href="https://childrenshealthdefense.org/research_tags/diphtheria-tetanus-pertusis-dtp/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;u&gt;cites&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; the Danish researchers.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Outside vaccine experts have raised another concern: that the CDC awarded the $1.6 million dollars without an open, competitive process.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;That's led &lt;a href="https://medicine.usask.ca/profiles/bmi-affiliated/angela-rasmussen.php" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Angela Rasmussen&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, a virologist at the University of Saskatchewan, to worry that the Bandim Health Project was hand-picked by RFK Jr.'s team to do the research, since they are known to have raised safety concerns about vaccines long considered safe.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"[The thing] people really need to know [is] behind this all — is cronyism, is bad science," she says. "It's babies getting chronic illnesses that can kill them."&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;In a statement to NPR, the U.S. HHS defended the study and said it is proceeding as planned and the protocol is being finalized. Their statement said the study "represents the world's first and perhaps only opportunity to test the overall health effects of [the hepatitis B vaccine at birth]."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>NPR</author><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 17:36:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiigFBVV95cUxOMG9nVGUxeFJZYjM5eHpxV2ZBN3lnZW1WN3lvRVl5OU5YS2RiOU1uNFhCR0RKZ3V6akgxcXJPWE96dk15TDdFTmg5alRQQW54WS01Mjh4a0JHWGhiaFc4d0RQbUZRakdtZ3hFN0VMN3ZGQzNhaENScjFVOVQtdld2bk1DS2V2czlIM3c</guid></item><item><title>医生说，这种日常习惯可能弊大于利- AOL.com</title><link>https://www.aol.com/articles/doctors-everyday-habit-may-doing-161400405.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="caas-body"&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure align-caption-with-image"&gt;&lt;div class="no-margin"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="caption-wrapper"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption-collapse"&gt;&lt;span class="caption"&gt;6 Surprising Signs You’re Drinking Too Much Water&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="photo-credit"&gt;d3sign - Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;i&gt;"Hearst Magazines and Yahoo may earn commission or revenue on some items through these links."&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Proper hydration keeps many of your bodily systems running smoothly and helps stave off &lt;a href="https://www.prevention.com/fitness/a65870951/signs-of-dehydration/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:dehydration;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;dehydration&lt;/a&gt;, which may lead to side effects like fatigue, muscle cramps, and headaches if left unaddressed. On the flip side, it is possible to take your H20 intake to the extreme and become overhydrated, especially if you fall into certain groups. There are signs you’re drinking too much water, though, that can help you recognize when it’s time to dial it back.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Meet the experts: &lt;a href="https://www.cedars-sinai.org/provider/natasha-trentacosta-938538.html" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Natasha Trentacosta, M.D.;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Natasha Trentacosta, M.D.&lt;/a&gt;, a sports medicine specialist and orthopedic surgeon at Cedars-Sinai Orthopaedics in Los Angeles; &lt;a href="https://www.wmchealth.org/physician-locator/michael-klein-1508866757" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Michael Klein, M.D.;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Michael Klein, M.D.&lt;/a&gt;, a kidney specialist with WMCHealth in Hawthorne, NY and an associate professor at New York Medical College.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Overhydration is when there is an excess of water intake compared to water loss,” says &lt;a href="https://www.cedars-sinai.org/provider/natasha-trentacosta-938538.html" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Natasha Trentacosta, M.D.;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Natasha Trentacosta, M.D.&lt;/a&gt;, a sports medicine specialist and orthopedic surgeon at Cedars-Sinai Orthopaedics in LA. Here, doctors explain the signs of overhydration you should know in order to modulate your water intake in a healthy way, plus who can become overhydrated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Signs of overhydration to know&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Mild water overload often is asymptomatic,” says &lt;a href="https://www.wmchealth.org/physician-locator/michael-klein-1508866757" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Michael Klein, M.D.;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Michael Klein, M.D.&lt;/a&gt;, a kidney specialist with WMCHealth in Hawthorne, NY and an associate professor at New York Medical College. Still, there are some signs that may suggest an underlying issue with how your body is processing water (more on those below). According to the experts we spoke to, the most common signs include:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Who can become overhydrated?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The average healthy person likely does not need to worry about overhydration. “Your body is very effective at adjusting,” says Dr. Klein. “Once you reach adequate water levels, your body just gets rid of the excess very efficiently, assuming a state of normal health.” This is also the reason you don’t immediately get sick from not drinking enough water, Dr. Klein adds, because your body can adjust to changes in your water intake.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Still, there are certain groups of people who need to be careful not to overhydrate. The first is people with certain kidney diseases, especially those who produce excessive amounts of antidiuretic hormone (ADH), which is also known as vasopressin. “People who have an excess of ADH have strict water restrictions and water can be deadly. They have to be very careful,” says Dr. Klein. He explains that in these people (whose official diagnosis is &lt;a href="https://medlineplus.gov/ency/article/000314.htm" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:syndrome of inappropriate antidiuretic hormone secretion;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;syndrome of inappropriate antidiuretic hormone secretion&lt;/a&gt;, or SIADH), ADH tells the body to hold onto water no matter how much you drink, which can lead to water intoxication if not accounted for.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A similar thing happens in people with liver disease and congestive heart failure, Dr. Klein says. “In &lt;a href="https://www.prevention.com/health/health-conditions/a30872553/heart-failure-symptoms/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:heart failure;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;heart failure&lt;/a&gt;, your kidneys think you are dehydrated, and they will secrete these hormones, and if you drink water, you can get profoundly water toxic,” he explains.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Overhydration may also happen in athletes if they drink excessive amounts of water following strenuous exercise or activity, says Dr. Trentacosta. “This dilutes the sodium in their bodies and results in hyponatremia,” she adds. Per the &lt;a href="https://go.redirectingat.com?id=74968X1596630&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.mayoclinic.org%2Fdiseases-conditions%2Fhyponatremia%2Fsymptoms-causes%2Fsyc-20373711&amp;amp;sref=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.prevention.com%2Fhealth%2Fa70049905%2Fcan-you-drink-too-much-water%2F" data-i13n="elm:affiliate_link;elmt:premonetized" rel="sponsored" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Mayo Clinic;elm:affiliate_link;elmt:premonetized;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Mayo Clinic&lt;/a&gt;, hyponatremia is a condition in which sodium levels drop dangerously low. In addition to the groups of people mentioned above, it may also occur in those taking diuretics or antidepressants, people who have adrenal gland insufficiency or low thyroid hormone, or those who have chronic and severe vomiting or &lt;a href="https://www.prevention.com/health/a65833239/causes-of-diarrhea-to-know-about/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:diarrhea;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;diarrhea&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Still, for most people, neither type will be an issue. “Normally, drinking large amounts of water, even up to six gallons, can be managed by the natural ability of our bodies to regulate water excretion through the combined efforts of the pituitary gland, kidneys, liver, and heart,” Dr. Trentacosta says. “But if any of these organs are dysfunctional, that upper limit can be lowered.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;The bottom line&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Overhydration is rare, but it can occur—and in some cases, it may be caused by a serious issue that needs to be addressed. If you’re regularly experiencing any of the symptoms above, it’s definitely worth giving your physician a call.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You Might Also Like&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>AOL.com</author><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 17:30:38 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiggFBVV95cUxOLXpZOTdkSjlKVlFBVnYtTDQxYm93QmlOQ2FqeWc4QUpHMkc3VHhMdW9HbVRxQ2FmMlczbXcyOXFGbG90UkpydG1xQ0EwNlJRa0I1MFE0c3dUcHhNVC1MTDJaYkMwWDNmVGNTT0t0dFh2LUNEZ1BYMTBSS3hrRkpNTnhR</guid></item><item><title>较少的年轻人死于癌症死亡的主要原因—结直肠癌除外- CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2026/01/22/health/colon-cancer-young-adult-deaths</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article__content" data-editable="content" itemprop="articleBody" data-reorderable="content"&gt;
                
    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkpfjqj8005q27p9huru360i@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Jenna Scott remembers the joy of being pregnant with her first and only child. She also remembers the immense abdominal pain.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkpfrgr7000c3b6p9wfliiza@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            During her pregnancy, she let her doctors know about the persistent discomfort. She was told it was normal, that the aches “came with the territory,” she said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkpfrgr7000d3b6p93749s0s@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            But after she delivered a healthy baby boy, the pain didn’t fade. It lingered.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkpfrgr7000e3b6pr1vwl8ef@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            More than a year later, Scott received a diagnosis that shook her sense of normalcy: stage 4 colon cancer. She was 31 years old at the time.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkpfrgr7000f3b6pvd2kyr6x@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “We did a colonoscopy and when I woke up, there was my husband, my doctor and four nurses in the room. The GI doctor said he didn’t need to send anything off to pathology to know that I had cancer,” Scott, now 39, said in an email.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkpfrgr7000g3b6p79h5x5u1@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Stage 4 cancer, also known as metastatic cancer, means the cancer has spread from its original location to other parts of the body. For Scott, she said the disease spread from her colon to her liver.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkpfrgr7000h3b6p216u5dvh@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “I’ve always been super fit and healthy. I’ve been an athlete all my life. I didn’t even grow up eating red meat. In an instant, my life changed completely and unexpectedly,” she said. “I was in a state of disbelief because that word ‘cancer’ didn’t live in my world. Cancer means death.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkpfrgr7000i3b6pv52s4t63@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            In a concerning trend, colorectal cancer now appears to be the deadliest cancer for young adults.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkpfrgr7000j3b6pggxl5evy@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Colorectal cancer has surpassed other cancer types to become the leading cause of cancer deaths among people under 50 in the United States, as of 2023, according to &lt;a href="https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jama/fullarticle/10.1001/jama.2025.25467?guestAccessKey=5eabd609-08b0-47c7-a738-916c7acdcc37&amp;amp;utm_source=For_The_Media&amp;amp;utm_medium=referral&amp;amp;utm_campaign=ftm_links&amp;amp;utm_content=tfl&amp;amp;utm_term=012226" target="_blank"&gt;new research&lt;/a&gt; published Thursday in the medical journal JAMA.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkpfrgr7000k3b6pvpe8cg3c@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Deaths from colon and rectal cancers in the under-50 age group rose by 1.1% annually since 2005, the research found. Because of this rise, colorectal cancer went from being the fifth most common cause of cancer deaths among people younger than 50 in the early 1990s to becoming the top cause in 2023.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkpfrgr7000l3b6ppujlttzm@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “We don’t know why it is increasing,” said Dr. Ahmedin Jemal, senior vice president of surveillance, prevention and health services research at the American Cancer Society and senior author of the new study.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkpfrgr7000m3b6p6mi1m4fv@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “Mortality for the other major causes of cancer deaths in young adults under 50 is declining. It is only colorectal cancer mortality that is increasing, but we really don’t know fully what contributes to this rising burden,” he said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkpfrgr7000n3b6ph4xvmax6@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Scott, an advocate for the nonprofit Colorectal Cancer Alliance, also finds the new research troubling.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkpfrgr7000o3b6pf8e78rv2@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            After years of treatment – which included chemotherapy medications, targeted therapy and surgery – she is now in stable condition, but she said that she must “continue chemotherapy and targeted therapy indefinitely,” because each time she has stopped treatment before, the cancer came back and spread further to other organs in her body.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkpfrgr7000p3b6puqa5mz52@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            As she now continues treatment, Scott said that her goal is to “become a grandmother one day.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

  

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkpfrgr7000r3b6pfy1a4p8g@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            For the new research, Jemal and his colleagues at the American Cancer society analyzed the annual numbers and rates of cancer deaths among people under 50 in the United States from 1990 through 2023, based on data from the US Centers for Disease Control and Prevention’s National Center for Health Statistics.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkpfrgr7000s3b6pt4uqnuil@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “It’s the most complete data we have,” Jemal said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkpfrgr7000t3b6ptlfa8y3n@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The researchers examined the five leading causes of cancer death among the under-50 age group. They found that overall, from 1990 through 2023, more than 1.2 million people died of cancer in the United States before age 50, and the death rate fell by 44% during that time.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkpfrgr7000u3b6pdduox5om@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The data also showed that deaths decreased for every leading cancer type, except for colorectal cancer.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkpfrgr7000v3b6pk6hpvwnm@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Among the five leading causes of cancer death in people under 50, the average annual decline in deaths from 2014 through 2023 was 0.3% for brain cancer, 1.4% for breast cancer, 2.3% for leukemia and 5.7% for lung cancer, according to the data.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkpfrgr7000w3b6pvjolml72@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The research findings suggest that as of 2023, the top five causes of cancer deaths among people younger than 50 in the United States were:
    &lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;div data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/list/instances/cmkpfrhhw001g3b6pjnd9591z@published" class="list-elevate vossi-list_elevate" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
  &lt;ol data-editable="items" class="list__items list__items--ol vossi-list_elevate__items vossi-list_elevate__items--ol"&gt;
      
      &lt;li data-editable="items.0.text" class="list__item vossi-list_elevate__item inline-placeholder"&gt;
        &lt;span class="list__text vossi-list_elevate__text "&gt;
            Colorectal cancer
        &lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      
      &lt;li data-editable="items.1.text" class="list__item vossi-list_elevate__item inline-placeholder"&gt;
        &lt;span class="list__text vossi-list_elevate__text "&gt;
            Breast cancer
        &lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      
      &lt;li data-editable="items.2.text" class="list__item vossi-list_elevate__item inline-placeholder"&gt;
        &lt;span class="list__text vossi-list_elevate__text "&gt;
            Brain cancer
        &lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      
      &lt;li data-editable="items.3.text" class="list__item vossi-list_elevate__item inline-placeholder"&gt;
        &lt;span class="list__text vossi-list_elevate__text "&gt;
            Lung cancer
        &lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      
      &lt;li data-editable="items.4.text" class="list__item vossi-list_elevate__item inline-placeholder"&gt;
        &lt;span class="list__text vossi-list_elevate__text "&gt;
            Leukemia
        &lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkpfrgr7000x3b6phrfmhd0u@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “We weren’t expecting colorectal cancer to rise to this level so quickly, but now it is clear that this can no longer be called an old person’s disease,” Jemal said in a news release.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkpfrgr7000y3b6puideed1k@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “We must double down on research to pinpoint what is driving this tsunami of cancer in generations born since 1950,” he added.&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;“In the meantime, people 45-49 years make up fifty percent of diagnoses under 50, so increased screening uptake will prevent disease as well as death.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkpfrgr7000z3b6phiqd8gvx@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            As a young adult with colorectal cancer, Scott said that the research findings were “pretty disturbing” for her.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkpfrgr700103b6pcjphhe3v@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “What has to happen to draw more awareness to this disease and the people who are mostly being affected by it today? Why are seemingly healthy adults and children continuing to die from this disease? Why are women becoming more and more affected? How do you prevent something when you nor your team of doctors know how you got it in the first place?” Scott said in the email. “We have to stop this increase in mortality.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkpfrgr700113b6p2juen9cq@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            There are nearly 60 new colorectal cancer cases diagnosed in people under 50 each day in the United States, according to the &lt;a href="https://colorectalcancer.org/basics/facts-and-statistics#:~:text=Colorectal%20cancer%20is%20the%20fourth%20most%20common%20cancer%20in,among%20men%20and%20women%20combined.&amp;amp;text=Each%20year%2C%20about%20150%2C000%20Americans%20are%20diagnosed%20with%20colorectal%20cancer.&amp;amp;text=More%20than%2050%2C000%20people%20will%20die%20from%20colorectal%20cancer%20this%20year.&amp;amp;text=One%20in%2024%20people%20will,colorectal%20cancer%20in%20their%20lifetime." target="_blank"&gt;Colorectal Cancer Alliance&lt;/a&gt; — that’s a diagnosis about every 25 minutes.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;h2 class="subheader inline-placeholder subheader-elevate vossi-subheader_elevate vossi-subheader_elevate--size-h2" data-editable="text" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/subheader/instances/cmkpfyybf00063b6pmn959hey@published" data-component-name="subheader" id="colon-cancer-screening-and-symptoms" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
        Colon cancer screening and symptoms
&lt;/h2&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkpfrgr700133b6p9e1fk5qi@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The new research is an important reminder for people under 50 to stay up-to-date on their cancer screenings, Jemal said. It’s recommended for people at average risk of colorectal cancer to &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/colorectal-cancer/screening/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;start regular screening at age 45&lt;/a&gt;.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkpfrgr700143b6plwk5fwc3@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Yet “only 37% of adults ages 45 to 49 are up-to-date for their colorectal cancer screening,” Jemal said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkpkxq4o00013b6pxhtyfert@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “Colorectal cancer screening can not only detect cancer at the early stage, but also it removes the polyps before it becomes cancer,” he said. “So, it’s one of the two screening types that we have that not only detects cancer at early stage but also prevents it, the other being cervical cancer screening.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkpfrgr700153b6p61pyz36t@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The new research is “timely” and highlights a “red flag,” said Dr. Y. Nancy You, professor at the &lt;a href="https://nam11.safelinks.protection.outlook.com/?url=https%3A%2F%2Ffaculty.mdanderson.org%2Fprofiles%2Fyi-qian_you.html&amp;amp;data=05%7C02%7Cjacqueline.howard%40cnn.com%7Cafea9cdb895a4157d09d08de591d8b83%7C0eb48825e8714459bc72d0ecd68f1f39%7C0%7C0%7C639046180643527548%7CUnknown%7CTWFpbGZsb3d8eyJFbXB0eU1hcGkiOnRydWUsIlYiOiIwLjAuMDAwMCIsIlAiOiJXaW4zMiIsIkFOIjoiTWFpbCIsIldUIjoyfQ%3D%3D%7C0%7C%7C%7C&amp;amp;sdata=pNczevsVBSBzaiEytcgwRqBZp7EtBo0lwCnU0kqwvBA%3D&amp;amp;reserved=0" target="_blank"&gt;University of Texas MD Anderson Cancer Center&lt;/a&gt; and director of its Young-onset Colorectal Cancer Program, who was not involved in the new paper.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkpfrgr700163b6pgh7ra4q9@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            But while screening for colorectal cancer among healthy younger adults with no symptoms is critically important, “that’s only part of the story. I think there is a tremendous gap – and opportunity – in expeditiously diagnosing and treating people who are already symptomatic,” You said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkpfrgr700173b6pfysu5l6a@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Common &lt;a href="https://www.cancer.org/cancer/types/colon-rectal-cancer/detection-diagnosis-staging/signs-and-symptoms.html" target="_blank"&gt;symptoms of colorectal cancer&lt;/a&gt; include:
    &lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;div data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/list/instances/cmkphbd5t00083b6sng2ehfhi@published" class="list-elevate vossi-list_elevate" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
  &lt;ul data-editable="items" class="list__items list__items--ul vossi-list_elevate__items vossi-list_elevate__items--ul"&gt;
      
      &lt;li data-editable="items.0.text" class="list__item vossi-list_elevate__item inline-placeholder"&gt;
        &lt;span class="list__text vossi-list_elevate__text "&gt;
            Blood in the stool or rectal bleeding
        &lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      
      &lt;li data-editable="items.1.text" class="list__item vossi-list_elevate__item inline-placeholder"&gt;
        &lt;span class="list__text vossi-list_elevate__text "&gt;
            Unexplained changes in bowel habits — such as diarrhea, constipation or narrowing of the stool — for more than a few days
        &lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      
      &lt;li data-editable="items.2.text" class="list__item vossi-list_elevate__item inline-placeholder"&gt;
        &lt;span class="list__text vossi-list_elevate__text "&gt;
            Persistant abdominal pain or cramping
        &lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      
      &lt;li data-editable="items.3.text" class="list__item vossi-list_elevate__item inline-placeholder"&gt;
        &lt;span class="list__text vossi-list_elevate__text "&gt;
            Weakness or fatigue
        &lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      
      &lt;li data-editable="items.4.text" class="list__item vossi-list_elevate__item inline-placeholder"&gt;
        &lt;span class="list__text vossi-list_elevate__text "&gt;
            Unintended weight loss
        &lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      
      &lt;li data-editable="items.5.text" class="list__item vossi-list_elevate__item inline-placeholder"&gt;
        &lt;span class="list__text vossi-list_elevate__text "&gt;
            Lingering sensation of fullness, needing to have a bowel movement even after going
        &lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkpfrgr700183b6p83t1mmb0@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “There is an unmeasurable group of young adults who have symptoms that may be consistent with colorectal cancer, but either sit on the symptoms because they are busy or are scared, or eventually access their health care system but encounter a provider who thinks it’s just a hemorrhoid and doesn’t trigger further investigations,” You said, referring to when patients’ symptoms sometimes get dismissed by their providers.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkpfrgr700193b6pcd4nn6xs@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “So, there are definitely delays in diagnosing young adults who are already symptomatic.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkpfrgr7001a3b6prjw4hwki@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            When there are delays in diagnosing cancer, it becomes more likely that the disease will be diagnosed at later stages, such as stage 3 or 4. When cancer is at an advanced stage, it may have spread beyond the tumor itself into surrounding regions or other parts in the body, making it more difficult to treat and the patient becomes less likely to survive, regardless of age.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkpfrgr7001b3b6pi78l25ro@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            That’s why the increase in colorectal cancer deaths appears to be happening at a time when more people under 50 are being diagnosed with advanced-stage disease, said Dr. Andrea Cercek, a gastrointestinal medical oncologist at Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center, who was not involved in the new research.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkpfrgr7001c3b6phtx90on9@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            For colorectal cancer, “those under 45 are not screened, so they’re not diagnosed until they have symptoms. In many of those, about three-fourths, those symptoms are actually because they have much more advanced disease, and then the outcomes are worse, regardless of their age,” Cercek said, adding that the new research highlights a greater need to diagnose young patients quickly and not dismiss their symptoms because of age.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkpfrgr7001d3b6pbkgq7ook@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            It’s estimated that &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC7423740/" target="_blank"&gt;more than 60%&lt;/a&gt; of colorectal cancer patients under 50 are diagnosed after the disease has already advanced to stage 3 or 4.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkpfrgr7001e3b6plwge7fkp@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “In this younger group, when we do see later stage of diagnosis, that is highly associated with lower survival,” said Christine Molmenti, an associate professor and cancer epidemiologist at Northwell Health in New York, who was not involved in the new research.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkpfrgr7001f3b6plv77e88d@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “I’ve met a lot of patients under 50 with this disease, and I think it is very heartbreaking,” she said. “Anecdotally, what we see a lot of times is that these patients are healthy. They’re fit. Sometimes they’re athletes. There were a couple of patients who had not survived the disease, but their parents told us that they ran a marathon four months before their stage 4 colon cancer diagnosis. And often times young people ignore symptoms, or their symptoms are dismissed. So, I think there needs to be awareness.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

              &lt;/div&gt;
                  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>CNN</author><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 16:00:58 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMieEFVX3lxTE1qM3U0SHM1Z3VScUpPS21FZkZsMTh6RnFkdWt6TzFTYkplZlpndlpIZEVFcjlNNG9NczJqdU1YaTNSRVhGLU9LUHpWVHVwMm05R0JpaGZ1cndaR3NBYmcwb1hZZXNaNHBwY0pjZllwVkdkNWNRWFd3dg</guid></item><item><title>科学家发现将肥胖与痴呆风险联系起来的新线索-《华盛顿邮报》</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/health/2026/01/22/dementia-obesity-blood-pressure-science/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="3EMHBUBUHBCKJF6PZM4BICIRZE" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Obesity in midlife may cause vascular dementia later in life by raising blood pressure over decades&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;and quietly damaging brain vessels, according to new research released Thursday.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="WK4IO25SVVGALGSEBQ2D3JBBEA" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;The danger could be significant. Having a higher body mass index increases the risk of vascular dementia by roughly 50 to 60 percent, according to the study, published in the Journal of Clinical Endocrinology &amp;amp; Metabolism. An association between obesity and dementia has long been the subject of study, and the new research strongly indicates there is indeed a link.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 15:31:51 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikwFBVV95cUxNT3FjX1J1QnlHSlI5aklabThsLWcyV2pMcEVSZXFrenJxbWxWaFhhYjd1dnlsUWlGTFRldklJVU9ZOW95NUd2d09BazRGbExfZ19GenNheDlYZFZvZ2xpUzBvWXRENVhYakNibVFLVWdRME5mdUs1OHdpczdXU1BxVGZ5NjJ3dXRyUVR3ck9kV25LU1k</guid></item><item><title>新的“水坑”警告狗主人对致命的老鼠传播的细菌传播-美国太阳报</title><link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/15823591/dog-owners-deadly-bacteria/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="single__content entry-content m-bottom article__content"&gt;
							


&lt;div class="wp-block-tnl-wp-lead-asset-lead-asset"&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_15799399" class="wp-caption alignnone aligncenter"&gt;&lt;img fetchpriority="high" loading="eager" decoding="async" data-no-modal="true" src="https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/rear-view-caucasian-young-woman-1047408429.jpg" alt="Rear view of a young woman hugging her dog" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-15799399" srcset="https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/rear-view-caucasian-young-woman-1047408429.jpg?quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 6000w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/rear-view-caucasian-young-woman-1047408429.jpg?resize=300,200&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 300w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/rear-view-caucasian-young-woman-1047408429.jpg?resize=768,512&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 768w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/rear-view-caucasian-young-woman-1047408429.jpg?resize=1024,683&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 1024w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/rear-view-caucasian-young-woman-1047408429.jpg?resize=1536,1024&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 1536w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/rear-view-caucasian-young-woman-1047408429.jpg?resize=2048,1365&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 2048w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/rear-view-caucasian-young-woman-1047408429.jpg?resize=600,400&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 600w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/rear-view-caucasian-young-woman-1047408429.jpg?resize=878,585&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 878w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/rear-view-caucasian-young-woman-1047408429.jpg?resize=744,496&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 744w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/rear-view-caucasian-young-woman-1047408429.jpg?resize=720,480&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 720w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/rear-view-caucasian-young-woman-1047408429.jpg?resize=576,384&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 576w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/rear-view-caucasian-young-woman-1047408429.jpg?resize=457,305&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 457w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/rear-view-caucasian-young-woman-1047408429.jpg?resize=440,293&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 440w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/rear-view-caucasian-young-woman-1047408429.jpg?resize=424,282&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 424w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/rear-view-caucasian-young-woman-1047408429.jpg?resize=389,260&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 389w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/rear-view-caucasian-young-woman-1047408429.jpg?resize=360,240&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 360w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/rear-view-caucasian-young-woman-1047408429.jpg?resize=340,227&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 340w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/rear-view-caucasian-young-woman-1047408429.jpg?resize=320,213&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 320w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/rear-view-caucasian-young-woman-1047408429.jpg?resize=314,209&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 314w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/rear-view-caucasian-young-woman-1047408429.jpg?resize=306,204&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 306w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/rear-view-caucasian-young-woman-1047408429.jpg?resize=280,187&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 280w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/rear-view-caucasian-young-woman-1047408429.jpg?resize=260,174&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 260w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/rear-view-caucasian-young-woman-1047408429.jpg?resize=246,164&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 246w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/rear-view-caucasian-young-woman-1047408429.jpg?resize=234,156&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 234w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/rear-view-caucasian-young-woman-1047408429.jpg?resize=195,130&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 195w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/rear-view-caucasian-young-woman-1047408429.jpg?resize=180,120&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 180w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/rear-view-caucasian-young-woman-1047408429.jpg?resize=171,114&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 171w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/rear-view-caucasian-young-woman-1047408429.jpg?resize=160,107&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 160w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/rear-view-caucasian-young-woman-1047408429.jpg?resize=144,96&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 144w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/rear-view-caucasian-young-woman-1047408429.jpg?resize=107,71&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 107w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/rear-view-caucasian-young-woman-1047408429.jpg?resize=93,62&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 93w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/rear-view-caucasian-young-woman-1047408429.jpg?resize=84,56&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 84w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/rear-view-caucasian-young-woman-1047408429.jpg?resize=60,40&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 60w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/rear-view-caucasian-young-woman-1047408429.jpg?resize=105,70&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 105w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/rear-view-caucasian-young-woman-1047408429.jpg?resize=81,54&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 81w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/rear-view-caucasian-young-woman-1047408429.jpg?resize=200,133&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 200w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/rear-view-caucasian-young-woman-1047408429.jpg?resize=231,154&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 231w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/rear-view-caucasian-young-woman-1047408429.jpg?resize=322,215&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 322w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/rear-view-caucasian-young-woman-1047408429.jpg?resize=662,441&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 662w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/rear-view-caucasian-young-woman-1047408429.jpg?resize=90,60&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 90w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/rear-view-caucasian-young-woman-1047408429.jpg?resize=120,80&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 120w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/rear-view-caucasian-young-woman-1047408429.jpg?resize=960,640&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 960w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/rear-view-caucasian-young-woman-1047408429.jpg?resize=620,413&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 620w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/rear-view-caucasian-young-woman-1047408429.jpg?resize=150,100&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 150w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/rear-view-caucasian-young-woman-1047408429.jpg?resize=1620,1080&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 1620w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/rear-view-caucasian-young-woman-1047408429.jpg?resize=50,33&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 50w" sizes="(max-width: 6000px) 100vw, 6000px"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="wp-caption-text"&gt;&lt;span&gt;People have made a warning to pet owners&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="credit"&gt;Credit: Getty&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;









&lt;p&gt;PET owners are being warned to keep a close eye on their furry friends amid fears of a potentially lethal outbreak.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Dog lovers have been placed on high alert, as authorities warn of a potentially dangerous disease.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class="single__inline-module inline-module inline-module--newsletter aligncenter inline-module--thesun wp-block-nypost-editor-newsletter" data-source-unit="Inline Newsletter Module "&gt;
	&lt;div class="inline-module__inner"&gt;
		&lt;div class="inline-module__title-wrapper"&gt;
			
							&lt;p class="inline-module__unsubmitted-title-wrapper"&gt;
											&lt;h3 class="inline-module__title headline headline--combo-sm-md"&gt;
							Sign up for &lt;span class="newsletter-name theme-main"&gt;The US Sun&lt;/span&gt; newsletter						&lt;/h3&gt;
					
									&lt;/p&gt;
			
							&lt;p class="inline-module__success-title-wrapper"&gt;
					&lt;h3 class="inline-module__title headline headline--combo-sm-md"&gt;
						Thank you!					&lt;/h3&gt;
				&lt;/p&gt;
					&lt;/div&gt;

		

	&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;


&lt;figure id="attachment_15785148" class="wp-caption alignnone aligncenter"&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" decoding="async" data-modal-image="15785148" src="https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/dog-walker-enjoying-outdoors-park-938047928_fc5689.jpg?w=960" alt="A woman walking four dogs on leashes in a park." class="alignnone size-thesun-article-image wp-image-15785148" srcset="https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/dog-walker-enjoying-outdoors-park-938047928_fc5689.jpg?quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 5472w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/dog-walker-enjoying-outdoors-park-938047928_fc5689.jpg?resize=300,200&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 300w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/dog-walker-enjoying-outdoors-park-938047928_fc5689.jpg?resize=768,512&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 768w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/dog-walker-enjoying-outdoors-park-938047928_fc5689.jpg?resize=1024,683&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 1024w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/dog-walker-enjoying-outdoors-park-938047928_fc5689.jpg?resize=1536,1024&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 1536w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/dog-walker-enjoying-outdoors-park-938047928_fc5689.jpg?resize=2048,1365&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 2048w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/dog-walker-enjoying-outdoors-park-938047928_fc5689.jpg?resize=600,400&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 600w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/dog-walker-enjoying-outdoors-park-938047928_fc5689.jpg?resize=878,585&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 878w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/dog-walker-enjoying-outdoors-park-938047928_fc5689.jpg?resize=744,496&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 744w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/dog-walker-enjoying-outdoors-park-938047928_fc5689.jpg?resize=720,480&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 720w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/dog-walker-enjoying-outdoors-park-938047928_fc5689.jpg?resize=576,384&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 576w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/dog-walker-enjoying-outdoors-park-938047928_fc5689.jpg?resize=457,305&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 457w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/dog-walker-enjoying-outdoors-park-938047928_fc5689.jpg?resize=440,293&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 440w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/dog-walker-enjoying-outdoors-park-938047928_fc5689.jpg?resize=424,282&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 424w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/dog-walker-enjoying-outdoors-park-938047928_fc5689.jpg?resize=389,260&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 389w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/dog-walker-enjoying-outdoors-park-938047928_fc5689.jpg?resize=360,240&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 360w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/dog-walker-enjoying-outdoors-park-938047928_fc5689.jpg?resize=340,227&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 340w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/dog-walker-enjoying-outdoors-park-938047928_fc5689.jpg?resize=320,213&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 320w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/dog-walker-enjoying-outdoors-park-938047928_fc5689.jpg?resize=314,209&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 314w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/dog-walker-enjoying-outdoors-park-938047928_fc5689.jpg?resize=306,204&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 306w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/dog-walker-enjoying-outdoors-park-938047928_fc5689.jpg?resize=280,187&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 280w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/dog-walker-enjoying-outdoors-park-938047928_fc5689.jpg?resize=260,174&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 260w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/dog-walker-enjoying-outdoors-park-938047928_fc5689.jpg?resize=246,164&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 246w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/dog-walker-enjoying-outdoors-park-938047928_fc5689.jpg?resize=234,156&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 234w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/dog-walker-enjoying-outdoors-park-938047928_fc5689.jpg?resize=195,130&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 195w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/dog-walker-enjoying-outdoors-park-938047928_fc5689.jpg?resize=180,120&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 180w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/dog-walker-enjoying-outdoors-park-938047928_fc5689.jpg?resize=171,114&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 171w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/dog-walker-enjoying-outdoors-park-938047928_fc5689.jpg?resize=160,107&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 160w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/dog-walker-enjoying-outdoors-park-938047928_fc5689.jpg?resize=144,96&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 144w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/dog-walker-enjoying-outdoors-park-938047928_fc5689.jpg?resize=107,71&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 107w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/dog-walker-enjoying-outdoors-park-938047928_fc5689.jpg?resize=93,62&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 93w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/dog-walker-enjoying-outdoors-park-938047928_fc5689.jpg?resize=84,56&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 84w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/dog-walker-enjoying-outdoors-park-938047928_fc5689.jpg?resize=60,40&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 60w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/dog-walker-enjoying-outdoors-park-938047928_fc5689.jpg?resize=105,70&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 105w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/dog-walker-enjoying-outdoors-park-938047928_fc5689.jpg?resize=81,54&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 81w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/dog-walker-enjoying-outdoors-park-938047928_fc5689.jpg?resize=200,133&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 200w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/dog-walker-enjoying-outdoors-park-938047928_fc5689.jpg?resize=231,154&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 231w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/dog-walker-enjoying-outdoors-park-938047928_fc5689.jpg?resize=322,215&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 322w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/dog-walker-enjoying-outdoors-park-938047928_fc5689.jpg?resize=662,441&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 662w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/dog-walker-enjoying-outdoors-park-938047928_fc5689.jpg?resize=90,60&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 90w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/dog-walker-enjoying-outdoors-park-938047928_fc5689.jpg?resize=120,80&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 120w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/dog-walker-enjoying-outdoors-park-938047928_fc5689.jpg?resize=960,640&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 960w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/dog-walker-enjoying-outdoors-park-938047928_fc5689.jpg?resize=620,413&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 620w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/dog-walker-enjoying-outdoors-park-938047928_fc5689.jpg?resize=150,100&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 150w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/dog-walker-enjoying-outdoors-park-938047928_fc5689.jpg?resize=1620,1080&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 1620w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/dog-walker-enjoying-outdoors-park-938047928_fc5689.jpg?resize=50,33&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 50w" sizes="(max-width: 960px) 100vw, 960px"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="wp-caption-text"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Dog lovers have been told to be wary with their pets while on walks and out in public&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="credit"&gt;Credit: Getty&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;


&lt;p&gt;The public &lt;a href="https://www.the-sun.com/topic/health/"&gt;health&lt;/a&gt; emergency warning has been made in the &lt;a href="https://www.the-sun.com/topic/san-francisco/"&gt;San Francisco&lt;/a&gt; Bay Area and relates to a deadly &lt;a href="https://www.the-sun.com/topic/bacteria/"&gt;bacteria&lt;/a&gt; which has been reported in the area.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Officials in Berkeley, &lt;a href="https://www.the-sun.com/topic/california/"&gt;California&lt;/a&gt; say there has been a detection of leptospirosis – a potentially deadly bacterial disease which is transmitted by rats.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;It was found in a homeless encampment in the area, leading to health officials setting out a warning to locals.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The alert was issued by local health authorities and warned of the risks for dogs being walked, and residents.&lt;/p&gt;
		
		&lt;p class="article-readmore__content-clear"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

		


&lt;p&gt;Experts say recent rain has created favorable conditions for bacteria to thrive and be passed around.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="outstream" class="nuk-ad-placeholder"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Officials discovered strains of leptospirosis among multiple rats and say there have so far been at least two cases of dogs being infected after being walked near the Harrison Street encampment, located by Codornices Creek. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“Dogs are particularly at risk because they tend not to avoid puddles of water in the same way that humans do,” Dr Monica Gandhi, an infectious disease physician at UCSF told &lt;a href="https://www.sfgate.com/bayarea/article/berkeley-dangerous-bacterial-disease-21299405.php" rel="nofollow" data-nyp-affiliate="true"&gt;SFGATE&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;She also explained it cannot be spread from human to human, so it is animals who are most at risk from the outbreak.&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;p&gt;Humans can however pick it up from contaminated puddles and soil. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Leptospirosis is caused by leptospira bacteria, which is most commonly known to be spread through the urine of infected animals, mainly rats.&lt;/p&gt;


		&lt;div class="article-boxout"&gt;
			&lt;p class="article-boxout__header theme__background-color"&gt;
				&lt;h3 class="article-boxout__headline"&gt;What is Leptospirosis?&lt;/h3&gt;
			&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;div class="article-boxout__content theme__background-color-rgba-20"&gt;
				
									&lt;p class="article-boxout__content__intro"&gt;
						LEPTOSPIROSIS is caused by leptospira bacteria, which is most commonly known to be spread through the urine of infected animals, mainly rats.					&lt;/p&gt;
				
				&lt;div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The urine then contaminates soil and stagnant water and can spread to other animals.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Officials say there have been no human cases reported as yet, and are warning people to be wary. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The disease poses significant dangers to both animals and people if contaminated.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
		


&lt;p&gt;The urine then contaminates soil and stagnant water and can spread to other animals.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Officials say there have been no human cases reported as yet, and are warning people to be wary. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The disease poses significant dangers to both animals and people if contaminated.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The infections come primarily when contaminated water or soil comes into contact with cuts, eyes, the mouth, or mucous membranes. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;According to the city, the “combination of warm &lt;a href="https://www.the-sun.com/topic/weather-1/"&gt;weather&lt;/a&gt; followed by recent storms” has created “optimal conditions for the bacteria’s survival and transmission.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The bacteria can persist in soil or water for up to a month, increasing the risk of more infections long after the initial contamination.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;City officials have designated the Harrison Street area as a ‘red zone’ and advise people and &lt;a href="https://www.the-sun.com/topic/pets/"&gt;pets&lt;/a&gt; to stay at least a third of a mile away.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;A clean up operation is currently underway focussing on “water clean up, rat eradication, and public safety measures.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Environmental testing in the area is ongoing, and officials are calling on pet owners to vaccinate their animals against leptospirosis. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;But it is not just dogs at risk.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Owners of cats who are allowed free reign are also encouraged to consider vaccination, while all pet owners should prevent animals from drinking potentially contaminated water.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Other rules have also come into force to protect dogs further.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;If caught leaving their &lt;a href="https://www.the-sun.com/topic/dogs/"&gt;dogs&lt;/a&gt; outside in the harsh &lt;a href="https://www.the-sun.com/topic/winter/"&gt;winter&lt;/a&gt; weather, owners have been warned they could be hit with jail time and &lt;a href="https://www.the-sun.com/news/15725493/january-pet-laws-pennsylvania-california-new-jersey/"&gt;fines up to $1,000&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Certain parts of the &lt;a href="https://www.the-sun.com/where/united-states/"&gt;United States&lt;/a&gt; are set to record some of their lowest temperatures for the winter so far over the &lt;a href="https://www.the-sun.com/topic/next/"&gt;next&lt;/a&gt; few days.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Akron, &lt;a href="https://www.the-sun.com/where/ohio/"&gt;Ohio&lt;/a&gt; is one such area set to experience single-digit temperatures dropping to double-digit negatives with wind chill.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Likewise, pet owners are being reminded by local &lt;a href="https://www.the-sun.com/topic/police/"&gt;police&lt;/a&gt; to bring their animals inside or risk serious consequences.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;If found guilty of neglecting an animal, which can include leaving them outside in extremely cold temperatures such as those imminently coming, owners can be found guilty of a misdemeanor in the first degree.&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;figure id="attachment_15799399" class="wp-caption alignnone aligncenter"&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" decoding="async" data-modal-image="15799399" src="https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/rear-view-caucasian-young-woman-1047408429.jpg?w=960" alt="Rear view of a young woman hugging her dog" class="alignnone size-thesun-article-image wp-image-15799399" srcset="https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/rear-view-caucasian-young-woman-1047408429.jpg?quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 6000w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/rear-view-caucasian-young-woman-1047408429.jpg?resize=300,200&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 300w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/rear-view-caucasian-young-woman-1047408429.jpg?resize=768,512&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 768w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/rear-view-caucasian-young-woman-1047408429.jpg?resize=1024,683&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 1024w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/rear-view-caucasian-young-woman-1047408429.jpg?resize=1536,1024&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 1536w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/rear-view-caucasian-young-woman-1047408429.jpg?resize=2048,1365&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 2048w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/rear-view-caucasian-young-woman-1047408429.jpg?resize=600,400&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 600w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/rear-view-caucasian-young-woman-1047408429.jpg?resize=878,585&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 878w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/rear-view-caucasian-young-woman-1047408429.jpg?resize=744,496&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 744w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/rear-view-caucasian-young-woman-1047408429.jpg?resize=720,480&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 720w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/rear-view-caucasian-young-woman-1047408429.jpg?resize=576,384&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 576w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/rear-view-caucasian-young-woman-1047408429.jpg?resize=457,305&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 457w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/rear-view-caucasian-young-woman-1047408429.jpg?resize=440,293&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 440w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/rear-view-caucasian-young-woman-1047408429.jpg?resize=424,282&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 424w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/rear-view-caucasian-young-woman-1047408429.jpg?resize=389,260&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 389w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/rear-view-caucasian-young-woman-1047408429.jpg?resize=360,240&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 360w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/rear-view-caucasian-young-woman-1047408429.jpg?resize=340,227&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 340w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/rear-view-caucasian-young-woman-1047408429.jpg?resize=320,213&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 320w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/rear-view-caucasian-young-woman-1047408429.jpg?resize=314,209&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 314w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/rear-view-caucasian-young-woman-1047408429.jpg?resize=306,204&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 306w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/rear-view-caucasian-young-woman-1047408429.jpg?resize=280,187&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 280w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/rear-view-caucasian-young-woman-1047408429.jpg?resize=260,174&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 260w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/rear-view-caucasian-young-woman-1047408429.jpg?resize=246,164&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 246w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/rear-view-caucasian-young-woman-1047408429.jpg?resize=234,156&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 234w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/rear-view-caucasian-young-woman-1047408429.jpg?resize=195,130&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 195w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/rear-view-caucasian-young-woman-1047408429.jpg?resize=180,120&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 180w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/rear-view-caucasian-young-woman-1047408429.jpg?resize=171,114&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 171w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/rear-view-caucasian-young-woman-1047408429.jpg?resize=160,107&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 160w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/rear-view-caucasian-young-woman-1047408429.jpg?resize=144,96&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 144w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/rear-view-caucasian-young-woman-1047408429.jpg?resize=107,71&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 107w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/rear-view-caucasian-young-woman-1047408429.jpg?resize=93,62&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 93w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/rear-view-caucasian-young-woman-1047408429.jpg?resize=84,56&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 84w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/rear-view-caucasian-young-woman-1047408429.jpg?resize=60,40&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 60w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/rear-view-caucasian-young-woman-1047408429.jpg?resize=105,70&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 105w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/rear-view-caucasian-young-woman-1047408429.jpg?resize=81,54&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 81w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/rear-view-caucasian-young-woman-1047408429.jpg?resize=200,133&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 200w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/rear-view-caucasian-young-woman-1047408429.jpg?resize=231,154&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 231w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/rear-view-caucasian-young-woman-1047408429.jpg?resize=322,215&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 322w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/rear-view-caucasian-young-woman-1047408429.jpg?resize=662,441&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 662w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/rear-view-caucasian-young-woman-1047408429.jpg?resize=90,60&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 90w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/rear-view-caucasian-young-woman-1047408429.jpg?resize=120,80&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 120w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/rear-view-caucasian-young-woman-1047408429.jpg?resize=960,640&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 960w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/rear-view-caucasian-young-woman-1047408429.jpg?resize=620,413&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 620w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/rear-view-caucasian-young-woman-1047408429.jpg?resize=150,100&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 150w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/rear-view-caucasian-young-woman-1047408429.jpg?resize=1620,1080&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 1620w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2026/01/rear-view-caucasian-young-woman-1047408429.jpg?resize=50,33&amp;amp;quality=90&amp;amp;strip=all 50w" sizes="(max-width: 960px) 100vw, 960px"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="wp-caption-text"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Pet owners have been warned to keep a close eye on their dogs&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="credit"&gt;Credit: Getty&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;						&lt;/div&gt;
						
													&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The US Sun</author><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 15:25:26 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMic0FVX3lxTE1FTnFkRDl0bHZSc3R4dmRpN21zdGFQYlhFUnBjRjRUdFgwR2cwdzYwZ1lfaXdVYUgtcGxaSmZXblNBa1B0dWNvYTBWZk9DSEdjQUFNLWd0QzhoRE9BdHozUDNhTXI4SkRSZVd1a3JpZUhwNFk</guid></item><item><title>一些免疫系统可以战胜癌症。这会变成毒品吗？ -《纽约时报》</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2026/01/22/health/lung-cancer-antibodies-immune-system.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The New York Times</author><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 14:46:32 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiwFBVV95cUxOMlBadWR6MmhsMzlRSEVZWEFkOUI2aUpyeVdnZTl3OXdJUHNrSFMyR2EyVHItRjFnR1NDbElYRFlEb0xuTXB2SWRsVkF6U01XZm1mek1xZm1Md1g5ZHNGUlZER1k3bTZBTWd1LXdRRlVoX05JNjNablhzakdlVmJaVkxSQU5LMVE0V0x3</guid></item><item><title>新研究直接将较高的体重指数与血管性痴呆风险增加联系起来；血压可能有助于解释原因- ABC新闻</title><link>https://abcnews.go.com/Health/new-study-directly-links-higher-bmi-increased-risk/story?id=129421387</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="xvlfx ZRifP TKoO eaKKC EcdEg bOdfO qXhdi NFNeu UyHES " data-testid="prism-article-body"&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao MvWXB TjIXL aGjvy ebVHC "&gt;High blood pressure and body mass index, or BMI, may be directly linked to the increased risk of developing vascular dementia, according to a new study published in the Journal of Clinical Endocrinology and Metabolism.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;This is the strongest evidence to date showing a direct relationship between BMI and the increased risk of developing vascular dementia, a risk heavily influenced by elevated blood pressure, according to the study.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Researchers say these findings highlight how important reducing these risk factors are to help prevent this form of dementia and protect brain health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;The study's findings show that being overweight and having high blood pressure "are direct causes of increased vascular dementia risk," said Dr. Ruth Frikke-Schmidt, study co-author, chief physician at Copenhagen University Hospital -- Rigshospitalet and clinical professor at University of Copenhagen, Denmark.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;"That makes them highly actionable targets for dementia prevention at the population level," Frikke-Schmidt told ABC News.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Vascular dementia is a type of dementia caused by damage to blood vessels that leads to reduced blood and oxygen to the brain, according to the &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://www.nhlbi.nih.gov/health/vascular-dementia" target="_blank" dir="ltr"&gt;National Heart, Blood and Lung Institute&lt;/a&gt;. The initial damage to blood vessels leading to this condition is often due to other underlying health problems such as high blood pressure, atherosclerosis, or diabetes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Symptoms vary depending on the affected brain area but often include confusion, memory problems and difficulty with daily activities. There is no cure, making prevention key, experts say.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;In the study, researchers analyzed data from large European populations across Copenhagen and the United Kingdom. Using analytical methods that mimic a randomized controlled trial, the researchers found that as BMI increased by approximately 4.5 points, the risk of vascular dementia rose across all BMIs, directly linking BMI to an increased risk of developing vascular dementia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Additional analysis showed that elevated blood pressure, in association with BMI, directly contributed to increased risk of vascular dementia, adding to a growing body of evidence strongly linking cardiovascular health to brain function.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;"What is good for the heart is good for the brain," Frikke-Schmidt said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;BMI is a measure of a person's body weight relative to their height. While doctors say the number should be taken in context with an individual's overall health, the &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://www.cdc.gov/bmi/adult-calculator/bmi-categories.html" target="_blank" dir="ltr"&gt;Centers for Disease Control and Prevention&lt;/a&gt; categorizes an ideal BMI as 18.5 to 24 for adults. Overweight and obesity are categorized as a BMI 25-29 and BMI 30 or greater, respectively.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Dr. Leah Croll, assistant professor of neurology at the SUNY Downstate Health Sciences University, told ABC News many dementia cases may be preventable, and this new research adds to evidence showing how important targeting risk factors like elevated BMI and cardiovascular disease are to preserving brain health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;"Dementia prevention is the wave of the future," Croll said. Adding that it's important to reinforce or develop habits to maintain a healthy weight and manage blood pressure through diet, exercise, and routine medical care.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;While some people may be more motivated to lose weight, Croll said that blood pressure is a silent symptom that can be easier to ignore or may often go unnoticed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;"A paper like this really allows me to have conversations with my patients in the clinic where I can motivate them to stay on top of their blood pressure," Croll said. "If you can stay on top of your blood pressure, that seems to significantly impact your brain health later on in life."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Dr. Jennifer Miao, a board-certified cardiologist and ABC News Medical Unit fellow, told ABC News it's important for people to monitor their blood pressure and should know how to measure it and know what the numbers mean.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;"This can be done at a local pharmacy, urgent care or walk-in clinic, community health centers or by purchasing a blood pressure cuff to use at home," Miao said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Blood pressure contains two numbers -- a systolic number on the top and a diastolic number on the bottom. Normal blood pressure is less than 120 on the top and less than 80 on the bottom, according to the &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="" target="_blank" dir="ltr"&gt;American Heart Association&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;"If left untreated, high blood pressure can have significant and harmful effects on overall health," Miao said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;&lt;em class=" "&gt;Camille Charles, DO, is a pediatric resident and member of the ABC News Medical Unit. Jade A. Cobern, MD, MPH, is a practicing physician, board-certified in pediatrics and general preventive medicine, and is a fellow of the ABC News Medical Unit.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ABC News</author><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 14:15:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMioAFBVV95cUxNdGtCV2czeDd5Q2FSM1RzUG83c1JFX01Yd19rRWZvZlFPNnVMMVNNMlZmSVhuWmp3Wm84aHNQOUpPcXZQclQzdFNwd0dCMkpTcDNmdWpDSGVwVTR0RmFDV2ZONGpkdFRRZ29tTXZwMzBOamVMS01pMzUwUU5WQ294WHNBLTAwcGR6QTBlZkZ2Rm9PMUpTdzlTNmYwY3dPajJl</guid></item><item><title>任何服用维生素D的人都会对四种症状发出警告- tyla.com</title><link>https://www.tyla.com/life/vitamin-d-warning-over-consumption-626061-20260122</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;In recent years, NHS doctors have shed increasing light on the ways that Vitamin D can be used to boost a person's wellbeing - especially during the cold, dark winter months.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;Apparently, however, anyone hoping to secure the ultimate &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.tyla.com/beauty"&gt;'glow-up'&lt;/a&gt; this year, or hoping to improve their general &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.tyla.com/health"&gt;health&lt;/a&gt;, needs to approach these currently viral supplements with caution.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;The warning comes in light of four symptoms having reportedly emerged among some patients who've been prescribed these pills, that are said indicate a person's body isn't taking to them very well, or &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.tyla.com/life/pharmacist-warning-vitamin-d-supplements-923470-20250924"&gt;that they're consuming too much.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="floating-video-player_container__u4D9_"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;For those unfamiliar with the benefits of Vitamin D, this specific nutrient is famed for its ability to regulate the amount of calcium and phosphate in the body, which are both vital when it comes to maintaining healthy bones, teeth, and muscle health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="article-image_articleImage__eyzAn"&gt;&lt;cite class="image-credit_imageCredit__YMlqS"&gt;Vitamin D predominantly comes from the sun (Getty Stock Image)&lt;/cite&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;It also wards off bone deformities, like rickets, as well as painful conditions, including osteomalacia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;The easiest way to soak up this nutrient is from the sun, which poses quite the issue for anyone living in the northern hemisphere, with sunlight being something or a rarity between October and March.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;As such, many are turning to Vitamin D supplements to up for the nutrition they're missing out on over the winter, with the British government recommending &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.tyla.com/uk-news"&gt;UK&lt;/a&gt; residents taking a daily vitamin of 10mg during this period.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;"From October to March we can’t make enough vitamin D from sunlight, so to keep bones and muscles healthy, it’s best to take a daily 10 microgram supplement of vitamin D," a spokesperson for the &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.tyla.com/nhs"&gt;NHS&lt;/a&gt; emphasised recently. "You can get vitamin D from most pharmacies and retailers."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;As we say, however, many medics have recently argued that this shouldn't be a blanket rule, claiming some patients have reported experiencing four indicators that the supplements are having adverse effects on their health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="article-image_articleImage__eyzAn"&gt;&lt;cite class="image-credit_imageCredit__YMlqS"&gt;Switching up your dosage might be advised (Getty Stock Images)&lt;/cite&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;Biomedical scientist Tobias Mapulanga explained: "As the NHS encourages vitamin D in winter, many people are reaching for bottles in the darker months and accidentally overshooting, then blaming the fallout on seasonal bugs, when constant thirst and needing the loo more often, queasiness, tummy pain or constipation, headaches or brain fog, and new aches or cramps appear soon after increasing your intake or adding sprays or gummies, that points to a supplement backfiring.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;"The stakes are clear: the right amount supports you, but doubling up can turn a well-meant routine into feeling worse rather than better."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Constantly needing a wee, but still feeling thirsty&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;If you find some weeks after starting to take Vitamin D supplements that you're needing to urinate more often, and constantly feel thirsty, it could be an indictor that you're taking too much then you need.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;This is because Vitamin D has the potential to disrupt both fluid and salt balance, which came leave a person both parched, but needing the loo.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;It is recommended in these cases, to take absolutely no more than the prescribed 10mg, and to always keep water close by.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="article-image_articleImage__eyzAn"&gt;&lt;cite class="image-credit_imageCredit__YMlqS"&gt;Vitamin D can cause extreme thirst (Getty Stock Images)&lt;/cite&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Feeling nauseous&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;Enduring general sickness, burping more than you usually would, or suffering from a sour stomach could also be a sign that something is wrong.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;This could be because some variations of Vitamin D could contain sweeteners or flavourings that throw off a person's stomach acid levels, and trigger irritation. It's recommended in these cases to either take your supplement with a main meal, and switch from taking sprays of gummies to tablets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Achy bones and muscles&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;If you notice you're cramping more often, or just feeling generally much more fatigued that usual, it could be a sign that Vitamin D supplements aren't for you. An excessive amount of this nutrient can upset the minerals that your muscles rely on, and this, mixed with potential dehydration, could cause muscles to cramp.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;It's recommended to adjust your amount in these cases, as well as to drink a large glass of water with meals, and add things like yoghurt, leafy greens, beans and bananas into your diet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="article-image_articleImage__eyzAn"&gt;&lt;cite class="image-credit_imageCredit__YMlqS"&gt;Too much Vitamin D can cause aches and pains (Getty Stock Images)&lt;/cite&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Struggling to focus&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;Has your brain felt foggier than usual since you started taking Vitamin D supplements? If so, again, it could indicate you've taken too much.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;High doses of this specific nutrient can cause a person's calcium levels to surge, with additives like sweeteners also having the potential to muddle their thinking. In these cases, it is recommended that a person takes their pill with food, or to choose a product listing only cholecalciferol as a bulking agent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>tyla.com</author><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 14:03:42 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiggFBVV95cUxPYjNlUUpOZVBCMXRJR01kQm9FWXpubGs0MzBWbVd6a2MwaWhWNnB0ZF9oTlBIU3I1QW1EUTZXMG5Mcjk3eTdwUFMxcXB5T2hJbVhteTktTmNiRVplN2VyQ1BaRHhveTAwd25sa0RDSTRLWUdxeE9ILS1uVTNlQ216Y2FB</guid></item><item><title>研究发现，推动睾丸激素测试的“Manosphere”影响者正在说服健康的年轻人，他们有问题-卫报</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/society/2026/jan/22/manosphere-influencers-testosterone-tests-young-men</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body-commercial-selector article-body-viewer-selector dcr-hdpgoq"&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“If you’re not waking up in the morning with a boner, there’s a large possibility that you have low testosterone levels,” an influencer on TikTok with more than 100,000 followers warns his viewers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Despite screening for low testosterone being medically unwarranted in most young men, this group is being aggressively targeted online by influencers and wellness companies promoting hormone tests and treatments as essential to being a “real man”, a study published in the journal Social Science and Medicine has found.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="sign-in-gate"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Researchers analysed 46 high-impact posts about low testosterone and testing made by TikTok and Instagram accounts with a combined following of more than 6.8 million, to examine how masculinity and men’s health are being depicted and monetised online.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="4dde43ac-b3ef-42bb-bb66-44fb1419ccf8" data-spacefinder-role="richLink" data-spacefinder-type="model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.RichLinkBlockElement" class="dcr-47fhrn"&gt;&lt;gu-island name="RichLinkComponent" priority="feature" deferuntil="idle" props='{"richLinkIndex":3,"element":{"_type":"model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.RichLinkBlockElement","prefix":"Related: ","text":"Social media misinformation driving men to seek unneeded NHS testosterone therapy, doctors say","elementId":"4dde43ac-b3ef-42bb-bb66-44fb1419ccf8","role":"richLink","url":"https://www.theguardian.com/society/2025/nov/08/social-media-misinformation-driving-men-to-nhs-clinics-in-search-of-testosterone-they-dont-need"},"ajaxUrl":"https://api.nextgen.guardianapps.co.uk","format":{"design":0,"display":0,"theme":0},"isInStarRatingVariant":false}'&gt;&lt;/gu-island&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The lead author of the study, Emma Grundtvig Gram, a public health researcher at the University of Copenhagen, said influencers promoting routine testosterone screening often framed normal variations in energy, mood, libido or ageing “as signs of pathology”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;This meant “men may come to perceive themselves as inherently deficient or in need of medical intervention”, she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“This creates a sense of urgency for solutions, which in turn fuels lucrative markets for pharmaceuticals, supplements and medical devices, even in the absence of clear clinical benefit. More broadly, this contributes to the medicalisation of masculinity itself. It reinforces a narrow, idealised model of masculinity, while marginalising non-traditional or diverse expressions of gender.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Testosterone naturally declines with age but it is not inevitable for all men, and lower levels may also be linked to factors including type 2 diabetes, obesity, metabolic syndrome and the use of certain medications.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Gram and her colleagues found the posts often targeted younger, fit men and contained messaging aligned with the “manosphere” – online communities that circulate ideas about male superiority.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“Within this narrative, so-called ‘alpha men’ are promoted as dominant, sexually successful and physically powerful, and our study found testosterone was positioned as the key to achieving this status,” Gram said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“This connection is important because it shows that testosterone marketing is not just about health, but is embedded in wider cultural and ideological narratives about gender and power, and the manosphere is not simply an ideology, but also an industry.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Prof Ada Cheung, an endocrinologist in the University of Melbourne’s department of medicine who was not involved in the study, said routine screening for low testosterone in asymptomatic men, including younger men, was not supported by Australian guidelines.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Generally, testing is recommended only when symptoms such as delayed puberty or reduced libido are present, or in specific clinical circumstances, such as after testicular surgery or chemotherapy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Symptoms commonly attributed to low testosterone were often non-specific and overlapped with fatigue, stress, anxiety, depression and relationship difficulties, Cheung said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“This often leads to discussions about the normal range of testosterone, the limited evidence for benefit in otherwise healthy men, and the potential risks of unnecessary treatment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“It’s not hard to get testosterone on the black market or on the internet or in gyms, so many who want to try it may not seek out medical advice necessarily. Risks of unwarranted testosterone testing or treatment include masking of underlying conditions, and unnecessary exposure to side-effects.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;These can include infertility, cardiovascular risk and thickened blood.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="523d0149-d6b2-465b-a07a-8f7627ec2df8" data-spacefinder-role="richLink" data-spacefinder-type="model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.RichLinkBlockElement" class="dcr-47fhrn"&gt;&lt;gu-island name="RichLinkComponent" priority="feature" deferuntil="idle" props='{"richLinkIndex":17,"element":{"_type":"model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.RichLinkBlockElement","prefix":"Related: ","text":"Looking for Mr T: the politicisation of testosterone","elementId":"523d0149-d6b2-465b-a07a-8f7627ec2df8","role":"richLink","url":"https://www.theguardian.com/global/2019/jul/28/looking-for-mr-t-the-politicisation-of-testosterone-and-toxic-masuclinity"},"ajaxUrl":"https://api.nextgen.guardianapps.co.uk","format":{"design":0,"display":0,"theme":0},"isInStarRatingVariant":false}'&gt;&lt;/gu-island&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Gram’s study found 72% of social media posts analysed also had financial interests, such as selling testosterone tests, treatments or supplements, or were sponsored by industry. Two-thirds of posts included direct links or promo codes to purchase products.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“We found that conflicts of interest were often not readily visible to users,” Gram said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Prof Oliver Jones, a chemist and analytical scientist at RMIT University also not involved in the study, said he found it troubling how easy it was for people with no or few health qualifications to “go online, claim to know what they are talking about and then make up any old rubbish, usually to sell something, with no consequences whatsoever”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;He said a single testosterone test, assuming it was accurate, could “at best, only tell you the concentration of testosterone in your blood at the time you took the test”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“You can’t diagnose a medical condition based on one data point,” he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“The concentration of testosterone in your blood varies between individuals, at different times of the day, and can even be influenced by other health conditions. It is just a number; it requires context to make sense out of such data, which I think you can only really get from an appropriately trained medical professional.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Guardian</author><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 14:02:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMioAFBVV95cUxOWlY2bmJaUWl4OXluZWdqZkcyQ3ZkMFVfM3lYQlcyX1VXUTBLald4YmJxSUx4QngxLXREU1hIVEc5RXNlcG0wSE1HZEhpbXExb2FadGpCWkQ2b2o2UTFPc0hqcld4bms5TmRHVjdUNmhESWozdGJZMUx3cGJmQmlNREFIS09vVWJXMFY4QllnbFR5WU8zQThOdEQtWWNpaGUz</guid></item><item><title>纽约州立大学北部分校寻求一小群志愿者进行针对常见致命感染的疫苗研究- syracuse.com</title><link>https://www.syracuse.com/health/2026/01/suny-upstate-seeks-small-army-of-volunteers-for-vaccine-study-against-common-deadly-infection.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content   "&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="UXJBRTUK5NGC7JRZ7MAORPSKAQ"&gt;Syracuse, NY -- Upstate Medical University is looking for 1,000 volunteers -- &lt;a href="https://www.upstate.edu/news/articles/2026/2026-01-15-cdiff.php" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://www.upstate.edu/news/articles/2026/2026-01-15-cdiff.php"&gt;its largest clinical trial to date&lt;/a&gt; -- to test a vaccine against a deadly infection that primarily afflicts people in healthcare settings. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-1" data-gaid="inarticle-1"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="WKRUDOCOKZHBJPWKMAKLM32UVY"&gt;The effort, led by pharmaceutical giant Pfizer, is aimed at preventing bacterial infections caused by Clostridioides difficile, commonly known as c. diff. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-2" data-gaid="inarticle-2"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="U5KG2WNHQJF4NNR2CQ56MEEAAI"&gt;C. diff is most common in people who have recently had antibiotics in a hospital, nursing home or other health facility. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-3" data-gaid="inarticle-3"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="H2VRFKASVRDX7KTC6SZ72L34DU"&gt;It causes typically causes diarrhea, abdominal pain and fever. But severe cases can be deadly. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-4" data-gaid="inarticle-4"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="H5LEHF44Y5A2VLBXHPXPPPSRYQ"&gt;Roughly half a million Americans contract a C. diff infection each year, causing anywhere from &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/c-diff/media/pdfs/Cdiff-Factsheet-P.pdf" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://www.cdc.gov/c-diff/media/pdfs/Cdiff-Factsheet-P.pdf"&gt;15,000 to 50,000 deaths&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-5" data-gaid="inarticle-5"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="NV5KYU3IQZAZRHAT62IAPQQDFU"&gt;“People who need to take antibiotics for one reason or another is the greatest risk factor for C. diff,” said lead researcher, Upstate’s Dr. Stephen Thomas. “Antibiotics can disrupt the balance of good and bad bacteria in the gut and when this occurs the C. diff bacteria (bad) can rise up and cause disease.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-6" data-gaid="inarticle-6"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="I2WKPHC5QFBBHAUVCJKEO35O3Y"&gt;The Upstate Institute for Global Health is organizing the effort locally. Worldwide, the goal is to enroll 32,000 people for the study. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-7" class="middleParagraph" data-gaid="inarticle-7"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="FA3RSW6GCNH2VBDPDSUZXGE7L4"&gt;To qualify, participants must have never had C. diff and meet one of the following criteria:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-8" data-gaid="inarticle-8"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class="article__unordered-list"&gt;&lt;li id="ESFH6D3CKFHXXMQ2EL4BVUG474"&gt;&lt;span&gt;65 years or older&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li id="A4KYLT3X3FGZRBWKI7NDUY235I"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Received antibiotics in the last three months&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li id="UKCKTAMC75DGPAIXW7POIMKC6Y"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Been hospitalized at least once or had two ER visits in the last year&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li id="7HE5VCLCHZF4PIF3ROCDDH4U34"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Had 10 or more healthcare visits in the last year&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li id="6NKJDL2AXZAZRJWW3T7JDLCMPA"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Are scheduled to be hospitalized or have elective surgery&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-9" data-gaid="inarticle-9"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="7SW4HSTDRVGQTONSNFHZZ6OCUQ"&gt;Upstate researchers will be available to discuss the trial in person between 10 a.m. and 11 a.m. Thursday, Jan. 22, 2026, at the Upstate Institute for Global Health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-10" data-gaid="inarticle-10"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="J5VD5VGAKNHHLJV2KBKVDX2CGY"&gt;The institute is located at 5010 Campuswood Drive, Suite 100, East Syracuse.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-11" data-gaid="inarticle-11"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="ZLQQMHZ7QBHKPNNGDNPHQW7T3Q"&gt;Those who can attend can contact the Global Health Institute at &lt;a href="mailto:trials@upstate.edu" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;trials@upstate.edu&lt;/a&gt; or (315) 464-9869.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-12" data-gaid="inarticle-12"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-enter:RLH2ST7SBRH6HD4FJNYF5C3IXM" data-fusion-component="RLH2ST7SBRH6HD4FJNYF5C3IXM"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-exit:RLH2ST7SBRH6HD4FJNYF5C3IXM" data-fusion-component="RLH2ST7SBRH6HD4FJNYF5C3IXM"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-13" data-gaid="inarticle-13"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>syracuse.com</author><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 13:35:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi1AFBVV95cUxQQWdfZUh0UThQc2FUUF96VkN6bjhtMWRNRGRvWWJoWHpEbFY3SEpRVFpMd2RLNVNzV3JZdVJpUzY1UzdsMl9wSk5wU1N1SHAyYjdBc3UzM3pNQU5FaVdsU09RazB0ODZlREJDNHgwWldlYlFDNkxZUk8tSFVvSnFxYk9JZVVsdjR0VVpGVldoa25wVnFPNlBjTlZKSVpwY1VKYWdFN1pfcWFuaTloTDliRzdFYzNETThsOUJUZUx2ZF9NZDdSTzJtZWdjNmpXYlA5SUwyeNIB6AFBVV95cUxPQVFhY2FfSlhVeEd3QWUxVnBnWkpZYUYzaDNhOTlXSmxJYk03bWgzMVFleXItT0p0RkNQNEFzUGg1eGM0cGZXVUw3T2ZYUWZuQndKdFBJZ3FBZl9FU3EydXVObnlWRl9nNkp3c2pmb0ZTaTU2ZHBBNmV6V0RFblQ0VHc1dUt4SVNLcGppSlpYRTROX0JYZDhXTkNTdkZ6QXM0S05TRHRTWTlMcVAwRUQ5NnhVUUIyXzUtZk1pR1VCNV9ibml6eGhxZzZObUU0NnkwaWdPLXdfc3dXY3l3aGFJcGhmSEdZR2Yz</guid></item><item><title>科学家在精子中发现了一种RNA “衰老时钟” ，将年长的父亲与儿童的大脑和代谢紊乱联系起来-印度国防评论</title><link>https://indiandefencereview.com/rna-aging-clock-sperm-explain-children-older-fathers-health-risks/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content dynamic-entry-content" itemprop="text"&gt;
			
&lt;p&gt;Unlike the widely known biological clock in women, male reproductive aging has often been overlooked. Public and medical narratives have long portrayed sperm quality as relatively unaffected by age, with men sometimes fathering children into their seventies or eighties. Yet growing evidence suggests otherwise. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Children of older fathers have higher statistical chances of neurodevelopmental disorders, metabolic issues, and even stillbirth. This has prompted several fertility societies, including the American Society for Reproductive Medicine, to recommend an upper limit of 40 years for sperm donation. Until now, however, the biological mechanisms behind these risks have remained largely unexplained.&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;div class="wp-block-image"&gt;
&lt;figure class="aligncenter size-large"&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" decoding="async" src="https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/molecular-aging-cliff-in-sperm-could-explain-why-children-of-older-fathers-face-increased-health-risks-1200x727.jpg" alt="Molecular “aging Cliff” In Sperm Could Explain Why Children Of Older Fathers Face Increased Health Risks." class="wp-image-104685" srcset="https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/molecular-aging-cliff-in-sperm-could-explain-why-children-of-older-fathers-face-increased-health-risks-scaled.jpg 1200w, https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/molecular-aging-cliff-in-sperm-could-explain-why-children-of-older-fathers-face-increased-health-risks-420x255.jpg 420w, https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/molecular-aging-cliff-in-sperm-could-explain-why-children-of-older-fathers-face-increased-health-risks-520x315.jpg 520w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="wp-element-caption"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Molecular “aging cliff” in sperm could explain why children of older fathers face increased health risks – © The EMBO Journal &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Now, researchers from the University of Utah and the University of Nevada have uncovered a potential molecular explanation, published in &lt;em&gt;The EMBO Journal&lt;/em&gt;. Their findings point to a sudden and dramatic transformation in sperm RNA profiles, an internal biological signal that could serve as a marker for aging sperm and its effects on the embryo.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;The Invisible Layer of Sperm Biology&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The discovery began with a reexamination of sperm composition. For years, scientists focused almost exclusively on the DNA within sperm heads. It was known that sperm DNA becomes fragmented with age, but sperm also carry RNA, molecules that help execute genetic instructions. According to the research team, standard sequencing tools failed to detect many of these RNAs because they are chemically modified and thus invisible to conventional methods.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;To overcome this, the scientists developed PANDORA-seq, a new technique that strips away chemical disguises from RNA, revealing previously undetectable fragments. When applied to sperm from mice, the researchers uncovered a massive population of small non-coding RNAs, including transfer RNA-derived (tsRNAs) and ribosomal RNA-derived fragments (rsRNAs). These elements are not just cellular debris. As explained in &lt;a href="https://link.springer.com/article/10.1038/s44318-025-00687-8" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;the study&lt;/a&gt;, they act as regulators during early embryo development, influencing gene expression at a critical stage.&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;div class="wp-block-image"&gt;
&lt;figure class="aligncenter size-large"&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" decoding="async" src="https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/discovery-of-an-aging-cliff-in-mouse-sperm-sncrna-profiles-using-pandora-seq-1200x727.jpg" alt="Discovery Of An ‘aging Cliff’ In Mouse Sperm Sncrna Profiles Using Pandora Seq" class="wp-image-104683" srcset="https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/discovery-of-an-aging-cliff-in-mouse-sperm-sncrna-profiles-using-pandora-seq-scaled.jpg 1200w, https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/discovery-of-an-aging-cliff-in-mouse-sperm-sncrna-profiles-using-pandora-seq-420x255.jpg 420w, https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/discovery-of-an-aging-cliff-in-mouse-sperm-sncrna-profiles-using-pandora-seq-520x315.jpg 520w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="wp-element-caption"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Discovery of an ‘aging cliff’ in mouse sperm sncRNA profiles using PANDORA-seq – © The EMBO Journal&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;


&lt;p&gt;What surprised the team was not just the presence of these RNAs, but the sudden change in their profile. Between 50 and 70 weeks of age in mice, equivalent to mid-life in humans, the RNA profile of sperm shifted sharply. It wasn’t a gradual decline, but a dramatic drop, described by lead author Qi Chen as an “a&lt;em&gt;ging cliff.&lt;/em&gt;” The study found a parallel in human &lt;a href="https://indiandefencereview.com/sperm-whales-communication-unique-humans/" data-type="post" data-id="95098"&gt;sperm &lt;/a&gt;samples collected from the same donors years apart: the same lengthening of rsRNAs occurred in both species.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;A Reverse Clock Inside Sperm Cells&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Conventional wisdom suggests that aging leads to shorter, degraded molecular structures. But this study revealed the opposite. According to the authors, specific ribosomal RNAs in sperm heads actually become longer with age, not shorter. The balance shifts: more long fragments, fewer short ones. This inversion puzzled researchers.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Instead of indicating decay, the elongated RNAs may signal a breakdown in the sperm’s molecular processing system. The study suggests that oxidative stress may be damaging the enzymes responsible for trimming these RNAs to their functional lengths. As these enzymes lose efficiency, longer RNAs accumulate. This transformation could rewrite the genetic script that sperm deliver to the egg.&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;div class="wp-block-image"&gt;
&lt;figure class="aligncenter size-large"&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" decoding="async" src="https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/discovery-of-an-aging-cliff-in-mouse-sperm-sncrna-profiles-using-pandora-seq-1-1200x727.jpg" alt="Discovery Of An ‘aging Cliff’ In Mouse Sperm Sncrna Profiles Using Pandora Seq" class="wp-image-104684" srcset="https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/discovery-of-an-aging-cliff-in-mouse-sperm-sncrna-profiles-using-pandora-seq-1-scaled.jpg 1200w, https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/discovery-of-an-aging-cliff-in-mouse-sperm-sncrna-profiles-using-pandora-seq-1-420x255.jpg 420w, https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/discovery-of-an-aging-cliff-in-mouse-sperm-sncrna-profiles-using-pandora-seq-1-520x315.jpg 520w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="wp-element-caption"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Conserved age-related length shift of rsRNAs in human sperm cohorts – © The EMBO Journal&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;


&lt;p&gt;The researchers also found this change was localized. Only by isolating sperm heads, separating them from their tails, which contain high concentrations of mitochondrial RNA, ould the signal be clearly detected. As noted by Tong Zhou, a co-corresponding author of the paper, previous sequencing of whole sperm likely masked the shift, as tail RNA overwhelmed the signal from the head. The sperm head, which fuses with the egg and carries the key genetic material, holds the altered rsRNAs, making this discovery all the more significant.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Old RNAs, New Consequences for Embryos&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;To test whether these RNA changes have functional consequences, the team created a synthetic RNA cocktail. This blend mimicked the profile of sperm from older males, rich in long rsRNAs and poor in short ones. When injected into mouse embryonic stem cells, the cocktail triggered major shifts in gene activity. Specifically, it activated pathways tied to metabolism and switched on genes linked to neurodegenerative diseases like Parkinson’s and Alzheimer’s.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;These results echo previous epidemiological data that link advanced paternal age to increased risks of developmental and metabolic disorders in children. According to &lt;a href="https://attheu.utah.edu/facultystaff/scientists-discover-a-hidden-rna-aging-clock-in-human-sperm/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;the University of Utah researchers&lt;/a&gt;, this RNA-based mechanism could be a “&lt;em&gt;molecular smoking gun&lt;/em&gt;” explaining those associations. The altered RNA signals alone, without any changes to DNA, were enough to reprogram the cells.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;While current male fertility tests focus on sperm count, motility, and shape, this research suggests that RNA content may carry critical, overlooked information. James M. Hotaling, one of the study authors, pointed out that these findings could lead to future diagnostic tools to assess “&lt;em&gt;sperm RNA age&lt;/em&gt;” and refine reproductive counseling for &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC10909733/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;older fathers.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;

				&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Indian Defence Review</author><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 13:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMinwFBVV95cUxNVXctSG9xcTBQcUxnUXFDNl9MNWpLVnlNTEhTblZoX2JNd21NUVlOMTlpQ3pWNHVRdVFIV2doeUtxX28zS29QV1F3cF9RY2dUYnFpMGt1ajl3aWNial9NUzNDRDJHQm5CZlBWbHhFTzZkLWwyN2lzaVAwelRHU2RhLTdfdlZUVU5IcTFtdVlUZ2RUZ3JrZTRkWmd5dzhmb3M</guid></item><item><title>人体在两个令人惊讶的精确年龄开始分解，而且不是渐进的-银河日报</title><link>https://dailygalaxy.com/2026/01/human-body-breaks-down-at-two-precise-ages/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content dynamic-entry-content" itemprop="text"&gt;
			
&lt;p&gt;Aging has traditionally been viewed as a gradual and continuous process shaped by time, genetics, and environment. However, advances in molecular biology are challenging this assumption, revealing that physiological aging may proceed unevenly across the lifespan rather than at a constant pace.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;A multi-omics study has identified &lt;strong&gt;two distinct age ranges&lt;/strong&gt;. These inflection points suggest that aging is driven not only by accumulation, but also by disruption, with implications for how biological age is measured and how disease risk, screening strategies, and preventive interventions are approached in mid- to late adulthood.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Evidence Points to Critical Biological Turning Points&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;A team at &lt;em&gt;Stanford School of Medicine&lt;/em&gt; tracked over 135,000 biological markers in 108 individuals over several years. The study, led by Dr. Michael Snyder, chair of genetics, found that &lt;strong&gt;81 percent of molecules associated with aging changed in non-linear patterns&lt;/strong&gt;. Rather than progressing steadily, molecular activity underwent rapid shifts at two defined ages: &lt;strong&gt;44 and 60&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Published in &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s43587-024-00692-2" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Nature Aging&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;, the research focused on multi-omic datasets, including &lt;strong&gt;metabolomic, proteomic, and microbiome&lt;/strong&gt; data. It revealed significant changes in cardiovascular, immune, and metabolic functions during the identified age ranges. These included fluctuations in lipid metabolism, alcohol and caffeine processing, and markers tied to cardiovascular disease.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Biological samples were collected at regular intervals, enabling time-sensitive insights. Participants in their 40s exhibited measurable shifts in pathways associated with &lt;strong&gt;muscle maintenance&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://dailygalaxy.com/2026/01/sunburn-cause-finally-discovered-rna-damage-not-dna/" target="_blank" data-type="post" data-id="117958" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;stress response&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;, and organ function. Those in their early 60s showed altered indicators of immune system regulation, kidney filtration, and chronic inflammation.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Dr. Xiaotao Shen, a co-author, noted a high density of molecular transitions clustered around the two age markers. These did not appear in adjacent age ranges, suggesting discrete periods of elevated biological volatility.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;The Microbiome as a Core Driver&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The study placed particular emphasis on the &lt;strong&gt;human microbiome&lt;/strong&gt;, a dense microbial ecosystem primarily located in the gastrointestinal tract. Shifts in microbiome composition were strongly associated with both age thresholds. These changes are linked to key physiological processes, including nutrient absorption, immune signaling, and neurochemical production.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Researchers observed that microbial diversity and abundance changed in parallel with systemic molecular markers. This co-variation reinforces existing research suggesting the microbiome plays a role in modulating the biological aging process. Disruptions in microbial equilibrium have previously been associated with cognitive decline, inflammatory disorders, and metabolic disease.&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;div class="wp-block-image"&gt;
&lt;figure class="aligncenter size-full is-resized"&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" decoding="async" src="https://dailygalaxy.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-17.png.webp" alt="Image" class="wp-image-118245"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="wp-element-caption"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Sample collection and multi-omics data acquisition of the cohort. Four types of biological samples were collected, and 10 types of omics data were acquired. Credit: Nature Aging&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Although the study did not directly identify causality, the concurrent shifts across molecular systems and microbial ecosystems suggest a high degree of interdependence.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Behavior and Biology Intersect in Midlife&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The research also addressed the possibility that lifestyle patterns may coincide with or trigger biological inflection points. Dr. Snyder highlighted midlife behavioral trends such as increased alcohol intake and sustained stress as potential contributors to metabolic disruptions. “Alcohol metabolism may falter due to increased consumption that often occurs in midlife,” he said in an earlier interview.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;While these hypotheses remain under investigation, prior studies have linked long-term stress and poor sleep quality to deteriorating cardiovascular and immune function. The data from the Stanford study align temporally with &lt;strong&gt;life-stage transitions&lt;/strong&gt;, such as peak occupational pressure and shifts in family responsibilities, which may carry physiological consequences.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The concept of &lt;strong&gt;allostatic load&lt;/strong&gt;, referring to cumulative biological wear and tear from chronic stress, provides a theoretical framework for understanding how psychosocial factors might influence the timing of biological aging.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Limited Scope, High Resolution&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Despite its depth, the study presents several limitations. The sample size of 108 individuals restricts statistical generalizability, and the cohort was not demographically representative. Broader replication will require expanded datasets with greater ethnic, geographic, and socioeconomic diversity.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The data are observational, not interventional; as such, causality cannot be inferred. While the research identifies correlations between molecular changes and age, it does not establish whether these changes are driven by internal biological clocks, external environmental triggers, or their interaction.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Data collection also required &lt;strong&gt;frequent biospecimen analysis&lt;/strong&gt;, which may not be feasible in large-scale clinical environments. This logistical burden highlights a tension between the precision of the findings and their scalability for public health interventions.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Cost remains another barrier. Multi-omic data generation and high-resolution longitudinal tracking are resource-intensive, limiting accessibility to elite research institutions with long-term funding.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Rethinking Health Strategies for the 40s and 60s&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;If validated through further studies, these findings could influence clinical screening guidelines and reshape how midlife health risk is assessed. Current models often rely on chronological age as a proxy for physiological risk. The Stanford research proposes an alternative framework rooted in &lt;strong&gt;biological transitions&lt;/strong&gt; tied to specific life stages.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Emerging &lt;strong&gt;precision medicine initiatives&lt;/strong&gt; could incorporate molecular screening at midlife to predict susceptibility to chronic disease. Pharmaceutical development may also pivot toward therapies targeting the biological mechanisms that intensify around these identified inflection points.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The findings may be relevant for institutions developing aging-related policies, including retirement age planning, healthcare forecasting, and insurance actuarial models.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;

				&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Daily Galaxy</author><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 13:15:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigAFBVV95cUxQZzhSM3ZKN1psWjZybC1zbzc0SlpUOFNBRDc2VVl2Yy1Da1hnU3h1cXl2WGhOLUMyd1VNTnNDX0xHMXBadlRzeTh5eTRzYVZkOE9Zb1VoLTlxN2hBdExBVGYxTVV0WFhLVm9zeWE1cnhXWE16ZlR5WFNLdmhORkdQaw</guid></item><item><title>随着美国卫生部长肯尼迪的言论成为现实，疫苗制造商感到不寒而栗-路透社</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/sustainability/boards-policy-regulation/vaccine-makers-feel-chill-us-health-secretary-kennedys-rhetoric-becomes-reality-2026-01-22/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Reuters</author><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 12:31:06 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi6wFBVV95cUxPcFhTNHdaM3dZZVFjNm02TUNTQ2tSZ3k2MllWTE9hSWtRcUNMblhROG9pVlZWX21INGFWNUpBMDZMMHdhM09uUEZMTHotY05ZbTJPYXEtSzZ5WUFqYWVMMWROYUQxSm02V2tSYW9vSS0xRkxWYU5Xam5XYTNlcUpIa0pxX25ISkZEdXAtSi1YWnlhbTVOZmZLTko2OF9IX3E1VGNvOEZYcmtCUnlJTS1Nbl9FaVE5T2FRSHUxeWFEUVdpcWxSNFQwbFZGTEp6TUNjOFZvQTUzc0RfWkhXWHhWRGM1MzhjUUt4UEpF</guid></item><item><title>6种可以推翻Ozempic的新型减肥药物- Gizmodo</title><link>https://gizmodo.com/6-new-weight-loss-drugs-that-could-dethrone-ozempic-2000712002</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content prose dark:prose-invert lg:prose-xl prose-science dark:prose-science"&gt;
                &lt;p&gt;The arrival of semaglutide and similar GLP-1 drugs in recent years has ushered in a new era of obesity treatment. These drugs, which mimic the GLP-1 hormone, help people lose substantially more weight than they typically would with diet and exercise alone.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="not-prose my-8 -mx-5 xs:max-w-xs xs:mx-auto"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Semaglutide was developed by Novo Nordisk. It’s the active ingredient in the type 2 diabetes drug Ozempic and the obesity treatment Wegovy, both taken as a weekly shot. Though only Wegovy is approved for obesity, Ozempic has become the cultural shorthand for GLP-1 therapy (notably, Ozempic is often prescribed off-label for weight loss). But Ozempic’s reign on top looks to be coming to a close, if it isn’t already here.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="not-prose"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Eli Lilly’s tirzepatide (Zepbound and Mounjaro) combines GLP-1 with a second hunger-related hormone called GIP and provides greater weight loss on average than semaglutide. And there’s a bevy of GLP-1-based drugs on the horizon vying for approval, with some likely to reach the public this year. Even Novo Nordisk is looking to upgrade its products. Last December, it &lt;a href="https://gizmodo.com/the-wegovy-pill-is-officially-here-2000702882"&gt;won&lt;/a&gt; FDA approval for a once-daily pill form of Wegovy.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;So here are some of the Ozempic rivals most likely to make a splash in the world of obesity treatment in the years to come.&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;h2&gt;1. Orforglipron&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;Developed by Eli Lilly, orforglipron mimics the GLP-1 hormone. Unlike most GLP-1 drugs, however, it’s taken as a once-daily pill.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;In Phase III clinical trial data &lt;a href="https://gizmodo.com/a-pill-to-fight-obesity-is-on-the-verge-of-approval-2000648312"&gt;released&lt;/a&gt; last year, people on the highest dose of orforglipron lost, on average, 10% of their baseline body weight, compared to the 2.5% average weight loss seen in people taking a placebo. A study released last month also &lt;a href="https://gizmodo.com/eli-lillys-experimental-pill-could-help-you-ditch-glp-1-obesity-shots-trial-finds-2000701348"&gt;found&lt;/a&gt; that orforglipron could help people maintain most of the weight they lost on other GLP-1 drugs such as semaglutide or tirzepatide. Eli Lilly has since petitioned the FDA to approve orforglipron as an obesity treatment, with a decision expected sometime this spring.&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;p&gt;Should it win approval, though, orforglipron will likely face some headwinds. The drug’s effectiveness might be below that of other popular drugs on the market, including Novo Nordisk’s oral version of Wegovy, &lt;a href="https://gizmodo.com/the-wegovy-pill-is-officially-here-2000702882"&gt;approved&lt;/a&gt; late last year. But the company is banking on orforglipron having enough advantages to entice some doctors and patients.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;For starters, many may prefer a daily pill over a weekly injection, either as a first-line treatment or as maintenance therapy. And unlike the Wegovy pill, orforglipron can be used without any food or timing restrictions (oral Wegovy needs to be taken in the morning on an empty stomach, at least 30 minutes before eating, to be most effective).&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;h2&gt;2. CagriSema&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;CagriSema is a weekly injectable drug being developed by Novo Nordisk. It combines the GLP-1 mimic semaglutide with cagrilintide, which mimics another hunger-related hormone called amylin.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;In late-stage clinical trials, people taking CagriSema have lost up to 22.7% of their baseline weight over a year’s time. The company &lt;a href="https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/novo-nordisk-files-for-fda-approval-of-cagrisema-the-first-once-weekly-combination-of-glp1-and-amylin-analogues-for-weight-management-302645862.html"&gt;officially submitted&lt;/a&gt; the drug for FDA approval in late December, with a decision expected this year.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;If approved, CagriSema could arguably become the most effective GLP-1 drug currently available to the public. It would also signify that amylin-based drugs could be another viable approach to obesity treatment. At the same time, the Phase III results weren’t quite as impressive as Novo Nordisk appeared to be expecting (&lt;a href="https://www.pharmexec.com/view/novo-nordisk-cagrisema-falls-short-25-weight-loss-target-patients-obesity-overweight#:~:text=The%20results%20come,tirzepatide.2"&gt;25% or greater&lt;/a&gt; weight loss), and it will face stiff market competition from Eli Lilly’s existing drug tirzepatide, which has provided slightly lower but similar results in clinical trials.&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;h2&gt;3. VK2735&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;Eli Lilly and Novo Nordisk have dominated the landscape of GLP-1 therapy so far, but there are some competitors looking to challenge that dominance. For example, there’s Viking Therapeutics and its candidate VK2735. The drug combines GLP-1 and the hormone GIP (similar to tirzepatide) and is being developed in both an injectable and oral form.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;In the latest Phase II data &lt;a href="https://ir.vikingtherapeutics.com/2025-08-19-Viking-Therapeutics-Announces-Positive-Top-Line-Results-from-Phase-2-VENTURE-Oral-Dosing-Trial-of-VK2735-Tablet-Formulation-in-Patients-with-Obesity#:~:text=SAN%20DIEGO%2C%20Aug.,categorized%20as%20mild%20or%20moderate."&gt;released&lt;/a&gt; last August, people taking oral VK2735 lost up to 12% of their body weight over a 13-week period. Typically, it takes about six months to a year for a GLP-1 drug to reach its peak effectiveness, indicating that VK2735’s ceiling hasn’t been reached yet. That said, the drug did have a relatively high dropout rate of 28%, with most related to gastrointestinal events like vomiting. Though GI symptoms are a common side effect of GLP-1 therapy, the discontinuation rate was higher than those &lt;a href="https://www.nejm.org/doi/full/10.1056/NEJMoa2032183#:~:text=More%20participants%20in%20the%20semaglutide%20group%20than%20in%20the%20placebo%20group%20(7.0%25%20vs.%203.1%25)%20discontinued%20treatment%20owing%20to%20adverse%20events%20(mainly%20gastrointestinal%20events)%20(Table%203%20and%20Fig.%20S9)."&gt;seen&lt;/a&gt; with other GLP-1 drugs like semaglutide, so it’s at least something to keep an eye on.&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;p&gt;The company is moving forward with its development of VK2735, having &lt;a href="https://ir.vikingtherapeutics.com/2025-06-25-Viking-Therapeutics-Announces-Initiation-of-Phase-3-Obesity-Clinical-Program-with-GLP-1-GIP-Agonist-VK2735"&gt;launched&lt;/a&gt; two Phase III trials last June.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;4. MariTide&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;Another potential rival to Eli Lilly and Novo Nordisk might come from Amgen’s MariTide, short for maridebart cafraglutide.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;MariTide has some intriguing differences compared to current drugs. It’s intended to be taken as an injection once a month, as opposed to the weekly injections required by current GLP-1s. The drug also takes a different chemical approach to treating obesity. While it still mimics GLP-1 activity, it also blocks the hormone GIP, in contrast to drugs like tirzepatide and VK2735, which mimic both GLP-1 and GIP.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;So far, this alternate approach appears promising. In &lt;a href="https://www.amgen.com/newsroom/press-releases/2025/06/results-from-amgens-phase-2-obesity-study-of-monthly-maritide-presented-at-the-american-diabetes-association-85th-scientific-sessions"&gt;Phase II clinical trials&lt;/a&gt;, people with obesity have lost up to 20% of their weight over a year’s time while taking MariTide. People with type 2 diabetes also lost up to 17%, which is notable since people with diabetes typically lose substantially less weight on GLP-1 therapy than those without diabetes.&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;p&gt;Amgen is currently conducting several Phase III trials of MariTide. Should it eventually win approval, the drug could offer a more convenient option for some potential users while also illustrating that there’s more than one way to treat obesity.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;5. Retatrutide&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;Retatrutide is being developed by Eli Lilly, and it might be the most hyped experimental drug seen so far.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;In clinical trial data &lt;a href="https://gizmodo.com/eli-lillys-weight-loss-superdrug-worked-so-well-during-trials-some-quit-over-losing-too-much-2000698424"&gt;released&lt;/a&gt; last month, people with obesity and knee osteoarthritis taking retatrutide lost up to 71 pounds over 68 weeks’ time, or nearly 30% of their baseline weight. Those results appear to be the most impressive documented for any weight loss drug to date and come close to matching the average effectiveness seen with traditional bariatric surgeries. Users also experienced a substantial reduction in knee pain.&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;p&gt;Retatrutide’s effectiveness likely stems from it mimicking not one, not two, but three hormones that regulate our hunger and metabolism at once: GLP-1, GIP, and glucagon.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The drug probably isn’t going to be for everyone. Some people might simply not need or want to lose that much weight, and there is some early evidence that the drug’s side effects might be a bit more intolerable than drugs like semaglutide. Still, given the sheer potential effectiveness on display here, retatrutide could certainly become the next big thing in weight loss treatment.&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;p&gt;Eli Lilly plans to release results from other Phase III studies of retatrutide in 2026, with an FDA approval likely not too far down the road.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;6. Rejuva&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;Fractyl Health’s &lt;a href="https://www.fractyl.com/our-platforms/rejuva/"&gt;Rejuva&lt;/a&gt; isn’t as close to reaching the public as the other drugs mentioned so far. But it is the most futuristic-sounding option on the list.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;It’s an injectable gene therapy designed to boost the body’s own production of GLP-1, possibly for life. Early studies in mice have suggested that a single course of Rejuva might be able to match the benefits seen with other GLP-1-based drugs. The company also argues that Rejuva could be easier to tolerate, since the therapy would really only stimulate added production in response to food, as opposed to the high circulating levels of GLP-1 induced by drugs.&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;p&gt;The company is developing Rejuva for type 2 diabetes and obesity, with its obesity therapy intended to boost both GLP-1 and GIP production. It’s &lt;a href="https://ir.fractyl.com/news-releases/news-release-details/fractyl-health-announces-potent-preclinical-results-rjva-002"&gt;expected&lt;/a&gt; to start the first human trial of Rejuva, for people with poorly controlled diabetes, this year.&lt;/p&gt;      &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Gizmodo</author><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiigFBVV95cUxQYjBvVU96Wld5U3k0dmVOVm5RckRCcHlkRDJIajNyUTNzMU9KR2pOWDJrZTBSYUJIeTNsS05aazlvbmZiVGgtV2laUEJQZzdsSkx2VmVVdldPaXZSakRwVFV4SkE4NlhEd1d6OS1PVmJCS05LMjU4eXc2YW9CVU5DTFlBWDloZDRrdHc</guid></item><item><title>美国数据显示，许多患者在停止GLP-1后可能会减肥</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/many-patients-may-keep-off-lost-pounds-after-stopping-glp-1-us-data-suggests-2026-01-22/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Reuters</author><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:16:57 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi4gFBVV95cUxOS1U2TnJXT09pU2x5UGkxaGFWeGJMemJob0d2S2VfcVNrV1lpYVV5cWFsNnVDTkRGZGpMaTY4ZzQyNHoxaE0wV1RPUzhUQTRJak1qRHRSRUJWaUxJMWVySVBEbFNhTUVYbjBWOHhzeXdSOXh2V0Nwemd5MGJhM24wZWp2M3lSaEUtZXVNNXBjY191ZTNKSWtpcTVjQXZJRHoydVhzTDdfYWloMFpsSlF3cEJOaEwxdU1YSHRhZVJva2tWUDAxbGltbmRnUkhqVUhJS011SEJsbDBSR3FMVTFSMTRB</guid></item><item><title>并非所有的坐姿都是平等的。一种类型只是与更好的大脑健康有关。- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/not-all-sitting-is-equal-one-type-was-just-linked-to-better-brain-health</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/excessive-sitting-raises-risk-of-early-death-now-we-know-how-much"&gt;Excessive sitting&lt;/a&gt; isn't good for a person's physical or mental health, but there's a type of sedentary activity that may not &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/sitting-could-be-shrinking-your-brain-and-exercise-may-not-help"&gt;shrink our brains&lt;/a&gt; or cost our cognition to the same extent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A systematic review of 85 studies has now found good reason to differentiate between 'active' sitting, like playing cards or reading, and 'passive' sitting, like watching TV.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The former may actually boost brain health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That's probably because active sitting engages the brain, whereas passive sitting lets a person take a back seat both physically and cognitively.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/scientists-revealed-how-much-exercise-you-need-to-offset-sitting-all-day"&gt;Scientists Revealed How Much Exercise You Need to 'Offset' Sitting All Day&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Total sitting time has been shown to be related to brain health; however, sitting is often treated as a single entity, without considering the specific type of activity," &lt;a href="https://news.uq.edu.au/2026-01-not-all-sitting-same-when-it-comes-brain-health"&gt;explains&lt;/a&gt; public health researcher Paul Gardiner from the University of Queensland in Australia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Most people spend many hours sitting each day, so the type of sitting really matters … These findings show that small everyday choices – like reading instead of watching television – may help keep your brain healthier as you age."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Obviously, &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/exercise-boosts-brain-function-across-all-ages-massive-study-confirms"&gt;exercise remains incredibly important&lt;/a&gt; for cognitive health, but giving your brain a workout is also important, and that doesn't necessarily mean you have to be on your feet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_189878" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-189878" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2026/01/people_playing_cards_642.jpg" alt="three men at a table playing a card game" class="wp-image-189878 size-full" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2026/01/people_playing_cards_642.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2026/01/people_playing_cards_642-600x374.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-189878" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;'Active' sitting is better for your brain than passive forms of sitting. (&lt;a href="https://www.canva.com/photos/MAGiNppUFiI/"&gt;Drs Producoes/Getty Images/Canva&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Across numerous studies, Gardiner and colleagues found that active sitting activities, like reading, playing card games, and using a computer, showed "overwhelmingly positive associations with cognitive health, enhancing cognitive functions such as executive function, situational memory, and working memory."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Meanwhile, passive sitting was most consistently associated with negative cognitive outcomes, including increased &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/major-study-links-15-factors-to-early-dementia-risk"&gt;risk of dementia&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/castingcall?utm_source=SA_website&amp;amp;utm_medium=article&amp;amp;utm_campaign=casting_call"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2026/01/Mid-Article-Promos-Casting-Call-1-642x272.jpg" alt="Audition now for ScienceAlert's Casting Call" class="alignnone wp-image-189354 size-medium" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2026/01/Mid-Article-Promos-Casting-Call-1-642x272.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2026/01/Mid-Article-Promos-Casting-Call-1-1200x509.jpg 1200w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2026/01/Mid-Article-Promos-Casting-Call-1-768x326.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2026/01/Mid-Article-Promos-Casting-Call-1-600x255.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2026/01/Mid-Article-Promos-Casting-Call-1.jpg 1266w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The effect sizes were small but significant. The study authors hope their results will help inform future health research and more nuanced health guidance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For example, the researchers suggest guidelines should recognize the difference between passively watching TV and actively using a computer, and encourage people to take &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/exercise-snacks-throughout-your-day-have-real-health-benefits-study-finds"&gt;short breaks&lt;/a&gt; to stimulate their brains and move.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Their review focused on studies of typical sedentary activities in natural settings, rather than structured programs designed to boost brain function, making it relevant to people's everyday lives.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Health advice could shift from simply saying 'sit less' to encouraging more mentally engaging activities while sitting," &lt;a href="https://news.uq.edu.au/2026-01-not-all-sitting-same-when-it-comes-brain-health"&gt;argues&lt;/a&gt; Gardiner.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"This could help people make easy, realistic changes that support long‑term brain health and potentially reduce dementia risk."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study was published in the &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1177/13872877251394751"&gt;Journal of Alzheimer's Disease&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:00:45 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiowFBVV95cUxNWkdhZFNoeXVady1CRmlGeVgtRGhFM1dGbFVORmFCWmxGSm1hbE5zX0JnY2lUUld3QUk0Tm15cTR3Y1hOcElCRUlSMDczUU9jRVlLWXBqc1BidklISUY4T2dQQ2lLbEQ1Z19RUlBKT2w2dG1Ic05TTEFDcTk0djhyMVVSNGc1LWplWWZlNWM4VHFrS1owNFQ2eXZCbTlPSEpIa2JN</guid></item><item><title>您衰老得好吗？尝试这些简单的测试来找出答案。-《纽约时报》</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2026/01/22/well/aging-tests-longevity.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The New York Times</author><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 10:00:11 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMidEFVX3lxTE9nSHU1V0tnMVFJakt0Y2FOekZhNmVPWnc3djJsRjU5M0ZydGN1eDl6SzRtaFBaeHlpZXBQaUhkZGF2Mm5zc0pDVW5ad2RxOUxVZC02Tm1Pa2tTTW1BZXFXbDRIdVZFRlNSTThVcGh1OFZkaDVL</guid></item><item><title>美国麻疹病例的30年高位，在一个图表中- Axios</title><link>https://www.axios.com/2026/01/22/measles-cases-us-status-chart</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Axios</author><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 09:48:24 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMib0FVX3lxTFB1TWl0UkRJaHNDUnpyMEpYTHY4MUdldlZqUnhaS0h2dHVwMW5sb1dCNHRrSUIyR3VWMVp0c20wVzJ6N1Jtc0MzdXpCTUEwcmJfUnpoWFFJNTRFUWpYTF83dG5DX1lTVnJZWWxLWDMtWQ</guid></item><item><title>妊娠剧吐使我寻求绝育- BBC</title><link>https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/c9wxvre2d4xo</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article&gt;&lt;p data-component="headline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 hNbOGD"&gt;&lt;h1 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 idLnWK"&gt;I'm 26 and want to be sterilised over pregnancy sickness&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="byline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="byline" class="sc-3adb3607-0 fkltMW"&gt;&lt;span data-testid="byline-contributors" class="sc-3adb3607-12 csUdlZ"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="byline-contributors-contributor-0" class="sc-3adb3607-5 iMnQuR"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-3adb3607-7 echTHp"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-3adb3607-8 dcphMW"&gt;Kate Morgan&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-testid="byline-contributors-contributor-0-role-location" class="sc-3adb3607-9 dRohlg"&gt;Wales community correspondent&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 gtLOOD"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="hero-image" class="sc-5340b511-1 cMIbKV"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20260113-125315-2e65791d43-web-2.37.1-4/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 gUePlo hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/f6e9/live/e25b2e80-f756-11f0-aff3-fb80c79e9828.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/f6e9/live/e25b2e80-f756-11f0-aff3-fb80c79e9828.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/f6e9/live/e25b2e80-f756-11f0-aff3-fb80c79e9828.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/f6e9/live/e25b2e80-f756-11f0-aff3-fb80c79e9828.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/f6e9/live/e25b2e80-f756-11f0-aff3-fb80c79e9828.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/f6e9/live/e25b2e80-f756-11f0-aff3-fb80c79e9828.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/f6e9/live/e25b2e80-f756-11f0-aff3-fb80c79e9828.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/f6e9/live/e25b2e80-f756-11f0-aff3-fb80c79e9828.jpg.webp" loading="eager" alt="Dandelion &amp;amp; Rose Photography Chloe and her family all wear beige and stand outside in the sunshine with trees visible in the background as part of a professional family photoshoot. Chloe is visibly pregnant and holds her stomach smiling, while her partner holds their son." class="sc-5340b511-0 hLdNfA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 jVqbAn"&gt;Dandelion &amp;amp; Rose Photography&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;Chloe, pictured after she began medication for her extreme sickness, could not face another pregnancy&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;A woman who almost terminated her second pregnancy because of severe sickness says sterilisation is now her best option due to difficulties accessing treatment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Chloe, 26, said she couldn't face another pregnancy because of &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.nhs.uk/pregnancy/complications/severe-vomiting/" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;hyperemesis gravidarum&lt;/a&gt; (HG), which causes prolonged severe nausea and vomiting that may last until birth.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Plaid Cymru MS Lindsay Whittle has called for better access to Xonvea - an anti-sickness medication which is not routinely available in Wales.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The Welsh government said it recognised the debilitating impact extreme pregnancy sickness can have, which is why healthcare professionals can prescribe a range of treatments, including Xonvea in certain cases.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Chloe, from Newport, was admitted to hospital with dehydration early in her first pregnancy, when she had never even heard of HG.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"I literally spent the whole of my first trimester in bed on ice cubes, because I couldn't eat or drink," she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 gXrNRM"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 cMIbKV"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20260113-125315-2e65791d43-web-2.37.1-4/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 gUePlo hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/a3cd/live/29b04a40-f757-11f0-aff3-fb80c79e9828.png.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/a3cd/live/29b04a40-f757-11f0-aff3-fb80c79e9828.png.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/a3cd/live/29b04a40-f757-11f0-aff3-fb80c79e9828.png.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/a3cd/live/29b04a40-f757-11f0-aff3-fb80c79e9828.png.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/a3cd/live/29b04a40-f757-11f0-aff3-fb80c79e9828.png.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/a3cd/live/29b04a40-f757-11f0-aff3-fb80c79e9828.png.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/a3cd/live/29b04a40-f757-11f0-aff3-fb80c79e9828.png.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/a3cd/live/29b04a40-f757-11f0-aff3-fb80c79e9828.png.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Chloe Chloe sits on a grey and cream rug with her daughter who is playing with colourful stacking cups and looking over at the camera, wearing a knitted beige jumper and leggings with a floral pattern. Chloe is wearing a black and white dress with a black cardigan, smiling down at her daughter." class="sc-5340b511-0 hLdNfA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 jVqbAn"&gt;Chloe&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;Chloe was so unwell during her pregnancies she was not able to look after herself&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"I struggled to shower, my partner would sometimes have to bathe me; I physically could not care for myself."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Chloe was given reduced duties at work until her son was born in 2023 and the sickness stopped.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;As a result of her difficult pregnancy, Chloe did not want a second child, but fell pregnant unplanned.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"I remember when I found out I literally turned around to my partner and I was like, 'what do we do?'" she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 gXrNRM"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 cMIbKV"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20260113-125315-2e65791d43-web-2.37.1-4/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 gUePlo hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/bab3/live/4301c410-f757-11f0-aff3-fb80c79e9828.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/bab3/live/4301c410-f757-11f0-aff3-fb80c79e9828.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/bab3/live/4301c410-f757-11f0-aff3-fb80c79e9828.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/bab3/live/4301c410-f757-11f0-aff3-fb80c79e9828.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/bab3/live/4301c410-f757-11f0-aff3-fb80c79e9828.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/bab3/live/4301c410-f757-11f0-aff3-fb80c79e9828.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/bab3/live/4301c410-f757-11f0-aff3-fb80c79e9828.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/bab3/live/4301c410-f757-11f0-aff3-fb80c79e9828.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Chloe Chloe, a woman with light brown hair and clear rimmed glasses, sits with her daughter as a newborn baby lying on her and wearing a pink dress with frills." class="sc-5340b511-0 hLdNfA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 jVqbAn"&gt;Chloe&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;Chloe says she had never even heard of HG until her first hospital admission&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Chloe, a toddler and baby sleep coach, said her mental health deteriorated and she was unable to take her antidepressants due to the severe sickness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"It got to the point that I had an abortion booked for her because I was unable to care for myself and my son, and I literally said to my partner 'I'm worried about my own safety'."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;But an &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.nhs.uk/conditions/ectopic-pregnancy/" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;ectopic pregnancy&lt;/a&gt; scare meant she saw a gynaecologist who was able to prescribe xonvea.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The medicine is recommended as an effective first line treatment by the Royal College of Obstetricians and Gynaecologists, alongside alternatives such as &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.nhs.uk/medicines/cyclizine/about-cyclizine/" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;cyclizine&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.nhs.uk/medicines/prochlorperazine/" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;prochlorperazine&lt;/a&gt; and ondansetron, which are regularly prescribed by doctors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;One box of 20 tablets of xonvea costs £28.50, considerably higher than other alternatives.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;It is not routinely available in Wales but can be prescribed when other treatments have failed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The most recent data showed that 223 prescriptions for xonvea were issued by 103 GP practices in October.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;Chloe said she has learned to cherish Daisy more because of the difficult journey they had been through&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Chloe said it helped change her journey and she felt well enough to cancel her termination.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"At the start, it just meant that I was able to take my antidepressants, which then helped level my mood. I was able to eat a little piece of toast. And then as time went on and my hormones started to settle, I was then able to eat a proper meal," she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The mother-of-two said she was now in the process of arranging a sterilisation, unable to face another pregnancy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 hNbOGD"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 gXmhTb"&gt;How common is hyperemesis gravidarum?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;According to NHS Wales, about one to three of every 100 pregnant women get HG, although it may go unreported.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The symptoms include severe nausea, vomiting, dehydration and weight loss, with people often needing hospital treatment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;Dr Forbes said facilitating terminations for much-wanted pregnancies was heartbreaking for patients as well as staff&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Dr Georgina Forbes, a specialist doctor in sexual and reproductive health, said she knew from her own experience how devastating HG can be for patients.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;She said: "My experience is that women were coming for abortions and had not actually been able to access that drug freely or were struggling to get it, and by the time they come to me, they are entirely at their wits' end. They are broken."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Forbes, who is chair of the College of Sexual and Reproductive Healthcare's Wales committee, called for the Welsh government to reconsider the decision on xonvea, dismissing concerns about its cost.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"If you consider the cost every time a woman is hospitalised, that is going to be hundreds, if not thousands of pounds, depending on how long they stay, how many bags of IV fluid they need, how many other medications. So that's just the cost to health care," she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Whittle added constituents had written to him detailing "heart-wrenching" stories of living with HG, along with his experience supporting one woman's campaign for better access to the drug in his role on the Senedd's petitions committee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"It's less than the price of a meal out in an average restaurant, and that's not silly money, is it?" he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"And if that's all it costs, then quite frankly, let's just get on with the job that we're supposed to be doing here in Wales."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;In response, the Welsh government said: "GPs in every health board area in Wales regularly prescribe xonvea."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;It added it relies on independent advice from &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.nice.org.uk/" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;Nice&lt;/a&gt; or the All-Wales Medicines Strategy (AWMSG) group to make medicines routinely available on the NHS.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"Without formal Nice guidance, AWMSG's appraisal remains the most current formal evaluation of xonvea in Wales.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"This did not recommend routine use due to insufficient cost-effectiveness data," a spokesperson said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The AWMSG said it had been "proactively engaging with the manufacturer for over 18 months and are actively exploring the options available to them".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BBC</author><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 06:08:15 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiWkFVX3lxTE51NGF4aHQxek1Ec3VSRXlDZVpQRy1EQjh3aDh4UDE2bW1aWWFqZEl2TWRTY3BVSEJ6MjhQbGpuZmxScWR0ZDItMThJcHBFY0MzOTVuWDVNLVBxd9IBX0FVX3lxTFBLZUhLcjV2a2ZVTUVVa0lhQ2hndm5VRUNZZkZfX0lOSlQxdTMwZjdYdzlqYVZETkczU0NrbTJKc2kzMnQ0NDQwN3FnSXFiVTNBb3N6bUhnM1NFWVdIbklr</guid></item><item><title>天然化合物可能是预防肝病的关键- SciTechDaily</title><link>https://scitechdaily.com/naturally-occurring-compound-may-hold-key-to-preventing-liver-disease/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>SciTechDaily</author><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 05:02:07 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimwFBVV95cUxOWlhjNzUwalpNUHA4YlhPMDVRMV96aFIzSmVhT2RwVnMzVlBhMFRMa0ZBUjV4QXRxN3FkQkZYYnlSSDR6ZkNVejFMcFlFWjJYRUFSQy0wbEQtVURaR19lZjNnQmNRSGdtc2NhWEdCQm9RVWZvTGJxOTNYb0JUYWVad3lxOFpzeW11dmpJcnk3WDVWYlNhNktyVnFkaw</guid></item><item><title>我问物理治疗师如何缓解背部疼痛，她建议进行这三个练习，以帮助恢复臀部、核心和上背部的平衡- Fit&amp;Well</title><link>https://www.fitandwell.com/exercise/flexibility/i-asked-a-physical-therapist-how-to-alleviate-a-sore-back-and-she-recommended-these-three-exercises-to-help-restore-balance-between-the-hips-core-and-upper-back</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="article-body" class="article__body "&gt;

&lt;p id="54db06bd-144a-4021-ba74-99c206902cda"&gt;Are you suffering from a sore back, mild discomfort or even chronic back pain? There could be a number of reasons why it’s happening.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="ad-unit-1" class="ad-unit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Physical therapist and director of &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://ptcentral.org/%20%20https://www.linkedin.com/in/devin-vassella/%20%20https://www.facebook.com/PTCentralOK/%20%20DevinVTrachman" target="_blank" data-url="https://ptcentral.org/%20%20https://www.linkedin.com/in/devin-vassella/%20%20https://www.facebook.com/PTCentralOK/%20%20DevinVTrachman" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none" data-mrf-recirculation="inline-link"&gt;Physical Therapy Central&lt;/a&gt; Devin Trachman explains that standing or sitting in prolonged positions or repetitive muscle use can overload the spine and surrounding tissues.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a id="elk-seasonal" data-url="" href="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p id="54db06bd-144a-4021-ba74-99c206902cda-2"&gt;“If you sit slouched with a forward-head posture, this increases the load on the neck and spine dramatically,” she says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The further forward your head gets, the harder the muscles of the neck and upper back have to work to keep your head up. “This leads to more fatigue, tightness and pain.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="ad-unit-2" class="ad-unit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Similarly, if you stand with locked knees or your weight shifted onto one leg, you are adding extra stress to your lower back instead of distributing it through the hips and legs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“This can lead to aching, compression in the lower back and muscular fatigue,” she says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But there is something you can do to fix these issues. “Give your spine the combination of variety, support and strength—and you will see that pain will most likely begin to improve,” says Trachman.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div id="slice-container-newsletterForm-articleInbodyContent-sRnywJexXiXzTezeUitTN9" class="slice-container newsletter-inbodyContent-slice newsletterForm-articleInbodyContent-sRnywJexXiXzTezeUitTN9 slice-container-newsletterForm"&gt;&lt;div data-hydrate="true" class="newsletter-form__wrapper newsletter-form__wrapper--inbodyContent"&gt;&lt;div class="newsletter-form__container"&gt;&lt;section class="newsletter-form__main-section"&gt;&lt;p class="newsletter-form__strapline"&gt;Start your week with achievable workout ideas, health tips and wellbeing advice in your inbox.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;She suggests trying the following three exercises to encourage your hips, core and upper body to do their proper share of the work to keep you upright.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a id="elk-1-wall-angel" data-url="" href="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;h2 class="article-body__section" id="section-1-wall-angel"&gt;&lt;span&gt;1. Wall angel&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;div class="youtube-video youtube-facade" data-nosnippet id="1UU4VvklQ44"&gt;
&lt;div class="video-aspect-box"&gt;
&lt;div class="watch-on-iframe-1UU4VvklQ44" data-yt-video-token="1UU4VvklQ44" title="How to Perform Wall Angel for Tight Upper Back - YouTube"&gt;
&lt;span class="youtube-video-title"&gt;How to Perform Wall Angel for Tight Upper Back - YouTube&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;img src="https://img.youtube.com/vi/1UU4VvklQ44/maxresdefault.jpg" alt="How to Perform Wall Angel for Tight Upper Back - YouTube" data-aspect-ratio="16/9" loading="lazy"&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;svg class="play-button" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 234.67 165.33"&gt;&lt;path fill="red" d="M229.763 25.817c-2.699-10.162-10.65-18.165-20.748-20.881C190.716 0 117.333 0 117.333 0S43.951 0 25.651 4.936C15.553 7.652 7.6 15.655 4.903 25.817 0 44.236 0 82.667 0 82.667s0 38.429 4.903 56.85C7.6 149.68 15.553 157.681 25.65 160.4c18.3 4.934 91.682 4.934 91.682 4.934s73.383 0 91.682-4.934c10.098-2.718 18.049-10.72 20.748-20.882 4.904-18.421 4.904-56.85 4.904-56.85s0-38.431-4.904-56.85"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path fill="#fff" d="m93.333 117.559 61.333-34.89-61.333-34.894z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;
&lt;a class="watch-on-youtube-1UU4VvklQ44" href="https://youtu.be/1UU4VvklQ44" target="_blank" data-url="https://youtu.be/1UU4VvklQ44" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;Watch On &lt;svg class="youtube-logo" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 507.9 113.39"&gt;&lt;g fill="#fff"&gt;&lt;path d="M64.792 80.99V32.396l42.082 24.297zm93.803-63.285a20.285 20.285 0 0 0-14.32-14.32C131.642 0 80.99 0 80.99 0S30.337 0 17.705 3.385a20.286 20.286 0 0 0-14.32 14.32C0 30.338 0 56.693 0 56.693S0 83.049 3.385 95.68A20.285 20.285 0 0 0 17.705 110c12.632 3.386 63.285 3.386 63.285 3.386s50.652 0 63.285-3.386a20.284 20.284 0 0 0 14.32-14.32c3.385-12.632 3.385-38.988 3.385-38.988s0-26.355-3.385-38.988m94.473 74.326c.887-2.314 1.332-6.098 1.332-11.35V58.556c0-5.097-.445-8.822-1.332-11.178-.888-2.355-2.452-3.533-4.69-3.533-2.163 0-3.69 1.178-4.577 3.533-.888 2.356-1.332 6.081-1.332 11.178V80.68c0 5.25.424 9.035 1.275 11.35.848 2.318 2.392 3.475 4.633 3.475 2.239 0 3.803-1.157 4.691-3.475zm-17.953 11.122c-3.207-2.16-5.486-5.52-6.835-10.079-1.352-4.554-2.027-10.617-2.027-18.185v-10.31c0-7.644.771-13.784 2.316-18.417 1.544-4.633 3.956-8.011 7.24-10.135 3.282-2.123 7.587-3.186 12.916-3.186 5.251 0 9.459 1.082 12.626 3.243 3.165 2.162 5.482 5.542 6.95 10.136 1.466 4.595 2.2 10.715 2.2 18.36v10.31c0 7.567-.714 13.65-2.142 18.243-1.43 4.595-3.747 7.955-6.951 10.077-3.205 2.124-7.548 3.186-13.03 3.186-5.64 0-10.06-1.082-13.263-3.243m248.053-57.981c-.81 1.005-1.352 2.646-1.621 4.923-.272 2.278-.404 5.734-.404 10.367v5.097h11.697V60.46c0-4.555-.155-8.011-.463-10.367-.309-2.355-.868-4.014-1.678-4.98-.812-.966-2.067-1.449-3.766-1.449-1.7 0-2.954.503-3.765 1.506zm-2.025 29.886v3.591c0 4.557.132 7.974.404 10.251.269 2.279.828 3.94 1.68 4.982.849 1.041 2.16 1.564 3.938 1.564 2.392 0 4.035-.927 4.923-2.781.887-1.853 1.37-4.942 1.447-9.268l13.785.812c.077.62.116 1.469.116 2.548 0 6.565-1.795 11.47-5.387 14.712-3.589 3.242-8.669 4.865-15.232 4.865-7.876 0-13.398-2.47-16.564-7.414-3.168-4.94-4.75-12.586-4.75-22.935V63.589c0-10.657 1.641-18.436 4.924-23.342 3.281-4.903 8.9-7.355 16.854-7.355 5.482 0 9.691 1.004 12.626 3.012 2.933 2.01 5 5.137 6.197 9.383 1.197 4.247 1.796 10.117 1.796 17.607v12.163h-26.757m-284.953-1.33-18.187-65.68h15.869l6.37 29.77c1.623 7.339 2.82 13.594 3.591 18.766h.464c.54-3.706 1.738-9.922 3.591-18.65l6.603-29.886h15.869l-18.417 65.68v31.51h-15.754v-31.51M322.115 34.23v71.007h-12.511l-1.39-8.688h-.347c-3.399 6.564-8.496 9.845-15.291 9.845-4.71 0-8.185-1.543-10.425-4.633-2.24-3.087-3.359-7.915-3.359-14.48V34.23h15.985v52.126c0 3.168.348 5.426 1.043 6.776.695 1.353 1.853 2.027 3.475 2.027 1.39 0 2.722-.423 3.996-1.275 1.274-.849 2.22-1.928 2.838-3.241V34.229h15.986m81.995.001v71.007h-12.511l-1.391-8.688h-.345c-3.402 6.564-8.498 9.845-15.292 9.845-4.711 0-8.186-1.543-10.426-4.633-2.24-3.087-3.358-7.915-3.358-14.48V34.23h15.985v52.126c0 3.168.347 5.426 1.041 6.776.696 1.353 1.855 2.027 3.476 2.027 1.391 0 2.723-.423 3.996-1.275 1.275-.849 2.22-1.928 2.839-3.241V34.229h15.985"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="M365.552 20.908h-15.87v84.329h-15.637v-84.33h-15.869V8.05h47.376v12.858m76.811 53.636c0 5.174-.215 9.229-.639 12.162-.424 2.937-1.139 5.021-2.143 6.255-1.004 1.236-2.357 1.854-4.053 1.854a7.404 7.404 0 0 1-3.65-.927c-1.12-.618-2.026-1.544-2.722-2.78V50.796c.54-1.93 1.467-3.513 2.78-4.749 1.313-1.234 2.74-1.853 4.285-1.853 1.623 0 2.876.637 3.766 1.91.886 1.275 1.505 3.418 1.853 6.43.348 3.011.523 7.297.523 12.857zm14.652-28.964c-.967-4.478-2.531-7.721-4.692-9.73-2.163-2.007-5.136-3.011-8.919-3.011-2.935 0-5.676.83-8.224 2.49a16.926 16.926 0 0 0-5.908 6.545h-.117l.001-37.416h-15.405v100.777h13.204l1.622-6.717h.347c1.235 2.393 3.088 4.285 5.56 5.675 2.47 1.39 5.213 2.085 8.225 2.085 5.404 0 9.382-2.491 11.931-7.471 2.548-4.982 3.823-12.76 3.823-23.341V64.23c0-7.953-.484-14.17-1.448-18.65"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/g&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p id="d532cd11-68df-48d4-8397-fb92cadff068"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sets: &lt;/strong&gt;2 &lt;strong&gt;Reps: &lt;/strong&gt;10&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul id="e07d9914-2001-4f94-92d6-42519823e995"&gt;&lt;li&gt;Stand with your head, shoulders, lower back and hips against a wall, with a slight bend in your knees.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Raise your arms to the sides, with your elbows at shoulder height and bent to 90°, palms facing forward and backs of your arms against the wall.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Slowly slide your hands overhead, keeping the backs of the hands, arms and shoulders in contact with the wall.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Slowly reverse the movement of your arms.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;a id="elk-2-hip-flexor-stretch" data-url="" href="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;h2 class="article-body__section" id="section-2-hip-flexor-stretch"&gt;&lt;span&gt;2. Hip flexor stretch&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;div class="youtube-video youtube-facade" data-nosnippet id="tsGPYSQbZx4"&gt;
&lt;div class="video-aspect-box"&gt;
&lt;div class="watch-on-iframe-tsGPYSQbZx4" data-yt-video-token="tsGPYSQbZx4" title="Hip Flexor Stretch Lunge Position - Ask Doctor Jo - YouTube"&gt;
&lt;span class="youtube-video-title"&gt;Hip Flexor Stretch Lunge Position - Ask Doctor Jo - YouTube&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;img src="https://img.youtube.com/vi/tsGPYSQbZx4/maxresdefault.jpg" alt="Hip Flexor Stretch Lunge Position - Ask Doctor Jo - YouTube" data-aspect-ratio="16/9" loading="lazy"&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;svg class="play-button" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 234.67 165.33"&gt;&lt;path fill="red" d="M229.763 25.817c-2.699-10.162-10.65-18.165-20.748-20.881C190.716 0 117.333 0 117.333 0S43.951 0 25.651 4.936C15.553 7.652 7.6 15.655 4.903 25.817 0 44.236 0 82.667 0 82.667s0 38.429 4.903 56.85C7.6 149.68 15.553 157.681 25.65 160.4c18.3 4.934 91.682 4.934 91.682 4.934s73.383 0 91.682-4.934c10.098-2.718 18.049-10.72 20.748-20.882 4.904-18.421 4.904-56.85 4.904-56.85s0-38.431-4.904-56.85"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path fill="#fff" d="m93.333 117.559 61.333-34.89-61.333-34.894z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;
&lt;a class="watch-on-youtube-tsGPYSQbZx4" href="https://youtu.be/tsGPYSQbZx4" target="_blank" data-url="https://youtu.be/tsGPYSQbZx4" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;Watch On &lt;svg class="youtube-logo" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 507.9 113.39"&gt;&lt;g fill="#fff"&gt;&lt;path d="M64.792 80.99V32.396l42.082 24.297zm93.803-63.285a20.285 20.285 0 0 0-14.32-14.32C131.642 0 80.99 0 80.99 0S30.337 0 17.705 3.385a20.286 20.286 0 0 0-14.32 14.32C0 30.338 0 56.693 0 56.693S0 83.049 3.385 95.68A20.285 20.285 0 0 0 17.705 110c12.632 3.386 63.285 3.386 63.285 3.386s50.652 0 63.285-3.386a20.284 20.284 0 0 0 14.32-14.32c3.385-12.632 3.385-38.988 3.385-38.988s0-26.355-3.385-38.988m94.473 74.326c.887-2.314 1.332-6.098 1.332-11.35V58.556c0-5.097-.445-8.822-1.332-11.178-.888-2.355-2.452-3.533-4.69-3.533-2.163 0-3.69 1.178-4.577 3.533-.888 2.356-1.332 6.081-1.332 11.178V80.68c0 5.25.424 9.035 1.275 11.35.848 2.318 2.392 3.475 4.633 3.475 2.239 0 3.803-1.157 4.691-3.475zm-17.953 11.122c-3.207-2.16-5.486-5.52-6.835-10.079-1.352-4.554-2.027-10.617-2.027-18.185v-10.31c0-7.644.771-13.784 2.316-18.417 1.544-4.633 3.956-8.011 7.24-10.135 3.282-2.123 7.587-3.186 12.916-3.186 5.251 0 9.459 1.082 12.626 3.243 3.165 2.162 5.482 5.542 6.95 10.136 1.466 4.595 2.2 10.715 2.2 18.36v10.31c0 7.567-.714 13.65-2.142 18.243-1.43 4.595-3.747 7.955-6.951 10.077-3.205 2.124-7.548 3.186-13.03 3.186-5.64 0-10.06-1.082-13.263-3.243m248.053-57.981c-.81 1.005-1.352 2.646-1.621 4.923-.272 2.278-.404 5.734-.404 10.367v5.097h11.697V60.46c0-4.555-.155-8.011-.463-10.367-.309-2.355-.868-4.014-1.678-4.98-.812-.966-2.067-1.449-3.766-1.449-1.7 0-2.954.503-3.765 1.506zm-2.025 29.886v3.591c0 4.557.132 7.974.404 10.251.269 2.279.828 3.94 1.68 4.982.849 1.041 2.16 1.564 3.938 1.564 2.392 0 4.035-.927 4.923-2.781.887-1.853 1.37-4.942 1.447-9.268l13.785.812c.077.62.116 1.469.116 2.548 0 6.565-1.795 11.47-5.387 14.712-3.589 3.242-8.669 4.865-15.232 4.865-7.876 0-13.398-2.47-16.564-7.414-3.168-4.94-4.75-12.586-4.75-22.935V63.589c0-10.657 1.641-18.436 4.924-23.342 3.281-4.903 8.9-7.355 16.854-7.355 5.482 0 9.691 1.004 12.626 3.012 2.933 2.01 5 5.137 6.197 9.383 1.197 4.247 1.796 10.117 1.796 17.607v12.163h-26.757m-284.953-1.33-18.187-65.68h15.869l6.37 29.77c1.623 7.339 2.82 13.594 3.591 18.766h.464c.54-3.706 1.738-9.922 3.591-18.65l6.603-29.886h15.869l-18.417 65.68v31.51h-15.754v-31.51M322.115 34.23v71.007h-12.511l-1.39-8.688h-.347c-3.399 6.564-8.496 9.845-15.291 9.845-4.71 0-8.185-1.543-10.425-4.633-2.24-3.087-3.359-7.915-3.359-14.48V34.23h15.985v52.126c0 3.168.348 5.426 1.043 6.776.695 1.353 1.853 2.027 3.475 2.027 1.39 0 2.722-.423 3.996-1.275 1.274-.849 2.22-1.928 2.838-3.241V34.229h15.986m81.995.001v71.007h-12.511l-1.391-8.688h-.345c-3.402 6.564-8.498 9.845-15.292 9.845-4.711 0-8.186-1.543-10.426-4.633-2.24-3.087-3.358-7.915-3.358-14.48V34.23h15.985v52.126c0 3.168.347 5.426 1.041 6.776.696 1.353 1.855 2.027 3.476 2.027 1.391 0 2.723-.423 3.996-1.275 1.275-.849 2.22-1.928 2.839-3.241V34.229h15.985"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="M365.552 20.908h-15.87v84.329h-15.637v-84.33h-15.869V8.05h47.376v12.858m76.811 53.636c0 5.174-.215 9.229-.639 12.162-.424 2.937-1.139 5.021-2.143 6.255-1.004 1.236-2.357 1.854-4.053 1.854a7.404 7.404 0 0 1-3.65-.927c-1.12-.618-2.026-1.544-2.722-2.78V50.796c.54-1.93 1.467-3.513 2.78-4.749 1.313-1.234 2.74-1.853 4.285-1.853 1.623 0 2.876.637 3.766 1.91.886 1.275 1.505 3.418 1.853 6.43.348 3.011.523 7.297.523 12.857zm14.652-28.964c-.967-4.478-2.531-7.721-4.692-9.73-2.163-2.007-5.136-3.011-8.919-3.011-2.935 0-5.676.83-8.224 2.49a16.926 16.926 0 0 0-5.908 6.545h-.117l.001-37.416h-15.405v100.777h13.204l1.622-6.717h.347c1.235 2.393 3.088 4.285 5.56 5.675 2.47 1.39 5.213 2.085 8.225 2.085 5.404 0 9.382-2.491 11.931-7.471 2.548-4.982 3.823-12.76 3.823-23.341V64.23c0-7.953-.484-14.17-1.448-18.65"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/g&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p id="8c3608f9-eec7-4542-8be0-16f22e5aaa47"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sets: &lt;/strong&gt;2-3 &lt;strong&gt;Time: &lt;/strong&gt;30sec each side&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul id="394d9295-968e-4046-86cb-4f5b40b4d386"&gt;&lt;li&gt;From kneeling, step your right foot forward, with your right knee bent at 90° and your right ankle directly under your right knee.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Keeping your spine straight, tuck your pelvis under slightly and shift your weight forward until you feel a stretch in the front of your left hip.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Hold for 30 seconds, repeating 2-3 times before swapping sides.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;a id="elk-3-abdominal-brace" data-url="" href="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;h2 class="article-body__section" id="section-3-abdominal-brace"&gt;&lt;span&gt;3. Abdominal brace&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;div class="youtube-video youtube-facade" data-nosnippet id="Km1yg7ltdjo"&gt;
&lt;div class="video-aspect-box"&gt;
&lt;div class="watch-on-iframe-Km1yg7ltdjo" data-yt-video-token="Km1yg7ltdjo" title="PFGP Seated Abdominal Bracing - YouTube"&gt;
&lt;span class="youtube-video-title"&gt;PFGP Seated Abdominal Bracing - YouTube&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;img src="https://img.youtube.com/vi/Km1yg7ltdjo/maxresdefault.jpg" alt="PFGP Seated Abdominal Bracing - YouTube" data-aspect-ratio="16/9" loading="lazy"&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;svg class="play-button" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 234.67 165.33"&gt;&lt;path fill="red" d="M229.763 25.817c-2.699-10.162-10.65-18.165-20.748-20.881C190.716 0 117.333 0 117.333 0S43.951 0 25.651 4.936C15.553 7.652 7.6 15.655 4.903 25.817 0 44.236 0 82.667 0 82.667s0 38.429 4.903 56.85C7.6 149.68 15.553 157.681 25.65 160.4c18.3 4.934 91.682 4.934 91.682 4.934s73.383 0 91.682-4.934c10.098-2.718 18.049-10.72 20.748-20.882 4.904-18.421 4.904-56.85 4.904-56.85s0-38.431-4.904-56.85"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path fill="#fff" d="m93.333 117.559 61.333-34.89-61.333-34.894z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;
&lt;a class="watch-on-youtube-Km1yg7ltdjo" href="https://youtu.be/Km1yg7ltdjo" target="_blank" data-url="https://youtu.be/Km1yg7ltdjo" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;Watch On &lt;svg class="youtube-logo" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 507.9 113.39"&gt;&lt;g fill="#fff"&gt;&lt;path d="M64.792 80.99V32.396l42.082 24.297zm93.803-63.285a20.285 20.285 0 0 0-14.32-14.32C131.642 0 80.99 0 80.99 0S30.337 0 17.705 3.385a20.286 20.286 0 0 0-14.32 14.32C0 30.338 0 56.693 0 56.693S0 83.049 3.385 95.68A20.285 20.285 0 0 0 17.705 110c12.632 3.386 63.285 3.386 63.285 3.386s50.652 0 63.285-3.386a20.284 20.284 0 0 0 14.32-14.32c3.385-12.632 3.385-38.988 3.385-38.988s0-26.355-3.385-38.988m94.473 74.326c.887-2.314 1.332-6.098 1.332-11.35V58.556c0-5.097-.445-8.822-1.332-11.178-.888-2.355-2.452-3.533-4.69-3.533-2.163 0-3.69 1.178-4.577 3.533-.888 2.356-1.332 6.081-1.332 11.178V80.68c0 5.25.424 9.035 1.275 11.35.848 2.318 2.392 3.475 4.633 3.475 2.239 0 3.803-1.157 4.691-3.475zm-17.953 11.122c-3.207-2.16-5.486-5.52-6.835-10.079-1.352-4.554-2.027-10.617-2.027-18.185v-10.31c0-7.644.771-13.784 2.316-18.417 1.544-4.633 3.956-8.011 7.24-10.135 3.282-2.123 7.587-3.186 12.916-3.186 5.251 0 9.459 1.082 12.626 3.243 3.165 2.162 5.482 5.542 6.95 10.136 1.466 4.595 2.2 10.715 2.2 18.36v10.31c0 7.567-.714 13.65-2.142 18.243-1.43 4.595-3.747 7.955-6.951 10.077-3.205 2.124-7.548 3.186-13.03 3.186-5.64 0-10.06-1.082-13.263-3.243m248.053-57.981c-.81 1.005-1.352 2.646-1.621 4.923-.272 2.278-.404 5.734-.404 10.367v5.097h11.697V60.46c0-4.555-.155-8.011-.463-10.367-.309-2.355-.868-4.014-1.678-4.98-.812-.966-2.067-1.449-3.766-1.449-1.7 0-2.954.503-3.765 1.506zm-2.025 29.886v3.591c0 4.557.132 7.974.404 10.251.269 2.279.828 3.94 1.68 4.982.849 1.041 2.16 1.564 3.938 1.564 2.392 0 4.035-.927 4.923-2.781.887-1.853 1.37-4.942 1.447-9.268l13.785.812c.077.62.116 1.469.116 2.548 0 6.565-1.795 11.47-5.387 14.712-3.589 3.242-8.669 4.865-15.232 4.865-7.876 0-13.398-2.47-16.564-7.414-3.168-4.94-4.75-12.586-4.75-22.935V63.589c0-10.657 1.641-18.436 4.924-23.342 3.281-4.903 8.9-7.355 16.854-7.355 5.482 0 9.691 1.004 12.626 3.012 2.933 2.01 5 5.137 6.197 9.383 1.197 4.247 1.796 10.117 1.796 17.607v12.163h-26.757m-284.953-1.33-18.187-65.68h15.869l6.37 29.77c1.623 7.339 2.82 13.594 3.591 18.766h.464c.54-3.706 1.738-9.922 3.591-18.65l6.603-29.886h15.869l-18.417 65.68v31.51h-15.754v-31.51M322.115 34.23v71.007h-12.511l-1.39-8.688h-.347c-3.399 6.564-8.496 9.845-15.291 9.845-4.71 0-8.185-1.543-10.425-4.633-2.24-3.087-3.359-7.915-3.359-14.48V34.23h15.985v52.126c0 3.168.348 5.426 1.043 6.776.695 1.353 1.853 2.027 3.475 2.027 1.39 0 2.722-.423 3.996-1.275 1.274-.849 2.22-1.928 2.838-3.241V34.229h15.986m81.995.001v71.007h-12.511l-1.391-8.688h-.345c-3.402 6.564-8.498 9.845-15.292 9.845-4.711 0-8.186-1.543-10.426-4.633-2.24-3.087-3.358-7.915-3.358-14.48V34.23h15.985v52.126c0 3.168.347 5.426 1.041 6.776.696 1.353 1.855 2.027 3.476 2.027 1.391 0 2.723-.423 3.996-1.275 1.275-.849 2.22-1.928 2.839-3.241V34.229h15.985"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="M365.552 20.908h-15.87v84.329h-15.637v-84.33h-15.869V8.05h47.376v12.858m76.811 53.636c0 5.174-.215 9.229-.639 12.162-.424 2.937-1.139 5.021-2.143 6.255-1.004 1.236-2.357 1.854-4.053 1.854a7.404 7.404 0 0 1-3.65-.927c-1.12-.618-2.026-1.544-2.722-2.78V50.796c.54-1.93 1.467-3.513 2.78-4.749 1.313-1.234 2.74-1.853 4.285-1.853 1.623 0 2.876.637 3.766 1.91.886 1.275 1.505 3.418 1.853 6.43.348 3.011.523 7.297.523 12.857zm14.652-28.964c-.967-4.478-2.531-7.721-4.692-9.73-2.163-2.007-5.136-3.011-8.919-3.011-2.935 0-5.676.83-8.224 2.49a16.926 16.926 0 0 0-5.908 6.545h-.117l.001-37.416h-15.405v100.777h13.204l1.622-6.717h.347c1.235 2.393 3.088 4.285 5.56 5.675 2.47 1.39 5.213 2.085 8.225 2.085 5.404 0 9.382-2.491 11.931-7.471 2.548-4.982 3.823-12.76 3.823-23.341V64.23c0-7.953-.484-14.17-1.448-18.65"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/g&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p id="14a18b66-c93e-4c9d-9b46-b75a31a1181d"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sets&lt;/strong&gt;: 10 &lt;strong&gt;Time&lt;/strong&gt;: 10sec&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul id="c2e860fb-43c5-4886-aa8f-26078c556c48"&gt;&lt;li&gt;Sit upright in a chair with your back straight and your feet flat on the floor.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Lightly tighten your abdominal muscles as though you are zipping up a snug pair of jeans.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Breathe normally while you maintain the brace. Hold for 10 seconds, then relax before repeating.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div id="slice-container-person-sRnywJexXiXzTezeUitTN9-ZhMgYRid0OSDCvy4qlnzvcUQUJ4LFcxT" class="slice-container person-wrapper person-sRnywJexXiXzTezeUitTN9-ZhMgYRid0OSDCvy4qlnzvcUQUJ4LFcxT slice-container-person"&gt;&lt;div class="person person--separator person--strapline"&gt;&lt;span class="person__strapline"&gt;About our expert&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="person__heading"&gt;&lt;span class="person__strapline-inline"&gt;About our expert&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="person__name-socials"&gt;&lt;span class="person__name"&gt;Dr Devin Trachman&lt;/span&gt;&lt;nav class="button-social-group person__social-buttons" aria-labelledby="button-social-group- person__social-buttons"&gt;&lt;p id="button-social-group- person__social-buttons"&gt;Social Links Navigation&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a class="button-social   " href="https://www.facebook.com/PTCentralOK/" target="_blank" aria-label="FACEBOOK"&gt;&lt;span class="button-social__icon"&gt;&lt;svg class="icon_facebook" viewbox="0 0 24 24" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"&gt;&lt;circle cx="12" cy="12" fill="#3b5998" r="12"&gt;&lt;/circle&gt;&lt;path d="M13.079 19h-2.9v-7H8.738V9.592h1.442V8.136c0-1.96.813-3.136 3.136-3.136h1.933v2.408h-1.2c-.91 0-.965.35-.965.966v1.218h2.183L15.01 12h-1.931z" fill="#fff"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a class="button-social   " href="https://www.instagram.com/devintrachman_dpt/?hl=en" target="_blank" aria-label="INSTAGRAM"&gt;&lt;span class="button-social__icon"&gt;&lt;svg class="icon_instagram" viewbox="0 0 24 24" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"&gt;&lt;circle cx="12" cy="12" fill="#de3073" r="12"&gt;&lt;/circle&gt;&lt;path d="M18.958 9.116a5.121 5.121 0 00-.336-1.708 3.557 3.557 0 00-2.044-2.044 5.12 5.12 0 00-1.694-.322C14.142 5.014 13.89 5 12 5s-2.142.014-2.884.042a5.213 5.213 0 00-1.708.322 3.665 3.665 0 00-2.044 2.044 5.213 5.213 0 00-.322 1.708C5.014 9.858 5 10.1 5 12s.014 2.142.042 2.884a5.12 5.12 0 00.322 1.694 3.44 3.44 0 00.812 1.246 3.4 3.4 0 001.232.8 5.175 5.175 0 001.708.336c.742.028.98.042 2.884.042s2.142-.014 2.884-.042a5.082 5.082 0 001.694-.336 3.456 3.456 0 002.044-2.044 5.006 5.006 0 00.336-1.694C18.986 14.142 19 13.9 19 12s-.014-2.142-.042-2.884zM17.7 14.828a3.946 3.946 0 01-.252 1.3 2.189 2.189 0 01-.518.8 2.165 2.165 0 01-.8.532 4.641 4.641 0 01-1.3.238c-.742.028-.966.042-2.828.042s-2.1-.014-2.828-.042a3.837 3.837 0 01-1.3-.252A2.258 2.258 0 016.54 16.13a3.91 3.91 0 01-.238-1.3c-.028-.742-.042-.966-.042-2.828s.014-2.086.042-2.828a3.787 3.787 0 01.238-1.3A2.445 2.445 0 017.87 6.54a3.856 3.856 0 011.3-.238c.742-.028.952-.042 2.828-.042s2.086.014 2.828.042a3.787 3.787 0 011.3.238 2.445 2.445 0 011.33 1.33 4.641 4.641 0 01.238 1.3c.027.742.042.952.042 2.828s-.011 2.088-.036 2.83zM12 8.4a3.6 3.6 0 103.6 3.6A3.6 3.6 0 0012 8.4zm.181 5.929a2.338 2.338 0 01-.362-4.662 2.43 2.43 0 01.362 0 2.338 2.338 0 010 4.662zm3.557-6.909a.84.84 0 11-.84.84.84.84 0 01.84-.838z" fill="#fff"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a class="button-social   " href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/devin-vassella/" target="_blank" aria-label="LINKEDIN"&gt;&lt;span class="button-social__icon"&gt;&lt;svg class="icon_linkedin" viewbox="0 0 24 24" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"&gt;&lt;circle cx="12" cy="12" fill="#2962ff" r="12"&gt;&lt;/circle&gt;&lt;path fill="#FFF" d="M4.98 3.5C4.98 4.881 3.87 6 2.5 6S.02 4.881.02 3.5C.02 2.12 1.13 1 2.5 1s2.48 1.12 2.48 2.5zM5 8H0v16h5V8zm7.982 0H8.014v16h4.968v-8.398c0-4.67 6.029-5.053 6.029 0V24H24V13.869c0-7.88-8.922-7.593-11.018-3.714V8z" transform="scale(.65) translate(7,4)"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a class="button-social   " href="https://ptcentral.org/" target="_blank" aria-label="WEBSITE"&gt;&lt;span class="button-social__icon button-social__icon-website"&gt;&lt;svg class="icon-website" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 1000 1000"&gt;&lt;path d="M1000 500A501 501 0 0 0 503 0h-6A501 501 0 0 0 0 500c0 275 223 499 498 500h4a501 501 0 0 0 498-500zM529 936V765h133c-31 90-79 154-133 171zM337 765h134v171c-54-17-101-81-134-171zM61 539h176a899 899 0 0 0 22 167H110a439 439 0 0 1-49-166zM471 64v191H331c31-101 82-173 140-191zm199 191H529V64c58 18 109 90 140 191zm270 226H763c-1-59-7-115-18-167h155a438 438 0 0 1 40 167zm-235 0H529V314h156a857 857 0 0 1 19 167zM471 314v167H296a859 859 0 0 1 19-167h156zM237 481H60a438 438 0 0 1 41-167h154a921 921 0 0 0-18 167zm59 58h175v167H320a837 837 0 0 1-24-166zm233 167V539h175a831 831 0 0 1-24 167H529zm234-166h176a436 436 0 0 1-49 166H741a893 893 0 0 0 22-166zm104-285H731c-20-68-47-126-81-169a443 443 0 0 1 217 169zM350 86c-33 43-61 101-81 169H133A443 443 0 0 1 350 86zM148 765h127c20 59 45 110 75 150a442 442 0 0 1-202-150zm502 150c30-39 56-91 75-150h127a442 442 0 0 1-202 150z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/nav&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;aside class="person__role"&gt;Orthopedic physical therapist&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="person__bio"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr Devin Trachman PT, DPT, MTC, OCS is a board-certified orthopedic physical therapist and clinic owner specializing in strength, mobility and injury prevention for active adults. She’s passionate about helping people move better, feel stronger, and enjoy a healthy, pain-free life well beyond their 30s and 40s.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Fit&amp;Well</author><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMisgJBVV95cUxNZ1Eycmw5SmtzaFlJZnlVQ2hRUzBfMTBoMlFSb1FoRjVGRno3QTV1cVhLaktETk1STWhOS3FvWUxDQnkwX2Y4bDhLOUZvekNXUGZmTFgxTVhQOTVVQTE1M2xnNnBTWnNERlRBMVhjcjdoVUdGUXVFekR2d0VfTDlnUnhRUVN1bTZaOHg0bUhtWVZnQlZ6bFRtWW5Rc0FkTVNsWFZxOWQtTHRiSnEzVmVHbzNOLXBUcjZ3d2kwUVFUajVzanlTX2ZQcjhXY2VrclNYcmptV3l4cmsxNGl1djlVMDdFNll1cU9FVEthRld3VmQzUEFrUDN5SWJYM1JsQk9ieVZHenB4RmxrUmUzU1NmeDNHRHZuYm5FWl85aVNaZ0Jpc0FWQlJSN2NRTVZDVHZYNHc</guid></item><item><title>由于美国即将失去无麻疹地位， RFK Jr.的新CDC副手淡化了其重要性- CBS新闻</title><link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/measles-elimination-rfk-jr-cdc-deputy-downplays/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;section class="content__body"&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;After a year of ongoing &lt;span class="link"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/news/united-states-measles-outbreak-south-carolina-elimination/" target="_blank" data-invalid-url-rewritten-http=""&gt;measles outbreaks&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; that have sickened more than &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/measles/data-research/index.html" rel="nofollow noopener"&gt;2,400 people&lt;/a&gt;, the United States is poised to lose its status as a measles-free country. However, the newly appointed principal deputy director at the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention, Ralph Abraham, said he was unbothered by the prospect at a briefing for journalists this week.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It's just the cost of doing business with our borders being somewhat porous for global and international travel," Abraham said. "We have these communities that choose to be unvaccinated. That's their personal freedom."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Infections from other countries, however, accounted for only &lt;a href="https://publichealth.jhu.edu/ivac/resources/us-measles-tracker" rel="nofollow noopener"&gt;about 10%&lt;/a&gt; of measles cases detected since Jan. 20, 2025, the official start of the deadly measles outbreak in West Texas, which spread to other states and Mexico. The rest were acquired domestically. This marks a change since the U.S. eliminated measles in 2000. Measles occasionally popped up in the U.S. from people infected abroad, but the cases rarely sparked outbreaks, because of extremely high rates of vaccination. Two doses of the measles, mumps, and rubella vaccine strongly &lt;span class="link"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/news/how-many-lives-vaccines-have-saved/" target="_blank" data-invalid-url-rewritten-http=""&gt;prevent infection&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; and halt the virus's spread.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To maintain its measles elimination status, the U.S. must prove that the virus has not circulated continuously in the nation for a year, between Jan. 20, 2025, and Jan. 20, 2026. To answer the question, &lt;a href="https://kffhealthnews.org/news/article/measles-virus-outbreak-spread-genomic-analysis-elimination-status-cdc-rfk-us/" rel="nofollow noopener"&gt;scientists are examining&lt;/a&gt; whether the major outbreaks in &lt;span class="link"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/news/united-states-measles-outbreak-south-carolina-elimination/" target="_blank" data-invalid-url-rewritten-http=""&gt;South Carolina&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;, Utah, Arizona, and Texas were linked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Health officials confirmed that the main measles virus strain in each of these outbreaks is D8-9171. But because this strain also occurs in Canada and Mexico, CDC scientists are now analyzing the entire genomes of measles viruses — about 16,000 genetic letters long — to see whether those in the United States are more closely related to one another than to those in different countries.&lt;/p&gt;

    
    &lt;p id="mpu-plus-outstream-middle" data-ad="mpu-plus-outstream-middle" class="ad-mpu-plus-outstream-middle ad-wrapper " data-ad-unit='"mpu-plus-outstream-middle"'&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The CDC expects to complete its studies within a couple of months and make the data public. Then the Pan American Health Organization, which oversees the Americas in partnership with the World Health Organization, will decide whether the U.S. will lose its measles elimination status. And that would mean that &lt;a href="https://publichealth.jhu.edu/ivac/2025/estimating-the-financial-costs-of-measles-outbreaks" rel="nofollow noopener"&gt;costly,&lt;/a&gt; potentially deadly, and preventable measles outbreaks could become common again.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="embed__float-wrap"&gt;
    &lt;figure class="embed embed--type-image is-image embed--float-left embed--size-small" data-ads='{"extraWordCount":50}'&gt;
    
                                    
      &lt;span class="img embed__content"&gt;&lt;img src="https://assets3.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2026/01/22/48ff2e8b-955e-4901-afbb-3f7ba8bc55c6/thumbnail/620x391/b4656dbf0118576dba4f8806e470c89c/ap19218565695725.jpg#" alt="Ralph Abraham " class=" lazyload" srcset="https://assets3.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2026/01/22/48ff2e8b-955e-4901-afbb-3f7ba8bc55c6/thumbnail/620x391/b4656dbf0118576dba4f8806e470c89c/ap19218565695725.jpg 1x, https://assets3.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2026/01/22/48ff2e8b-955e-4901-afbb-3f7ba8bc55c6/thumbnail/1240x782/3044fd8cc5fba4dca07dd43ef08cda02/ap19218565695725.jpg 2x" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;

      
          &lt;figcaption class="embed__caption-container"&gt;
        
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__caption"&gt;Ralph Abraham in 2019.&lt;/span&gt;
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__credit"&gt;
            
                Michael Democker / AP

                          &lt;/span&gt;
              &lt;/figcaption&gt;
      &lt;/figure&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;"When you hear somebody like Abraham say 'the cost of doing business,' how can you be more callous," said pediatrician and vaccine specialist Paul Offit, in an &lt;a href="https://rasmussenretorts.substack.com/p/one-year-in-how-the-trump-administration?utm_source=live-stream-redirect&amp;amp;triedRedirect=true" rel="nofollow noopener"&gt;online discussion&lt;/a&gt; hosted by the health blog &lt;a href="https://insidemedicine.substack.com/p/one-year-in-how-the-trump-administration" rel="nofollow noopener"&gt;Inside Medicine&lt;/a&gt; on Jan. 20. "Three people died of measles last year in this country," Offit added. "We eliminated this virus in the year 2000 — eliminated it. Eliminated circulation of the most contagious human infection. That was something to be proud of."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Abraham said vaccination remains the most effective way to prevent measles but that parents must have the freedom to decide whether to vaccinate their children. Several states have loosened school vaccine requirements since 2020, and &lt;span class="link"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/news/vaccination-rate-decline-measles-polio-outbreaks/" target="_blank" data-invalid-url-rewritten-http=""&gt;vaccine rates&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.kff.org/medicaid/kindergarten-routine-vaccination-rates-continue-to-decline/" rel="nofollow noopener"&gt;have dropped&lt;/a&gt;. A record rate of kindergartners, representing about &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/schoolvaxview/data/index.html" rel="nofollow noopener"&gt;138,000 children,&lt;/a&gt; obtained &lt;span class="link"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/news/vaccination-rates-kindergarteners-fall-exemptions-rise/" target="_blank" data-invalid-url-rewritten-http=""&gt;vaccine exemptions&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; for the 2024-25 school year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Information on vaccines has been muddied by Health and Human Services Secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr., who previously founded an anti-vaccine organization. He has undermined vaccines throughout his tenure. On national television, he has repeated scientifically debunked rumors that vaccines may cause &lt;a href="https://kffhealthnews.org/news/article/trump-autism-announcement-rfk-tylenol-pregnancy-vaccines/" rel="nofollow noopener"&gt;autism&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.factcheck.org/2025/03/rfk-jr-misleads-about-measles-vaccine-in-hannity-interview/" rel="nofollow noopener"&gt;brain swelling, and death&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

    
    
    &lt;p id="mpu-flex-inc3" data-ad="mpu-flex-inc" class="ad-mpu-flex-inc ad-wrapper " data-ad-unit='["mpu-flex-inc",3]'&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jennifer Nuzzo, director of the Pandemic Center at Brown University, disparaged the Trump administration's focus on finding genetic technicalities that may spare the country's measles-free status. "This is the wrong thing to pay attention to. Our attention has to be on stopping the outbreaks," she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"If we keep our status, it should be because we have stopped the spread of measles," she said. "It's like they're trying to be graded on a curve."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Trump administration &lt;a href="https://kffhealthnews.org/news/article/texas-measles-outbreak-cdc-vaccines-rfk-trump/" rel="nofollow noopener"&gt;impeded the CDC's ability&lt;/a&gt; to assist West Texas during the first critical weeks of its outbreak and &lt;a href="https://kffhealthnews.org/news/article/russell-vought-trump-omb-doge-public-health-budget-shutdown/" rel="nofollow noopener"&gt;slowed the release&lt;/a&gt; of federal emergency funds, according to KFF Health News investigations. However, the agency stepped up its activity last year, providing local health departments with measles vaccines, communication materials, and testing. Abraham said HHS would give South Carolina $1.5 million to respond to its outbreak, which began nearly four months ago and had reached 646 cases as of Jan. 20.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If the CDC's genomic analyses show that last year's outbreaks resulted from separate introductions from abroad, political appointees will probably credit Kennedy for saving the country's status, said Demetre Daskalakis, a former director of the CDC's national immunization center, who &lt;span class="link"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/news/senior-cdc-officials-resign-after-monarez-ouster-cite-concerns-over-scientific-independence/" target="_blank" data-invalid-url-rewritten-http=""&gt;resigned in protest&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; of Kennedy's actions in August.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And if studies suggest the outbreaks are linked, Daskalakis predicted, the administration will cast doubt on the findings and downplay the reversal of the country's status: "They'll say, who cares."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Indeed, at the briefing, Abraham told a &lt;a href="https://www.statnews.com/2026/01/20/cdc-measles-briefing-lost-elimination-status-cost-of-doing-business/" rel="nofollow noopener"&gt;reporter from Stat&lt;/a&gt; that a reversal in the nation's status would not be significant: "Losing elimination status does not mean that the measles would be widespread."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Data shows otherwise. Case counts last year were the highest since 1991, before the government enacted vaccine policies to ensure that all children could be protected with measles immunization.&lt;/p&gt;

    
    
    &lt;p id="mpu-flex-inc4" data-ad="mpu-flex-inc" class="ad-mpu-flex-inc ad-wrapper " data-ad-unit='["mpu-flex-inc",4]'&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Lauren Sausser contributed reporting.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://kffhealthnews.org/about-us" rel="nofollow noopener"&gt;KFF Health News&lt;/a&gt; is a national newsroom that produces in-depth journalism about health issues and is one of the core operating programs at KFF—an independent source of health policy research, polling, and journalism. Learn more about &lt;a href="https://www.kff.org/about-us" rel="nofollow noopener"&gt;KFF&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

    

                  
        
    
  
          
  
  



  
    
    
  &lt;/section&gt;

  

  
    
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>CBS News</author><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 02:07:25 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigwFBVV95cUxNS04wWWZ2UkQ4WEZ0RWxWTVpvVXZzSVV4MmVKRGFvekktYmVoRDB1d2FDM20wRkxxal9sdGJDeEU4Y3NET3ItdzVxNC12NGF6SEZ5U0RMejJvU1NLOXR6cU1waTlHRmlON3IwVHdSLTV5WEw4VG5mdENCY05abDVDQS1za9IBiAFBVV95cUxQcndOTzVXVUV2SUtYZ2gxU2g3dHlDNzV1aGc5bmU3OF9kMExzVVd6UnBXbFNybnNDd2JHSXNOdFNmT2JBaWhYVWxJS0c4Z0hSVnRYT0kwOENDVG82R1dBTWtqdUFVZDdhd1laYTRIeGg0RlQ1bm9sR2szRnFmbmxMZXN3OU5aTE9H</guid></item><item><title>美国四分之一死亡病例背后的心脏病和中风--《纽约时报》</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2026/01/21/well/us-leading-death-cause-stroke-heart-disease.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The New York Times</author><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 01:11:28 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikgFBVV95cUxPcmQ0OGpZZU95a2Z5MkM5RmUtTmNueUlJNk03WENtdFNSOVY1NkdXNjJwQkxLZHcwdl9Ra3VwWEtVNkI3U2p2bFJ5b0tjeDJxN1gtYWQxY1AtUmpHTjhUN0x2ZWE4LUQ5TGpMc0NyTk91Nk5Ma3E1Q2tUVlJLNlhOM1h3V1VwWHo1alo2dmY4Ylh2UQ</guid></item><item><title>瑟斯顿县报告首例流感相关死亡病例急剧上升- komonews.com</title><link>https://komonews.com/news/local/thurston-county-influenza-related-death-washington-state-death-flu-related-symptoms-phss-washington-state-department-of-health-statewide-illness</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;h2 class="StoryPage_headline__AP3j8"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thurston County reports first flu-related death as state sees sharp rise in cases&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;div class="ByLineContainer_storyBylineContainer__0JNT7" id="js-Story-Byline-0"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="ByLine_storyByLineText__cze7l"&gt;by KOMO News Staff&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="ByLineContainer_storyDatelineText__yS9e8"&gt;Wed, January 21, 2026 at 4:01 PM&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="ByLineContainer_storyDatelineText__yS9e8"&gt;&lt;span class="ByLineContainer_updatedText__0D6FY"&gt;Updated &lt;/span&gt;Wed, January 21, 2026 at 8:42 PM&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;button class="UserWayButton_userWayButton__h8S9a ByLineContainer_userWayButton___vCFL"&gt;&lt;img alt="UserWay icon for accessibility widget" src="/resources/defaults/news_3.0/icons/accessibility/userway-transparent.svg"&gt;&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>komonews.com</author><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 00:04:49 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihwJBVV95cUxPcVplNklWYWNYQXZEdS1xVWJmUkxVVWhLVk5OZ0VURWJteGVXT0VJeWtHV2ptSktWNlllUWdVRmQ5SDNJMkp0M0hfU3ZSVzlLVjc2YkIwdF81d2w2RGNxRGtMN2NMYlJZbml1V0RPTndHMlB0Vk9oTndFblgxU0JGQjZMbjEzRzJzSmhiNF9UbTJKN0I0Vl91ek9NZ2hDV0JpcmlqbDh3ei1HOVE5U0UzN283akc2TzQzV3BuLWlpeXYtMGVzS2JNYUlPbEVBZTRNUy0xTnE3UFRSYlVLQzVkTEpSU1NXZWswY2tuc2dHSDVMQTRVMEVWaGZmTVBnZTNWaXRwZ0xBcw</guid></item><item><title>JoAnn Carolyn Chesser - duluthnewstribune.com</title><link>https://www.duluthnewstribune.com/obituaries/obits/joann-caroline-chesser-xqtidbnooiccncioyds0</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="RichTextArticleBody RichTextBody"&gt;
    
      &lt;p&gt;JoAnn Chesser, 89, passed away peacefully with family by her side at Diamond Willow, Proctor on January 16, 2026, after a long battle with Alzheimer’s.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
JoAnn lived a life grounded in kindness, service, and a deep commitment to her family and community. Guided by her faith and a lifelong dedication to helping others, JoAnn was deeply involved at St. Paul’s Episcopalian Church, volunteered at CHUM helped start the Rhubarb Festival, volunteered with Meals on Wheels, and was active in the Whole Foods Co-op community. Whether serving a meal, lending a hand, or sharing a warm smile, she touched countless lives through her generosity and compassion. JoAnn retired from St. Louis County as a social worker, after years of helping others.  She loved to cook and bake around the holidays. She would take the grandchildren on several camping trips where they learned all about “roughing it” and shared several stories over the campfire.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
JoAnn is preceded in death by her parents, Milton and Vivian “Lulu” Haff; her brothers, John and Bob; and her sisters, Midgie and Mary Ann. Their memories remained close to her heart throughout her life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
A devoted mother and nurturing presence, JoAnn is survived by her sons, David (Ann) Chesser and Robert (Lori) Chesser. She also held a special place in her heart for her niece and nephew, Heidi and Brian (Nikki) Cagle, whom she helped raise and loved as her own.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
JoAnn also leaves behind her sisters Sally, Judy and Lonetta, her sister-in-law Ann, several nieces and nephews, as well as many grandchildren and great-grandchildren, all of whom she cherished deeply. She will be remembered for her gentle spirit, humor, and unwavering love.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
Visitation will be held on Friday Jan. 30, 2026, from 10AM until the 11AM Memorial Service in St. Paul’s Episcopal Church, 1710 E. Superior St., Duluth, MN 55812.  Arrangements by Dougherty Funeral Home.  JoAnn will be buried later this spring in Cross Lake, MN.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
JoAnn will be dearly missed, but her legacy of service, family devotion, and kindness will continue to shine through the lives she touched.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
The family would like to thank the staff at Diamond Willow and Essentia Hospice for the care they gave JoAnn.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
In lieu of flowers the family asks that you make a donation in her name to The Alzheimer’s Association or Second Harvest Northland in hopes that the community will remember her as well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;
    
&lt;/div&gt;

                              
                            
                            
                            &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>duluthnewstribune.com</author><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 21:10:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimgFBVV95cUxPU1ZTY2ZaMzVlWGJ2enpkaGp1ZVZXeHFhRVpDRmJsNDV0WDgxMTZEM3BCZzhkdlFGc0ZvTWlwTHlRSVFDdEplaE1OX3FjX1BvWHUtOFBHTGN6d2xSMmI2aEpnOWRmZE9hQXBnOW41Q1RYTU0zaXh0bDVPNzBrZGNNemVTNU1HMm15RXRrY3BTemt0eWd2TTAyMHZn</guid></item><item><title>“你周围的每个人都生病了” ：冬季病毒席卷湾区- SFGATE</title><link>https://www.sfgate.com/bayarea/article/winter-viruses-bay-area-21307077.php</link><description>&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;
    
        
&lt;/body&gt;
</description><author>SFGATE</author><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 21:06:30 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigAFBVV95cUxOMFJrMHpBc0dQdk5DajlPYnF2ZFM4T2Jqajd6WENLNzROQW5mT3djeFhPcE90T0VrYm5MSTExejdjc3JQR2F5NlB1VEREUWpTRnZ6TngxLXJLa0psLXh5bUQ1WkhvUTNDUC0xYUxwUUdoZ3ZwSFdZejNsS3pvV2phTQ</guid></item><item><title>女性对饮用葡萄酒的不寻常反应导致“令人心碎”的癌症诊断- AOL.com</title><link>https://www.aol.com/articles/womans-unusual-reaction-drinking-wine-193927494.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="caas-body"&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure align-caption-with-image"&gt;&lt;div class="no-margin"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="caption-wrapper"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption-collapse"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kennedy News &amp;amp; Media&lt;/p&gt; Hollie Thursby&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;h3&gt;NEED TO KNOW&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul class="caas-list caas-list-bullet"&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hollie Thursby started experiencing unusual neck pain when she drank wine&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The 28-year-old mom of two was later diagnosed with stage 2 Hodgkin lymphoma, a type of blood cancer&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;She said pain from drinking alcohol is a little-known side effect of the disease, and now she is undergoing chemotherapy&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;A young woman discovered she had blood cancer after having a strange reaction to drinking alcohol.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In December 2024, Hollie Thursby — a 28-year-old from Sunderland, England — had just given birth to her son when she started experiencing unusual neck pain when she drank wine, she told Kennedy News and Media, via the &lt;a href="https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-15466515/Mother-two-28-struggled-neck-pain-drinking-wine-sign-deadly-cancer.html" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Daily Mail;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Daily Mail&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“After I had [my son] Jack, I'd have a couple of glasses of wine with a meal. I would get pain in my neck and behind my ear on the left side. I could have prosecco and sometimes it would hurt and sometimes it wouldn't. I could have lager and it wouldn't hurt but with wine it would really, really hurt.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Additionally, Thursby found herself feeling very itchy and exhausted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I'd been shattered for a long time,” she told the outlet. "I was unbearably tired, I would need to have a nap during the day which is not particularly normal… I complained that I was having really, really itchy skin. My legs were unbearably itchy.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure align-caption-with-image"&gt;&lt;div class="no-margin"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="caption-wrapper"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption-collapse"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kennedy News &amp;amp; Media&lt;/p&gt; Hollie Thursby&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://people.com/people-puzzler-8620185" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:The PEOPLE Puzzler crossword is here! How quickly can you solve it? Play now;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;The PEOPLE Puzzler crossword is here! How quickly can you solve it? Play now&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thursby said she thought the fatigue was simply due to her being a busy mom with a toddler and newborn baby at home. But in January 2025, she decided to see a doctor.  However, when she mentioned her symptoms, she said doctors “blamed it on her hormones.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I listened to what the GP said and obviously didn't think anything else of it,” she told the outlet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Months later, Thursby returned to her doctor after discovering a lump on her neck. They ultimately sent her for a CT scan and biopsy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In October 2025, she received the “heartbreaking” diagnosis of stage 2 Hodgkin lymphoma, a type of blood cancer. According to the &lt;a href="https://www.cancer.org/cancer/types/hodgkin-lymphoma/detection-diagnosis-staging/signs-and-symptoms.html" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:American Cancer Society;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;American Cancer Society&lt;/a&gt;, symptoms of Hodgkin lymphoma include swollen lymph nodes, which can cause pain when drinking, fever, night sweats and feelings of lethargy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“When I spoke to the blood cancer doctor, she said she's been working for 17 years and has only seen it one other time,” Thursby said. “But pain when you drink alcohol is actually a known side effect of Hodgkin lymphoma. 'It's something about the acidity in the wine and not when you drink other alcohol.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure align-caption-with-image"&gt;&lt;div class="no-margin"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="caption-wrapper"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption-collapse"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kennedy News &amp;amp; Media&lt;/p&gt; Hollie Thursby undergoing chemotherapy&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Never miss a story — sign up for &lt;a href="https://people.com/people-news-daily-newsletter-sign-up-8692701" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:PEOPLE's free daily newsletter;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;PEOPLE's free daily newsletter&lt;/a&gt; to stay up-to-date on the best of what PEOPLE has to offer​​, from celebrity news to compelling human interest stories. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In November, Thrusby, a primary school teacher, started chemotherapy to treat her cancer, which she’ll continue in the coming months. After losing her mother to a blood disorder as a child, she told the outlet she’s now worried about not being in her own children’s lives.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Not being able to look after the boys is the worst thing about it all,” she said. “I'm worried that I'm dying and that I'm going to leave them. I can't leave them without a mammy. I grew up without a mum and it was horrendous, I can't do that to the boys.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Despite the unknown, Thursby said she has a lot of support and is trying to stay optimistic now that she has a confirmed diagnosis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“We're all devastated but we all know now and we've got a treatment plan, which is what we need,” she said. “I'm just doing everything I can to get better for them. I keep telling myself this is only temporary, I just need to keep going.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Read the original article on &lt;a href="https://people.com/unusual-reaction-to-drinking-wine-leads-to-cancer-diagnosis-11889195" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:People;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;People&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>AOL.com</author><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 19:55:40 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiAFBVV95cUxQTmppSm05SVFvb2podzlHeTc3djJMOFQ3RzdZQ1JoMFZXbllESGdnQXo1RS10UmRqaVo5aU5SNlVMNUxQNlZWOHVTNlBNX1NaSWNicXEyWThGRzdTOVdkV29oeGY4V05iVWJ3dFdzN2ZJZjhKRElWeUR1cmhmQWw2cldZcXNVbU04</guid></item><item><title>女性对饮用葡萄酒的不寻常反应导致“令人心碎”的癌症诊断-雅虎新闻新加坡</title><link>https://sg.news.yahoo.com/womans-unusual-reaction-drinking-wine-193927663.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="" data-article-body="true"&gt;&lt;h3 class="mb-4 text-lg font-bold"&gt;NEED TO KNOW&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul class="mb-4"&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Hollie Thursby started experiencing unusual neck pain when she drank wine&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The 28-year-old mom of two was later diagnosed with stage 2 Hodgkin lymphoma, a type of blood cancer&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;She said pain from drinking alcohol is a little-known side effect of the disease, and now she is undergoing chemotherapy&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;A young woman discovered she had blood cancer after having a strange reaction to drinking alcohol.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;In December 2024, Hollie Thursby — a 28-year-old from Sunderland, England — had just given birth to her son when she started experiencing unusual neck pain when she drank wine, she told Kennedy News and Media, via the &lt;a href="https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-15466515/Mother-two-28-struggled-neck-pain-drinking-wine-sign-deadly-cancer.html" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Daily Mail;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;&lt;em&gt;Daily Mail&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“After I had [my son] Jack, I'd have a couple of glasses of wine with a meal. I would get pain in my neck and behind my ear on the left side. I could have prosecco and sometimes it would hurt and sometimes it wouldn't. I could have lager and it wouldn't hurt but with wine it would really, really hurt.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Additionally, Thursby found herself feeling very itchy and exhausted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“I'd been shattered for a long time,” she told the outlet. "I was unbearably tired, I would need to have a nap during the day which is not particularly normal… I complained that I was having really, really itchy skin. My legs were unbearably itchy.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="relative mb-4"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="relative text-sm mt-1 pr-2.5"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kennedy News &amp;amp; Media&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; Hollie Thursby&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://people.com/people-puzzler-8620185" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:The PEOPLE Puzzler crossword is here! How quickly can you solve it? Play now;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;The PEOPLE Puzzler crossword is here! How quickly can you solve it? Play now&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Thursby said she thought the fatigue was simply due to her being a busy mom with a toddler and newborn baby at home. But in January 2025, she decided to see a doctor.  However, when she mentioned her symptoms, she said doctors “blamed it on her hormones.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“I listened to what the GP said and obviously didn't think anything else of it,” she told the outlet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Months later, Thursby returned to her doctor after discovering a lump on her neck. They ultimately sent her for a CT scan and biopsy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;In October 2025, she received the “heartbreaking” diagnosis of stage 2 Hodgkin lymphoma, a type of blood cancer. According to the &lt;a href="https://www.cancer.org/cancer/types/hodgkin-lymphoma/detection-diagnosis-staging/signs-and-symptoms.html" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:American Cancer Society;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;American Cancer Society&lt;/a&gt;, symptoms of Hodgkin lymphoma include swollen lymph nodes, which can cause pain when drinking, fever, night sweats and feelings of lethargy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“When I spoke to the blood cancer doctor, she said she's been working for 17 years and has only seen it one other time,” Thursby said. “But pain when you drink alcohol is actually a known side effect of Hodgkin lymphoma. 'It's something about the acidity in the wine and not when you drink other alcohol.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="relative mb-4"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="relative text-sm mt-1 pr-2.5"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kennedy News &amp;amp; Media&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; Hollie Thursby undergoing chemotherapy&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Never miss a story — sign up for &lt;a href="https://people.com/people-news-daily-newsletter-sign-up-8692701" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:PEOPLE's free daily newsletter;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;PEOPLE's free daily newsletter&lt;/a&gt; to stay up-to-date on the best of what PEOPLE has to offer​​, from celebrity news to compelling human interest stories. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;In November, Thrusby, a primary school teacher, started chemotherapy to treat her cancer, which she’ll continue in the coming months. After losing her mother to a blood disorder as a child, she told the outlet she’s now worried about not being in her own children’s lives.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“Not being able to look after the boys is the worst thing about it all,” she said. “I'm worried that I'm dying and that I'm going to leave them. I can't leave them without a mammy. I grew up without a mum and it was horrendous, I can't do that to the boys.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Despite the unknown, Thursby said she has a lot of support and is trying to stay optimistic now that she has a confirmed diagnosis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“We're all devastated but we all know now and we've got a treatment plan, which is what we need,” she said. “I'm just doing everything I can to get better for them. I keep telling myself this is only temporary, I just need to keep going.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Read the original article on &lt;a href="https://people.com/unusual-reaction-to-drinking-wine-leads-to-cancer-diagnosis-11889195" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:People;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;People&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Yahoo News Singapore</author><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 19:39:27 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihAFBVV95cUxNRHdsWE13RHA0Mnl2SHhTX3paUTN5MjlGTm9LdUE4anVxeEUzOXQ5NkpMVE80ZTBnYkE0cFZUNXZUbkx3UUJIU3YyVFNkdnBGRU1DZGdzM1lCNHp6Q0RkWFppY0tEeTgtRzNOU3NEWm5hZ0VLUG56ekFVMHpfRmlPZlNWX2Q</guid></item></channel></rss>