<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>GNews Health</title><link>https://news.google.com/</link><description></description><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>是什么让地中海饮食如此健康-《华盛顿邮报》</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMilwFBVV95cUxQRXZ1V2tIWnVDUXRjNTN1RjB4a2hITHVBZXdDOUxFRG5LbGxVRXZYUHNGTEtkbVB6RWc1Y24teGRpSUM5TjRELWw0TkYwS0x1eHVNM1ZKam44UGpMeER1Nk1hQjJ1NHk1UkhJMkp2dGMzWjVZSjU4Q1JyenJHS1RVOFM0ZVgtdXZSVlZJYXdZT3oycWduSVA4?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="meteredContent grid-center"&gt;&lt;div class="teaser-content"&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="XNZZEFXJXVCDROS5UG4XQYMQVU" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.consumerreports.org/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;i&gt;Consumer Reports&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;i&gt; has no financial relationship with any advertisers on this site.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="ANJ2VRAWA5DY7ETG6KQP3OULHE" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Despite its well-deserved reputation for contributing to health problems, inflammation in small doses is actually good for our bodies. It helps fight off foreign invaders like viruses and bacteria and subsides once the threat is gone. But when inflammation doesn’t let up and becomes chronic, it can lead to the development of Type 2 diabetes, heart disease, dementia and cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-subscribe-cta" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="RHVZZF6PYJGADG7UX3FIN45GYY" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;In addition to age, a common risk factor for &lt;a href="https://www.consumerreports.org/health/medical-conditions/ways-to-reduce-inflammation-a3226961950/" target="_blank"&gt;chronic inflammation&lt;/a&gt; is a high-fat, high-sugar diet. But eating the right foods each day can help keep chronic inflammation at bay, says Vanessa King, clinical nutrition manager for the Queen’s Health System in Honolulu and a spokesperson for the Academy of Nutrition and Dietetics. And the foundation of anti-inflammatory eating? Antioxidant-rich fruits and vegetables, olive oil, whole grains, legumes, lean proteins, and food high in omega-3 fats.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="BDMGYRRJD5B2ZCZGH3TDSSEDCM" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;The Mediterranean diet emphasizes those foods and is backed by extensive research. For example, after older adults followed this plan for six months, they had lower levels of inflammatory markers in their blood, while those who followed their usual diet didn’t, according to a &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/36678237/" target="_blank"&gt;2023 study in the journal Nutrients&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-topic-follow-interstitial" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="NDS573G63VAEBOYYWMCXBOWU3I" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;It’s not hard to follow a Mediterranean-style eating plan. Here are six anti-inflammatory foods that can help you stack the odds in your favor.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="7S6G6L3RBVHCPAQG2VUYL6ZVBE" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;While fruit is always a nutritious choice, there’s evidence that cherries and &lt;a href="https://www.consumerreports.org/health/anti-aging/anti-aging-benefits-of-berries-a1160192451/" target="_blank"&gt;berries&lt;/a&gt;, in particular, can lower inflammation, thanks to an array of plant nutrients, including polyphenols and carotenoids. Eating sweet or tart &lt;a href="https://www.consumerreports.org/health/nutrition-healthy-eating/are-cherries-good-for-you-a8970252133/" target="_blank"&gt;cherries&lt;/a&gt; was linked with decreased markers of inflammation in 11 studies in a &lt;a href="https://www.mdpi.com/2072-6643/10/3/368" target="_blank"&gt;2018 research review in Nutrients&lt;/a&gt;. Those same compounds in many other berries, including cranberries, strawberries and blueberries, have been found to lower the body’s inflammatory response.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="H54M7UTXCREELCC4RK5SMVTQBU" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;To get more: Add frozen berries or cherries to your morning oatmeal or defrost and mix them with plain yogurt for sweetness without added sugar.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="34C6PBKNBJCPBJ2VFQDUXMEQPE" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;“Dark, leafy green vegetables may lower inflammation by increasing antioxidant levels,” says David Dunaief, an internist in East Setauket on Long Island and in Brooklyn Heights, N.Y., and author of a &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC8669909/" target="_blank"&gt;2019 study in the American Journal of Lifestyle Medicine&lt;/a&gt; that looked at the benefits of veggies. Antioxidants help balance unstable molecules that can damage the body’s tissues, and the decreased stress on the body leads to lower inflammation. In Dunaief’s study, eating roughly 2½ cups of dark, leafy green vegetables per day helped slash levels of C-reactive protein (CRP), a marker of bodywide inflammation, by 66 percent in about six months.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="C6M66XRDXJDBXHJI5HOE334QS4" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.consumerreports.org/health/healthy-eating/are-beans-good-for-you-a8342413430/" target="_blank"&gt;Beans and legumes&lt;/a&gt;, such as chickpeas and lentils, offer plenty of healthy protein. Their fiber and antioxidant compounds are known for helping to prevent inflammation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="KJCGSACOENHVXCZMWZCSHBLXKA" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;To get more: Try blending a cup of baby spinach into a morning smoothie, eating a kale salad with lunch and adding bok choy to your stir-fry dinner. For beans and legumes, heat up a bowl of lentil or black bean soup or blend white beans with olive oil, lemon juice and garlic for a delicious dip.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="X5NKBLHYJBE7FCIF5ELKPNMFIQ" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.consumerreports.org/health/nutrition-healthy-eating/is-olive-oil-good-for-you-a1973596216/" target="_blank"&gt;Extra-virgin olive oil&lt;/a&gt; contains several beneficial plant compounds that have anti-inflammatory effects. For example, one called &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/16136122/" target="_blank"&gt;oleocanthal&lt;/a&gt; targets the same pathways as the pain reliever ibuprofen. When you taste an olive oil that contains the compound, you’ll feel a bitter spiciness in your throat upon swallowing it. (See CR’s &lt;a href="https://www.consumerreports.org/health/cooking-oils/how-to-choose-a-good-extra-virgin-olive-oil-a8557720032/" target="_blank"&gt;olive oil ratings&lt;/a&gt;.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="6TVHRP4DF5G5HE4JQO5P7B2GYY" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;To get more: Some of the &lt;a href="https://www.consumerreports.org/health/cooking-oils/how-to-choose-a-good-extra-virgin-olive-oil-a8557720032/" target="_blank"&gt;olive oil&lt;/a&gt; you eat should be uncooked. Cooking olive oil with low levels of oleocanthal can further reduce those levels. So add uncooked oil to salad dressings or drizzle it on grilled fish or steamed vegetables.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="46VTSU4XGZA77OTJMEWLRDMXAM" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;One way the Mediterranean eating plan — and fermented foods like &lt;a href="https://www.consumerreports.org/health/yogurt/check-the-label-to-choose-a-healthy-yogurt-a6795393781/" target="_blank"&gt;yogurt&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.consumerreports.org/health/nutrition-healthy-eating/what-is-kefir-is-kefir-good-for-you-a8009668301/" target="_blank"&gt;kefir&lt;/a&gt;, in particular — can reduce inflammation is by improving the diversity and activity of gut bacteria. A &lt;a href="https://www.cell.com/cell/pdf/S0092-8674(21)00754-6.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;2021 study in the journal Cell&lt;/a&gt; found that blood levels of 19 inflammatory proteins decreased significantly in healthy adults who consumed a lot of fermented foods. (They ate an average of six servings per day for 10 weeks.) Those who were asked to eat a high-fiber diet didn’t have the same decrease in inflammatory proteins.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="YTLNISAQQRAJBMMV4NFGRA55UU" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;To get more: Have yogurt, kefir or cottage cheese (labeled “cultured” or “probiotic”) at breakfast, and sauerkraut or other pickled vegetables (look for jars labeled “fermented” or “raw” in a store’s refrigerated section) with lunch or dinner.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="EFZV7FG5GNGVTENDBOGC7P5APU" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Research suggests that eating tomatoes and tomato products may help lower inflammation. When 22 healthy men ate a serving of sofrito, a type of tomato-based sauce, their levels of two important markers of inflammation dropped, according to a &lt;a href="https://www.mdpi.com/2072-6643/11/4/851" target="_blank"&gt;2019 Spanish study in the journal Nutrients&lt;/a&gt;. Lycopene is one of the main anti-inflammatory compounds in tomatoes, and cooked tomato foods are typically the most concentrated source of the nutrient. Like some other tomato sauces, sofrito also has onions, garlic and olive oil, which are also anti-inflammatory. (See CR’s &lt;a href="https://www.consumerreports.org/health/pasta-sauce/best-jarred-pasta-sauces-a2568686470/" target="_blank"&gt;ratings of jarred tomato sauces&lt;/a&gt;.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="RQVM7S5XHBGGJPYB3VNNJW55TA" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Some people with arthritis may avoid eating tomatoes and other nightshade vegetables like potatoes and eggplant, thinking that they trigger inflammation and joint pain. But there’s no research showing that nightshades cause inflammation. Indeed, plant nutrients in tomatoes (and other nightshade vegetables) are strongly anti-inflammatory.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="45M2ZMDNONB7ZISEU65RWLXPBE" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;To get more: Aim to eat tomato sauce or other tomato products daily for the most benefits. For a sauce that doesn’t require hours of simmering, try a sofrito: Dice an onion and sauté in olive oil until browned. Add 5 minced garlic cloves, 3 chopped tomatoes, 1 chopped bell pepper and 7 ounces of tomato paste. Simmer for about 20 minutes, adding liquid as needed for the consistency you want.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="3RHJS6SSANFSHNPHEWHE26NGGE" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Oily fish like salmon, sardines, mackerel, and anchovies are high in omega-3 fats. In a &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC8199776/" target="_blank"&gt;2021 study in the journal Molecules&lt;/a&gt;, people at high risk of heart disease and Type 2 diabetes who ate those fish twice a week for eight weeks saw lower blood levels of inflammatory markers like CRP.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="DJ3XRYRI55GKLHOUSQOJBE3ZOY" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;To get more: You don’t need to spend a lot of kitchen time or money on fish. The kinds mentioned here are all available in cans or pouches. A couple of times a week, pop one open on a bed of leafy greens, top it with fresh herbs like basil or dill, and drizzle with high-quality extra-virgin olive oil.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="4YDCLPG5WVAVNH56QRQCVDDVHI" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Fried foods have high levels of acrylamide, a chemical by-product thought to produce inflammation. Do a quick sauté, steam or boil instead.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="HHWVJCNZSJCFDGG7J2TZR3MBOI" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Refined carbohydrates made from white flour contribute to high blood sugar, which can create oxidative stress and set off low-grade inflammation. Choose higher-fiber carbs, like whole grains, which aid digestion and lower heart disease risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="BUAEEZ4G6BGYFLS5YMFID4DP6Y" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Added sugars (in sugary beverages, candy, desserts) promote inflammation. In animals, at least, they may do so by altering the gut microbiome.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="C7TULURFYNB4TNCAFM42AVDHBQ" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Processed meats (lunch meats, bacon, sausage) are linked to inflammation that can contribute to cancer. Being overweight may boost the risk. The American Institute for Cancer Research suggests avoiding these meats altogether.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-header" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p id="MX42FHQYCNA47FRI3ZJH4W7M4Q" class="wpds-c-esEUdQ wpds-c-esEUdQ-hyvuql-isBold-true wpds-c-esEUdQ-ieHKbcq-css headingStyleOverrides" data-apitype="header" data-contentid="MX42FHQYCNA47FRI3ZJH4W7M4Q" data-testid="article-header"&gt;Copyright 2025, Consumer Reports Inc.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-header" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p id="NGIOUE72HRGJHDJS2MZ36HBWDU" class="wpds-c-esEUdQ wpds-c-esEUdQ-hqvHjm-isBold-false wpds-c-esEUdQ-ifBuccc-css headingStyleOverrides" data-apitype="header" data-contentid="NGIOUE72HRGJHDJS2MZ36HBWDU" data-testid="article-header"&gt;Consumer Reports is an independent, nonprofit organization that works side by side with consumers to create a fairer, safer and healthier world. CR does not endorse products or services and does not accept advertising. Read more at &amp;lt;a href="http://www.consumerreports.org/"&amp;gt;ConsumerReports.org&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 13:02:02 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilwFBVV95cUxQRXZ1V2tIWnVDUXRjNTN1RjB4a2hITHVBZXdDOUxFRG5LbGxVRXZYUHNGTEtkbVB6RWc1Y24teGRpSUM5TjRELWw0TkYwS0x1eHVNM1ZKam44UGpMeER1Nk1hQjJ1NHk1UkhJMkp2dGMzWjVZSjU4Q1JyenJHS1RVOFM0ZVgtdXZSVlZJYXdZT3oycWduSVA4</guid></item><item><title>为什么你对抹茶的痴迷可能会扰乱你的铁水平-独立报</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiowFBVV95cUxPNDhkN0M3MklnemEwMElCdkRELTZiMU00TjhPOWphQzNCT2F5SG1OWHFlUzFoYmNrcmdwclc2bS04T2FKR2RKN1pWLXlkTHA1NFMzUURMcFplQllIS1VsTlcyel83U0pXV2lmOWZHNnlxM25hLTJFR0Q1WVVRb3JVMWFSb2c1d3BIRjVPempPSDE5cVUxclA3b1ZaQW16dnBQYmtv?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="sc-jbiisr-0 gryCYY sc-jbiisr-1" id="main"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="hydrate-root sc-10wlkbs-0" data-component="SupportNSCNative" data-loading="lazy" data-theme-name="base"&gt;&lt;aside class="sc-hez36s-0 dFpFuY"&gt;&lt;div class="sc-hez36s-1 dmMyEN"&gt;&lt;h3 data-testid="support-nsc-title" class="sc-hez36s-2 fXvmgM"&gt;Your support helps us to tell the story&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;div class="sc-hez36s-8 juUDRT"&gt;&lt;div class="sc-hez36s-13 cqPbFA"&gt;&lt;div class="sc-aja53j-0 rAFIl sc-hez36s-16 jZSKtc"&gt;&lt;div class="sc-aja53j-6 PdmgT"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="dropdown-with-gradient-collapsed-content-container" class="sc-aja53j-5 hJPJVF"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div data-testid="dropdown-with-gradient-collapsed-content" class="sc-aja53j-4 lcJUSj"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div data-testid="support-nsc-collapsed-content-tablet" class="sc-hez36s-7 laZbyn"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-1uza6dc-0 cKWiEj"&gt;From reproductive rights to climate change to Big Tech, The Independent is on the ground when the story is developing. Whether it's investigating the financials of Elon Musk's pro-Trump PAC or producing our latest documentary, 'The A Word', which shines a light on the American women fighting for reproductive rights, we know how important it is to parse out the facts from the messaging.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-1uza6dc-0 cKWiEj"&gt;At such a critical moment in US history, we need reporters on the ground. Your donation allows us to keep sending journalists to speak to both sides of the story.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-1uza6dc-0 cKWiEj"&gt;The Independent is trusted by Americans across the entire political spectrum. And unlike many other quality news outlets, we choose not to lock Americans out of our reporting and analysis with paywalls. We believe quality journalism should be available to everyone, paid for by those who can afford it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;strong class="sc-1uza6dc-1 huxBsk"&gt;Your support makes all the difference.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;button class="sc-aja53j-1 dLkuvY sc-aja53j-7 eMEmGu"&gt;&lt;span data-testid="dropdown-with-gradient-dropdown-tablet" class="sc-aja53j-3 dHXFkr"&gt;&lt;span data-action-type="Read more" class="sc-aja53j-2 jrwZqm"&gt;Read more&lt;/span&gt;&lt;svg class="sc-eaj12q-0 hUgQwJ sc-culv3z-0 eifaJK sc-a5wy94-0 hyKPon"&gt;&lt;use href="#ee6613da15642019"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;The world has &lt;a href="/health-and-fitness/matcha-health-benefits-b2775853.html"&gt;developed a thirst for matcha&lt;/a&gt; – a bright green &lt;a href="/topic/japanese"&gt;Japanese&lt;/a&gt; drink that's &lt;a href="/life-style/health-and-families/matcha-health-benefits-coffee-b2749510.html"&gt;sought after for its health &lt;/a&gt;benefits and &lt;a href="/topic/caffeine"&gt;caffeine&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, the drink of choice for many may have a downside. Not only is its &lt;a href="/asia/japan/matcha-shortage-japan-global-supply-heatwave-b2797101.html"&gt;popularity drying up global supplies&lt;/a&gt;, but drinking too much of it could contribute to an &lt;a href="/topic/iron"&gt;iron&lt;/a&gt; deficiency. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="/topic/nutritionists"&gt;Nutritionists&lt;/a&gt; warn the green lattes can affect &lt;a href="/topic/iron"&gt;iron&lt;/a&gt; absorption and &lt;a href="/topic/vegetarians"&gt;vegetarians&lt;/a&gt; are at a higher risk than meat eaters. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="article-im-prompt"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Matcha is made from the green &lt;a href="/topic/tea"&gt;tea&lt;/a&gt; plant, Camellia Sinensis, which is ground into a powder. Because it’s grown in the shade the plant produces more chlorophyll, which not only gives it a deep green colour but also means it contains more nutrients. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rob Hobson, a nutritionist and author of &lt;em&gt;Unprocess Your Family Life&lt;/em&gt;, explains the drink does have health benefits. “It contains polyphenols which protects the body against oxidative damage. So, it helps to reduce &lt;a href="/topic/inflammation"&gt;inflammation&lt;/a&gt; which then helps to protect against chronic diseases,” he told the &lt;em&gt;Independent&lt;/em&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="taboola-mid-article-thumbnails-ii" class="sc-looa6c-0 cPCVUJ"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="sc-awdjp1-2 cbpRGD sc-awdjp1-3 image align-center"&gt;&lt;figure class="sc-1cbdeug-0 cXcwgU"&gt;&lt;div data-gallery-length="3" class="sc-awdjp1-0 jzbPdB"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.independent.co.uk/2025/07/26/15/34/iStock-2199126862.jpg" srcset="https://static.independent.co.uk/2025/07/26/15/34/iStock-2199126862.jpg?quality=75&amp;amp;width=320&amp;amp;auto=webp 320w, https://static.independent.co.uk/2025/07/26/15/34/iStock-2199126862.jpg?quality=75&amp;amp;width=640&amp;amp;auto=webp 640w" loading="lazy" alt="Drinking too much matcha could contribute to an iron deficiency, nutritionists warn" class="sc-1mc30lb-0 ggpMaE inline-gallery-btn"&gt;&lt;p class="hydrate-root sc-10wlkbs-0 sc-awdjp1-1 bMDiiD" data-component="AutoGalleryButton" data-theme-name="base"&gt;&lt;button class="sc-1uf4o3q-0 dkRtZs inline-gallery-btn" id="trigger-autogallery-316313"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-1uf4o3q-1 hwVecx"&gt;open image in gallery&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-1cbdeug-1 sc-1cbdeug-3 bpFomM hgzWpY"&gt;Drinking too much matcha could contribute to an iron deficiency, nutritionists warn&lt;span class="sc-1cbdeug-7 CXMrn"&gt; (Getty/iStock)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Because it contains &lt;a href="/topic/caffeine"&gt;caffeine&lt;/a&gt; it helps with mental focus. But it also contains L-theanine which helps to lessen that jittery edge that you get from caffeine,” he added. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Research has also suggested these polyphenols in matcha can reduce the risk of heart disease. But the same health boosting polyphenols also make it harder for the body to absorb iron. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gunter Kuhnle, a professor of nutrition and food science at the University of Reading explained matcha &lt;a href="/topic/tea"&gt;tea&lt;/a&gt; can affect iron absorption by binding the (non-haem) iron that is found in many plant foods – such as lentils, leafy greens and tofu. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“It contains the compounds catechins and tannins – which are both polyphenols – that can bind to iron in the digestive tracts, and this stops them from being taken up by the body,” Professor Kuhnle told the &lt;em&gt;Independent&lt;/em&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="sc-awdjp1-2 cbpRGD sc-awdjp1-3 image align-center"&gt;&lt;figure class="sc-1cbdeug-0 cXcwgU"&gt;&lt;div data-gallery-length="3" class="sc-awdjp1-0 cnxcc"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.independent.co.uk/2025/06/24/11/56/iStock-2179940383.jpg" srcset="https://static.independent.co.uk/2025/06/24/11/56/iStock-2179940383.jpg?quality=75&amp;amp;width=320&amp;amp;auto=webp 320w, https://static.independent.co.uk/2025/06/24/11/56/iStock-2179940383.jpg?quality=75&amp;amp;width=640&amp;amp;auto=webp 640w" loading="lazy" alt="The same health boosting polyphenols that make it good for your heart also make it harder for the body to absorb iron" class="sc-1mc30lb-0 ggpMaE inline-gallery-btn"&gt;&lt;p class="hydrate-root sc-10wlkbs-0 sc-awdjp1-1 bMDiiD" data-component="AutoGalleryButton" data-theme-name="base"&gt;&lt;button class="sc-1uf4o3q-0 dkRtZs inline-gallery-btn" id="trigger-autogallery-316314"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-1uf4o3q-1 hwVecx"&gt;open image in gallery&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-1cbdeug-1 sc-1cbdeug-3 bpFomM hgzWpY"&gt;The same health boosting polyphenols that make it good for your heart also make it harder for the body to absorb iron&lt;span class="sc-1cbdeug-7 CXMrn"&gt; (Getty/iStock)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;“These complexes then pass through the gut and are not useful for the body – this can reduce iron uptake by up to 50 per cent, but this varies a lot between individuals and depends on the timing of the meal and the type of food,” he added. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He explained there is a similar problem with green tea because it also contains high levels of polyphenols. Although rare, in one instance a 48-year-old man became anaemic from excessive green tea consumption Professor Kuhnle said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Hobson stressed that you don’t need to worry if you have a balanced diet, but warned &lt;a href="/topic/vegetarians"&gt;vegetarians&lt;/a&gt; are at a greater risk. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That’s because it only affects non-haem iron which is in tofu and lentils and not haem iron which is found in meat. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“If you are vegan or vegetarian and you are relying on lentils, leafy green and tofu for your iron, then you might want to avoid drinking matcha with your meals because it can inhibit iron absorption in the gut,” Mr Hobson said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He also stressed that if you are low in iron anyway and take iron supplements, you should avoid taking these at the same time as drinking a matcha. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;An iron deficiency, also called anaemia, can cause tiredness, shortness of breath, paler skin, headaches and heart palpitations, according to the NHS. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="taboola-mid-article-thumbnails-ii" class="sc-looa6c-0 cPCVUJ"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Low iron is common among &lt;a href="/topic/teenage-girls"&gt;teenage girls&lt;/a&gt;, vegans and vegetarians with a study by Lund University in Sweden finding 38 per cent of participants who were &lt;a href="/topic/teenage-girls"&gt;teenage girls&lt;/a&gt; and 70 per cent of participants who were vegetarian or vegan, affected by the deficiency. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you want to reap the health benefits of matcha, in addition to not drinking it at mealtimes, make sure to avoid adding a lot of syrup or cream. Mr Hobson instead suggests the healthiest option is to drink it plain. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Independent</author><pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 10:04:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiowFBVV95cUxPNDhkN0M3MklnemEwMElCdkRELTZiMU00TjhPOWphQzNCT2F5SG1OWHFlUzFoYmNrcmdwclc2bS04T2FKR2RKN1pWLXlkTHA1NFMzUURMcFplQllIS1VsTlcyel83U0pXV2lmOWZHNnlxM25hLTJFR0Q1WVVRb3JVMWFSb2c1d3BIRjVPempPSDE5cVUxclA3b1ZaQW16dnBQYmtv</guid></item><item><title>您什么时候知道什么时候停止癌症治疗？她知道--她最后的控制--《卫报》</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMilAFBVV95cUxPZ0x2dnJGNUNETjZxY3otMWJLVzNLaXI5eE0zc2Z3NU1DQUJ6cXEwcGlBZTJyRGJiZmpBOWw2RV9YNG1SUEU4MFh2NUQzODBCVlRURGFybS1ZSjJ4aFk4WEN1VnFRWEtHQjJoX2cwVzJwb0x2Vy1CX3ZBWmFKRVNXeVBmRWVXQjhZbnBRcGg2YUFRMzhE?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body-commercial-selector article-body-viewer-selector content__main-column--interactive dcr-11jq3zt"&gt;&lt;figure id="e2f17894-7304-41bd-a79c-f11a1d3c82d5" data-spacefinder-role="inline" data-spacefinder-type="model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.InteractiveAtomBlockElement" class="element element-atom dcr-173mewl"&gt;&lt;figure class="interactive interactive-atom dcr-e6xisx" data-atom-id="interactives/2023/01/interactive-article-structure/portrait-image-mainmedia-feature" data-atom-type="interactive-layout"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figure id="10876d41-3dd4-48ca-a498-5bfe18efa699" data-spacefinder-role="inline" data-spacefinder-type="model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.ImageBlockElement" class="element element--inline element-inline dcr-173mewl"&gt;&lt;figcaption data-spacefinder-role="inline" class="dcr-fd61eq"&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-1inf02i"&gt;&lt;svg viewbox="0 0 18 13"&gt;&lt;path d="M18 3.5v8l-1.5 1.5h-15l-1.5-1.5v-8l1.5-1.5h3.5l2-2h4l2 2h3.5l1.5 1.5zm-9 7.5c1.9 0 3.5-1.6 3.5-3.5s-1.6-3.5-3.5-3.5-3.5 1.6-3.5 3.5 1.6 3.5 3.5 3.5z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-1qvd3m6"&gt;Betsy Lewis, 75, poses for a portrait at her home in Houston, Texas.&lt;/span&gt; Photograph: Danielle Villasana/The Guardian&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p id="sign-in-gate"&gt;&lt;gu-island name="SignInGateSelector" priority="feature" deferuntil="visible" props='{"contentType":"Interactive","sectionId":"society","tags":[{"id":"society/cancer","type":"Keyword","title":"Cancer"},{"id":"society/health","type":"Keyword","title":"Health"},{"id":"wellness/wellness","type":"Keyword","title":"Well actually"},{"id":"campaign/email/well-actually","type":"Campaign","title":"Well Actually (Newsletter sign up)"},{"id":"lifeandstyle/lifeandstyle","type":"Keyword","title":"Life and style"},{"id":"society/society","type":"Keyword","title":"Society"},{"id":"type/interactive","type":"Type","title":"Interactive"},{"id":"tone/features","type":"Tone","title":"Features"},{"id":"tracking/commissioningdesk/us-narrative--commissioning-","type":"Tracking","title":"US Narrative (Commissioning)"},{"id":"tracking/commissioningdesk/us-visuals","type":"Tracking","title":"US Visuals"}],"isPaidContent":false,"isPreview":false,"host":"https://www.theguardian.com","pageId":"society/ng-interactive/2025/aug/04/stop-cancer-treatment-essay","idUrl":"https://profile.theguardian.com","contributionsServiceUrl":"https://contributions.guardianapis.com","editionId":"US"}'&gt;&lt;/gu-island&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;I can remember many things about the afternoon I told Betsy that she had stage IV lung cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;I can still see how the single ray of sunshine from the skylight in the atrium behind us entered the crack between the curtains in her hospital room, shooting right through the crystalline IV bag hanging from the pole next to her, turning it into a depressing sort of disco ball.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;I can still hear the sardonic laugh we shared about the unwieldy chest tube emerging from between her ribs that was slowly re-inflating her lung after a biopsy had caused it to partially collapse.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;But, as her oncologist, what I remember most clearly was her outward equanimity about it all. She was 72 years old, divorced, fierce and sarcastic. She’d later tell me how caring for her mother as she’d slowly declined with chronic obstructive pulmonary disease had put her “firmly in the quality over quantity camp”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="569095b1-937f-4148-b5ef-0cd06ab97ca9" data-spacefinder-role="showcase" data-spacefinder-type="model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.ImageBlockElement" class="element element--showcase element-showcase dcr-5h0uf4"&gt;&lt;figcaption data-spacefinder-role="inline" class="dcr-9ktzqp"&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-1inf02i"&gt;&lt;svg viewbox="0 0 18 13"&gt;&lt;path d="M18 3.5v8l-1.5 1.5h-15l-1.5-1.5v-8l1.5-1.5h3.5l2-2h4l2 2h3.5l1.5 1.5zm-9 7.5c1.9 0 3.5-1.6 3.5-3.5s-1.6-3.5-3.5-3.5-3.5 1.6-3.5 3.5 1.6 3.5 3.5 3.5z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-1qvd3m6"&gt;Betsy Lewis.&lt;/span&gt; Photograph: Danielle Villasana/The Guardian&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;She had already been treated for breast cancer, having gone through surgery, radiation and hormonal therapies some years before. She knew very well the promises and limitations of modern oncology, and that each path had its costs. Hard-earned experience meant she harbored few illusions about any of it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;I went over the PET scan she’d had prior to her admission to the hospital. Masses in both lungs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;“We know what that means,” she said, pursing her lips.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;My job was to provide information, I thought then. Her job would be deciding what we did with it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;“Well, yes, I don’t think we’re looking at something that’s curable.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;Betsy would later tell me that while she wouldn’t call herself a control freak, she felt driven by a deep need to remain in control of her own circumstances.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;We would spend the next two years figuring out what that meant.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr class="dcr-z9ge1j"&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;Two weeks later, we went over the biopsy results in my outpatient office. The pathologist had finalized a diagnosis of lung adenocarcinoma; subsequent testing had shown that her tumor harbored a significant level of PDL1 expression.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;“And what does that mean?”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;“It means it would be reasonable to treat you with immunotherapy alone”, I said, explaining that we could use a drug called pembrolizumab to better allow her own immune system to find and kill the cancer cells inside of her body. “We don’t have to start with any chemotherapy.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;“Good, because I’m never going to do any chemotherapy.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;I nodded, though I’d heard these declarations before from dozens of other patients. But when the scans showed progression, and the progression was causing pain, and the prospect of one’s death loomed ever closer, red lines drawn in the light of better health suddenly didn’t seem so final.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;“Sure, we can talk about that when we get there.” I instinctively recoiled from challenging my patients’ values. This was what it meant to give our patients autonomy, I thought.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;]She didn’t say anything, but the look in her eyes told me what I needed to know.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;I’d later asked how her previous experience getting treated for breast cancer informed her approach to this new diagnosis, how she’d come into it with a rare clarity on what she would and would not accept.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;“The only negative that stuck with me from breast cancer was never to get married again, because my husband was not supportive.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;We laughed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;“You know, people say, ‘Oh, they fought and fought and fought,’ and I don’t know that I agree with that. I don’t ever want to be kept alive. I don’t ever want my life to be one day of suffering and fighting after another. I don’t want that.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="af8799f1-0856-4c48-8315-39ebeb785cc9" data-spacefinder-role="inline" data-spacefinder-type="model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.ImageBlockElement" class="element element--inline element-inline dcr-173mewl"&gt;&lt;figcaption data-spacefinder-role="inline" class="dcr-fd61eq"&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-1inf02i"&gt;&lt;svg viewbox="0 0 18 13"&gt;&lt;path d="M18 3.5v8l-1.5 1.5h-15l-1.5-1.5v-8l1.5-1.5h3.5l2-2h4l2 2h3.5l1.5 1.5zm-9 7.5c1.9 0 3.5-1.6 3.5-3.5s-1.6-3.5-3.5-3.5-3.5 1.6-3.5 3.5 1.6 3.5 3.5 3.5z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-1qvd3m6"&gt;Betsy Lewis.&lt;/span&gt; Photograph: Danielle Villasana/The Guardian&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;I could appreciate that. I agreed it wasn’t true that the only sane response to lived experience was more of it. But I also thought chemotherapy occupied an unfair place in the popular imagination. Sometimes, the pain, weight loss and weakness that patients and families blamed on paclitaxel or oxaliplatin were just as much caused by the cancer itself. And often, in the grieving imagination of those left behind, a death from cancer gradually became a death from the treatment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;Still, there was no denying the toll taken by the indefinite treatments we recommended to patients with incurable cancers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;“My next door neighbor was about 10 years younger than I am and she was diagnosed with pancreatic cancer. At the same time, my uncle by marriage was diagnosed with a glioblastoma. I was diagnosed with breast cancer. It was like, ‘Don’t drink the water where we are, you know?’”. She paused until I got the joke.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;“I watched both of them, my uncle and my dear friend go from treatment to treatment to treatment. Never, quote, “giving up” and being pushed by their families to continue treatment. And I thought it was very inhumane. If you’re going to extend somebody’s life by a week and a half or six months, and those six months are going to be hell, I’m not going to sign up for them.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr class="dcr-z9ge1j"&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;A 2016 study had led to pembrolizumab’s approval for a subset of people with advanced lung cancer. Nearly half of the patients in the trial responded to that drug alone without the use of chemotherapy. And, in a disease where survival is often measured in months, nearly a third were still alive five years later. On average, the patients in the trial lived about two years – a meaningful gain for those who might live only a few months without treatment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;I talked about this data with Betsy and her family before she eventually agreed to undergo therapy. She later told me she appreciated that I’d been honest and open about the numbers, that she’d had a good idea from the beginning of how long the treatment would be effective.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;Growing up, Betsy’s family called her Big Momma - “and it wasn’t a compliment…it was basically implied that I was bossy or needed to have things done my way”. That baseline need was further sharpened by her mother’s exacting standards and the subsequent responsibilities she took on caring for her brother, who suffered from severe mental illness. It further solidified, years later, when she had to find ways to make ends meet as a single mother.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;In an important way, her fastidiousness was rooted in the knowledge that so much depended on her doing things right the first time. As the decades passed, friends and family learned she could be counted on to help them navigate complicated medical decisions like choosing a nursing home or arranging a home health aide. Now, she’d draw on that energy to get through her own cancer treatment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="28fc6818-f1f8-476f-93fd-985761ba1b35" data-spacefinder-role="showcase" data-spacefinder-type="model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.ImageBlockElement" class="element element--showcase element-showcase dcr-5h0uf4"&gt;&lt;figcaption data-spacefinder-role="inline" class="dcr-9ktzqp"&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-1inf02i"&gt;&lt;svg viewbox="0 0 18 13"&gt;&lt;path d="M18 3.5v8l-1.5 1.5h-15l-1.5-1.5v-8l1.5-1.5h3.5l2-2h4l2 2h3.5l1.5 1.5zm-9 7.5c1.9 0 3.5-1.6 3.5-3.5s-1.6-3.5-3.5-3.5-3.5 1.6-3.5 3.5 1.6 3.5 3.5 3.5z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-1qvd3m6"&gt;Lewis says family and friends have been an instrumental source of support.&lt;/span&gt; Photograph: Danielle Villasana/The Guardian&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;Over her first few months on pembrolizumab, her chest and back were slowly covered with a fine red rash that itched like hell – a condition called immune dermatitis, which resulted from the same T-cells that were being activated to fight the patient’s cancer mistakenly targeting their skin. The itching went from a mild annoyance to an around-the-clock obsession that made sleep impossible. Betsy herself described her years-long experience with it as “almost torture”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;We recommended plastic jars full of steroid creams, metal tubes of steroid ointments and soothing lotions of varying potency. We also tried an assortment of antihistamines without much success. Poring over case reports online, I found some data to support the prescription of gabapentin – a medication typically used to treat diabetic neuropathy – for her itching. That helped a little.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;She was also getting more and more fatigued. She still worked from home part-time, but she’d finish for the day and collapse on her couch, sleeping for hours at a time. We checked her thyroid and cortisol levels, both of which are commonly affected by immunotherapy. Both normal. We checked her blood counts. Nearly normal. I couldn’t find anything to fix. We were prisoners of the measurable. I was left recommending her to sleep as much as she could and do only as much as her body allowed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;Yet despite all of the negatives, the treatment was also clearly working to control her cancer’s growth.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;I can recall the feeling of anxious anticipation when I got the message that the results of her first scan were ready. It echoed what I’d felt in high school when I’d gotten a large envelope in the mail from a college I’d applied to – a fragile expectation that contained within it an implicit admonition not to get my hopes up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;I took a deep breath and clicked on the result. Her cancer was shrinking. The response continued at six months out. It continued at 12 months.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;It was difficult to live like that, from scan to scan. Not many are equipped to handle that kind of sustained uncertainty. Betsy seemed to be doing well enough with it, though. At least that’s what she let me see.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;We felt it was worth it to continue. For now.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;“I am very good at weighing pluses and minuses,” she told me, “but my pluses and minuses can be very different than someone else’s.” I wondered how long this new equilibrium could last.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr class="dcr-z9ge1j"&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;In the first two years after we diagnosed Betsy’s cancer, I wrote 33 progress notes in her chart. That meant I saw her 33 times, an average of aboutp once every three weeks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;We developed a strange kind of intimacy. I didn’t know where she grew up, what her house looked like, what her favorite movie was. Yet, I’d seen into her lungs. I knew why she couldn’t sleep. I had data that told me how long she might live.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;I was witnessing her facing death. I knew in a very real way what she was about.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;That vulnerability went only one way, however. Though Betsy and my other patients got to know me, I was able to hide behind the dry-cleaned fabric of my white coat and the emotional remove of my role as doctor. That was how I had been taught to be. My patients didn’t need to know about my hangovers, my heartbreaks. They didn’t need to know, I told myself, what treatments I’d recommend to my own family members.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;Yet I still think Betsy learned enough about what I was about to stick around. I wasn’t as hidden as I thought. There were plenty of oncologists in our city. For a patient to stay with me was a choice, the implications of which I never took lightly. Our relationship was about more than five year overall survival numbers and maintaining adequate kidney function.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;To be the doctor she needed, I knew I’d have to find a way to keep giving her more.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr class="dcr-z9ge1j"&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;In the spring following Betsy’s diagnosis, she was admitted to the hospital with bacterial pneumonia. The cough lingered for weeks, though she eventually recovered enough to make a trip to Colorado.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;A few months later, she suffered a viral upper respiratory tract infection that was soon complicated by another bacterial pneumonia. Her scans became more difficult to interpret, the smoothly outlined opacities of her cancer now superimposed with the ground glass caused by repeated infections. PET-CT scans showed more metabolic activity in the lungs as well, but it wasn’t clear whether this was a sign of growing cancer cells or an immune system struggling to fight off multiple infections.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;We spent long visits talking about the implications of those hard-to-parse scans, poring over measurements of size, of metabolic activity. I tried to provide reasonable explanations for any increases, explanations that didn’t involve a growing resistance to the therapy that had been so successful for over a year. I wanted to take what I knew about her case to tell a story that was reassuring. I couldn’t adhere any longer to some imagined ideal of impartiality at odds with what I understood it meant to care for another person.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;I remember one such visit particularly well, a little over a year into therapy. The scan we’d done before the appointment showed new findings in both breasts. This was not an area that lung cancer was known for going, I told her. We couldn’t explain this away.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="0d1babf0-f5dd-4b11-bbb0-f56d2c9a1996" data-spacefinder-role="inline" data-spacefinder-type="model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.ImageBlockElement" class="element element--inline element-inline dcr-173mewl"&gt;&lt;figcaption data-spacefinder-role="inline" class="dcr-fd61eq"&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-1inf02i"&gt;&lt;svg viewbox="0 0 18 13"&gt;&lt;path d="M18 3.5v8l-1.5 1.5h-15l-1.5-1.5v-8l1.5-1.5h3.5l2-2h4l2 2h3.5l1.5 1.5zm-9 7.5c1.9 0 3.5-1.6 3.5-3.5s-1.6-3.5-3.5-3.5-3.5 1.6-3.5 3.5 1.6 3.5 3.5 3.5z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-1qvd3m6"&gt;Lewis holds a Star of David necklace with a diamond that belonged to her paternal grandmother.&lt;/span&gt; Photograph: Danielle Villasana/The Guardian&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;She was unmoved. “I’ve had that right breast biopsied a few times since I was treated for the breast cancer way back when.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;“Still, I’d like you to go see the breast surgeon. Get it checked out. There’s a small spot on the PET scan in the left breast too, even though we can’t feel anything there.” She went under protest.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;A few weeks later, after talking Betsy into another biopsy, the surgeon called me. It was a small cancer on the left side.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;My colleagues and I discussed her case with all the relevant specialists, and we shared our recommendations with her. She didn’t want to have surgery and she didn’t want to risk an anti-estrogen medication. What was the point of being aggressive with treating the breast cancer at all, she wondered, given that it was more likely that lung cancer would threaten her life first?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;Even the medicine sounded like too much. She’d taken it for five years following her first breast cancer diagnosis nearly a decade ago, and it had made her so tired. The pembrolizumab was making her tired enough.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;We agreed – we would watch it. We’d act not to control the cancer, but to control what we would and would not do about it. The decision had emerged from Betsy’s own history with breast cancer and its treatments. She knew in a very real way what each option would cost her.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;“So what’s going on with my lung cancer, anyway?” Even a change of subject couldn’t get us any real relief.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;One scan pointed to it looking worse, another better. I squinted at the pixels on the screen. Maybe if I looked hard enough, I thought, I could see what was going on inside of those inscrutable cells. It was like staring into the sun.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;“I’d have to say things are relatively stable. We’ve been seeing small changes in both ways over the last year. Nothing conclusive.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;An exhale. A shift in gravity and light. “I don’t know how long I can keep doing this.” Bone-deep exhaustion. The rash and itching that kept her up at night. Nothing I’d tried had worked. She kept refusing oral steroids — the big gun — because prednisone spiked her anxiety and wrecked what little sleep she got.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;I could see what was coming. And while I could no longer confine myself to a dry recounting of the facts, I didn’t know what else I could say to change Betsy’s mind.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;What did it mean to fight? Wasn’t it more important to ask what we were fighting for?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr class="dcr-z9ge1j"&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;August in Houston. A hot, hot afternoon. The humid air so heavy it could be cut into blocks and stored.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;That day, nearly two years into her treatment, Betsy told me she couldn’t work any longer, couldn’t do anything after noon but nap and lie on her couch.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;When I think about that appointment now, nearly a year later, it seems delusional that I tried so desperately to convince her to change her mind after she went on to tell me she didn’t want any more infusions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;But I was motivated, I think, by a need to move beyond a dispassionate recitation of facts and options. I wanted to help her make a choice that was consistent with what mattered most to her, especially if it wasn’t obvious at first.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;It was a transition that Drs Linda and Ezekiel Emanuel had written about in a landmark 1992 examination of the doctor-patient relationship they’d published in the Journal of the American Medical Association, describing how clinicians might move from a purely informative mode to what they termed a deliberative one. But I didn’t know any of that then. I just wanted her to leave my clinic without any regrets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;So I tried to talk her out of her decision. She wasn’t in the hospital, after all. She’d just traveled across the country for her step-daughter’s wedding. She was living alone and independently in her own home. Her last scans showed that the cancer wasn’t growing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;The patients in the trial had each received three years of Keytruda, and she’d be stopping short of two.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;Would she take a break from treatment and restart in a few months when she was feeling better, I asked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;No.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;Would she take a break and consider chemotherapy?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;Also no.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;Her daughter Lindsey later told me that she had made the decision to stop therapy with the firm expectation that the end of her life would soon follow. She’d lived with a sense of fatalism since her breast cancer diagnosis; both of her parents hadn’t made it to their 80s. She’d helped so many navigate their final weeks and months, and the knowledge of death’s inevitability was never far from her mind.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;Her sister Leslie shared with me that she also had a sense that the treatment had bought her enough time to get her affairs in order. Now that she knew she’d done all she could to make sure her children would be taken care of financially, she felt she could let go.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;When, against her expectations, she made it to fall, she planned for Thanksgiving to be her grand goodbye. Family from across the country flew to Houston to be with her, and everything was arranged just so. But then she made it to Hanukkah, then New Year’s. She continued to feel well enough; she was still working; the scans showed no growth.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="8d012e3b-b9d8-4d17-9f9c-bdb4f67f94bc" data-spacefinder-role="showcase" data-spacefinder-type="model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.ImageBlockElement" class="element element--showcase element-showcase dcr-5h0uf4"&gt;&lt;figcaption data-spacefinder-role="inline" class="dcr-9ktzqp"&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-1inf02i"&gt;&lt;svg viewbox="0 0 18 13"&gt;&lt;path d="M18 3.5v8l-1.5 1.5h-15l-1.5-1.5v-8l1.5-1.5h3.5l2-2h4l2 2h3.5l1.5 1.5zm-9 7.5c1.9 0 3.5-1.6 3.5-3.5s-1.6-3.5-3.5-3.5-3.5 1.6-3.5 3.5 1.6 3.5 3.5 3.5z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-1qvd3m6"&gt;Lewis, right, talks with a friend at her home in Houston, Texas.&lt;/span&gt; Photograph: Danielle Villasana/The Guardian&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;Lindsey tried to remind her mother about how the data showed that a small fraction of patients had made it to five years with something like the therapy she’d gotten. “She goes back and forth between being very fatalistic, like where I’m dying imminently… to ‘I’m not that bad, back off, you’re not my mother’”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;She’d crested the hill, taken her hands off the handlebars, entrusted herself to what fate had in store. Her final act of control was to relinquish it. Maybe she thought it was the choice that would best ensure the kind of death she wanted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;But when February rolled around and she was still going strong, Lindsey had to finally ask, “OK, we need to start talking about your birthday. We’re running out of time. Do you want this party or not?”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr class="dcr-z9ge1j"&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;On an unseasonably cool May afternoon, I joined Betsy’s family and friends to celebrate her 75th birthday in her backyard, where we shared memories over lemonade and fajitas.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;When we’d stopped the pembrolizumab nine months before, none of us had known if this celebration was in the cards. Now, we sat together, watching the sun set over the neatly manicured flower beds and the precisely arranged folding tables. Drinks were arrayed on the side-board in the dining room, and trays of tortillas lay ready in the kitchen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;Being on the treatment had made this perfect night possible. Coming off the treatment also had.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;When I’d told her I wanted to write about her story, Betsy said that she supported the idea. She wanted her family to understand why she’d made the choice that she had.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;I asked her how her relationships with those closest to her had changed in the months since she’d stopped therapy. “Well, everybody is making their pilgrimages. You don’t have to lift a finger, or you can just sit in your house and people can come, and then when it’s time for them to go, they can go home.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;But, for now, it wasn’t time to go home yet, not for another few hours.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;When faced with serious illness, I think we all want to reach that state of balance in which we neither welcome death nor push it away. Betsy had come closer to that equilibrium than most, and she’d done that by being true to herself. As much as she still expected the end of her life was near, that didn’t mean she wouldn’t celebrate it while she still could.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="a1b547ae-c826-4659-82aa-e81ae10afdab" data-spacefinder-role="inline" data-spacefinder-type="model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.ImageBlockElement" class="element element--inline element-inline dcr-173mewl"&gt;&lt;figcaption data-spacefinder-role="inline" class="dcr-fd61eq"&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-1inf02i"&gt;&lt;svg viewbox="0 0 18 13"&gt;&lt;path d="M18 3.5v8l-1.5 1.5h-15l-1.5-1.5v-8l1.5-1.5h3.5l2-2h4l2 2h3.5l1.5 1.5zm-9 7.5c1.9 0 3.5-1.6 3.5-3.5s-1.6-3.5-3.5-3.5-3.5 1.6-3.5 3.5 1.6 3.5 3.5 3.5z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-1qvd3m6"&gt;Lewis gently admires a plant in her home.&lt;/span&gt; Photograph: Danielle Villasana/The Guardian&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;The cake was brought out of the kitchen, and as we sang, circled around, I read the inscription in icing - “Happy Birthday, Bestsy” it said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;Her sister said the misspelling had been intentional. On this night, so perfectly planned, we all needed a little reminder that some things in these beautiful lives of ours would always remain just beyond our ability to control them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Guardian</author><pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilAFBVV95cUxPZ0x2dnJGNUNETjZxY3otMWJLVzNLaXI5eE0zc2Z3NU1DQUJ6cXEwcGlBZTJyRGJiZmpBOWw2RV9YNG1SUEU4MFh2NUQzODBCVlRURGFybS1ZSjJ4aFk4WEN1VnFRWEtHQjJoX2cwVzJwb0x2Vy1CX3ZBWmFKRVNXeVBmRWVXQjhZbnBRcGg2YUFRMzhE</guid></item><item><title>物理治疗师说，这些是您每天应该做的改善骨骼健康的三项体重运动- Fit&amp;Well</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMi-wFBVV95cUxQQlFGc0JvTFh5SVN4WWI3NjZ3X2NpeDdBNVMtMUNWTGVOMmVWSjVlZHNad2hjS1laenYySEV4ZVFZRGpGTEkzTWt5U3lpclN4eTRGUUtHcTVnZ1BwZm9qdTB6SGxkQTdONG5vR1d6WXpXazNNb3I4X0NXbmZQUU9HRElGcmpJbEdSVC01YWZkTDJLMzVwSHZERHcxQ2wyMHZsRFVvNjVnbnd2b3FIRGl6VTI3SS1VdU9hbHBsX25uVnFHRDdEdC1melF5MDNUQmZqMzFKdXVwd1J4UldMVkg0YllaYWxBLVczQlMxODZWdlRQTjdNWFJ4OXRLcw?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="article-body" class="article__body "&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You often hear about the importance of building muscle for longevity, but another important part of aging well is looking after your bone health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="ad-unit-1" class="ad-unit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most people reach peak bone mass &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://orthoinfo.aaos.org/en/staying-healthy/healthy-bones-at-every-age/" target="_blank" data-url="https://orthoinfo.aaos.org/en/staying-healthy/healthy-bones-at-every-age/" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;between the ages of 20 and 30&lt;/a&gt;, but this can differ depending on your sex and genetics.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In general, your body naturally begins to lose bone mass from your mid-to-late 30s, but you can slow down the process with the right nutrition and exercise.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Diane Carroll is an orthopedic physical therapist at the Hospital for Special Surgery at &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.hss.edu/locations/florida/hss-at-nch" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.hss.edu/locations/florida/hss-at-nch" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;Naples Comprehensive Health&lt;/a&gt; in Florida, and she says there are three exercises she’d recommend for people who want to improve bone health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="ad-unit-2" class="ad-unit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Weight training is very good for building bone,” Carroll tells &lt;em&gt;Fit&amp;amp;Well&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This doesn’t mean you have to lift weights—any form of resistance strength training will help you improve your bone health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“It doesn't need to be anything heavy,” she adds. “It could be a resistance band, it could be a weight or it could be your bodyweight.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div id="slice-container-newsletterForm-articleInbodyContent-KoBA3VVhogtQNCzFPP2kXB" class="slice-container newsletter-inbodyContent-slice newsletterForm-articleInbodyContent-KoBA3VVhogtQNCzFPP2kXB slice-container-newsletterForm"&gt;&lt;div data-hydrate="true" class="newsletter-form__wrapper newsletter-form__wrapper--inbodyContent"&gt;&lt;div class="newsletter-form__container"&gt;&lt;section class="newsletter-form__main-section"&gt;&lt;p class="newsletter-form__strapline"&gt;Start your week with achievable workout ideas, health tips and wellbeing advice in your inbox.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Here are the three moves she recommends for beginners.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="article-body__section" id="section-diane-carroll-s-three-move-routine-for-better-bone-health"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Diane Carroll’s three move routine for better bone health&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you want to build bone in a specific area, you should aim to strengthen the muscles in that area.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But if you’re focused on building better overall health, full-body exercises work well—"the simpler the better," says Carroll.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="article-body__section" id="section-1-sit-to-stand"&gt;&lt;span&gt;1. Sit to stand&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The muscles in your legs are very functional,” Carroll says. “This movement replicates what they need to do all day—standing up from a chair, pushing you up onto a curb and holding you up against gravity.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Sit on a standard height chair with both feet on the floor.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Push through your feet and extend your legs to stand up without using your arms.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Push your hips back and bend your knees to sit back down without using your arms. Try not to hunch or arch your back and keep your core engaged throughout.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Repeat for 30 seconds.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h3 class="article-body__section" id="section-2-calf-raise"&gt;&lt;span&gt;2. Calf raise&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Stand with your feet hip-width apart, with your hand on a wall or other support if needed.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Rise onto your toes, lifting your heels off the floor.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Pause, then slowly lower your heels to the floor.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Repeat for 30 seconds.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h3 class="article-body__section" id="section-3-standing-leg-raise"&gt;&lt;span&gt;3. Standing leg raise&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Stand with your feet hip-width apart and your hands on your hips.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Keeping your leg straight, torso still and spine in a neutral position throughout, raise your right leg in front of you, then lower it with control.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Raise your right leg out to the side, then lower it with control.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Raise your right leg behind you, then lower it with control.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Continue for 30 seconds, then repeat on your left leg.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Fit&amp;Well</author><pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 06:02:57 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi-wFBVV95cUxQQlFGc0JvTFh5SVN4WWI3NjZ3X2NpeDdBNVMtMUNWTGVOMmVWSjVlZHNad2hjS1laenYySEV4ZVFZRGpGTEkzTWt5U3lpclN4eTRGUUtHcTVnZ1BwZm9qdTB6SGxkQTdONG5vR1d6WXpXazNNb3I4X0NXbmZQUU9HRElGcmpJbEdSVC01YWZkTDJLMzVwSHZERHcxQ2wyMHZsRFVvNjVnbnd2b3FIRGl6VTI3SS1VdU9hbHBsX25uVnFHRDdEdC1melF5MDNUQmZqMzFKdXVwd1J4UldMVkg0YllaYWxBLVczQlMxODZWdlRQTjdNWFJ4OXRLcw</guid></item><item><title>如果您在凌晨3-5点之间醒来时没有闹钟，那么您的大脑正在试图告诉您一些重要的事情- VegOut</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMi1wFBVV95cUxONmRldWtJSVJTUF96MlJ6eGctX0EyckRQc2xPRTdiSzItMjdVSHhuSnBScmVUSVppNzVXU0hrM0hhZl9RajlWamN0NkowV1AtZm9UV29GclZ4a2NDY3VKVm5wME1tYXg5ZHhkX3c1b052VGVzc19DX2JFMnlZbmw2VTltNVRyM0tHNHhEZ25kc2Fmam45NFNhU3BoWkQxdzJQa2xNa0RuMGxWbkZraGhReFdKS3M1bDB1cU5oVmFkckFsR2IyNGc4Ti1KbW1nN1hhcEdYZmJaWQ?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="page__content mt-4"&gt;
							&lt;p&gt;The clock read 3:47 AM when I found myself staring at the ceiling again, mind racing like I'd just chugged three espressos. No alarm. No noise. Just my brain deciding that the middle of the night was prime time for consciousness. If this sounds familiar, you're part of a surprisingly large club—one that meets nightly in the liminal space between deep sleep and dawn.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For months, I assumed this was just another quirk of modern life, like doom-scrolling or having strong opinions about oat milk brands. But after diving into the research (spurred by my own obsessive sleep tracking), I discovered something fascinating: these early morning wake-ups might be your body trying to communicate something important about your circadian rhythm, stress levels, or overall health.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;The science of the 3 AM club&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here's what's actually happening when you bolt awake at ungodly hours: Your body follows a complex 24-hour cycle that governs everything from hormone production to body temperature. Around 2-3 AM, something interesting occurs—your cortisol levels begin their natural rise, preparing your body for eventual morning awakening.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In a perfect world, this rise is gradual, gently nudging you toward consciousness around 6 or 7 AM. But for many of us, this system has gone haywire. Dr. Michael Breus's research on sleep chronotypes suggests that our modern environment has stretched the natural variation in sleep patterns to extremes we've never seen before in human history.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Think of it like this: Your cortisol is supposed to be a slow-building crescendo, but stress turns it into a jarring alarm bell. When you're already running high on stress hormones during the day, that &lt;a href="https://www.ptsduk.org/sleep-and-cortisol-in-ptsd/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;natural 3 AM rise can overflow your metaphorical cup&lt;/a&gt;, yanking you into consciousness when you should be in deep sleep.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Why your sleep cycles matter more than you think&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Every night, you cycle through different &lt;a href="https://www.sleepfoundation.org/stages-of-sleep" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;stages of sleep&lt;/a&gt; approximately every 90-120 minutes. The fascinating part? The architecture of these cycles changes throughout the night. Early on, you get more deep, restorative sleep. But as morning approaches, you spend more time in REM sleep—the stage where your brain is almost as active as when you're awake.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is where things become crucial. REM sleep is when your brain processes emotions and consolidates memories. It's also when you're most likely to wake up and actually remember it. Those 3-5 AM wake-ups often coincide with longer REM periods, which might explain why your brain feels so annoyingly alert—it's already revved up, processing the day's experiences and emotions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dr. Matthew Walker's research shows that even short-term sleep debt can disrupt this delicate dance, creating a cascade of effects that make quality sleep increasingly elusive. Think of it as a snowball rolling downhill—each night of poor sleep makes the next night harder, accumulating into an avalanche of exhaustion.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;The chronotype connection&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Not everyone's internal clock runs on the same schedule. Some of us are &lt;a href="https://www.ox.ac.uk/news/2023-03-17-having-genetics-night-owl-protects-night-shift-workers-against-sleep-loss" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;genetically programmed night owls&lt;/a&gt;, while others are natural early birds. The research reveals something surprising—scientists have identified at least nine different genes that influence whether you're more likely to thrive at dawn or come alive after dark.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But here's the kicker: our modern world has &lt;a href="https://www.brainfacts.org/thinking-sensing-and-behaving/sleep/2020/night-owl-chronotypes-in-a-morning-lark-world-122120" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;pushed these natural variations to extremes&lt;/a&gt;. Where morning larks and night owls might have been separated by just a few hours in pre-industrial times, we now see spreads of up to 12 hours between extreme chronotypes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This matters because fighting your natural chronotype is like swimming upstream—possible, but exhausting. If you're a night owl forced into a morning lark's schedule, those 3 AM wake-ups might be your body's protest against social jet lag, the disconnect between your internal clock and external demands.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;What your body might be trying to tell you&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After tracking my sleep for months (yes, I became that person), patterns emerged. The nights I woke at 3 AM weren't random—they followed days of high stress, late-night screen time, or when I'd pushed through exhaustion instead of listening to my body's signals.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Research backs this up. Studies show that chronic stress creates a vicious cycle: elevated cortisol disrupts sleep, poor sleep increases stress, and round and round we go. It's like being stuck in a biological escape room where the only exit is better sleep hygiene—which feels impossible when you can't sleep.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But it's not just stress. These wake-ups can signal:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Accumulated sleep debt&lt;/strong&gt;: Your body cycles through sleep stages differently to compensate for chronic under-sleeping&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Blood sugar fluctuations&lt;/strong&gt;: Late-night snacks or skipped dinners can cause metabolic disruptions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Circadian misalignment&lt;/strong&gt;: Your internal clock is out of sync with your lifestyle&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hormonal shifts&lt;/strong&gt;: Particularly relevant during perimenopause or other life transitions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;The recovery paradox&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here's where it gets frustrating: the research on "catching up" on sleep is mixed at best. That weekend sleep-in you're banking on? It might not fix the problem. One study found it takes &lt;a href="https://www.health.harvard.edu/blog/weekend-catch-up-sleep-wont-fix-the-effects-of-sleep-deprivation-on-your-waistline-2019092417861" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;four days to recover&lt;/a&gt; from just one hour of lost sleep.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The science suggests that consistency matters more than marathon sleep sessions. Your circadian rhythm craves routine like a houseplant craves sunlight—regular, predictable, and at the right times.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;What actually works (based on science and self-experimentation)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After months of trial and error, here's what moved the needle:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Light is everything&lt;/strong&gt;: Our circadian rhythms evolved with natural light cycles. Getting bright light exposure within 30 minutes of waking and dimming lights 2-3 hours before bed made a bigger difference than any supplement.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The cortisol management game&lt;/strong&gt;: Since that 3 AM cortisol spike is inevitable, the goal is managing your baseline. Regular exercise (but not too late), stress-reduction practices that actually work for you (not just what Instagram wellness influencers suggest), and protecting your wind-down time all help keep that cortisol cup from overflowing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Temperature hacking&lt;/strong&gt;: Your body temperature naturally drops during sleep. Keeping the bedroom cool (around 65-68°F) and taking a warm shower before bed (the subsequent cooling mimics your natural temperature drop) can help maintain sleep.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Embrace your chronotype&lt;/strong&gt;: Stop fighting your genetics. If you're a natural night owl, trying to become a 5 AM workout person might be making things worse. Work with your biology, not against it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;The bigger picture&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Those 3 AM wake-ups taught me something important: our bodies are constantly communicating with us, but we've gotten terrible at listening. In our always-on culture, we treat sleep like an inconvenience to optimize rather than a fundamental biological need.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The research is clear: sleep isn't just about quantity—it's about quality, timing, and consistency. Those early morning wake-ups might be annoying, but they're also data points in understanding your body's needs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After implementing these changes, my 3 AM wake-ups shifted from nightly occurrences to occasional visitors. More importantly, I stopped seeing them as failures and started seeing them as feedback. Sometimes I still find myself staring at the ceiling in the pre-dawn darkness, but now I know it's not just insomnia—it's biology trying to find balance in an unbalanced world.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The solution isn't perfection; it's paying attention. Your body is remarkably good at self-regulation when you give it the right conditions. Those 3 AM wake-ups? They're not your enemy. They're your internal clock asking for a conversation about how you're living your days.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And maybe, just maybe, it's time we started listening.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="vegou-quiz-after-article" id="vegou-441597890"&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;What’s Your Plant-Powered Archetype?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ever wonder what your everyday habits say about your deeper purpose—and how they ripple out to impact the planet?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This 90-second quiz reveals the plant-powered role you’re here to play, and the tiny shift that makes it even more powerful.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;12 fun questions. Instant results. Surprisingly accurate.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;						&lt;/div&gt;
					&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>VegOut</author><pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 04:01:54 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi1wFBVV95cUxONmRldWtJSVJTUF96MlJ6eGctX0EyckRQc2xPRTdiSzItMjdVSHhuSnBScmVUSVppNzVXU0hrM0hhZl9RajlWamN0NkowV1AtZm9UV29GclZ4a2NDY3VKVm5wME1tYXg5ZHhkX3c1b052VGVzc19DX2JFMnlZbmw2VTltNVRyM0tHNHhEZ25kc2Fmam45NFNhU3BoWkQxdzJQa2xNa0RuMGxWbkZraGhReFdKS3M1bDB1cU5oVmFkckFsR2IyNGc4Ti1KbW1nN1hhcEdYZmJaWQ</guid></item><item><title>病人的单纯视力可以触发我们的免疫系统- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMilAFBVV95cUxQNVFud1l4SG5oV015emFLSzhHMGQ5bzg0ZWRaWTcybUFudHVTcUJSQWZJc1dXMUR3QXlFLUNTd3RZVm8zZGQzYjhHcmlHeWM4MEFyVXU2bDlURHpmTlhGT2M1dEtqaDJUUTU4Z2hoME9SWlBSeG9TMC02N2RmU0FWSmdkVFJIMlhPdS1kSnlYVFUxYkxp?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The mere sight of a sick person may set off an alarm system in your brain and body, even if they are too far away to infect you.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A series of experiments using virtual reality headsets has now revealed just how  "&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1038/s41593-025-02008-y"&gt;exquisitely sensitive&lt;/a&gt;" our brains are to symptoms of sickness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When participants saw a virtual avatar at varying distances showing clear signs of illness (like a feverish rash), their brains suddenly kicked into gear and their immune systems were put on high alert.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When they saw a healthy, neutral-looking avatar, on the other hand, their brains did not show the same activation patterns, and their bloodwork lacked an immediate elevation in immune markers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/the-mere-thought-of-being-hungry-could-alter-your-immune-system?utm_source=SA_article&amp;amp;utm_campaign=related_link"&gt;The Mere Thought of Being Hungry Could Alter Your Immune System&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some of these markers are known as innate lymphoid cells (ILCs). ILCs can spike in the blood when the body is directly exposed to a pathogen, but all&lt;span&gt; it took in this case was the sight of a virtual infection and the mere prospect of exposure.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Together, these data show that ILCs react to infections not only when they are detected in the body but also when they are processed as a potential threat approaching the body," &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1038/s41593-025-02008-y"&gt;write&lt;/a&gt; the international team of authors, led by immunologist Sara Trabanelli from the University of Lausanne in Switzerland.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_169460" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-169460" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/07/VRHeadsetExperiment-642x204.png" alt="VR Headset Trial" class="size-medium wp-image-169460" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/07/VRHeadsetExperiment-642x204.png 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/07/VRHeadsetExperiment-1024x326.png 1024w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/07/VRHeadsetExperiment-768x244.png 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/07/VRHeadsetExperiment-1536x489.png 1536w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/07/VRHeadsetExperiment-2048x652.png 2048w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/07/VRHeadsetExperiment-600x191.png 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-169460" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;a) Participants were first exposed to a neutral avatar (baseline) and then shown either neutral, infectious, or fearful avatars. b) Avatars were presented at one of five distances (D5 = far, D1 = near). (Trabanelli et al., &lt;span&gt;&lt;em&gt;Nature Neuroscience, &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;2025)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;When researchers used  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/artificial-intelligence" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73092" data-postid="169457" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;machine learning&lt;/a&gt; to statistically analyze the results of their experiments, they found that the brain's threat-detection activity could largely explain the immune response.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;After seeing a virtual sick person at a distance, the brains of participants lit up in a unique pattern, which was not seen when the avatar had a fearful expression or a neutral expression.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The sick avatars that were furthest away elicited the strongest response from the brain's network. Interestingly, some of these activated areas are the same as those that can be triggered after a  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/what-is-influenza" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="103478" data-postid="169457" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;flu&lt;/a&gt; vaccine is given.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The findings suggest that when the brain senses a looming threat, it responds rapidly, triggering activity in brain parts like the hypothalamus, which then communicate with the immune system.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This gives the body time to put up a fight.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_169991" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-169991" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/07/reaction_times_sensory_642.jpg" alt="graphs" class="wp-image-169991 size-full" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/07/reaction_times_sensory_642.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/07/reaction_times_sensory_642-313x415.jpg 313w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/07/reaction_times_sensory_642-600x794.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-169991" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Graphs showing the greatest difference between control and test reaction times were during the infection cohort trial. (Trabanelli et al., &lt;em&gt;Nature Neuroscience&lt;/em&gt;, 2025)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;The recent experiments took place among 248 healthy adults in total, and in one of the trials, participants wearing VR were asked to press a button when they felt a touch on their face.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When their VR sets featured a virtual sick person, participants pressed the button faster upon feeling the touch than when they saw a neutral or fearful avatar.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This suggests that their brains are primed because of the sight of sickness. The anticipation probably evolved as a fight-or-flight response, the researchers suspect, though they caution there's still a lot to resolve, including how perceived infectiousness and disgust interact.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"These findings suggest an integrated neuro–immune reaction in humans toward infection threats, not solely following physical contact," &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1038/s41593-025-02008-y"&gt;conclude&lt;/a&gt; the authors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thanks to our brains for staying vigilant on our behalf.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The study was published in &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1038/s41593-025-02008-y"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Nature Neuroscience&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 02:54:35 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilAFBVV95cUxQNVFud1l4SG5oV015emFLSzhHMGQ5bzg0ZWRaWTcybUFudHVTcUJSQWZJc1dXMUR3QXlFLUNTd3RZVm8zZGQzYjhHcmlHeWM4MEFyVXU2bDlURHpmTlhGT2M1dEtqaDJUUTU4Z2hoME9SWlBSeG9TMC02N2RmU0FWSmdkVFJIMlhPdS1kSnlYVFUxYkxp</guid></item><item><title>淋病疫苗开始在英国各地推广- BBC</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiWkFVX3lxTE1IZEFmQnBqN0QwM3RtdE1MQUVncU04MGJnaHduNVlfZENLdVZTSVRVTUhQWFBXOEFQRjNEeElOTGZVQnppTnc3dkR4cms1RmlSaDA0SEJvbUFkZ9IBX0FVX3lxTE0yamk4QlFvcmlPZ1hBR0JmU01KWGltUmNiaHZ0TGtFemNFQ0VRZU5oRVJmc1BOT2pUWk9ZLWVmOXJIaWZXWHpOYVduWGp2bFFjVlNGcnE1Y3lrLTg0emlJ?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article&gt;&lt;p data-component="headline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 fDtfvH"&gt;&lt;h1 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 dfvxux"&gt;'I'm in control of my sexual health' - UK gonorrhoea vaccine rollout begins&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="byline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="byline-new" class="sc-801dd632-0 eSlECZ"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="byline-new-contributors" class="sc-801dd632-12 jSIeFi"&gt;&lt;div class="sc-801dd632-5 kRoBHa"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;span class="sc-801dd632-7 lasLGY"&gt;Josh Parry&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="sc-801dd632-8 hwLppI"&gt;&lt;span&gt;LGBT &amp;amp; Identity Reporter&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 gyQxwn"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="hero-image" class="sc-d1200759-1 kycbVO"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20250728-162205-9b8a2dcb37-web-2.26.0-8/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-d1200759-0 dkIvM hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/0a2b/live/ab1f8e60-6eea-11f0-82b6-9dfc7a8edfd2.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/0a2b/live/ab1f8e60-6eea-11f0-82b6-9dfc7a8edfd2.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/0a2b/live/ab1f8e60-6eea-11f0-82b6-9dfc7a8edfd2.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/0a2b/live/ab1f8e60-6eea-11f0-82b6-9dfc7a8edfd2.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/0a2b/live/ab1f8e60-6eea-11f0-82b6-9dfc7a8edfd2.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/0a2b/live/ab1f8e60-6eea-11f0-82b6-9dfc7a8edfd2.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/0a2b/live/ab1f8e60-6eea-11f0-82b6-9dfc7a8edfd2.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/0a2b/live/ab1f8e60-6eea-11f0-82b6-9dfc7a8edfd2.jpg.webp" loading="eager" alt="Joey Knock A man on the London underground smiles at the camera. He's holding his right arm up to hold onto the handrails and the photo looks like it was taken candidly. He's wearing an orange t-shirt with white stars and round tortoise-shell glasses. " class="sc-d1200759-0 dvfjxj"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-d1200759-2 gwFzuU"&gt;Joey Knock&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jvncPH"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 FPsqq"&gt;Joey decided to pay a private pharmacy for a course of gonorrhoea vaccinations in 2024&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Gonorrhoea vaccines will be widely available from today in sexual health clinics across the UK, in a bid to tackle record-breaking levels of infections.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;The jabs will first be offered to those at highest risk - mostly gay and bisexual men who have a history of multiple sexual partners or sexually transmitted infections.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;NHS England say the roll out is a world-first, and predict it could prevent as many as 100,000 cases, potentially saving the NHS almost £8m over the next decade.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;The Terrence Higgins Trust, who &lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/articles/cly3el161k3o" class="sc-f9178328-0 bGFWdi"&gt;campaigned for the vaccine&lt;/a&gt; to be introduced in the UK, told the BBC it was "a huge win" for sexual health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Gonorrhoea is a bacterial infection that is transmitted through unprotected sex.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Symptoms can include pain, unusual discharge, inflammation of the genitals and infertility, but in some cases it can have no symptoms at all.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;The NHS says &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.nhs.uk/conditions/gonorrhoea/" class="sc-f9178328-0 bGFWdi"&gt;it can be avoided&lt;/a&gt; by the proper use of condoms and by accepting the vaccine if offered.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Doctors &lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/health-65810160" class="sc-f9178328-0 bGFWdi"&gt;are becoming increasingly worried&lt;/a&gt; about the number of infections, and hope the vaccine, which is 30-40% effective, will also help slow the &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.gov.uk/government/publications/meningococcal-b-vaccination-for-the-prevention-of-gonorrhoea-jcvi-advice-10-november/jcvi-advice-on-the-use-of-meningococcal-b-vaccination-for-the-prevention-of-gonorrhoea" class="sc-f9178328-0 bGFWdi"&gt;growing number of antibiotic-resistant cases.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;The vaccine, known as the 4CMenB vaccine, was designed for preventing meningitis B in babies, but the bacteria that causes the two diseases are so closely related that the jab is also effective against gonorrhoea.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;There were more than 85,000 cases of gonorrhoea in 2023 - the highest since records began almost 100 years ago.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;One of those diagnosed was Joey Knock, who says the infection gave him diarrhoea, made him feel "wiped out" and led to him taking time off work to recover.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;He told BBC News: "I discussed it with my friends and I definitely had worse symptoms [than them] with it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;"I felt really bad, I couldn't keep food down and I just felt totally run down."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 hoQmHM"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-d1200759-1 kycbVO"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20250728-162205-9b8a2dcb37-web-2.26.0-8/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-d1200759-0 dkIvM hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/ee80/live/0ff579f0-6ee4-11f0-b6d6-fddc6f14031a.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/ee80/live/0ff579f0-6ee4-11f0-b6d6-fddc6f14031a.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/ee80/live/0ff579f0-6ee4-11f0-b6d6-fddc6f14031a.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/ee80/live/0ff579f0-6ee4-11f0-b6d6-fddc6f14031a.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/ee80/live/0ff579f0-6ee4-11f0-b6d6-fddc6f14031a.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/ee80/live/0ff579f0-6ee4-11f0-b6d6-fddc6f14031a.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/ee80/live/0ff579f0-6ee4-11f0-b6d6-fddc6f14031a.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/ee80/live/0ff579f0-6ee4-11f0-b6d6-fddc6f14031a.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Joey Knock A man smiles at the camera at a music festival. He is wearing a green crocheted bowler hat, pink thick-rimmed sunglasses and a purple bandana around his neck. He's also wearing a mesh cropped tanktop and a rainbow coloured jacket covered in different coloured tassels. People can be seen in the background enjoying the festival." class="sc-d1200759-0 dvfjxj"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-d1200759-2 gwFzuU"&gt;Joey Knock&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jvncPH"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 FPsqq"&gt;Joey says the severity of his gonorrhoea symptoms interfered with daily life&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Because he has many sexual partners, the 35-year-old decided to pay a private pharmacy for a course of gonorrhoea vaccinations in February 2024 before travelling abroad to a festival.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;He paid £220 and says he's glad he did it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;"It helps knowing that I'm taking control of my sexual health and doing what I can to stay safe and practise safer sex and be much less worried about the severity of the symptoms," he says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Joey says he uses the protection the vaccine offers him alongside other methods of safer sex, including taking PrEP, a drug which helps prevent HIV, and DoxyPep - antibiotics taken after sex to prevent bacterial STIs, a treatment not widely available on the NHS.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;He says he also occasionally uses condoms - but sees the vaccine as an extra tool to keep him safe in situations where he or his partner doesn't want to use them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Since being vaccinated, Joey has been re-infected with gonorrhoea but says the symptoms were much less severe.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;He told the BBC: "I've been able to get on with my day and it has just become something much more manageable, and getting tested regularly and knowing my body really helps too."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 hoQmHM"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-d1200759-1 kycbVO"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20250728-162205-9b8a2dcb37-web-2.26.0-8/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-d1200759-0 dkIvM hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/27bc/live/ff490d80-6ee1-11f0-b6d6-fddc6f14031a.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/27bc/live/ff490d80-6ee1-11f0-b6d6-fddc6f14031a.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/27bc/live/ff490d80-6ee1-11f0-b6d6-fddc6f14031a.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/27bc/live/ff490d80-6ee1-11f0-b6d6-fddc6f14031a.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/27bc/live/ff490d80-6ee1-11f0-b6d6-fddc6f14031a.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/27bc/live/ff490d80-6ee1-11f0-b6d6-fddc6f14031a.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/27bc/live/ff490d80-6ee1-11f0-b6d6-fddc6f14031a.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/27bc/live/ff490d80-6ee1-11f0-b6d6-fddc6f14031a.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt='Joey Knock A man wearing round tortoise shell glasses smiles at the camera, perched on the end of a hotel bed. He is wearing a white t-shirt adorned with rainbows on each arm and a picture of Mickey Mouse on the front with the word "Mickey" repeated in different colours in the background.' class="sc-d1200759-0 dvfjxj"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-d1200759-2 gwFzuU"&gt;Joey Knock&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jvncPH"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 FPsqq"&gt;Joey says having the vaccine has given him more confidence and has reduced the severity of his symptoms&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Matthew, a 63-year-old from East Scotland, was diagnosed with gonorrhoea 10 years ago and had a reaction known as &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.nhs.uk/conditions/reactive-arthritis/" class="sc-f9178328-0 bGFWdi"&gt;reactive arthritis&lt;/a&gt; - extreme pain in your joints caused by your body's reaction to an infection.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;He told the BBC that the experience, which has caused lasting damage to some of his fingers and toes, was so painful it's left him fearful of becoming re-infected and has impacted his mental health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;He says: "I'm constantly looking for symptoms and I'm constantly aware of it, and I feel a bit like I used to do in the 1980s when I was constantly fretting about HIV.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;"I'd get some sort of cough and think 'oh my god, what's happening?'"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;He is hoping to be one of the first people to get a vaccine in order to give himself and his sexual partners more protection.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;"You're not just protecting yourself, you're protecting your partners.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;"I think it will also relieve some of the burden on sexual health services, it's getting difficult to get appointments so if it can work to reduce the incidence of STIs I think it's really worth it."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Richard Angell, chief executive of the Terrence Higgins Trust, a leading sexual health charity, told the BBC the vaccine was a "remarkable addition to our toolkit on sexual health".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Dr Amanda Doyle, NHS national director for primary care and community services, said it was important "everyone eligible takes up the offer through sexual health services" in order to "keep each other safe".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;"It's a real step forward for sexual health," she added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;People who may be eligible for the vaccine are being asked to contact &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.nhs.uk/nhs-services/sexual-health-services/find-a-sexual-health-clinic/" class="sc-f9178328-0 bGFWdi"&gt;their local sexual health clinic&lt;/a&gt; for more information.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BBC</author><pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 00:10:53 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiWkFVX3lxTE1IZEFmQnBqN0QwM3RtdE1MQUVncU04MGJnaHduNVlfZENLdVZTSVRVTUhQWFBXOEFQRjNEeElOTGZVQnppTnc3dkR4cms1RmlSaDA0SEJvbUFkZ9IBX0FVX3lxTE0yamk4QlFvcmlPZ1hBR0JmU01KWGltUmNiaHZ0TGtFemNFQ0VRZU5oRVJmc1BOT2pUWk9ZLWVmOXJIaWZXWHpOYVduWGp2bFFjVlNGcnE1Y3lrLTg0emlJ</guid></item><item><title>这个令人惊讶的健康二人组正在悄悄破坏你的记忆- SciTechDaily</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMijwFBVV95cUxPX29oUW93ekd3bjdUMG5lVUpQbGxXMmVpT2ZQdWllSUhTMDFCQk5OQzFKam5NV3dSVjBSWUZQU1dVOXpLa25oNFBBNTVnelRIWVh3WEpRM3JualF6ZDFKeTMwWC1ZSGZMZGVoLTVibWZab0RjM2dncjhpRlVkdjR0d3hlWlFYY19hMWRDLW85QQ?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>SciTechDaily</author><pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2025 22:11:41 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijwFBVV95cUxPX29oUW93ekd3bjdUMG5lVUpQbGxXMmVpT2ZQdWllSUhTMDFCQk5OQzFKam5NV3dSVjBSWUZQU1dVOXpLa25oNFBBNTVnelRIWVh3WEpRM3JualF6ZDFKeTMwWC1ZSGZMZGVoLTVibWZab0RjM2dncjhpRlVkdjR0d3hlWlFYY19hMWRDLW85QQ</guid></item><item><title>PM2.5 ，肺癌高峰背后的基因变化- bangkokpost.com</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMinAFBVV95cUxPUllqNlpyNWFJckZMUUpoQXFjS0Y5Qkk5M1VlemNuNjBWdDB1aG53NmJ1d0JBc2hEcklHMVRMLUdBSXBWXzF0V0p2bWhOYkhsQUhSczNOcTBYWkd2RVZlVXROb0JwTXA4eEdVRklKZDZUY1JnTmR5dkJjajdlUXpTd1RZS29BczRlYjgxNExaSWpXZFZLcTdVSjdiTXo?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-info" id="position-set"&gt;
                &lt;div class="article-info--col"&gt;
                  &lt;p&gt;PUBLISHED : 4 Aug 2025 at 05:06&lt;/p&gt;
                                    
                &lt;/div&gt;
                
              &lt;/div&gt;

              
              
              &lt;div class="article-content"&gt;
                                  &lt;div class="box-img"&gt;
                    &lt;figure&gt;
                      &lt;img src="https://static.bangkokpost.com/media/content/20250804/c1_3080680_250804050909.jpg" srcset="https://static.bangkokpost.com/media/content/20250804/c1_3080680_250804050909_510.jpg 350w,https://static.bangkokpost.com/media/content/20250804/c1_3080680_250804050909_720.jpg 500w,https://static.bangkokpost.com/media/content/20250804/c1_3080680_250804050909_790.jpg 700w" class="img-fluid lazyload" fetchpriority="auto" decoding="async" alt="Smog covers northern Bangkok in February. (Photo: Chanat Katanyu)"&gt;
                                              &lt;figcaption&gt;
                          Smog covers northern Bangkok in February. (Photo: Chanat Katanyu)                        &lt;/figcaption&gt;
                                          &lt;/figure&gt;
                  &lt;/div&gt;
                                &lt;p&gt;PM2.5 air pollution and mutations in the EGFR gene are major drivers behind the increasing incidence of lung cancer among non-smoking women, particularly across Asia, says a leading Thai oncologist.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Col Assoc Prof Dr Naiyarat Prasongsook, a medical oncologist at Phramongkutklao Hospital, said more than 2.48 million people worldwide are living with lung cancer. Of these, Asia accounts for the largest share of 63.1% or about 1.56 million patients, while Europe reports about 484,000 cases, or 19.5% of the global total.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The surge in lung cancer cases has been steep in recent years. Between 2022 and 2025, the number of newly diagnosed cases rose by 269.4% in Asia and 136.9% in Europe. In Thailand alone, about 23,500 new cases are reported each year. It is also one of the leading causes of cancer-related deaths worldwide with 1.8 million deaths reported annually and a five-year survival rate of only 15–20%.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dr Naiyarat said that while smoking remains the leading cause of lung cancer, responsible for 62% of all cases, other risk factors are becoming more prominent.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Air pollution now accounts for 15% of cases, followed by second-hand smoke at 5.8%, indoor air pollution at 4% and occupational exposure at 4%.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"What's especially concerning is the growing number of non-smoking women diagnosed with lung cancer, particularly in Asia," he said. "Emerging evidence indicates that PM2.5 air pollution and EGFR gene mutations are significant contributors to the disease."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;EGFR (Epidermal Growth Factor Receptor) mutations are more prevalent in Asian populations, where up to 60% of lung cancer patients carry such abnormalities, he said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In Thailand, the figure is even higher --68% -- compared to much lower rates in Western populations. Dr Naiyarat warned that if current trends continue, lung cancer cases among Thai women are projected to reach 11,200 by 2030, a 35% increase from 8,300 cases in 2025.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Sadly, many patients seek medical attention only when symptoms become severe," he noted. "In its early stages, lung cancer often mimics common illnesses, such as persistent coughing, chest pain, fatigue or weight loss."&lt;/p&gt;              &lt;/div&gt;
                            
              
             &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>bangkokpost.com</author><pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2025 22:06:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMinAFBVV95cUxPUllqNlpyNWFJckZMUUpoQXFjS0Y5Qkk5M1VlemNuNjBWdDB1aG53NmJ1d0JBc2hEcklHMVRMLUdBSXBWXzF0V0p2bWhOYkhsQUhSczNOcTBYWkd2RVZlVXROb0JwTXA4eEdVRklKZDZUY1JnTmR5dkJjajdlUXpTd1RZS29BczRlYjgxNExaSWpXZFZLcTdVSjdiTXo</guid></item><item><title>心脏病专家恳请您将这3种经济实惠的食品添加到您的杂货清单中，以改善流通-雅虎主页</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMivAFBVV95cUxNOFg3STE4WGxfSWc0bHRmS1B0QzJWN3MxTnJyeHJ5LXNvb0VhV2Q4ckt6Y2Z6UldJclJRWXlKQ2lKb2dEcFFvbVJEYU1Zd1VIVEh1dy1ZQXNBal9wRkVubVdJcG54ckQ2dWh1S25OVlRFNkpjNTd5OUxNNGhYa3R6TGd2dE1GanczbTktcmh4WjdFQm1GMjR6MDlZRmx2V2lJZlphZUd0aDNxOHdhclpEMnFibTRiMlJIMlpjdA?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="" data-article-body="true"&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;a href="https://parade.com/health/3-foods-for-better-circulation-according-to-cardiologists" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Cardiologists Are Begging You To Add These 3 Budget-Friendly Foods to Your Grocery List for Better Circulation;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Cardiologists Are Begging You To Add These 3 Budget-Friendly Foods to Your Grocery List for Better Circulation&lt;/a&gt; originally appeared on &lt;a href="https://parade.com" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Parade;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Parade&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Cardiovascular disease is the leading cause of death in the &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/heart-disease/data-research/facts-stats/index.html" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:U.S.;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;U.S.&lt;/a&gt; and the &lt;a href="https://www.who.int/health-topics/cardiovascular-diseases#tab=tab_1" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:world;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;world&lt;/a&gt;, making it an important health condition to try to prevent. But cardiovascular disease is made up of a complicated group of conditions, so it’s often difficult to pin down just one cause. Still, cardiologists say that the &lt;a href="https://parade.com/health/best-diet-for-lowering-heart-attack-risk-according-to-cardiologists" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:right diet;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;right diet&lt;/a&gt; can help lower your risk.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;“A heart-healthy diet is an essential component to improved cardiovascular health,” says &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.rwjbh.org/doctors/james-d-mills-md/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Dr. James D. Mills, MD;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Dr. James D. Mills, MD&lt;/a&gt;,&lt;/strong&gt; director of General &amp;amp; Preventive Cardiology at Rutgers Robert Wood Johnson Medical School. Cardiovascular health involves several elements, but good circulation is crucial to supporting your heart and lowering the risk of blood clots. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The &lt;a href="https://www.heart.org/en/healthy-living/healthy-eating/eat-smart/nutrition-basics/aha-diet-and-lifestyle-recommendations" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:American Heart Association;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;American Heart Association&lt;/a&gt; (AHA) provides a lot of guidance on the best eating plan to follow to support cardiovascular health, but there’s a lot of advice to wade through. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;If you’re interested in revamping your diet and want to make quick and easy dietary changes, cardiologists say there are a few foods that can give you a lot of bang for your buck. Bonus: These are budget-friendly, too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://emojipedia.org/stethoscope" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:🩺;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;🩺&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="https://parade.com/newsletters/healthy-now" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:SIGN UP for tips to stay healthy &amp;amp; fit with the top moves, clean eats, health trends &amp;amp; more delivered right to your inbox twice a week;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SIGN UP for tips to stay healthy &amp;amp; fit with the top moves, clean eats, health trends &amp;amp; more delivered right to your inbox twice a week&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="https://emojipedia.org/pill" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:💊;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;💊&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mb-4 text-xl font-bold md:text-2xl"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Best Budget-Friendly Foods for Circulation&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The AHA &lt;a href="https://www.heart.org/en/healthy-living/healthy-eating/eat-smart/nutrition-basics/aha-diet-and-lifestyle-recommendations" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:urges;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;urges &lt;/a&gt;people to eat a &lt;a href="https://parade.com/1208358/margie-zable-fisher/plant-based-diet-foods/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:plant-forward diet;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;plant-forward diet&lt;/a&gt; for good cardiovascular health. That’s why beans, beets, and berries are good options to add to your grocery cart, according to cardiologists.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;All of these foods provide a variety of nutritional benefits, along with specific elements that make them good for the cardiovascular system, according to &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.memorialcare.org/providers/cheng-han-chen" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Dr. Cheng-Han Chen, MD;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Dr. Cheng-Han Chen, MD&lt;/a&gt;,&lt;/strong&gt; interventional cardiologist and medical director of the Structural Heart Program at MemorialCare Saddleback Medical Center in Laguna Hills, CA.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://parade.com/health/when-to-start-eating-after-waking-up-to-lose-weight" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Exactly When To Start Eating After Waking up if You’re Trying To Lose Weight, According to Experts;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Exactly When To Start Eating After Waking up if You’re Trying To Lose Weight, According to Experts&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="mb-4 text-lg font-bold"&gt;Beans&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“&lt;a href="https://parade.com/1316849/kristamarshall/black-bean-recipes/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Beans;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Beans &lt;/a&gt;are a good, well-rounded food source,” Dr. Chen says. There has been a big push in the dietary community for Americans to eat more beans. A &lt;a href="https://www.dietaryguidelines.gov/sites/default/files/2024-12/Part%20E.%20Chapter%201_Overarching%20Advice_FINAL_508.pdf" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:report;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;report &lt;/a&gt;released in 2024 from an advisory committee to the United States Department of Agriculture (USDA) suggests adjusting the Dietary Guidelines for Americans to recommend that people have at least 2.5 cups of beans and lentils a week. (&lt;a href="https://www.dietaryguidelines.gov/sites/default/files/2020-12/Dietary_Guidelines_for_Americans_2020-2025.pdf" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Current recommendations;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Current recommendations&lt;/a&gt; suggest having 1.5 cups of beans and lentils a week.)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Rich in &lt;a href="https://parade.com/1172611/ericasweeney/foods-high-in-soluble-fiber/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:soluble fiber;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;soluble fiber&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://parade.com/health/magnesium-for-sleep" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:magnesium;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;magnesium&lt;/a&gt;, and plant-based protein, beans help lower LDL (“bad”) cholesterol and improve blood vessel function,” says &lt;a href="https://wexnermedical.osu.edu/find-a-doctor/ragavendra-baliga-mbbs-23370" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Dr. Ragavendra Baliga, MBBS;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Dr. Ragavendra Baliga, MBBS&lt;/a&gt;, a cardiologist at The Ohio State University Wexner Medical Center. They also have a low glycemic load, meaning they won’t cause blood sugar spikes, he says. The magnesium in beans, along with their potassium content, helps to regulate blood pressure, too, points out &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.northwell.edu/find-care/find-a-doctor/dr-catherine-ruth-weinberg-md-mba-1174757199" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Dr. Catherine Weinberg, MD;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Dr. Catherine Weinberg, MD&lt;/a&gt;,&lt;/strong&gt; director of Adult Congenital Heart Disease at Northwell’s Lenox Hill Hospital.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://parade.com/health/high-protein-food-to-avoid-over-60-according-to-cardiologists" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Cardiologists Are Begging You To Eat Less of This High-Protein Food if You’re Over 60;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Cardiologists Are Begging You To Eat Less of This High-Protein Food if You’re Over 60&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="mb-4 text-lg font-bold"&gt;Beets&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Beets are also a circulation-friendly food, according to Dr. Mills. “Beets contain nitrates, which lead to higher levels of circulating nitric oxide,” he says. Nitric oxide helps widen blood vessels, ultimately improving their function, Dr. Mills explains. “They also have anti-inflammatory and antioxidant effects,” which can support circulation even more, says &lt;a href="http://medicine.buffalo.edu/content/medicine/faculty/profile.html?ubit=abcurtis" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Dr. Anne B. Curtis, MD;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dr. Anne B. Curtis, MD&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, cardiologist and professor at the University at Buffalo Jacobs School of Medicine and Biomedical Sciences.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="mb-4 text-lg font-bold"&gt;Berries&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;a href="https://parade.com/health/best-berry-for-heart-health-according-to-cardiologists" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Berries;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Berries&lt;/a&gt; also help your body produce nitric oxide, Dr. Weinberg says. “That tells your blood vessels to relax and widen,” she says. Berries are packed with polyphenols—compounds that act like antioxidants—and can help to reduce inflammation in the body, Dr. Baliga says. Chronic inflammation is &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC11592557/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:linked;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;linked&lt;/a&gt; to a range of serious health conditions, including cardiovascular disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://parade.com/health/i-am-71-in-the-best-shape-of-life-my-workout-routine" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:‘I’m 71 Years Old and in the Best Shape of My Life—Here’s Every Detail of My Workout Routine’;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;‘I’m 71 Years Old and in the Best Shape of My Life—Here’s Every Detail of My Workout Routine’&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mb-4 text-xl font-bold md:text-2xl"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Other Foods to Eat for Good Cardiovascular Health&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;There are a few other things to keep in mind around your diet if you’re trying to support good circulation and cardiovascular health as a whole. Dr. Weinberg suggests focusing on an anti-inflammatory diet, like the &lt;a href="https://parade.com/962840/marysauer/mediterranean-diet-plan/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Mediterranean diet;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Mediterranean diet&lt;/a&gt;. “Include omega-rich fatty fish, plenty of colorful vegetables and olive oil as your primary fat,” she says. “Sprinkle in some daily nuts and seeds for their heart-protective compounds. Try adding fermented foods like yogurt and kimchi, as emerging research connects gut health with heart health.”&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;It’s best to limit &lt;a href="https://parade.com/health/i-tried-cutting-out-ultra-processed-food-for-a-week" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:ultra-processed foods;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;ultra-processed foods&lt;/a&gt;, too, Dr. Chen says. These often have higher amounts of sodium and fat, with minimal nutritional value, he points out. “Try to avoid these as much as possible,” Dr. Chen says. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dr. Baliga also suggests focusing on whole foods, limiting added sugars and sodium, and being aware of portion sizes. “What we eat is as important as how consistently we eat it,” he says. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;It may take some tinkering to find the best diet for you, Dr. Weinberg says. “The key to lasting success is the 'smart swap,’” she says. “Instead of feeling deprived by just cutting out unhealthy foods, actively find satisfying and healthier replacements. This approach is what makes a heart-healthy diet sustainable.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Up Next: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://parade.com/health/popular-nighttime-habit-that-spikes-blood-pressure" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Related: This Popular Nighttime Habit Could Spike Your Blood Pressure, Cardiologists Warn;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Related: This Popular Nighttime Habit Could Spike Your Blood Pressure, Cardiologists Warn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mb-4 text-xl font-bold md:text-2xl"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sources:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul class="mb-4"&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.rwjbh.org/doctors/james-d-mills-md/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Dr. James D. Mills, MD;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Dr. James D. Mills, MD&lt;/a&gt;, director of General &amp;amp; Preventive Cardiology at Rutgers Robert Wood Johnson Medical School.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.memorialcare.org/providers/cheng-han-chen" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Dr. Cheng-Han Chen, MD;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Dr. Cheng-Han Chen, MD&lt;/a&gt;, interventional cardiologist and medical director of the Structural Heart Program at MemorialCare Saddleback Medical Center in Laguna Hills, CA&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;a href="https://parade.com/health/3-foods-for-better-circulation-according-to-cardiologists" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Cardiologists Are Begging You To Add These 3 Budget-Friendly Foods to Your Grocery List for Better Circulation;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Cardiologists Are Begging You To Add These 3 Budget-Friendly Foods to Your Grocery List for Better Circulation&lt;/a&gt; first appeared on Parade on Aug 3, 2025&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;i&gt;This story was originally reported by &lt;a href="https://parade.com/health/3-foods-for-better-circulation-according-to-cardiologists" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Parade;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Parade&lt;/a&gt; on Aug 3, 2025, where it first appeared.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Yahoo Home</author><pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2025 21:25:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMivAFBVV95cUxNOFg3STE4WGxfSWc0bHRmS1B0QzJWN3MxTnJyeHJ5LXNvb0VhV2Q4ckt6Y2Z6UldJclJRWXlKQ2lKb2dEcFFvbVJEYU1Zd1VIVEh1dy1ZQXNBal9wRkVubVdJcG54ckQ2dWh1S25OVlRFNkpjNTd5OUxNNGhYa3R6TGd2dE1GanczbTktcmh4WjdFQm1GMjR6MDlZRmx2V2lJZlphZUd0aDNxOHdhclpEMnFibTRiMlJIMlpjdA</guid></item><item><title>如果您想醒来时感到精神焕发，精力充沛，请告别这7种睡前习惯- VegOut</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiywFBVV95cUxNWUtMSmRZUHdMNGlyMzdPaXBBOUFsU3ZPTnhWbjlaZGxmQ3BQV1lrcDRYTENSVnhxT0JPRTAySWdHd0pBaWVnU3k2ZDdPVzdJX00xeng4QUhkaDdjcDFaYnhmY3RGazlJY2RtQzJHc1JXcm1YQUlYU3BXMFRSTV9BaWFTMjNjMTByWWEtSWZSODJYSjZEMTFkemh1Yl9ESm1kRFV5SWFQeWJVT21fY1NmYm5iSmUzZWZBQUllUnd4NEVaQUJ2NUw2RUJRZw?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="page__content mt-4"&gt;
							&lt;p data-start="301" data-end="361"&gt;Let’s be real: waking up &lt;em data-start="326" data-end="337"&gt;refreshed&lt;/em&gt; is the new luxury flex.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="363" data-end="576"&gt;In a world of hustle culture, 5 a.m. club influencers, and productivity gurus downing mushroom coffee, we’ve glorified early mornings—but no one’s talking about the stuff we do the &lt;em data-start="544" data-end="558"&gt;night before&lt;/em&gt; that wrecks them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="578" data-end="866"&gt;Sleep isn’t just about how many hours you get. It’s about &lt;em data-start="636" data-end="641"&gt;how&lt;/em&gt; you wind down. And most of us are unknowingly doing things before bed that sabotage our sleep quality. Then we wake up groggy, drag ourselves through the day, and wonder if we need to cut carbs or start microdosing sunlight.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="868" data-end="944"&gt;Spoiler: You probably just need to stop doing these seven things before bed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 data-start="951" data-end="1004"&gt;1. &lt;strong data-start="958" data-end="1004"&gt;Doomscrolling like it’s your part-time job&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p data-start="1006" data-end="1305"&gt;Look, I get it. You open TikTok to check one recipe, and suddenly you’re 43 videos deep into “people who disappeared mysteriously and were never found.” Or worse, the algorithm hits you with a “clean girl” nighttime routine while you’re lying in three-day-old pajamas next to a half-eaten rice cake.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="1307" data-end="1501"&gt;Doomscrolling might &lt;em data-start="1327" data-end="1333"&gt;feel&lt;/em&gt; like relaxing, but it’s mentally overstimulating. The constant hit of information—news, drama, opinions, memes—keeps your brain in high-alert mode, not wind-down mode.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="1503" data-end="1800"&gt;&lt;strong data-start="1503" data-end="1526"&gt;What to do instead:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br data-start="1526" data-end="1529"&gt;Set a “digital sunset.” That means putting your phone on airplane mode or Do Not Disturb 30-60 minutes before bed. Replace the scroll with something analog—a book, journaling, or even stretching. Yes, it’ll feel weird at first. Withdrawal is real. But so is better sleep.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 data-start="1807" data-end="1874"&gt;2. &lt;strong data-start="1814" data-end="1874"&gt;Eating late-night snacks that mess with your sleep cycle&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p data-start="1876" data-end="2126"&gt;This one hurts me personally because I’ve been known to do late-night reviews of vegan cheesy puffs. But here’s the truth: what you eat before bed &lt;em data-start="2023" data-end="2032"&gt;matters&lt;/em&gt;. Heavy meals, spicy food, and high-sugar snacks can disrupt your body’s natural sleep rhythm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="2128" data-end="2318"&gt;They mess with your digestion, blood sugar, and even core temperature—all things that impact how deeply you sleep and whether you wake up feeling like a slightly haunted version of yourself.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="2320" data-end="2556"&gt;&lt;strong data-start="2320" data-end="2332"&gt;The fix:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br data-start="2332" data-end="2335"&gt;If you &lt;em data-start="2342" data-end="2348"&gt;must&lt;/em&gt; snack, stick with something light and sleep-friendly: a banana with almond butter, a few walnuts, or chamomile tea with oat milk. Just don’t turn your bed into a snack lounge. Trust me, crumbs kill the vibe.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 data-start="2563" data-end="2605"&gt;3. &lt;strong data-start="2570" data-end="2605"&gt;Drinking alcohol to “wind down”&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p data-start="2607" data-end="2748"&gt;Ah yes, the sneaky one. Alcohol might &lt;em data-start="2645" data-end="2651"&gt;feel&lt;/em&gt; like a sedative—it helps you fall asleep faster—but it’s actually a sleep disruptor in disguise.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="2750" data-end="2987"&gt;That glass of wine or nightcap lowers sleep quality, interrupts REM cycles, and often leads to 3 a.m. wakeups with a racing heart and regret. You might fall asleep quicker, but you’ll wake up feeling like you got hit by a kombucha truck.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="2989" data-end="3208"&gt;&lt;strong data-start="2989" data-end="3013"&gt;What to try instead:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br data-start="3013" data-end="3016"&gt;If you want a wind-down ritual, swap the booze for a calming alternative. I’m a fan of magnesium drinks, herbal teas, or even a vegan moon milk blend (yes, that’s a thing, and it’s delicious).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 data-start="3215" data-end="3272"&gt;4. &lt;strong data-start="3222" data-end="3272"&gt;Taking your stress to bed with you (literally)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p data-start="3274" data-end="3328"&gt;You can’t fight cortisol with a lavender pillow spray.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="3330" data-end="3529"&gt;If your mind is racing with thoughts like “Did I reply to that email?” or “Why did I say that thing in 2017?”—your body isn’t going to shift into sleep mode. You’re still mentally in fight-or-flight.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="3531" data-end="3694"&gt;Many of us go from work to Netflix to bed without ever processing the stress of the day. That unprocessed energy doesn’t vanish—it just keeps spinning until 2 a.m.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="3696" data-end="3937"&gt;&lt;strong data-start="3696" data-end="3713"&gt;The solution:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br data-start="3713" data-end="3716"&gt;Introduce a “mental cleanse” before bed. This could be journaling, breathwork, or a simple brain dump—write down everything you’re thinking, even if it’s chaotic. Let the page hold your stress so your bed doesn’t have to.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 data-start="3944" data-end="4015"&gt;5. &lt;strong data-start="3951" data-end="4015"&gt;Having zero bedtime routine (and thinking it doesn’t matter)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p data-start="4017" data-end="4075"&gt;Not having a routine is a routine—it just happens to suck.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="4077" data-end="4261"&gt;Your body thrives on rhythm. If you’re crashing at different times each night, doing random things before bed, and expecting to sleep like a baby, you’re setting yourself up for chaos.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="4263" data-end="4354"&gt;Think of your bedtime routine as a signal to your body: “Hey, it’s safe to power down now.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="4356" data-end="4594"&gt;&lt;strong data-start="4356" data-end="4374"&gt;What to build:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br data-start="4374" data-end="4377"&gt;Start small. Choose 2–3 calming things to do every night before bed: light stretching, skincare, reading, or listening to a calming playlist. (I’ve got a lo-fi Spotify mix called &lt;em data-start="4556" data-end="4574"&gt;"Sleepy Peaches"&lt;/em&gt; if you're curious.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="4596" data-end="4696"&gt;Once it becomes a ritual, your body will start recognizing the signs—and falling asleep gets easier.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 data-start="4703" data-end="4781"&gt;6. &lt;strong data-start="4710" data-end="4781"&gt;Using your bed as your office, dining table, or social media throne&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p data-start="4783" data-end="5007"&gt;This one’s for the WFH crew and the snackers (yes, I see you). When your bed becomes a place for eating, scrolling, working, and watching YouTube documentaries on mushroom farming, your brain stops associating it with sleep.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="5009" data-end="5136"&gt;It’s classic Pavlovian conditioning. If your brain links your bed with stimulation, you’ll lie down and feel wired, not sleepy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="5138" data-end="5332"&gt;&lt;strong data-start="5138" data-end="5151"&gt;The move:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br data-start="5151" data-end="5154"&gt;Reclaim your bed as a &lt;em data-start="5176" data-end="5193"&gt;sleep-only zone&lt;/em&gt;. No laptops. No snacks. No reality TV. Treat your bed like a sacred space for rest—and maybe a little romance, but that’s another article.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 data-start="5339" data-end="5412"&gt;7. &lt;strong data-start="5346" data-end="5412"&gt;Skipping wind-down movement because you think you’re too tired&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p data-start="5414" data-end="5654"&gt;Here’s a plot twist: light movement before bed can &lt;em data-start="5465" data-end="5474"&gt;improve&lt;/em&gt; your sleep quality. Many people skip it thinking they need to stay still—but gentle movement can help release tension, calm your nervous system, and transition you into rest mode.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="5656" data-end="5805"&gt;You don’t need to do a full yoga flow. Even 5 minutes of deep breathing while lying on your back with your legs up against the wall can work wonders.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="5807" data-end="5831"&gt;&lt;strong data-start="5807" data-end="5829"&gt;Try this sequence:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul data-start="5832" data-end="5979"&gt;
&lt;li data-start="5832" data-end="5898"&gt;
&lt;p data-start="5834" data-end="5898"&gt;1 minute of box breathing (inhale 4, hold 4, exhale 4, hold 4)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li data-start="5899" data-end="5934"&gt;
&lt;p data-start="5901" data-end="5934"&gt;2 minutes legs-up-the-wall pose&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li data-start="5935" data-end="5979"&gt;
&lt;p data-start="5937" data-end="5979"&gt;2 minutes of neck or shoulder rolls in bed&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p data-start="5981" data-end="6054"&gt;You’ll be surprised how much more grounded—and sleepy—you feel afterward.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 data-start="6061" data-end="6128"&gt;Bonus: The mindset trap of “I’ll just push through it tomorrow”&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p data-start="6130" data-end="6202"&gt;This one isn’t a habit so much as a belief system. And it’s a toxic one.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="6204" data-end="6410"&gt;The idea that you can always catch up, power through, or caffeinate your way into productivity? It’s a myth. Chronic sleep sabotage catches up with you. You’re not weak for needing good sleep. You’re human.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="6412" data-end="6590"&gt;&lt;strong data-start="6412" data-end="6440"&gt;Reframing the narrative:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br data-start="6440" data-end="6443"&gt;You’re not being lazy by prioritizing rest. You’re being &lt;em data-start="6500" data-end="6511"&gt;strategic&lt;/em&gt;. Sleep is the foundation for everything else: focus, creativity, energy, mood.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="6592" data-end="6669"&gt;So let’s stop treating it like an afterthought. Let it be the main character.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 data-start="6676" data-end="6740"&gt;Final thoughts from someone who’s tried all the wrong things&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p data-start="6742" data-end="6890"&gt;I’ve spent too many nights up late reviewing vegan protein cookies and convincing myself that three hours of sleep was “fine.” (Spoiler: it wasn’t.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="6892" data-end="7169"&gt;But once I started changing these bedtime habits—even just one at a time—I stopped waking up feeling like a knocked-over succulent. I felt rested, energized, even &lt;em data-start="7055" data-end="7064"&gt;excited&lt;/em&gt; to get out of bed. (Which is wild, considering I’m not a morning person unless a new lo-fi album drops.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="7171" data-end="7269"&gt;So here’s my challenge to you: pick one of these habits and say goodbye to it this week. Just one.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="7271" data-end="7295"&gt;Then watch what happens.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="7297" data-end="7360"&gt;You might just wake up one morning and realize—you feel &lt;em data-start="7353" data-end="7359"&gt;good&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="7362" data-end="7407"&gt;Like, naturally good. No adaptogens required.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="vegou-quiz-after-article" id="vegou-2138231369"&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;What’s Your Plant-Powered Archetype?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ever wonder what your everyday habits say about your deeper purpose—and how they ripple out to impact the planet?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This 90-second quiz reveals the plant-powered role you’re here to play, and the tiny shift that makes it even more powerful.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;12 fun questions. Instant results. Surprisingly accurate.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;						&lt;/div&gt;
					&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>VegOut</author><pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2025 20:01:54 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiywFBVV95cUxNWUtMSmRZUHdMNGlyMzdPaXBBOUFsU3ZPTnhWbjlaZGxmQ3BQV1lrcDRYTENSVnhxT0JPRTAySWdHd0pBaWVnU3k2ZDdPVzdJX00xeng4QUhkaDdjcDFaYnhmY3RGazlJY2RtQzJHc1JXcm1YQUlYU3BXMFRSTV9BaWFTMjNjMTByWWEtSWZSODJYSjZEMTFkemh1Yl9ESm1kRFV5SWFQeWJVT21fY1NmYm5iSmUzZWZBQUllUnd4NEVaQUJ2NUw2RUJRZw</guid></item><item><title>富含维生素B12的食物，促进大脑健康-印度时报</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMi3wFBVV95cUxNbEVsSEVkVVQ2dUI3V21oVS1Qa3N1NFhlZkl2Q1BDYXdQZk9SVHJhanRPOHpQZkxrTXFHNUU3TzVFQWEwYUgzR1JvcnV5QzltMDZDQ1NqR3k0X2dPMkNvMWZYMUhZZVl1cUpmeHYzSzBqYjk3NW95c2EtT0VrZkViUEU1MlplN1FZOFB0Q2xPYWQ1OElRdlZ3ckEzbl94U0w0bVJhQXBLMVR4SjFKbnhiNWt2bk1qVlNnTlZYSGF2Q193WGVESTlxRmQtQjJKQVdoa1djamVxODBndTlUOE040gHkAUFVX3lxTE5xREFjUlphYzVPUUZOTmstd09RTWtsSW5DTENIenBuZEM0bmtDaHgzb1dLbjlLMTRjOEtzejJkNjNGaU1UVjgtVWFZZVlnVHgwT3kwWU5fOXUzVTB1ZnNZdU14YUZaeFh2cnk0WnFPVmRDMWFHRVFBdHcxR3FlNFE4RVVvVEVxWFZSWk5MalNvdWxsMkFwbHY2eEtXaGZZQVZRdXV2S2hMZllQb1ZPeWRFUU1yWGN3NGl6MVdTZE1sOHBUbnZvR0dyWlU2X3lxNnI3VDFGN2pfWGZpT0JRWk5zS3NlYg?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Think of vitamin B12 as your brain’s behind-the-scenes power source, quietly fueling memory, focus, and mental sharpness while keeping your nerves and red blood cells in check. It’s essential for everything from DNA production to preventing your brain from shrinking (yes, literally).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="4"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="7"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The catch? Your body can’t make it, so you’ve got to outsource it, preferably through what’s on your plate. If you’ve been feeling foggy, tired, or moody, low B12 might be part of the problem. Luckily, nature’s got your back. Here are some B12-rich foods that can help keep your brain switched on and firing smoothly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="10"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="11"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Eggs&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Eggs, especially the yolk, are a great source of B12 and also contain choline, another nutrient your brain loves. A couple of boiled eggs a day can go a long way in supporting memory and cognitive function, especially for vegetarians who might have fewer B12 options.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="13"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="15"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="16"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Fish&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fatty fish like salmon, sardines, and tuna aren’t just heart-friendly, they’re brain boosters, too. Loaded with B12 and omega-3s, these fish help protect brain cells, reduce inflammation, and may slow age-related mental decline.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="19"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="20"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Dairy products&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;From milk to curd, dairy is an easy and familiar source of B12, especially in Indian households. Regular consumption can help improve mental clarity, mood, and alertness, no fancy diet required.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="22"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="23"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Chicken and lean meats&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chicken and other lean meats are not only good sources of protein but also rich in B12. They're easy on digestion, help maintain energy throughout the day, and support both brain and body health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="25"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="26"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Fortified cereals&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many breakfast cereals come fortified with B12, perfect for vegetarians or those on the go. Pick whole-grain varieties for an added bonus of fiber and other brain-nourishing nutrients.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="30"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="32"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="33"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Paneer&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Paneer isn’t just a vegetarian staple, it also delivers a healthy dose of B12. Including it in your meals a few times a week can support nerve function and help clear out mental cobwebs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="35"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="36"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Fortified plant-based milks&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you’re vegan or can’t handle dairy, plant-based milks like soy, almond, or oat often come fortified with B12. They blend easily into smoothies, coffee, or even your morning chai.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="39"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="40"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Liver&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s not everyone’s favorite, but liver is one of the richest natural sources of B12. Even small portions now and then can supercharge your B12 levels and keep your brain in top shape.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="42"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="44"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="45"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Shellfish&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="46"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Clams and oysters are B12 powerhouses. They also bring zinc and iron to the table, nutrients that work together to support brain and nerve health. Even a once-a-week seafood dish can make a difference.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="48"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="49"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Nutritional Yeast&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Often fortified with B12, this cheesy-flavored vegan staple is great sprinkled on popcorn, salads, or pasta. It’s a sneaky but tasty way to keep your B12 levels up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="51"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2025 19:21:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi3wFBVV95cUxNbEVsSEVkVVQ2dUI3V21oVS1Qa3N1NFhlZkl2Q1BDYXdQZk9SVHJhanRPOHpQZkxrTXFHNUU3TzVFQWEwYUgzR1JvcnV5QzltMDZDQ1NqR3k0X2dPMkNvMWZYMUhZZVl1cUpmeHYzSzBqYjk3NW95c2EtT0VrZkViUEU1MlplN1FZOFB0Q2xPYWQ1OElRdlZ3ckEzbl94U0w0bVJhQXBLMVR4SjFKbnhiNWt2bk1qVlNnTlZYSGF2Q193WGVESTlxRmQtQjJKQVdoa1djamVxODBndTlUOE040gHkAUFVX3lxTE5xREFjUlphYzVPUUZOTmstd09RTWtsSW5DTENIenBuZEM0bmtDaHgzb1dLbjlLMTRjOEtzejJkNjNGaU1UVjgtVWFZZVlnVHgwT3kwWU5fOXUzVTB1ZnNZdU14YUZaeFh2cnk0WnFPVmRDMWFHRVFBdHcxR3FlNFE4RVVvVEVxWFZSWk5MalNvdWxsMkFwbHY2eEtXaGZZQVZRdXV2S2hMZllQb1ZPeWRFUU1yWGN3NGl6MVdTZE1sOHBUbnZvR0dyWlU2X3lxNnI3VDFGN2pfWGZpT0JRWk5zS3NlYg</guid></item><item><title>种子油恐慌：当互联网歇斯底里与实际科学相遇- Daily Kos</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiswFBVV95cUxNNWVUWXd4OVVpOEFTS3NrbXVGb3pCQ0F2Rl9TWDgtemRGamdVY0JDZ3d3Y3d3dzh5RXJnbWQzbEZkckgyMkxGVldGQV9KVVpyS0k0MzA4MXkwU3ItSWFmYlo5Ti1oQkJyd0dTMmotT1JsZzVWeWUwOU1FeGxJYmlka3h2UmhaRkg1TTJXZlJtcWpOTFV2am0tU2JaNFZlaVVkeTg2cS00Wk1TcjFtbm9Ocms5RQ?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="story__text"&gt;
          &lt;p&gt;The internet's latest health villain has arrived, and it's hiding in your kitchen cabinet. Seed oils—canola, soy, sunflower, and their botanical brethren—are being blamed for everything from brain fog to heart disease. Social media influencers call them the "Hateful Eight," while wellness gurus claim they're more toxic than industrial waste.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here's the thing: &lt;strong&gt;the science doesn't back up the hysteria.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What's Really Going On Here&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The anti-seed oil movement gained steam around 2020, largely thanks to carnivore diet advocates appearing on popular podcasts. The basic argument goes like this: these oils are processed with chemicals, they're high in omega-6 fatty acids, and they're supposedly causing widespread inflammation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sounds scary. Also sounds like the kind of oversimplified narrative that thrives on social media but crumbles under scientific scrutiny.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Evidence Actually Says...&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/06/250621103446.htm" target="_blank"&gt;2025 study analyzing blood markers from nearly 1,900 people&lt;/a&gt; found that higher levels of linoleic acid—the omega-6 fat that seed oil critics love to hate—were actually &lt;strong&gt;linked to lower inflammation&lt;/strong&gt;, not higher.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href="https://www.heart.org/en/news/2024/08/20/theres-no-reason-to-avoid-seed-oils-and-plenty-of-reasons-to-eat-them" target="_blank"&gt;American Heart Association&lt;/a&gt; states there's "no reason to avoid seed oils and plenty of reasons to eat them." &lt;a href="https://hsph.harvard.edu/news/scientists-debunk-seed-oil-health-risks/" target="_blank"&gt;Harvard researchers&lt;/a&gt; have pushed back on claims that these oils cause health problems ranging from headaches to heart disease.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even more telling: a &lt;a href="https://www.massgeneral.org/news/article/seed-oils-facts-myths" target="_blank"&gt;2017 meta-analysis of randomized controlled trials&lt;/a&gt; found that increased dietary intake of linoleic acid doesn't significantly affect blood concentrations of inflammatory markers. Only about 0.2% of omega-6s actually convert to the compounds that &lt;em&gt;could&lt;/em&gt; theoretically cause inflammation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Real Culprits&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here's what the seed oil panic gets wrong: it confuses correlation with causation. Yes, many foods containing seed oils are unhealthy—think french fries, packaged snacks, and processed junk. But these foods are also loaded with refined carbohydrates, sodium, and sugar.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As &lt;a href="https://hsph.harvard.edu/news/scientists-debunk-seed-oil-health-risks/" target="_blank"&gt;Harvard's Guy Crosby notes&lt;/a&gt;: "Sure, if you cut back on these foods, chances are you're going to feel better." But it's not the seed oils causing the problems—it's the overall nutritional disaster that is ultra-processed food.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Processing Panic&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Critics often point to hexane, a chemical solvent used in oil extraction, as evidence of toxicity. While hexane can be hazardous in gas form, it's used as a liquid solvent and then evaporated off. The EPA studied hexane extensively in the 1980s and found it safe for consumption in the trace amounts that might remain.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Meanwhile, mechanically extracted oils (cold-pressed, expeller-pressed) exist for those who prefer to avoid chemical processing entirely. They're more expensive and have shorter shelf lives, but they're available.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Context Matters&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href="https://public-health.uq.edu.au/article/2024/02/if-you%E2%80%99re-worried-about-inflammation-stop-stressing-about-seed-oils-and-focus-basics" target="_blank"&gt;University of Queensland's research&lt;/a&gt; puts it best: if you're worried about inflammation, "stop stressing about seed oils and focus on the basics."&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Those basics? Eat more fruits, vegetables, nuts, seeds, and lean proteins. Reduce ultra-processed foods. Get adequate omega-3s from fatty fish, walnuts, and flaxseeds. Exercise regularly. Manage stress.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Revolutionary stuff, right?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Political Angle&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It's worth noting that opposition to seed oils has become oddly politicized. &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Seed_oil_misinformation" target="_blank"&gt;Wikipedia documents&lt;/a&gt; how the movement has been "associated with the political right," with some academics describing it as part of "right-wing masculinist discourse."&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When health advice becomes a political identity marker, you know you've wandered far from actual science.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Bottom Line&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Can seed oils be part of a healthy diet? Absolutely. &lt;a href="https://www.massgeneral.org/news/article/seed-oils-facts-myths" target="_blank"&gt;Mass General's research&lt;/a&gt; shows they can be beneficial when used in cooking—stir-frying vegetables, roasting fish, making homemade salad dressings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href="https://www.frontiersin.org/journals/nutrition/articles/10.3389/fnut.2025.1502815/full" target="_blank" title=""&gt;systematic review published in Frontiers in Nutrition&lt;/a&gt; found that seed oils from canola, flaxseed, and sesame can positively influence lipid profiles and glycemic control while potentially reducing oxidative stress.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What Actually Matters&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Instead of obsessing over specific oils, focus on the bigger picture:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Eat mostly whole foods&lt;/strong&gt; rather than processed ones&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Include omega-3 rich foods&lt;/strong&gt; like fatty fish and walnuts&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Use a variety of fats&lt;/strong&gt; including olive oil, avocados, nuts, and yes, seed oils&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cook at home more often&lt;/strong&gt; so you control what goes into your food&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The seed oil panic is a perfect example of how complex nutritional science gets reduced to clickbait headlines and social media soundbites. While the influencers are busy demonizing canola oil, the real dietary villains—ultra-processed foods, excessive sugar, and overall poor eating patterns—continue doing actual damage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Save your energy for the fights that matter.&lt;/strong&gt; Your health will thank you for focusing on evidence-based nutrition rather than the latest internet panic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Want to reduce inflammation? Skip the seed oil hysteria and eat more vegetables. Revolutionary, I know.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Share this article on &lt;a href="https://bsky.app/intent/compose?text=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.dailykos.com%2Fstories%2F2025%2F8%2F3%2F2336602%2F-The-Seed-Oil-Panic-When-Internet-Hysteria-Meets-Actual-Science%3F_%3D2025-08-03T12%3A16%3A39.000-07%3A00" target="_blank"&gt;Bluesky&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/share_channel/?type=reshare&amp;amp;link=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.dailykos.com%2Fstories%2F2025%2F8%2F3%2F2336602%2F-The-Seed-Oil-Panic-When-Internet-Hysteria-Meets-Actual-Science%3F_%3D2025-08-03T12%3A16%3A39.000-07%3A00&amp;amp;app_id=966242223397117&amp;amp;source_surface=external_reshare&amp;amp;display&amp;amp;hashtag#" target="_blank"&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href="https://x.com/intent/tweet?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.dailykos.com%2Fstories%2F2025%2F8%2F3%2F2336602%2F-The-Seed-Oil-Panic-When-Internet-Hysteria-Meets-Actual-Science%3F_%3D2025-08-03T12%3A16%3A39.000-07%3A00" target="_blank"&gt;X/Twitter&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="is-empty-p"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

        &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Daily Kos</author><pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2025 19:16:39 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiswFBVV95cUxNNWVUWXd4OVVpOEFTS3NrbXVGb3pCQ0F2Rl9TWDgtemRGamdVY0JDZ3d3Y3d3dzh5RXJnbWQzbEZkckgyMkxGVldGQV9KVVpyS0k0MzA4MXkwU3ItSWFmYlo5Ti1oQkJyd0dTMmotT1JsZzVWeWUwOU1FeGxJYmlka3h2UmhaRkg1TTJXZlJtcWpOTFV2am0tU2JaNFZlaVVkeTg2cS00Wk1TcjFtbm9Ocms5RQ</guid></item><item><title>骑自行车增强帕金森病的大脑功能-神经科学新闻</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMia0FVX3lxTE03QTBPSVVFQ1RLZWtkU2dUMzNtcnRDWWdILXlhcFYxSDlpUXpaRG9yWnlIYVdoV3E1ZDd0dlF4WjROdXFnRmlacEtuZzNRbWpPQlFBdFRzUTRRTFVmQXN0U05GNVRtREplT3lZ?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content body-color clearfix link-color-wrap"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Questions Answered&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Q: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;How does exercise help Parkinson’s patients at the brain level?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br&gt;A: Long-term cycling regimens appear to alter brain signals in regions affected by Parkinson’s, suggesting neural reactivation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Q: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;What’s different about this study?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br&gt;A: Researchers used implanted deep brain stimulation (DBS) devices to record real-time brain signals before and after exercise, linking motor improvement to potential network-level brain changes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Q: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Did participants see real improvement?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br&gt;A: Yes—after 12 sessions of adaptive cycling, participants showed changes in motor-related brain signals and reported improvements in symptoms like walking and energy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary: &lt;/strong&gt;A new study reveals that long-term adaptive cycling can measurably reshape brain signals in people with Parkinson’s Disease, offering clues into how exercise relieves motor symptoms. Researchers used deep brain stimulation (DBS) implants to track neural activity before and after 12 sessions of dynamic cycling.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While no immediate changes were seen, significant alterations in motor-related brain signals appeared by the end of the program. The findings suggest that exercise may induce broader network-level changes in the brain, helping to restore connections disrupted by Parkinson’s.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Facts:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class="wp-block-list"&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Neural Rewiring:&lt;/strong&gt; After 12 cycling sessions, brain signals in motor regions changed measurably.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Adaptive Exercise:&lt;/strong&gt; Smart bikes adjusted resistance in real time to maximize engagement and motor benefit.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Network-Level Insight:&lt;/strong&gt; Findings hint at brain-wide rewiring beyond the DBS implant zone.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Source: &lt;/strong&gt;University Hospitals Cleveland Medical Center&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;It was the early 2000s when researchers first showed that exercise can help relieve the tremors that are common with Parkinson’s Disease. So far, researchers haven’t been able to explain how exercise helps. But they may be getting closer to an answer.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A novel study conducted at University Hospitals and the VA Northeast Ohio Healthcare System, through its Cleveland Functional Electrical Stimulation (FES) Center, provides clues, as it shows that long-term dynamic exercise programs might have wider restorative effects on the brain signals of Parkinson’s Disease (PD) patients than researchers previously thought.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="wp-block-image size-full"&gt;&lt;picture fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" class="wp-image-112073"&gt; &lt;source type="image/webp" srcset="https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/08/parkinsons-exercise-brain-neuroscience.jpg.webp 1200w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/08/parkinsons-exercise-brain-neuroscience-300x233.jpg.webp 300w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/08/parkinsons-exercise-brain-neuroscience-770x599.jpg.webp 770w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/08/parkinsons-exercise-brain-neuroscience-293x228.jpg.webp 293w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/08/parkinsons-exercise-brain-neuroscience-150x117.jpg.webp 150w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px"&gt;&lt;/source&gt; &lt;img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" src="https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/08/parkinsons-exercise-brain-neuroscience.jpg" alt="This shows an older man on an exercise bike in a hospital. A nurse is at his side. On the cycle is a monitor with a brain game." srcset="https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/08/parkinsons-exercise-brain-neuroscience.jpg 1200w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/08/parkinsons-exercise-brain-neuroscience-300x233.jpg 300w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/08/parkinsons-exercise-brain-neuroscience-770x599.jpg 770w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/08/parkinsons-exercise-brain-neuroscience-293x228.jpg 293w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/08/parkinsons-exercise-brain-neuroscience-150x117.jpg 150w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px"&gt; &lt;/picture&gt;&lt;figcaption class="wp-element-caption"&gt;Researchers did not observe immediate brain signal changes, but after 12 sessions, they saw a measurable change in the brain signals responsible for motor control and movement. Credit: Neuroscience News&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Researchers used recordings from participants’ deep brain stimulation devices to try to assess how long-term exercise programs might be re-activating connections damaged by Parkinson’s Disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Unlike previous studies, this investigation sought to decode the brain changes linked to motor symptom relief; both with the help of second-generation DBS devices and a long-term dynamic cycling exercise regimen in Parkinson’s patients.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Details on the study are published in the June 2025 issue of &lt;em&gt;Clinical Neurophysiology&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The pilot investigation, funded by a VA Merit Award from the Department of Veterans Affairs along with philanthropic funds to the Department of Neurology at University Hospitals (Penni and Stephen Weinberg Chair in Brain Health) was led by UH &amp;amp; VA neurologist Aasef Shaikh MD, PhD, who is also Vice Chair for Research at University Hospitals, Professor of Neurology, and Associate Medical Director of the Cleveland FES Center. Prajakta Joshi, lead author of the article, is a PhD candidate in biomedical engineering at the Shaikh Lab that is part of University Hospitals and Cleveland FES Center at the Louis Stokes Cleveland VA Medical Center.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“We’ve already established over years of study that dynamic cycling regimens are beneficial for treating Parkinson’s tremor,” said Dr. Shaikh. “The latest study adds the use of deep brain stimulation and an ongoing exercise program to visualize how long-term exercise might be rewiring neural connections in the brain.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another unique and critical part of the study, Dr. Shaikh added, was the collaboration between the two medical systems, which provided a larger pool of potential participants for recruiting purposes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About the Study&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Participants with Parkinson’s Disease – including military Veterans – were required to take part in 12 dynamic cycling sessions over a four-week period. All study participants had previously been implanted with deep brain stimulation devices to treat their motor symptoms; while simultaneously measuring the brain signals in the region where the electrodes are implanted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another critical aspect of the study was the adaptive cycling regimen investigators used. This technology empowers the bike to learn how patients perform while biking.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For example, viewing the connected game screen, riders are instructed to pedal up to 80 rpm, and to maintain that speed for about 30 minutes. Meanwhile, their pedaling intensity is shown by an on-screen balloon, and riders have to keep the balloon aloft over water but within specific parameters on screen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, the adaptive quality of the bike keeps riders guessing as to how much effort to apply. The bike’s motor assists them in attaining 80 rpm, but also adds and reduces resistance depending on the rider’s level of effort. Researchers believe this push and pull mechanism is particularly beneficial in treating Parkinson’s symptoms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kent State University PhD candidate Lara Shigo, a co-author of the study, acknowledges 80 RPMs is faster than a person would naturally choose to ride, but says the level doesn’t cause fatigue because the bike’s motor assists the rider in attaining that level.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Exciting Findings&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Brain signal recordings were captured from participants’ implanted DBS electrodes to assess participants’ brain signals before and after each exercise session.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Our goal was to understand the immediate and long-term effects of the exercise in that region of the brain where the electrodes are implanted, which is also the same area where Parkinson’s pathology is evident,” Dr. Shaikh said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Researchers did not observe immediate brain signal changes, but after 12 sessions, they saw a measurable change in the brain signals responsible for motor control and movement.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Joshi and the team observed that while modern DBS systems offer a novel window into brain activity, they are limited to capturing signals only from the regions where the electrodes are implanted. As a result, other brain areas that may also contribute to the observed patterns could remain unmonitored.                               &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The key insight, Joshi explains: “There may be a broader circuit involved. Numerous upstream and downstream pathways could be influenced by exercise, and it’s possible that we’re inducing a network-level change that drives the improvement in motor symptoms.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Additional work could help provide answers, Joshi adds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The good news is that our next investigations could bring us closer to revolutionary and personalized treatments for PD.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Patient Success&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Amanda “Mandy” Ensman, 59, was diagnosed with PD 12 years ago and participated in the study.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I knew I needed to start exercising. It really does make a difference,” she explained. “Biking helped me with a variety of symptoms I was struggling with, including my gait, walking and increased my energy levels.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mandy now regularly participates in physical therapy regularly at InMotion, where the study took place. The gym holds workout classes and programs that are geared specifically towards PD patients.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;About this exercise, neurogenesis, and Parkinson’s disease research news&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="has-background"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Author: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#88e9e6fbe4edf1a6e3ede4e5c8fde0e0e7fbf8e1fce9e4fba6e7faef" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Ansley Kelm&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Source: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://uhhospitals.org" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;University Hospitals Cleveland Medical Center&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Contact: &lt;/strong&gt;Ansley Kelm – University Hospitals Cleveland Medical Center&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Image: &lt;/strong&gt;The image is credited to Neuroscience News&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="has-background"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Original Research: &lt;/strong&gt;Open access.&lt;br&gt;“&lt;a href="https://dx.doi.org/10.1016/j.clinph.2025.03.018" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Electrophysiological correlates of dynamic cycling in Parkinson’s disease&lt;/a&gt;” by Aasef Shaikh et al. &lt;em&gt;&lt;em&gt;Clinical Neurophysiology&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr class="wp-block-separator has-text-color has-pale-cyan-blue-color has-alpha-channel-opacity has-pale-cyan-blue-background-color has-background"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Abstract&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Electrophysiological correlates of dynamic cycling in Parkinson’s disease&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="wp-block-heading" id="st015"&gt;Objective&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Physical exercise like dynamic cycling has shown promise in enhancing motor function in Parkinson’s disease (PD). We examined the underlying mechanisms of dynamic cycling in PD, emphasizing its impact on the activity of the subthalamic nucleus (STN), a pivotal region within the basal ganglia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="wp-block-heading" id="st020"&gt;Methods&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;The investigation involved 100 dynamic cycling sessions conducted among nine PD individuals. Each participant underwent a maximum of 12 sessions over a four-week period. Local field potentials (LFPs) originating from the STN were recorded before and after cycling, utilizing DBS electrodes positioned within the nucleus.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We evaluated both immediate and sustained impacts of dynamic cycling on LFP. The periodic LFP activity was assessed by determining the dominant spectral frequency and the power associated with that frequency. Aperiodic LFP activity was analyzed by calculating the 1/f exponent of the power spectrum.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="wp-block-heading" id="st025"&gt;Results&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Immediate and sustained effects of dynamic cycling on LFPs were evaluated. While immediate changes were insignificant, long-term effects showed an increasing trend in power and the 1/f exponent of the power spectrum, a measure of fluctuation in the signal, in the dorsolateral region of the STN. Ventral region of the STN did not show a significant response to the exercise intervention.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="wp-block-heading" id="st030"&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;These results highlight the impact of dynamic cycling on STN neuronal activity in PD. Prolonged interventions, even without immediate changes, bring about significant modifications, emphasizing the role of extended exercise in PD management and neuroplasticity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="wp-block-heading" id="st035"&gt;Significance&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;These results highlight the impact of dynamic cycling showing changing in the STN neurophysiology in PD.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p class="clear"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Neuroscience News</author><pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2025 18:49:57 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMia0FVX3lxTE03QTBPSVVFQ1RLZWtkU2dUMzNtcnRDWWdILXlhcFYxSDlpUXpaRG9yWnlIYVdoV3E1ZDd0dlF4WjROdXFnRmlacEtuZzNRbWpPQlFBdFRzUTRRTFVmQXN0U05GNVRtREplT3lZ</guid></item><item><title>男性避孕药在试验中“被发现是安全的” -泰晤士报</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMilwFBVV95cUxQcHdlRHBvTVBxSVZXMWhaUF9ubVVJSmg4U0Y1cERDb2xrNGFPXzk0WkhRbFpoeU9TX0NLTUpjNDBWMzdaZTJBWWFOX2Z3SllJS1VmaVhpazJRVUNvSEg3ajhaYUNrT1pOd2g0dzRndVM5bzJWNXQyS1Bac2hhVXhoSHBfMVFUbDVQTURnVEhGbE8weXBHVUdF?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="responsive__ArticleContent-sc-15gvuj2-8 kuowVf"&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;A new experimental male contraceptive pill has been shown to be safe in early-stage clinical trials, researchers have said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;The new hormone-free pill, which works by reversibly decreasing sperm count, was found to be safe in a trial involving 16 healthy male volunteers. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;Previous attempts to create a male contraceptive have largely failed owing to their side-effects, and this pill could give hope for a contraceptive with fewer negative effects than prior attempts. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;Women have several different contraceptive options, including the pill, the intrauterine device (IUD), the diaphragm, the hormonal patch, the female condom and tubal ligation — many of which come with unappealing side-effects. For men the choice has been limited for decades to condoms or a vasectomy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;The early-stage research, published in Communications&lt;span class="paywall-EAB47CFD"&gt; Medicine, found that the pill was safe in healthy male volunteers and did not lead to any major side-effects. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="paywall-EAB47CFD"&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;The researchers, scientists at YourChoice Therapeutics, a drug development company, wrote: “Since nearly half of all pregnancies in the world are unintended, there is a critical need for additional contraceptive options for men and women.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;The new method uses a chemical known as YCT-529 to target a specific receptor cell in the testes. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;• &lt;a href="https://www.thetimes.com/article/british-men-male-pill-contraceptive-birth-control-c8jqrl7rv" class="link__RespLink-sc-1ocvixa-0 csWvlP"&gt;&lt;b&gt;British men first in world to test new male contraceptive pill&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;The pill should be taken daily and works by blocking a vitamin A metabolite from binding to its receptor in the testes, essentially preventing sperm from being created in the first place. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;In previous animal studies, this compound was found to produce &lt;a href="https://www.thetimes.com/article/male-contraceptive-gene-protein-key-to-switching-off-fertility-r9c7q3gcq" class="link__RespLink-sc-1ocvixa-0 csWvlP"&gt;fully reversible and temporary infertility&lt;/a&gt; without any significant side-effects — and a different study in mice found that they continued to father offspring as normal after stopping the drug. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;In this trial, which is the first step in assessing the potential contraceptives’ safety, 16 male volunteers took the drug twice in increasing doses — from 10mg to 30mg, or 90mg to 180mg, with some taking a placebo for comparison. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;They were then monitored for 15 days to assess any side-effects and the impact on hormone levels. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;The drug was tested on healthy men aged between 32 and 59, all of whom had had vasectomies, as a precaution to avoid the risk of permanently affecting a participant’s fertility. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;The research team concluded: “Administration of single oral doses of 10–180 mg YCT-529, fasted, and 30 mg, fed, is well tolerated by healthy male subjects. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;“YCT-529 does not demonstrate an adverse cardiac safety profile, or change in haematology, coagulation or serum chemistry parameters, hormone or proinflammatory cytokine levels, sexual drive and mood, and shows good bioavailability (with no clear food effect).” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;YourChoice Therapeutics is currently running further trials to assess the safety of the drug over a longer period of time. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;Previous polls have found that &lt;a href="https://www.thetimes.com/article/the-male-contraceptive-pill-what-men-really-think-about-it-9dpf0zt67" class="link__RespLink-sc-1ocvixa-0 csWvlP"&gt;male contraceptives would be highly sought after&lt;/a&gt;, with one by YouGov in 2019 finding that a third of British men would consider taking a male contraceptive — the same percentage as the number of women taking hormonal contraception. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;Other male contraceptives are also now in the pipeline, including a hydrogel implant called Adam, which is also being tested in early clinical trials. It works as a reversible vastectomy, physically blocking sperm release until the implant is removed. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;The treatment is a water-soluble hydrogel that is ­injected into the vas deferens, or sperm ducts, preventing sperm from mixing with semen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="last-paragraph" class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;The results from the Adam clinical trial have not yet been published in a peer-reviewed journal and do not include data on the reversibility of the treatment. However, the scientists say that the sperm-blocking gel is designed to break down over time, meaning that the contraceptive effect should be reversed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p id="paywall-portal-article-footer"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Times</author><pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2025 18:45:38 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilwFBVV95cUxQcHdlRHBvTVBxSVZXMWhaUF9ubVVJSmg4U0Y1cERDb2xrNGFPXzk0WkhRbFpoeU9TX0NLTUpjNDBWMzdaZTJBWWFOX2Z3SllJS1VmaVhpazJRVUNvSEg3ajhaYUNrT1pOd2g0dzRndVM5bzJWNXQyS1Bac2hhVXhoSHBfMVFUbDVQTURnVEhGbE8weXBHVUdF</guid></item><item><title>加纳记录了20例新的Mpox病例，总数上升至302例- GhanaWeb</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMirgFBVV95cUxPb0VRQ1JPYU1KMUs3RWE0YUxZSFAwSVN6Y2ZTRjhzcDVZajAzcV93ajdWR19ORmhhU3FLTUV3aVJ3ZFVZd1JQOVJsT2JtOUdYSVRLb0tIODd2RXlJN0Z4YmJUYlpYeFQyZDhCeGJWNndKdWptRkdkY09PMjJzOENZREF0Sm1GRmNQVEY1RTRrWVJWdmxLRExJLUlCeEFSRlI3aW1Eb1ZnRHhDVE13U3c?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-left"&gt;
&lt;p class="article-image"&gt;&lt;a href="Ghana-records-20-new-Mpox-cases-total-rises-to-302-1994500?gallery=1"&gt;&lt;img src="https://cdn.ghanaweb.com/imagelib/pics/923/92356890.295.jpg" alt="Ghana Health Service logo" title="Ghana Health Service logo"&gt; &lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class="image_caption"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Ghana Health Service logo&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="article-content-area"&gt;&lt;p id="article-123"&gt;The Ghana Health Service (GHS) has confirmed 20 new cases of Mpox, bringing the total number of infections in the country to 302 as of July 30, 2025.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
This follows the announcement of Ghana’s first Mpox-related death on July 22,2025 alongside 23 new infections, which had raised the total number of confirmed cases to 257 at the time.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
According to health officials, the virus also known as Monkeypox continues to spread mainly through close physical contact with infected individuals. &lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Transmission can occur through contact with skin lesions, body fluids, or contaminated materials such as clothing and bedding.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
In a public notice, the GHS urged the public to remain vigilant and avoid close contact with individuals displaying symptoms such as fever, body aches, and distinctive rashes. &lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
It also advised the public to report any suspected cases to the nearest health facility.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
“Protect yourself and others by avoiding close contact with those showing symptoms, and ensure you report any suspected signs to the nearest health facility,” the statement said.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Although most individuals infected with Mpox recover without serious complications, health authorities have expressed concern following the recent death, particularly for high-risk groups such as children, pregnant women, and those with underlying health conditions.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
The GHS said it is working closely with regional health directorates to trace contacts and coordinate a national response, while also stepping up public education campaigns and urging the public to rely on verified sources of information.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Read statement below&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
MRA/EB&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Meanwhile, watch as Prophet Worlasi shares bombshell prophesies on Bawumia and NPP on The Lowdown:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;iframe class="gh-jwplayer" loading="lazy" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/xsSvpquWqGU?si=k0EQv258kBzqpzXU" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen&gt;VIDEO&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>GhanaWeb</author><pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2025 18:15:11 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMirgFBVV95cUxPb0VRQ1JPYU1KMUs3RWE0YUxZSFAwSVN6Y2ZTRjhzcDVZajAzcV93ajdWR19ORmhhU3FLTUV3aVJ3ZFVZd1JQOVJsT2JtOUdYSVRLb0tIODd2RXlJN0Z4YmJUYlpYeFQyZDhCeGJWNndKdWptRkdkY09PMjJzOENZREF0Sm1GRmNQVEY1RTRrWVJWdmxLRExJLUlCeEFSRlI3aW1Eb1ZnRHhDVE13U3c</guid></item><item><title>研究揭示了患有多动症症状的年轻人中独特的音乐习惯- PsyPost</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMinwFBVV95cUxOWjc0enpKR1RBY3RhaFY1bGZIVzBXWlZfRTRvS0JMN01tdmF4aURyaFZpOUYxRXNsWU9jNVI3WHEtUkk0V2NMd1V4Mm04bmpyNmhfSW5EaGMyeGhIRFhEM21YQzhSMEo4UG9ISzlJWUtXNnpPZVhiQ201U1U1U3dSX3NmY0N0TzNTdlVKOFVJQm1MZ3FPV2tEUmQzd3pDc3M?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="content-inner "&gt;&lt;p&gt;A new study published in &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.3389/fpsyg.2024.1508181" target="_blank"&gt;Frontiers in Psychology&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; reveals that young adults who screen positive for attention-deficit/hyperactivity disorder (ADHD) tend to listen to background music more frequently than their neurotypical peers during both cognitively demanding and less demanding activities. These individuals also show a stronger preference for stimulating music, regardless of the activity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;ADHD is a neurodevelopmental condition marked by symptoms of inattention, hyperactivity, or impulsivity. It often begins in childhood and persists into adulthood in a significant proportion of cases. Adults with ADHD, especially those with the inattentive presentation, may struggle with sustained attention, task management, and organization.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The disorder is also commonly associated with emotional challenges such as anxiety or depression. While stimulant medication can help regulate brain arousal and improve performance, researchers have also explored alternative strategies to support individuals with attentional difficulties, including environmental adjustments like background music.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the new study, doctoral candidates Kelly-Ann Lachance and Pénélope Pelland-Goulet, along with clinical neuropsychologist and full professor &lt;a href="https://www.musec.ca/en/frlaboratoire-musecenmusec-laboratory-english/" target="_blank"&gt;Nathalie Gosselin&lt;/a&gt; at the University of Montreal, sought to understand how young adults use music in daily life and whether those with ADHD symptoms differ from neurotypical individuals in their listening habits.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“We were interested in how young adults with and without ADHD use background music during daily activities, especially those requiring more cognitive effort, since prior lab studies rarely examine real-world listening habits,” the researchers explained. “Given that individuals with ADHD often struggle with attention, we wanted to understand whether they listen to music differently in everyday contexts. This interest was sparked years ago when a parent of a teenager with attention difficulties once asked Dr. Gosselin if letting their child study with music was a good idea—an unanswered question that stayed with her ever since.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The research team conducted an online survey with 434 participants between the ages of 17 and 30. Participants answered questions about their music listening habits, musical preferences, and the perceived effects of background music on emotional and cognitive functioning. The survey also included a standardized screening tool for ADHD symptoms. Based on the responses, participants were divided into two groups: those who screened positive for ADHD and those who did not.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers found that most young adults listen to background music during both cognitively demanding tasks—such as studying, problem-solving, and reading—and less demanding ones like cleaning, cooking, and exercising. However, individuals in the ADHD-screened group reported more frequent use of background music while studying and exercising compared to the neurotypical group. They also listened more frequently to music during low-effort activities overall.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Interestingly, distinct differences emerged between groups,” the researchers told PsyPost. “ADHD-screened participants not only listened to music more often during study tasks but also preferred stimulating music across both more and less cognitively demanding activities.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“In contrast, neurotypical participants tended to favor relaxing music during cognitively demanding activities and more stimulating music during less demanding ones. This pattern highlights a clear difference in how music is used and perceived—not just casually, but as a strategy to meet stimulation needs. It was interesting to see that these self-regulatory uses of music are already present in everyday life.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These findings align with existing psychological theories. One of them, the Moderate Brain Arousal model, suggests that individuals with ADHD often experience lower baseline levels of brain arousal. They may use external stimulation—such as music—to help reach an optimal arousal state that supports task engagement.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stimulating music, by activating the brain’s reward system and releasing dopamine, could help compensate for this baseline deficit and reduce tendencies toward mind-wandering or distraction during tasks like studying. In contrast, neurotypical individuals may seek less stimulation and favor music that is more calming or predictable when engaging in complex work.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers also investigated whether participants believed that background music improved their concentration or mood during cognitive tasks. Using a set of 27 statements, they conducted a factor analysis and identified two distinct dimensions of subjective experience: one related to cognitive functioning and the other to emotional functioning. Most participants reported that music helped with both, citing enhanced concentration and improved mood.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Contrary to expectations, there were no significant differences between groups in how they rated the emotional or cognitive benefits of background music. This suggests that despite listening more often to music in daily life, ADHD-screened individuals do not necessarily perceive stronger effects.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Our findings suggest that young adults with ADHD symptoms tend to listen to background music more frequently during activities that demand concentration, and they usually prefer more stimulating music, regardless of the activity type (e.g., more and less cognitively demanding),” the researchers said. “Many participants—both young adults with ADHD symptoms and neurotypical—also reported that music helped them stay focused and improved their mood. This suggests that background music might be a way for some people to manage their attention and emotions in everyday life.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers took care to account for potential confounding factors in their analysis. They controlled for variables such as musical training and mood symptoms and found that group differences in listening habits remained significant. For instance, even after adjusting for emotional distress, participants with ADHD symptoms still reported higher music use while exercising or doing simple tasks. This pattern suggests that the behavior is not solely driven by emotional coping but may also be related to attentional strategies or arousal regulation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But there are still some limitations to consider. One key limitation was the reliance on self-report data, which may be subject to recall bias or social desirability effects. In addition, the ADHD status of participants was determined through a screening questionnaire rather than a clinical diagnosis. This method may have included individuals with subclinical symptoms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Despite these limitations, the study adds to a growing body of evidence that music plays a meaningful role in how people manage attention and emotion in daily life. For individuals with attentional challenges, music may serve as a flexible and self-directed tool to help regulate arousal, reduce boredom, and support performance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Future research could build on these findings by using laboratory experiments or examining how different types of music affect cognitive performance and emotional state in individuals with ADHD. Longitudinal studies might also explore how music habits evolve over time or interact with other coping strategies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“In the short term, we have just launched a new survey targeting a younger population (ages 12 to 17) to explore their background music listening habits during daily activities,” the researchers said. “In English: https://ls.sondages.umontreal.ca/229667. In French: https://ls.sondages.umontreal.ca/978117.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“As for long-term goals, a key next step would be to examine how specific musical characteristics—such as tempo, lyrics, or familiarity—influence attention and emotional regulation in real time. Future research should be interested in developing personalized music-based strategies that could help individuals with attentional difficulties in academic or work settings.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Our findings reflect what many people may already sense intuitively: music is not just background noise—it plays a role in how we manage our attention, mood, and motivation,” the researchers added. “Understanding these everyday habits could help guide more individualized and practical approaches to supporting mental health and focus, especially in people with ADHD symptoms.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study, “&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.3389/fpsyg.2024.1508181" target="_blank"&gt;Listening habits and subjective effects of background music in young adults with and without ADHD&lt;/a&gt;,” was authored by Kelly-Ann Lachance Pénélope Pelland-Goulet, and Nathalie Gosselin.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>PsyPost</author><pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2025 18:07:16 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMinwFBVV95cUxOWjc0enpKR1RBY3RhaFY1bGZIVzBXWlZfRTRvS0JMN01tdmF4aURyaFZpOUYxRXNsWU9jNVI3WHEtUkk0V2NMd1V4Mm04bmpyNmhfSW5EaGMyeGhIRFhEM21YQzhSMEo4UG9ISzlJWUtXNnpPZVhiQ201U1U1U3dSX3NmY0N0TzNTdlVKOFVJQm1MZ3FPV2tEUmQzd3pDc3M</guid></item><item><title>根据心脏病专家的说法，这是强化心脏的最佳日常习惯- AOL.com</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMid0FVX3lxTE9HWkwyM3dIWjFvSnhtTGNJLWNBNWJXcjRzd21GbENrQzhmWUFsYVJmRzNheDZLVjdHZ3ozTEt0ek82NHc2MHYzdVFtcTR4emNrNmIydFRPS200SkR0Nk1taXJubU5uYUlKZENmTENFUEoyU3hwWTQ0?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="caas-body"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;a href="https://parade.com/health/best-daily-habit-to-strengthen-heart-according-to-cardiologists" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:This Is the Best Daily Habit To Strengthen Your Heart, According to Cardiologists;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;This Is the Best Daily Habit To Strengthen Your Heart, According to Cardiologists&lt;/a&gt; originally appeared on &lt;a href="https://parade.com" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Parade;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Parade&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It can be challenging to look too far into the future. The stress of everyday life may give you &lt;a href="https://parade.com/health/what-does-heartburn-feel-like" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:heartburn;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;heartburn&lt;/a&gt;, and the state of the world might feel heartbreaking. Yet, cardiologists are urging people to think long-term about their hearts, emphasizing that small habits now can add up to a healthier future.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;"&lt;a href="https://parade.com/health/relaxing-habit-harming-heart-health-according-to-cardiologists" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Heart health;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Heart health&lt;/a&gt; is driven so much by choices we make daily—what and why we eat and how active we are," says &lt;a href="https://mdschool.tcu.edu/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Dr. Mohanakrishna Sathyamoorthy, MD;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dr. Mohanakrishna Sathyamoorthy, MD&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, the chair of the department of internal medicine and Burnett School of Medicine and the principal cardiologist with Consultants in Cardiovascular Medicine and Science Fort Worth.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr. Sathyamoorthy says that intentionally making healthy choices is empowering, as it gives you agency over your cardiovascular health. However, you need to know what to do to do it. Cardiologists shared an important daily habit for strengthening the heart, why they recommend it and how to get started.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;🩺 &lt;a href="https://parade.com/newsletters/healthy-now" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:SIGN UP for tips to stay healthy &amp;amp; fit with the top moves, clean eats, health trends &amp;amp; more delivered right to your inbox twice a week;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;SIGN UP for tips to stay healthy &amp;amp; fit with the top moves, clean eats, health trends &amp;amp; more delivered right to your inbox twice a week&lt;/a&gt; 💊&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;The Best Daily Habit To Strengthen the Heart, Cardiologists Reveal&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cardiologists emphasize that it's crucial to &lt;a href="https://parade.com/health/strength-training-workouts" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:strength train;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;strength train&lt;/a&gt; two to three times per week. "There is no doubt from my view that bringing weight training is crucial to developing a balanced exercise regimen," Dr. Sathyamoorthy reports.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There's no doubt in the American Heart Association's mind either. The organization recommends that adults engage in strength training at least two days per week in its &lt;a href="https://www.heart.org/en/healthy-living/fitness/fitness-basics/aha-recs-for-physical-activity-in-adults" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:guidelines for physical activity;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;guidelines for physical activity&lt;/a&gt;. However, it is often overlooked as people focus more heavily on the also-important recommendations for aerobic activity (150 minutes of moderate or 75 minutes of vigorous activity per week).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Now, you may know that weight training can help build and maintain muscle. The heart is also a muscle. However, pumping iron doesn't benefit the heart in the same way—you're not going to make your ticker bulkier by lifting weights or doing bodyweight squats..&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Strength training...can help create a more conducive environment for the heart to work within," explains &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.getcare.tgh.org/providers/debbie-rinde-hoffman-1801899091" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Dr. Debbie Rinde-Hoffman, MD;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Dr. Debbie Rinde-Hoffman, MD&lt;/a&gt;,&lt;/strong&gt; a cardiologist and vice chief of business development with Tampa General Hospital Heart &amp;amp; Vascular Institute.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In other words, strength training makes the body stronger, and the heart doesn't operate in a vacuum—it benefits too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Strength training can lower weight, improve cholesterol and blood sugar and can improve blood pressure," says &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.northwell.edu/find-care/find-a-doctor/dr-guy-lowell-mintz-md-1508869884" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Dr. Guy L. Mintz, MD;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Dr. Guy L. Mintz, MD&lt;/a&gt;,&lt;/strong&gt; the director of cardiovascular health &amp;amp; lipidology for the Sandra Atlas Bass Heart Hospital and North Shore University Hospital. "Weight training builds lean muscle mass, and muscle burns more calories."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr. Mintz notes that this &lt;a href="https://parade.com/1371324/kaitlin-vogel/calories-burned-running/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:calorie burn;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;calorie burn&lt;/a&gt; continues even after the resistance workout (known as the "afterburn effect"). Speaking of "continues," the list of benefits strength training has for heart health doesn't stop there.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It also helps enhance insulin sensitivity, weight management, reduces inflammation and has a positive effect on our mood and sleep," states &lt;a href="https://doctors.hackensackmeridianhealth.org/provider/saleem-husain/1316861" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Dr. Saleem Husain, MD;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dr. Saleem Husain, MD&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, an interventional cardiologist at JFK University Medical Center.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://parade.com/health/popular-nighttime-habit-that-spikes-blood-pressure" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:This Popular Nighttime Habit Could Spike Your Blood Pressure, Cardiologists Warn;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;This Popular Nighttime Habit Could Spike Your Blood Pressure, Cardiologists Warn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Tips for Strength Training for a Stronger Heart Health&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;There are tons of advice and workout plans available online, which are handy when starting a workout regimen. However, Dr. Mintz stresses that people looking to start strength training for a stronger heart should remember to "make it fun." Customization is also key based on your goals and experience. Here's what cardiologists recommend if you're trying to ramp up your strength training efforts for heart health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;1. Know what qualifies as strength training&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Spoiler alert: It doesn't require a gym membership (but you might benefit from one if you like to use equipment that you don't have at home).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Anything that increases muscle activity above normal activity [qualifies as strength training]," Dr. Mintz explains. "This can include weights and resistance bands."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr. Husain notes that body weight moves also count—think push-ups, crunches, and squats.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;2. Work different muscle groups&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cardiologists advise people to engage all their muscle groups each week. You might work the upper body, core, and lower body on separate days or opt for a full-body session three times a week. It is a personal choice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"One method is to break up exercise into body sections," Dr. Sathyamoorthy says. "The other is to do circuit training, where you use machines to work each part of the body, repeating each full round two to three times for a good workout."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr. Sathyamoorthy adds that a bodyweight circuit approach, incorporating exercises such as push-ups, leg lifts, and squats, also works. "It's up to you, your goals and your comfort level," he says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;3. Understand how long to strength train for heart health&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;The American Heart Association makes specific recommendations for duration and intensity of aerobic exercise, but doesn't do the same for resistance efforts. Dr. Rinde-Hoffman says there's not a cookie-cutter answer to questions like, "How long should I strength train for my heart?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It might look different for individuals depending on their age, sex, degree of physical conditioning and underlying medical conditions," Dr. Rinde-Hoffman points out.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr. Husain recommends tacking on 15 to 20 minutes of strength training to cardio workouts two to three times each week.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;4. Go slow&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cardiologists recommend easing into resistance training if you're a beginner or if it's been a while. "I usually recommend training with low-level weights, which you can use without having to hold your breath," Dr. Husain says, who adds it's important to warm up and cool down.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ensure you can keep your posture throughout the set. "Correct form is key to avoiding injury," Dr. Mintz advises. "Do not jerk the weights." He adds that a personal trainer can help ensure you keep good form, and he suggests gradually increasing weight as your body can tolerate it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://parade.com/health/first-moves-trainers-teach-clients-for-stronger-core" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:The First 2 Moves Trainers Teach Clients Who Want a Stronger Core;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;The First 2 Moves Trainers Teach Clients Who Want a Stronger Core&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Other Advice&lt;/strong&gt; for a Stronger Heart&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr. Rinde-Hoffman emphasizes working every avenue you can to keep your heart as healthy as possible. She suggests:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class="caas-list caas-list-bullet"&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Managing underlying conditions, including high cholesterol and blood pressure&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Getting enough sleep&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Understanding other cardiovascular risk factors, like family history&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Getting regular aerobic exercise&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Getting enough sleep&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Prioritizing interpersonal connections&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Surprised to see the last one about connection there? "Prioritizing interpersonal connections with others is also helpful in promoting good heart health by reducing stress, promoting healthier lifestyle choices and improving overall mental health," she reports.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr. Mintz's key takeaway about heart health and lifestyle habits takes a similar route. "Cardiovascular benefits are increased when done together," he says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Up Next:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://parade.com/health/habit-people-with-high-cholesterol-should-break-according-to-cardiologists" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Related: Cardiologists Are Begging People With High Cholesterol To Stop Doing This One Thing ASAP;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Related: Cardiologists Are Begging People With High Cholesterol To Stop Doing This One Thing ASAP&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Sources:&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul class="caas-list caas-list-bullet"&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://mdschool.tcu.edu/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Dr. Mohanakrishna Sathyamoorthy, MD;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Dr. Mohanakrishna Sathyamoorthy, MD&lt;/a&gt;, the chair of the department of internal medicine and Burnett School of Medicine and the principal cardiologist with Consultants in Cardiovascular Medicine and Science Fort Worth&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;American Heart Association Recommendations for Physical Activity in Adults and Kids. &lt;a href="https://www.heart.org/en/healthy-living/fitness/fitness-basics/aha-recs-for-physical-activity-in-adults" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:American Heart Association;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;American Heart Association&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.getcare.tgh.org/providers/debbie-rinde-hoffman-1801899091" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Dr. Debbie Rinde-Hoffman, MD;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Dr. Debbie Rinde-Hoffman, MD&lt;/a&gt;, a cardiologist and vice chief of business development with Tampa General Hospital Heart &amp;amp; Vascular Institute&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.northwell.edu/find-care/find-a-doctor/dr-guy-lowell-mintz-md-1508869884" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Dr. Guy L. Mintz, MD;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Dr. Guy L. Mintz, MD&lt;/a&gt;, the director of cardiovascular health &amp;amp; lipidology for the Sandra Atlas Bass Heart Hospital and North Shore University Hospital&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://doctors.hackensackmeridianhealth.org/provider/saleem-husain/1316861" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Dr. Saleem Husain, MD;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Dr. Saleem Husain, MD&lt;/a&gt;, an interventional cardiologist at JFK University Medical Center&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://parade.com/health/best-daily-habit-to-strengthen-heart-according-to-cardiologists" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:This Is the Best Daily Habit To Strengthen Your Heart, According to Cardiologists;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;This Is the Best Daily Habit To Strengthen Your Heart, According to Cardiologists&lt;/a&gt; first appeared on Parade on Aug 3, 2025&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;This story was originally reported by &lt;a href="https://parade.com/health/best-daily-habit-to-strengthen-heart-according-to-cardiologists" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Parade;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Parade&lt;/a&gt; on Aug 3, 2025, where it first appeared.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>AOL.com</author><pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2025 17:56:27 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMid0FVX3lxTE9HWkwyM3dIWjFvSnhtTGNJLWNBNWJXcjRzd21GbENrQzhmWUFsYVJmRzNheDZLVjdHZ3ozTEt0ek82NHc2MHYzdVFtcTR4emNrNmIydFRPS200SkR0Nk1taXJubU5uYUlKZENmTENFUEoyU3hwWTQ0</guid></item><item><title>我想在婚礼上看起来很漂亮……但这几乎让我失去了未来--《每日邮报》</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiogFBVV95cUxQS3h5X29ldE81UE1fWnBBcThzQkhXcHE3NkZRVVFmZVlucFFEN2xab2hrSUNaLTNYOHk4MXdHYnM4LWNxWC1RekMzTk9FRDN2azVkM1FZZ1NSWHhHT2M4SEs2RHpXWFZOS1dBamREUWZmV3BBbGFwenR3TUJDUTZCQm1CYWJhOHhKcDlBeHYwS1ZMcTFudk9UNlUtSlYzNDN2SVE?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div itemprop="articleBody"&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;It’s hardly the sort of advice you expect to get from a physician: eat more, exercise less.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But that's precisely what Cynthia Donovan's doctor told her she must do if she were to stand any chance of having the baby for which she and her husband of four years longed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Now 39, Donovan is one of 1.62 million women in America affected by Functional Hypothalamic Amenorrhea (FHA).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The condition, characterized by a cessation of periods, can cause long-term health problems including cardiovascular issues, loss of bone density which, at its worst, can develop into osteoporosis and infertility.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;And as Donovan learned that day in 2015, it can be brought on by too much exercise, inadequate nutrition and psychological stress – or, in her case, preparing for a wedding.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;She tells the Daily Mail: ‘I’d always been fit and healthy, but my desire to have the perfect body tripled from the moment I got engaged.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;‘I couldn’t stop thinking, “My big day is coming up, so I’ve got to look my absolute best for the photographs which will be part of my life forever.”’&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Donovan was thrilled when her boyfriend proposed in May 2010. She was 25 years old and had just completed her master’s degree in science and nutrition at SUNY, Oneonta in upstate New York. It seemed like the perfect time to settle down.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Cynthia Donovan in her wedding dress. She says, 'I’d always been fit and healthy, but my desire to have the perfect body tripled from the moment I got engaged'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Donovan, who was 25 years old and had just completed her master’s degree in science and nutrition when she got engaged in 2010&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The ceremony was set for September 2011. Donovan had 16 months to reach her goal of wearing a size two gown.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;She went from being an average gym goer who worked out three to four times a week to exercising up to three hours every day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;She would complete two work outs in the morning and one at night, with a particular emphasis on cardio.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;As for food, she bulked up her meals with vegetables and seriously restricted her intake of even lean proteins such as chicken and fish and sources of ‘good fats’ like olive oil, avocado and nuts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;She counted calories obsessively, limiting herself to just 1,500 a day – significantly less than the recommended 2,000 for a woman of her five-foot-one frame.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Meanwhile, as she fixated on her appearance, she ignored what her body was telling her about her underlying health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Her periods stopped, but she simply assumed this was the temporary legacy of years spent on the birth control pill which she had only recently stopped taking.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The wedding in September 2011 was, Donovan says, ‘magical’ though in retrospect she feels a tinge of regret at how much she lost herself to what she now deems ‘societal pressure’ to look good.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;She and her new husband had discussed wanting kids before getting married and took for granted that they would start having a family before Donovan hit 30.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;‘It was always on the agenda for us, but we thought we’d wait a few years to enjoy married life together,’ she says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But, despite leaving the stress of the wedding behind, Donovan’s periods did not return.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;And, as the months passed, it went from being something she had dismissed without a second thought to a pressing concern.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;She consulted her gynecologist, but was told not to worry.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;She attributed it to the fact that Donovan had recently stopped taking the pill and told her that post-pill amenorrhea (the absence of menstruation) is common, and can last for three to six months.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But Donovan wasn’t convinced. She sought a second and third opinion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;A specialist diagnosed her with polycystic ovarian syndrome (PCOS), a hormonal disorder that affects fertility characterized by infrequent or prolonged menstrual cycles.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Donovan and her new husband had discussed wanting kids before getting married and took for granted that they would start a family&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Donovan's gynecologist told her not to worry about her lack of periods while a specialist diagnosed her with polycystic ovarian syndrome&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;She was prescribed Metformin, a common medication for the PCOS, underwent hormonal therapies, got acupuncture and took dietary supplements.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But nothing worked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;‘It was so frustrating because nobody could get to the bottom of what was going on,' Donovan says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;‘I was a wreck because I kept saying [to my husband], “What if we can’t have a baby together?” or “We love each other, yet we might never be parents.’&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But her husband was supportive and said that, if it came to it, they would try fertility treatment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Finally, in early 2015, her gynecologist referred her to a reproductive endocrinologist – a specialist in conditions relating to reproduction and hormone imbalances.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;He performed a battery of tests and told her the problem was not polycystic ovaries. She was suffering from Functional Hypothalamic Amenorrhea (FHA).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The brain, specifically the hypothalamus, is responsible for regulating ovulation and menstruation. Not enough healthy fats, low body weight and excessive exercise can all contribute to a disruption of this cycle.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The specialist suggested Donovan ate more calories and scaled down her exercise regimen if she wanted to become pregnant.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;She recalls: ‘It was hard to hear at first, but it showed that nutrition isn’t as black or white as some people think.’&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;She followed his advice, reducing the amount she exercised to three sessions a week and quitting her CrossFit gym membership altogether.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;She focused on gentler exercise such as yoga, stretching and walking.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;She cultivated a more relaxed attitude to food, eating an ice cream sundae if she wanted one and bulking up her meals with grains such as quinoa, drizzled in olive oil, instead of just vegetables.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But Donovan’s is a cautionary tale, because, while FHA is both treatable and preventable, in her case her period still didn’t return within a time frame with which she was comfortable.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;She turned to a fertility clinic and hormonal treatment to stimulate ovulation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;After three failed cycles of intra-uterine insemination (IUI) in December 2015 a fourth was successful and she found out she was pregnant.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Her son, Brian, now eight, was born in August 2016.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Donovan finally got pregnant on her fourth cycle of intra-uterine insemination (IUI)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Donovan with her son, Brian, soon after he arrived in August 2016&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;‘He was this gift,’ Donovan says. ‘I couldn’t believe I was finally holding this beautiful child in my arms.’&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;And while some women rush to try and get back into shape post-partum, Donovan made a point of not doing so.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;She stuck to her endocrinologist’s advice to take things easy, confident that it would pay off in the long run.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;She regained her period naturally in July 2017 – seven years after the onset of her FHA.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Just three months later, she conceived again without any medical intervention. ‘It was as if my body had reset itself,' she recalls.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Brian’s brother, Brayden, was born in September 2018.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Today Donovan doesn’t recognize the woman she was on her wedding day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;She says: ‘When I go through the photographs, I can’t help thinking, “Oh my gosh, that poor girl.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;‘Her focus wasn't even about the meaning of the wedding, it was about how she was going to look.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;‘Yes, I looked great, but was I truly living? Was I truly being healthy?’&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Now, she hopes other women will learn from her story.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Donovan with her sons, Brian, now eight, and six-year-old Brayden&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Donovan with her young boys. She hopes other women will learn from her story&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;She says: ‘You don’t have to micromanage everything, especially your body. Otherwise, you might miss out on the most joyous moments of your life.’&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;She feels so strongly about it, she has made it her business as a certified dietician to help others navigate FHA, its causes and its treatments.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;She hosts &lt;a class="class" rel="nofollow noreferrer noopener" target="_blank" href="https://www.instagram.com/period.nutritionist?igsh=NTc4MTIwNjQ2YQ%3D%3D&amp;amp;utm_source=qr"&gt;‘The Period Recovery Podcast’ &lt;/a&gt;and has teamed up with Dr Chrisandra Shufelt, Associate Director of the Mayo clinic’s women’s health research center in Jacksonville, Florida.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;According to Dr Shufelt: ‘The menstrual cycle should be considered a vital sign and, if you’re not having a regular period during your reproductive years, it’s a clear indication that something isn’t right.’&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But she offers encouraging news, saying, ‘You just need to identify the underlying cause, whether it’s stress, over-exercise or under-eating or a combination. It is treatable and preventable.’&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
            

            
            
            
            
            &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Daily Mail</author><pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2025 16:48:47 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiogFBVV95cUxQS3h5X29ldE81UE1fWnBBcThzQkhXcHE3NkZRVVFmZVlucFFEN2xab2hrSUNaLTNYOHk4MXdHYnM4LWNxWC1RekMzTk9FRDN2azVkM1FZZ1NSWHhHT2M4SEs2RHpXWFZOS1dBamREUWZmV3BBbGFwenR3TUJDUTZCQm1CYWJhOHhKcDlBeHYwS1ZMcTFudk9UNlUtSlYzNDN2SVE</guid></item><item><title>可穿戴设备有助于发现儿童术后并发症-《华盛顿邮报》</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMipwFBVV95cUxNTWNHY19WMHhmRHVNWlMzNkpBeEx5N2RTV2pKeWpSaEgtTXV3WThpQ2ZpUGRud2ZVQnNUdFpJN0JpWUpKUU9UdHFERC04VUZmRWhTeW00R2tRbzVJdnAzNWFmN2ZYZVQzOUtJUFQ5M19RSVh4NGJvdlpmckgyR1E1Q0xMR3lSMHZ2NzlhbFRlV2cxVS14NkRoWXE5UVFha3lmajF4MDVyOA?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="meteredContent grid-center"&gt;&lt;div class="teaser-content"&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="ILVBDOVTZZEINFW7U3R2OZJRWQ" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Wearable devices like Fitbits can help health care providers spot postsurgical complications in kids, a new &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1126/sciadv.adv2643" target="_blank"&gt;analysis&lt;/a&gt; in Science Advances finds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="5JJRPAN27ZC2JD2MP2W3J57MVU" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;About 1 in 7 children will have postoperative complications, but diagnoses can be delayed because they can be difficult for caretakers outside the hospital to spot.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-subscribe-cta" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="BMOYDVSH4JHIVCBNQV6D2UO5DQ" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;To determine if data recorded by wearable devices can help predict recovery in children, researchers gave Fitbits to 103 children ages 3 to 18. All were recovering from an appendectomy, a common surgery in kids. The devices monitored heart rate and step-count data, sleep and other biometrics. They recorded 2,163 total monitoring days.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="NDWOX3UPRFEXZLOUWCVQW4EN74" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;The researchers used the data to find circadian patterns in the children’s biometrics during each day after their surgery. Of 94 children whose data could be used, 58 had a normal recovery, 23 had abnormal symptoms such as diarrhea but no ultimate complication, and 13 had a postoperative complication.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="SFJSNPL3SVHMBOIDBPP7N6PLBQ" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;The researchers used a machine-learned model to predict complications using the Fibits and biorhythms. Daily patterns associated with activity, such as step count, ended up being the most important to predicting post-appendectomy recovery, followed by heart rhythms. Tracking biorhythms for as little as 120 minutes produced robust enough data for the model to analyze.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-topic-follow-interstitial" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="PV4PAE7YR5DN5HGVHEWSJL6HSQ" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Overall, the researchers were able to predict postoperative complications using the wearable data with 91 percent sensitivity and 74 percent specificity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="G5YQREBXVNAN3PMXQJELMBVBW4" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;“In our data, 89% of patients who had complications after discharge were readmitted and were all correctly predicted by the biorhythm model,” they write.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="GGWOOTM4XZC4XEQ7E6HOKC66V4" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Other research suggests biorhythms may not be as effective at tracking adults’ postoperative recovery. It might be easier to use biometrics to predict children’s recoveries because their lives are more structured, making it easier to establish a typical baseline for analysis, the researchers add.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="Z47KVTBYJ5AELGNOW6JI74UHWU" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Other studies should focus on other childhood procedures including tonsillectomies, the researchers suggest. But overall, the researchers write, the study shows that consumer wearables and monitoring could help “address key challenges in postoperative monitoring of children.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-header" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;h3 id="LM34GNWZWBAQNFZHSDI4KA7MDU" class="wpds-c-APnkR wpds-c-APnkR-ieHKbcq-css headingStyleOverrides" data-apitype="header" data-contentid="LM34GNWZWBAQNFZHSDI4KA7MDU" data-testid="article-header"&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2025 16:02:23 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipwFBVV95cUxNTWNHY19WMHhmRHVNWlMzNkpBeEx5N2RTV2pKeWpSaEgtTXV3WThpQ2ZpUGRud2ZVQnNUdFpJN0JpWUpKUU9UdHFERC04VUZmRWhTeW00R2tRbzVJdnAzNWFmN2ZYZVQzOUtJUFQ5M19RSVh4NGJvdlpmckgyR1E1Q0xMR3lSMHZ2NzlhbFRlV2cxVS14NkRoWXE5UVFha3lmajF4MDVyOA</guid></item><item><title>科学家声称，人类可能从与冬眠相关的基因中获得了未开发的“超能力” - Live Science</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiywFBVV95cUxQdFdaRnhadENKODRHUklKeW5UZ2Y1ZGxzTHdJdnV6U0tqcEZic0drc1BHMks4UFRuazU5dUVIUnY5eUhWdUFXTnJ6MWM4UFhhcWR6ZjhHTUdjNGhYeE5YcDQzRWpTRGN2U3NaUGZBMmFwbV84YUJPNE9qd0syNjZDYzRIbklET0pZWWhiY2sydGFqRFgxRm1JN3FJdnNiZGxSUTFKb3d2c013LUhkQ3FuMWJpaXQxTFdXUjQ1bGxfbmZrMWdKcHk1dXZFNA?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="article-body" class="text-copy bodyCopy auto"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hibernating mammals rely on particular genes to adjust their metabolisms as they enter that unique, low-energy state — and humans actually carry that same hibernation-related DNA.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="ad-unit-1" class="ad-unit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Now, early research hints that leveraging this particular DNA could help treat medical conditions in people, scientists say.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hibernation offers "a whole bunch of different biometrically important superpowers," senior study author&lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://medicine.utah.edu/faculty/christopher-t-gregg" target="_blank" data-url="https://medicine.utah.edu/faculty/christopher-t-gregg" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt; &lt;u&gt;Christopher Gregg&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, a human genetics professor at the University of Utah, told Live Science.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For example, ground squirrels can develop reversible &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.livescience.com/34757-insulin-resistance-develop-diabetes-heart-disease.html" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.livescience.com/34757-insulin-resistance-develop-diabetes-heart-disease.html"&gt;&lt;u&gt;insulin resistance&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; that helps them rapidly gain weight before they hibernate but starts fading as &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC3854349/#sec1" target="_blank" data-url="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC3854349/#sec1" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;hibernation gets underway&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. A better understanding of how hibernators flip this switch could be useful for tackling the insulin resistance that characterizes &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.livescience.com/40894-type-2-diabetes.html" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.livescience.com/40894-type-2-diabetes.html"&gt;&lt;u&gt;type 2 diabetes&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, Gregg suggested.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="ad-unit-2" class="ad-unit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hibernating animals also protect their nervous systems from damage that could be caused by sudden changes in blood flow. "When they come out of hibernation, their brain is reperfused with blood," Gregg said. "Often that would cause a lot of damage, like a &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.livescience.com/health/what-are-the-signs-of-stroke" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.livescience.com/health/what-are-the-signs-of-stroke"&gt;&lt;u&gt;stroke&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, but they've developed ways to prevent that damage from happening."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gregg and his colleagues think tapping into hibernation-related genes in people could unlock similar benefits.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.livescience.com/health/genetics/best-ever-map-of-the-human-genome-sheds-light-on-jumping-genes-junk-dna-and-more" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.livescience.com/health/genetics/best-ever-map-of-the-human-genome-sheds-light-on-jumping-genes-junk-dna-and-more"&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Best-ever map of the human genome sheds light on 'jumping genes,' 'junk DNA' and more&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div id="slice-container-newsletterForm-articleInbodyContent-7AZkmdVBg48FvFTEd52Fy3" class="slice-container newsletter-inbodyContent-slice newsletterForm-articleInbodyContent-7AZkmdVBg48FvFTEd52Fy3 slice-container-newsletterForm"&gt;&lt;div data-hydrate="true" class="newsletter-form__wrapper newsletter-form__wrapper--inbodyContent"&gt;&lt;div class="newsletter-form__container"&gt;&lt;section class="newsletter-form__main-section"&gt;&lt;p class="newsletter-form__strapline"&gt;Get the world’s most fascinating discoveries delivered straight to your inbox.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h2 id="a-hub-of-hibernation-genes-3"&gt;A 'hub' of hibernation genes&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a pair of studies published Thursday (July 31) in the journal Science, Gregg and his team pinpointed key levers that control genes related to hibernation, showing how they &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="http://www.science.org/doi/10.1126/science.adp4025" target="_blank" data-url="http://www.science.org/doi/10.1126/science.adp4025" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;differ between animals that hibernate&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; and those that don't. Then, in the lab experiments, they delved into the effects of &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="http://www.science.org/doi/10.1126/science.adp4701" data-url="http://www.science.org/doi/10.1126/science.adp4701" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;deleting these levers in lab mice&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Although mice don't &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.livescience.com/54982-why-do-animals-hibernate.html" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.livescience.com/54982-why-do-animals-hibernate.html"&gt;&lt;u&gt;hibernate&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, they can enter torpor — a lethargic state of decreased metabolism, movement and body temperature that typically lasts for less than a day — after fasting for at least six hours. This made mice a suitable genetic model for studying these effects.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Using the gene-editing technique&lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.livescience.com/58790-crispr-explained.html" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.livescience.com/58790-crispr-explained.html"&gt; &lt;u&gt;CRISPR&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, the scientists engineered mice with one of five conserved noncoding cis elements (CREs) deactivated, or "knocked out." These CREs act as levers to control genes that, in turn, code for proteins that carry out biological functions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The CREs targeted in the study lie near a gene cluster called the "fat mass and obesity-related locus," or the FTO locus, which is also found in humans. Gene variants found within the cluster have been tied to &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC10404889/" target="_blank" data-url="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC10404889/" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;an elevated risk of obesity and related conditions&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. Broadly speaking, the FTO locus is known to be important for controlling metabolism, energy expenditure and body mass.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;By knocking out the CREs, the researchers were able to change the mice's weights, metabolic rates and foraging behaviors. Some deletions sped up or slowed down weight gain, others turned metabolic rate up or down, and some affected how quickly the mice's body temperatures recovered after torpor, the researchers said in a &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.eurekalert.org/news-releases/1092569" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.eurekalert.org/news-releases/1092569" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;statement&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This finding is "highly promising," particularly given the FTO locus plays a well-known role in human obesity, &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.uaf.edu/chem/files/kdrew/" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.uaf.edu/chem/files/kdrew/" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Kelly Drew&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, a specialist on hibernation biology at the University of Alaska Fairbanks, told Live Science in an email.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Knocking out one CRE — called E1 — in female mice caused them to gain more weight on a high-fat diet than did a comparison group with all of their DNA intact. Deleting a different CRE, called E3, changed the foraging behavior of both male and female mice, specifically changing how they searched for food hidden in an arena.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"This suggests that important differences in foraging and decision processes may exist between hibernators and non-hibernators and the elements we uncovered might be involved," Gregg said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="unknowns-to-address-3"&gt;Unknowns to address&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study authors said their results could be relevant to humans, since the underlying genes don't differ much between mammals. "It's how [the mammals] turn those genes on and off at different times and then for different durations and in different combinations that shape different species," Gregg said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, "it's definitely not as simple as introducing the same changes in human DNA," &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://evogenomes.sites.ucsc.edu/people/lab-members/" target="_blank" data-url="https://evogenomes.sites.ucsc.edu/people/lab-members/" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Joanna Kelley&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, a professor who specialises in functional genomics at the University of California, Santa Cruz, told Live Science in an email. "Humans are not capable of fasting-induced torpor, which is the reason why mice are used in these studies," said Kelley, who was not involved in the work.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She suggested that future work include animals incapable of torpor, and focus on unpacking all the downstream effects of the deleted CREs. As is, the current study "definitely points the field in a new direction" in terms of how scientists understand the genetic controls driving changes in hibernators throughout the year, she added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Drew also highlighted that torpor in mice is triggered by fasting, while true hibernation is triggered by hormonal and seasonal changes and &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.livescience.com/what-is-a-circadian-rhythm" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.livescience.com/what-is-a-circadian-rhythm"&gt;&lt;u&gt;internal clocks&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. So while the CREs and genes the study identified are likely critical parts of a metabolic "toolkit" that responds to fasting, they may not be a "master switch" that turns hibernation on or off.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Nevertheless, uncovering these fundamental mechanisms in a tractable model like the mouse is an invaluable stepping stone for future research," Drew said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gregg emphasized that much remains unknown, including why the effects of some deletions differed in female mice versus male mice or how the changes in foraging behavior seen in mice might manifest in humans. The team also plans to research what would happen if they deleted more than one hibernation-linked CRE at a time in mice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Down the line, Gregg thinks it could be possible to tweak the activity of humans' "hibernation hub genes" with drugs. The idea would be that this approach could yield the benefits of that gene activity — like neuroprotection — without patients having to actually hibernate, he said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Live Science</author><pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2025 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiywFBVV95cUxQdFdaRnhadENKODRHUklKeW5UZ2Y1ZGxzTHdJdnV6U0tqcEZic0drc1BHMks4UFRuazU5dUVIUnY5eUhWdUFXTnJ6MWM4UFhhcWR6ZjhHTUdjNGhYeE5YcDQzRWpTRGN2U3NaUGZBMmFwbV84YUJPNE9qd0syNjZDYzRIbklET0pZWWhiY2sydGFqRFgxRm1JN3FJdnNiZGxSUTFKb3d2c013LUhkQ3FuMWJpaXQxTFdXUjQ1bGxfbmZrMWdKcHk1dXZFNA</guid></item><item><title>构成“平均饮食一半”的食物的肺癌警告- RSVP Live</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMigAFBVV95cUxOWTFVVHpZUGRaME11dGVkOVpDb1BzazdmampVTjFHbjlLYXRuUTktN2M2TWZSZVJNZ2hhck1iLTJJQzIxY3hoRE82S2RwU2ZnSV9GN0R6MjFPSkw5NjlDYkxGRnp0WThqa0N6NFRLWXhEYnV4M0E5VkY4ejBPR3BlZ9IBhgFBVV95cUxNOFhrclNkSGZuSVNkSHVIamEyT3NOMWhPSnBHakNEYkp0NEx0QUMxcWVTMnFZbVJaNEUtSjBFODhWRkhIZXY0RHpqeUxRSGFkRzdzeDJkUi1TZEhDWnRsclRNdTVLdEFIcFlWZTY0ZkVwZElMTzhXZjRFeW1qaGZmVEl3M3pfZw?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body" itemprop="articleBody"&gt;&lt;p&gt;A serious warning has been issued on the dangers of ultra processed foods after a new study has shown a link between their consumption and a higher risk of lung cancer and other serious &lt;a href="https://www.rsvplive.ie/all-about/health" rel="Follow" target="_self" data-link-tracking="InArticle|Link" data-content-type="section-topic"&gt;health&lt;/a&gt; issues.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;In many Western countries more than half of the average diet now consists of ultra-processed foods (UPFs), such as ready meals, fast food and fizzy drinks.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;These foods typically undergo multiple processing steps, contain long lists of additives and preservatives, and are ready-to-eat or heat.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Now, eating UPFs has been linked to lung cancer - the most common cancer in the world, according to the World Cancer Research Fund.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;A BMJ study in 2024 linked the consumption of UPFs to 32 harmful health effects including a higher risk of heart disease, &lt;a href="https://www.rsvplive.ie/all-about/cancer" rel="Follow" target="_self" data-link-tracking="InArticle|Link" data-content-type="section-topic"&gt;cancer&lt;/a&gt;, type 2 diabetes, adverse mental health and early death.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Researchers of the study published in the respiratory journal Thorax said that limiting consumption of these foods may help curtail the global impact of lung disease.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The researchers focused in particular on UPFs that included sour cream, as well as cream cheese, ice cream, frozen yoghurt, fried foods, bread, baked goods, salted snacks, breakfast cereals, instant noodles, shop-bought soups and sauces, margarine, confectionery, soft drinks, sweetened fruit drinks, restaurant/shop-bought hamburgers, hot dogs, and pizza.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The three types of food that featured the most were lunch meat (11 per cent), &lt;a href="https://www.rsvplive.ie/all-about/diet" rel="Follow" target="_self" data-link-tracking="InArticle|Link" data-content-type="section-topic"&gt;diet&lt;/a&gt; or caffeinated soft drinks (just over 7 per cent) and decaffeinated soft drinks (nearly 7 per cent).&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;And the findings showed that even after accounting for potentially influential factors, including smoking and overall diet, participants who ate the most UPFs were 41 per cent more likely to be diagnosed with lung cancer than those who ate the least.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Speaking on their findings they revealed: “The rise in UPF consumption may have driven global increases in obesity, cardiovascular disease, metabolic disorders, cancer and mortality, as these foods are confirmed risk factors for such conditions,”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;“Industrial processing alters the food matrix, affecting nutrient availability and absorption, while also generating harmful contaminants,” they added, highlighting acrolein, which is found in grilled sausages and caramel sweets and is a toxic component of cigarette smoke. Packaging materials may also have a role to play."&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>RSVP Live</author><pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2025 15:37:51 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigAFBVV95cUxOWTFVVHpZUGRaME11dGVkOVpDb1BzazdmampVTjFHbjlLYXRuUTktN2M2TWZSZVJNZ2hhck1iLTJJQzIxY3hoRE82S2RwU2ZnSV9GN0R6MjFPSkw5NjlDYkxGRnp0WThqa0N6NFRLWXhEYnV4M0E5VkY4ejBPR3BlZ9IBhgFBVV95cUxNOFhrclNkSGZuSVNkSHVIamEyT3NOMWhPSnBHakNEYkp0NEx0QUMxcWVTMnFZbVJaNEUtSjBFODhWRkhIZXY0RHpqeUxRSGFkRzdzeDJkUi1TZEhDWnRsclRNdTVLdEFIcFlWZTY0ZkVwZElMTzhXZjRFeW1qaGZmVEl3M3pfZw</guid></item><item><title>在沉迷于可口可乐的小镇内，居民每年饮用800升，出于令人心碎的原因，孩子们用瓶装软饮料喂养-每日邮报</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMinwFBVV95cUxOR19tVER2b1pZSER5ZmdjdHMxMnA0ZjRrTzAtMmlveWlIdzJWbi1MSU5CSjhDRmxEWENQTjMzY3h2YUN1Sjd4aTU5SlhJYXAxYVNZYUJSTEEydEN2aGREZGM2aDZQLUxMRzhzQ0lWd2pwdFFTdmc2NUpybVJncFhVM0pDNEJucmNGQVJqc05JOGlGdHZOelBCTUxMRmlua1nSAaQBQVVfeXFMUGpXTnlWeW5DdDdvWV81NHBFajZQX1FkamFBNzFmbmEtUmtGalVNeFJlQjhwZGlaMnQyWEZlRUZnb3hYaDJaamp1NEx1TkQxbXBBNzVjNjk0TEt5aV92X2ZzN25GTFp2MGgtY3VGVTJ1UnRCaHZzYk9LMi05bHEyOHQ2aDVmdUpnVzRoQjFETjgtM1F2eERXYnhkcjdMd3l4aG9sTTI?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div itemprop="articleBody"&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In a remote mountain town where clean drinking water is considered a luxury, locals are turning to Coca-Cola - and not just for refreshment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/mexico/index.html" id="mol-baf7f430-6ff8-11f0-8e2d-5577fc266f28"&gt;Mexico&lt;/a&gt;'s poorest and southernmost state of Chiapas, fizzy drinks are deeply ingrained in the local culture. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;And in the town of San Cristobal de las Casas, the obsession has spiralled out of control, with some residents guzzling up to two litres of Coca-Cola every day, or around 800 litres a year, according to the Chiapas and Southern Border Multidisciplinary Research Center. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The iconic red and white logos line shop shelves, street stalls and even sacred shrines.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;And the town's obsession with Coca-Cola does not stop there, as some residents are even known to fill their children's baby bottles with Coke instead of milk. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;An hour away from San Cristobal, in the Indigenous town of San Andres, locals consider the fizzy beverage liquid gold.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Shamans will use it as part of their religious ceremonies and regularly pray over bottles of Coca-Cola as they carry out rituals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Fridges stocked with bottles of Coke sit next to their sacred shrines, ready to sell to faithful locals who use them as offerings, as many believe the drink has healing powers. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;In Mexico's poorest and southernmost state of Chiapas, fizzy drinks are deeply ingrained in the local culture&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;The iconic red and white bottles line shop shelves, street stalls and even sacred shrines&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Shamans will use it as part of their religious ceremonies and regularly pray over bottles of Coca-Cola as they carry out rituals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But religion is not the only reason for the state's dependency on Coca-Cola, and behind the ritual lies a dark reality. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;With a growing population, safe drinking water has become increasingly scarce in the area, with some neighbourhoods only having access to running water a few times a week. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Just 7 per cent of households in Chiapas believe their water is safe to drink, according to a 2023 national survey, forcing many to buy bottled water or the fizzy drink, which is just as cheap.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;A local plant owned by Femsa, a food and drink conglomerate that owns the rights to bottle and sell Coca-Cola in Latin America, is allowed to extract more than 1.3million litres of water a day as part of a concession with the federal government, all while local communities struggle to find safe drinking water. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Critics believe the multinational is guilty of having created a web of addiction.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Doctor Marcos Arana, who campaigns against the power and influence of Coca-Cola, says that 'Coca-Cola has developed a strategy precisely so that it's available anywhere.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'They convince consumers to sell soft drinks on a small scale and obviously generates many captive customers'. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The crisis goes back to 1994, when Mexico signed the North American Free Trade Agreement, which paved the way for cheap and accessible soft drinks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Mexico's children consume more junk food than anywhere else in Latin America, according to UNICEF, which classifies the nation's childhood obesity epidemic as an emergency&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;In the town of San Cristobal de las Casas, the obsession has spiralled out of control, with some residents guzzling up to two litres of Coca-Cola every single day&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Just 7 per cent of households in Chiapas believe their water is safe to drink, according to a 2023 national survey, forcing many to buy bottled water or the fizzy drink, which is just as cheap&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;A local plant owned by Femsa, a food and drink conglomerate that owns the rights to bottle and sell Coca-Cola in Latin America, is allowed to extract more than 1.3 million litres of water a day as part of a concession with the federal government&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;But Coca-Cola's popularity has led to a 'catastrophic' obesity crisis in Chiapas&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;As a result, Coca-Cola has flooded the market and has become embedded in Mexico's daily life and culture.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But Coca-Cola's popularity has led to a 'catastrophic' obesity crisis in Chiapas, health officials say, with several residents now suffering from Type 2 diabetes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Mexico's children consume more junk food than anywhere else in Latin America, according to UNICEF, which classifies the nation's childhood obesity epidemic as an emergency. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Sugary drinks and highly processed foods account for 40 per cent of the total calories that children consume in a day, the agency reports. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;One third of Mexican children are already considered overweight or obese, according to government statistics. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;A 2020 study by the Organization for Economic Cooperation and Development showed Mexico stands to lose the greatest amount of life expectancy - an average of at least four years - due to obesity-related problems. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In coming years, the country could lose over five percent of its GDP to obesity-related problems, including lost work hours and health costs. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Health authorities say about 39 per cent of Mexicans are overweight and 36 per cent are obese. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;In the Indigenous town of San Andres, locals consider the fizzy beverage liquid gold&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Health authorities say about 39 per cent of Mexicans are overweight and 36 per cent are obese.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Obesity levels in Chiapas are largely linked to the consumption to the high-calorie sugary drink&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;About 10 per cent of Mexicans have some form of diabetes. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In Coca-Cola-addicted Chiapas, which boasts a population of more than 5,000, people die from diabetes-related illnesses, making it the second leading cause of death after heart disease in the state. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Obesity levels in Chiapas are largely linked to the consumption to the high-calorie sugary drink. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;And yet, Coca-Cola continues to flow despite its deadly cost.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Daily Mail</author><pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2025 15:12:51 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMinwFBVV95cUxOR19tVER2b1pZSER5ZmdjdHMxMnA0ZjRrTzAtMmlveWlIdzJWbi1MSU5CSjhDRmxEWENQTjMzY3h2YUN1Sjd4aTU5SlhJYXAxYVNZYUJSTEEydEN2aGREZGM2aDZQLUxMRzhzQ0lWd2pwdFFTdmc2NUpybVJncFhVM0pDNEJucmNGQVJqc05JOGlGdHZOelBCTUxMRmlua1nSAaQBQVVfeXFMUGpXTnlWeW5DdDdvWV81NHBFajZQX1FkamFBNzFmbmEtUmtGalVNeFJlQjhwZGlaMnQyWEZlRUZnb3hYaDJaamp1NEx1TkQxbXBBNzVjNjk0TEt5aV92X2ZzN25GTFp2MGgtY3VGVTJ1UnRCaHZzYk9LMi05bHEyOHQ2aDVmdUpnVzRoQjFETjgtM1F2eERXYnhkcjdMd3l4aG9sTTI</guid></item><item><title>白血病病毒如何隐藏在体内-这是未来治疗的关键- Medical Xpress</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiggFBVV95cUxNWi1NVXNXNmZwMDRGd05FZXVUb2c5OGRWb1ZGYVRPaGJvMmtTWE0zdkFkUTd0UlhQS1VYNzlXeFByWDJ2bFNjc25GSHo4WURYRjNObjRfcmxuQUcyeDRPSVNRY3pQU0R4YjExRE1zMWdrbkJobndhd05uOGJNOXJOYTFn?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="mt-4 article-main"&gt;
									    
&lt;div class="article-gallery lightGallery"&gt;
    &lt;div data-thumb="https://scx1.b-cdn.net/csz/news/tmb/2025/scientists-discover-ho-8.jpg" data-src="https://scx2.b-cdn.net/gfx/news/hires/2025/scientists-discover-ho-8.jpg" data-sub-html="A scheme illustrating the molecular mechanisms underlying HTLV-1 latency. Credit: &amp;lt;i&amp;gt;Nature Microbiology&amp;lt;/i&amp;gt; (2025). DOI: 10.1038/s41564-025-02006-7"&gt;
        &lt;figure class="article-img"&gt;
            &lt;img src="https://scx1.b-cdn.net/csz/news/800a/2025/scientists-discover-ho-8.jpg" alt="Scientists discover how leukemia virus stays hidden in the body—a key to future treatments" title="A scheme illustrating the molecular mechanisms underlying HTLV-1 latency. Credit: Nature Microbiology (2025). DOI: 10.1038/s41564-025-02006-7"&gt;
             &lt;figcaption class="text-darken text-low-up text-truncate-js text-truncate mt-3"&gt;
                A scheme illustrating the molecular mechanisms underlying HTLV-1 latency. Credit: &lt;i&gt;Nature Microbiology&lt;/i&gt; (2025). DOI: 10.1038/s41564-025-02006-7
            &lt;/figcaption&gt;        &lt;/figure&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;A research team from Kumamoto University has made a new discovery that reveals how the human T-cell leukemia virus type 1 (HTLV-1) silently persists in the body. Their finding potentially lays the foundation for new therapeutic approaches. Their study, &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41564-025-02006-7" target="_blank"&gt;published&lt;/a&gt; in &lt;i&gt;Nature Microbiology&lt;/i&gt;, identifies a previously unknown genetic "silencer" element that keeps the virus in a dormant, undetectable state.&lt;/p&gt;

                                        
                                                                                &lt;p class="w-100 my-4 d-print-none"&gt;
     
     
     &lt;ins class="adsbygoogle" data-ad-layout="in-article" data-ad-format="fluid" data-ad-client="ca-pub-0536483524803400" data-ad-slot="7587637799"&gt;&lt;/ins&gt;
     
&lt;/p&gt;  
                                         

                                                                                    &lt;p&gt;HTLV-1 is a cancer-causing retrovirus known to lead to adult T-cell &lt;a href="https://medicalxpress.com/tags/leukemia/" rel="tag" class="textTag"&gt;leukemia&lt;/a&gt;/lymphoma (ATL), an aggressive and often fatal disease. Although most infected individuals remain asymptomatic for life, a fraction eventually develop leukemia or other inflammatory conditions. The &lt;a href="https://medicalxpress.com/tags/virus/" rel="tag" class="textTag"&gt;virus&lt;/a&gt; achieves long-term persistence by entering a "latent" state, during which its genetic material hides inside the host's genome with minimal activity—evading immune detection.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this study, the research team, led by Professor Yorifumi Satou from the Joint Research Center for Human Retrovirus, Kumamoto University, identified a &lt;a href="https://medicalxpress.com/tags/specific+region/" rel="tag" class="textTag"&gt;specific region&lt;/a&gt; within the HTLV-1 genome that functions as a viral silencer. This sequence recruits host transcription factors, particularly the RUNX1 complex, which suppresses the virus's gene expression. When this silencer region was removed or mutated, the virus became more active, leading to greater immune recognition and clearance in lab models.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Remarkably, when the HTLV-1 silencer was artificially inserted into HIV-1—the virus that causes AIDS—the HIV virus adopted a more latent-like state, with reduced replication and cell killing. This suggests that the silencer mechanism could potentially be harnessed to design better therapies for HIV as well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"This is the first time we've uncovered a built-in mechanism that allows a human leukemia virus to regulate its own invisibility," said Professor Satou. "It's a clever evolutionary tactic, and now that we understand it, we might be able to turn the tables in treatment."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The findings offer hope not only for understanding and treating HTLV-1, especially in endemic regions like southwestern Japan, but also for broader retroviral infections.&lt;/p&gt;

                                        
                                                                                
                                        											&lt;div class="article-main__more p-4"&gt;
												                                                    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;More information:&lt;/strong&gt;
                                                    Kenji Sugata et al, Intragenic viral silencer element regulates HTLV-1 latency via RUNX complex recruitment, &lt;i&gt;Nature Microbiology&lt;/i&gt; (2025). &lt;a data-doi="1" href="https://dx.doi.org/10.1038/s41564-025-02006-7" target="_blank"&gt;DOI: 10.1038/s41564-025-02006-7&lt;/a&gt;
																								
																								&lt;/p&gt;
																							&lt;/div&gt;
                                        											
																					
                                                                                                                        
                                        
                                        &lt;div class="d-none d-print-block"&gt;
                                            &lt;p class="mb-4"&gt;
                                                 &lt;strong&gt;Citation&lt;/strong&gt;:
                                                 How leukemia virus stays hidden in the body—and a key to future treatments (2025, August 3)
                                                 retrieved 4 August 2025
                                                 from https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-08-leukemia-virus-stays-hidden-body.html
                                            &lt;/p&gt;
                                            &lt;p class="border text-muted p-3"&gt;
                                            This document is subject to copyright. Apart from any fair dealing for the purpose of private study or research, no
                                            part may be reproduced without the written permission. The content is provided for information purposes only.
                                            &lt;/p&gt;
                                        &lt;/div&gt;
                                        
									&lt;/div&gt;
								&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Medical Xpress</author><pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2025 15:00:01 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiggFBVV95cUxNWi1NVXNXNmZwMDRGd05FZXVUb2c5OGRWb1ZGYVRPaGJvMmtTWE0zdkFkUTd0UlhQS1VYNzlXeFByWDJ2bFNjc25GSHo4WURYRjNObjRfcmxuQUcyeDRPSVNRY3pQU0R4YjExRE1zMWdrbkJobndhd05uOGJNOXJOYTFn</guid></item><item><title>结肠癌在年轻人中迅速激增；美国胃肠病学家推荐4种水果来削减结肠癌-印度时报</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiugJBVV95cUxNR0RHNUdoaTQyVzJUVTNfSnVLVFNEWVE2V2JMZnRLYlRpbmZtY0ZFc3NpdHdIM1U3VGtaak9tbWJaeHBDTmRJM2o2Y2xFUGtROGJVRGFNWWNYZEpPcHg4MjM5eHNCZVlFb21DNk96djl1ZHZQS2tkc1YtQWZ2RG4teGJ0a1VrU0pSaUNVV1FhOFFHcWtsa0V2VWFXLUhKWWM3cGV5ZEZpQk1SRXAtNndzLVFiTVIwVWtMSWZtbngwMTRCLXJrSmI5Unl1dkhSSDktQURMU1o0VWhsS3pJV0F6TjduUEZDQ2NzaEF6bm1iQ25nOEt4a1EtVU9WYzdMdEJpRzhIdWFYUmYxR2hSOGR0dmdwbTJabG9Ec1VwVGZ5ejVHUVRxUDBIdXFldDEwWUR3X3hhN2tHbkFCUdIBvwJBVV95cUxPRzdFM3BXNEVMSlhoWmIwYUtBSUFUc1B3RHlHdHRBdTRsZ2FzbHdIYXJWeGJpSm5GeEZiV25hcVhuUWF6ZkR2SDc2Z2NDRl9fOENueGZwNEp1ME84cTktSGZoNTlHOGI3empVcC03MW1xY195RUhZaUxnZFpKRWdEOG9aNHJjdmg5WlIteDE2cF9JUzFHMDliMHNHU3NLZzY4OS1GUTg3RDJjT2J5MkpkSzAzb0Mxam9VLTd5RmhkczBEVnNHd0dYSXVTX0JsbUtJWnZfYmRVR25YNExsYk5XNy1HTGlycmNZTWJFRWJZdE5qN2FkYlh3X3BCN1hIdFB4cm93MzlnalRmcnJnSm1jQmFldXphdjJ6VkxibzdBZkdtX3FDcVJ6cW9TWHNJYUM5cnhCYVJKME1jd013bXhv?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="0"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Doctors in recent years have noticed an alarming trend: colon cancer, once considered a condition primarily affecting older adults, is now being diagnosed more frequently in individuals under the age of 50.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="3"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Colorectal cancer, also known as colon cancer, is a type of cancer that develops in the tissues of the colon or rectum. It's one of the most common types of cancer worldwide and the second leading cause of cancer death in the United States. Thanks to obesity and alcohol consumption, bowel cancer has become the primary cause of the rising death toll among young adults.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="5"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The colon and rectum are both parts of the large intestine, which is part of the digestive system. Colorectal cancer often begins as a growth called a polyp inside the colon or rectum. Most colorectal cancers are curable when localized to the bowel. However, recurrence following surgery is a major problem and is often the ultimate cause of death. Colorectal cancer can develop when cells in the colon or rectum change and no longer behave normally. These changes can lead to precancerous conditions, such as adenomas, or colorectal cancer itself. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The most common type of colorectal cancer is adenocarcinoma, which starts in the gland cells that line the colon or rectum.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="12"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Colorectal cancer, the most common gastrointestinal cancer, disproportionately affects Black, Hispanic, Indigenous, and Asian populations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="14"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to the &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cancer.org/cancer/types/colon-rectal-cancer/about/key-statistics.html" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="_blank" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;American Cancer Society&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, colon cancer impacts more than 100,000 Americans every year. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="18"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="20"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, healthcare providers are relentlessly trying to draw our attention to the kind of lifestyle—including dietary habits, workouts, and sleeping patterns—that could be our ally in order to prevent colon cancer, especially in young adults. In this fight to prevent this aggressive type of cancer, nature’s basket must be our go-to, instead of processed and ultra-processed foods. A US-based Gastroenterologist, Joseph Salhab, D.O., recently shared a list of nutrition-packed fruits and vegetables that have been shown to reduce colon cancer risk, per a &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/37213399/" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="_blank" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;2023 study&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; published in the World Journal of Gastroenterology.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="27"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="29"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="30"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Fruits to reduce the risk of colon cancer (when and how to eat them)&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="31"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="32"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Watermelon&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="33"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;More than just a summertime favorite, watermelon may offer real health benefits, including &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/37213399/" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="_blank" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;a 26% reduction&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; in colon cancer risk with regular consumption, according to recent findings. Gastroenterologists recommend the fruit for its high lycopene content, a powerful antioxidant believed to protect cells from damage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="39"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="41"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Best time to eat:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; Mid‑morning or afternoon snack, to both hydrate and curb cravings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="44"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Spruce it up:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; As Dr. Salhab highlights, watermelon is also incredibly hydrating, which supports digestive health and promotes regular bowel movements. Try it in savory dishes like a Watermelon, Cucumber &amp;amp; Feta Salad, or enjoy its natural sweetness in a refreshing No-Churn Watermelon Ice Cream.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="48"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="49"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Apples&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="50"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The saying "an apple a day keeps the doctor away" may hold more truth than expected. Rich in gut-friendly fiber, apples have been shown to &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/37213399/" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="_blank" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;reduce colon cancer risk by 25%&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; when consumed in higher amounts. They also contain polyphenols, which Dr. Salhab notes offer antioxidant and anti-inflammatory properties.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="54"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="56"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Best time to eat:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; Raw as breakfast or after lunch.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="59"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Spruce it up:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; Apples are not only portable and satisfying on their own, but also versatile in meals, from salads and overnight oats to a classic snack with peanut butter for a fiber and protein-rich combo.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="63"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="64"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Kiwi&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="65"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;With a potential to &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/37213399/" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="_blank" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;lower colorectal cancer risk by 13%&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, kiwi is another fruit that shines in both nutrition and taste. Dr. Salhab calls it an excellent source of fiber, helping to support digestion. It’s also loaded with vitamin C, which plays a role in immune function, heart health, and skin repair.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="69"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="71"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Best time to eat:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; With breakfast or as part of fruit bowls to kickstart digestion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="74"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Spruce it up:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; While kiwi adds brightness to fruit salads and yogurt bowls, it also pairs beautifully with savory fare, like in Easy Fish Tacos with Kiwi Salsa.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="78"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="79"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Citrus fruits (oranges, grapefruit, lemons, limes)&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="80"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Including more citrus fruits in your diet, such as oranges, grapefruits, lemons, limes, and tangerines, may also contribute to lower colon cancer risk, with studies showing &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/37213399/" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="_blank" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;a 9% decrease&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; linked to higher citrus intake. These fruits are loaded with vitamin C, which acts as an antioxidant to help neutralize free radicals and possibly minimize DNA damage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="84"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="86"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Best time to eat:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; Fresh citrus juice or whole fruit in the morning or midday.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="90"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Spruce it up:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; Citrus also provides flavonoids, a type of polyphenol that may slow aging, reduce inflammation, and support cancer prevention. Celebrate warm weather and gut health with a Citrus Salad with Pomegranate &amp;amp; Mint, or repurpose scraps into a zero-waste Orange Peel Smoothie.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="93"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="94"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Why fruits are a great ally in cancer prevention&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="95"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;While dietary fiber and plant-based foods are known to reduce colorectal cancer risk, not all fruits are equal. A 2023 meta-analysis found protective associations specifically for citrus, apples, watermelon, and kiwi. Compared to a low intake:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="97"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Watermelon reduced risk by 26%&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="99"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="100"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Apples by 25%&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="102"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="103"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Kiwi by 13%&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="105"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="106"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Citrus by 9%, with an optimal intake of around 120 g/day&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="108"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="109"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, it is important to note that while fruit can play a supportive role, no single food can prevent or cure cancer. An amalgamation of protective habits, like consuming a high-fiber, plant-rich diet, combined with exercise, well-managed weight, and minimal alcohol, is essential. High-fiber, plant-rich diets are associated with significantly lower colorectal cancer risk; every extra 10 grams of fiber daily may reduce risk by about 7%. Cutting processed and red meats, sugary drinks, ultraprocessed foods, and limiting alcohol is essential, increasing risk by up to 40% in some studies. Furthermore, maintaining a healthy weight and exercising regularly helps reduce inflammation and the risk of digestive cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="114"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2025 14:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiugJBVV95cUxNR0RHNUdoaTQyVzJUVTNfSnVLVFNEWVE2V2JMZnRLYlRpbmZtY0ZFc3NpdHdIM1U3VGtaak9tbWJaeHBDTmRJM2o2Y2xFUGtROGJVRGFNWWNYZEpPcHg4MjM5eHNCZVlFb21DNk96djl1ZHZQS2tkc1YtQWZ2RG4teGJ0a1VrU0pSaUNVV1FhOFFHcWtsa0V2VWFXLUhKWWM3cGV5ZEZpQk1SRXAtNndzLVFiTVIwVWtMSWZtbngwMTRCLXJrSmI5Unl1dkhSSDktQURMU1o0VWhsS3pJV0F6TjduUEZDQ2NzaEF6bm1iQ25nOEt4a1EtVU9WYzdMdEJpRzhIdWFYUmYxR2hSOGR0dmdwbTJabG9Ec1VwVGZ5ejVHUVRxUDBIdXFldDEwWUR3X3hhN2tHbkFCUdIBvwJBVV95cUxPRzdFM3BXNEVMSlhoWmIwYUtBSUFUc1B3RHlHdHRBdTRsZ2FzbHdIYXJWeGJpSm5GeEZiV25hcVhuUWF6ZkR2SDc2Z2NDRl9fOENueGZwNEp1ME84cTktSGZoNTlHOGI3empVcC03MW1xY195RUhZaUxnZFpKRWdEOG9aNHJjdmg5WlIteDE2cF9JUzFHMDliMHNHU3NLZzY4OS1GUTg3RDJjT2J5MkpkSzAzb0Mxam9VLTd5RmhkczBEVnNHd0dYSXVTX0JsbUtJWnZfYmRVR25YNExsYk5XNy1HTGlycmNZTWJFRWJZdE5qN2FkYlh3X3BCN1hIdFB4cm93MzlnalRmcnJnSm1jQmFldXphdjJ6VkxibzdBZkdtX3FDcVJ6cW9TWHNJYUM5cnhCYVJKME1jd013bXhv</guid></item><item><title>健康专家警告Benadryl可能没有想象的那么有用- NewsNation</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMidkFVX3lxTE1sTFNXejlXTXkydTZLVkI3ekRJdHk3b1NZZHFYMzVkSURNYndTbUMzZG5POFEyNnYzNGw1aTlyNEQ0Mk9EX25kSXoyOUJHVktSSFBXaW9sS2JYbGduUUM2MFhlX2g3M0pCd3RwbUhhU2dJZGg3OVHSAXtBVV95cUxNakY3NmJBeGNIY2FaQ0xSbU9Yc0pHMW5fb1E3OHFac05LSDRFUEFhQlpPWlpWTEd1b0VneE1wZy1PTGdvcDZaNHlVblBtam01ZzYyemI5LU9relF1RFVOaU45WkV5TmlZUXplLUxicS11MjdXTEltVWNveXM?oc=5</link><description>&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;
    
    
    &lt;noscript&gt;
      
    &lt;/noscript&gt;
  &lt;/body&gt;
</description><author>NewsNation</author><pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2025 14:24:24 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMidkFVX3lxTE1sTFNXejlXTXkydTZLVkI3ekRJdHk3b1NZZHFYMzVkSURNYndTbUMzZG5POFEyNnYzNGw1aTlyNEQ0Mk9EX25kSXoyOUJHVktSSFBXaW9sS2JYbGduUUM2MFhlX2g3M0pCd3RwbUhhU2dJZGg3OVHSAXtBVV95cUxNakY3NmJBeGNIY2FaQ0xSbU9Yc0pHMW5fb1E3OHFac05LSDRFUEFhQlpPWlpWTEd1b0VneE1wZy1PTGdvcDZaNHlVblBtam01ZzYyemI5LU9relF1RFVOaU45WkV5TmlZUXplLUxicS11MjdXTEltVWNveXM</guid></item></channel></rss>