<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>GNews Health</title><link>https://news.google.com/</link><description></description><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>血液测试可以预测谁最容易患上常见遗传性心脏病--《卫报》</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/society/2025/dec/25/blood-test-predict-risk-inherited-heart-condition-hypertrophic-cardiomyopathy</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body-commercial-selector article-body-viewer-selector dcr-hdpgoq"&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Scientists are developing a simple blood test to predict who is most at risk from the world’s most common inherited heart condition.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Millions of people worldwide have hypertrophic cardiomyopathy (HCM), a disease of the heart muscle where the wall of the heart becomes thickened. It is caused by a change in one or more genes and mostly passed on through families.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="sign-in-gate"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Some feel fine most of the time and have few or no symptoms. But others can suffer complications, such as heart failure and abnormal heart rhythms, which can lead to a cardiac arrest.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The problem is there is no cure. Doctors also &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/science/2025/jan/08/outdated-guidelines-mean-doctors-failing-to-spot-heart-condition-in-women" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;do not know which patients&lt;/a&gt; with the genetic condition are most at risk from deadly complications.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;But now a team of scientists from universities including Harvard and Oxford have found a way to forecast risk for people living with HCM.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The blood test could identify those patients most in danger of complications, enabling them to be monitored more closely or receive life-saving treatment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;In a landmark study, the team measured the levels of a protein, N-terminal Pro-B-type natriuretic peptide (NT-Pro-BNP), in the blood of 700 HCM patients.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;NT-Pro-BNP is released by the heart as part of normal pumping. But high levels are a sign the heart is working too hard. Those with the highest levels had poorer blood flow, more scar tissue and changes in their heart which could lead to atrial fibrillation or heart failure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;A blood test measuring NT-Pro-BNP could transform the care of millions of people with the world’s most common inherited heart condition.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The study leader, Prof Carolyn Ho, the medical director of the cardiovascular genetics centre at Harvard medical school, said the test could help “target the right therapies to the right patients at the right time”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;She added: “Continued studies on blood biomarkers will lead to better understanding of HCM so that, in future, we can offer our patients a blood test to identify who is at high versus low risk of experiencing serious consequences of the disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“People with the highest risk could be targeted for potentially life-saving treatments as they stand to receive the greatest benefit, while those at lowest risk could avoid unnecessary treatment.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Lara Johnson, 34, from Southampton in the UK, is one of many who could benefit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="3eeff211-4533-46b2-bfc2-0e18861b2e1f" data-spacefinder-role="richLink" data-spacefinder-type="model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.RichLinkBlockElement" class="dcr-47fhrn"&gt;&lt;gu-island name="RichLinkComponent" priority="feature" deferuntil="idle" props='{"richLinkIndex":13,"element":{"_type":"model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.RichLinkBlockElement","prefix":"Related: ","text":"Parasite cleanses: why are so many people obsessed with intestinal worms?","elementId":"3eeff211-4533-46b2-bfc2-0e18861b2e1f","role":"richLink","url":"https://www.theguardian.com/lifeandstyle/2025/dec/09/parasite-cleanses-people-obsessed-intestinal-worms"},"ajaxUrl":"https://api.nextgen.guardianapps.co.uk","format":{"design":0,"display":0,"theme":0}}'&gt;&lt;/gu-island&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Eight years ago, she began experiencing breathlessness and fatigue. After being referred by her GP for hospital tests, she was diagnosed with HCM. Several relatives on her father’s side were subsequently also diagnosed with the condition.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“One of the hardest parts of living with HCM is the constant uncertainty, never knowing what might change next,” Johnson said. “A simple blood test, which could help identify future risks earlier, would take away so much of that anxiety.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;She added: “It could give people like me a chance to prepare and adjust our lifestyles as needed, and help us to feel more in control. That kind of clarity wouldn’t only help me, it would make a world of difference for my whole family.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Prof Bryan Williams, the chief scientific and medical officer of the British Heart Foundation, which funded the research, said the test “could benefit patients around the world”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“After a diagnosis of HCM, patients and their families want to know what the future holds. This study shows that measuring various proteins circulating in the blood could help predict how the heart is functioning and future risk of complications from heart disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“This new method may also provide insights in the evolution of the structure and function of the heart in people with HCM that could point to new ways of treating this condition to reduce future risk.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Guardian</author><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiwwFBVV95cUxPUlppcm1LVVd3MDZPbEtJd25TX3Y4Z2NwdDh2d3RWcTJhLTNBN3BJaHAtX3BlMUxOdDVfSkF3Vlk1TG1NcU1JVDVWRUNkU183VFJMc0M0SEJZQWJmRm5HczA3OTFzY3pmNGJxaEtqOVcxeXpRSW5QS255QUhJODhKdkNYNV9mNWxhdTZfNl9Gai0tQ1VQQVRUOG9kTlVjNDN6ckhYQnJyMjUxcncyNkp6YWpISXR3QlNkN29jRlNuelZWRzQ</guid></item><item><title>新技术以创纪录的速度和效率消除“永久化学物质” - ScienceDaily</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/12/251224032401.htm</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p id="first" class="lead"&gt;A research team at Rice University, working with international collaborators, has created the first environmentally friendly technology that can quickly trap and break down toxic "forever chemicals" (PFAS) in water. The results, published recently in &lt;em&gt;Advanced Materials&lt;/em&gt;, represent a meaningful advance against one of the most stubborn pollution threats worldwide.&lt;/p&gt;

						&lt;div id="text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The project was led by Youngkun Chung, a postdoctoral fellow mentored by Michael S. Wong, a professor at Rice's George R. Brown School of Engineering and Computing. The effort also included Seoktae Kang, a professor at the Korea Advanced Institute of Science and Technology (KAIST), and Keon-Ham Kim, a professor at Pukyung National University in South Korea.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What Are PFAS and Why Are They a Problem&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PFAS, short for per- and polyfluoroalkyl substances, are man-made chemicals that date back to the 1940s. They have been used in many everyday products, including Teflon pans, waterproof clothing, and some food packaging. PFAS became popular because they resist heat, grease, and water, but that same durability also means they break down very slowly, which is why they are often called "forever chemicals."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PFAS have now spread widely and can be found in water, soil, and air around the world. Research has linked exposure to liver damage, reproductive disorders, immune system disruption, and certain cancers. Cleanup has been difficult because once PFAS enter the environment, they are hard to remove and even harder to destroy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why Current PFAS Removal Methods Fall Short&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Many standard approaches rely on adsorption, meaning the chemicals stick to materials such as activated carbon or ion-exchange resins. These methods are common, but they have major limitations, including low efficiency, slow operation, limited capacity, and the buildup of additional contaminated waste that still has to be handled.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="insertion_middle"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Current methods for PFAS removal are too slow, inefficient and create secondary waste," said Wong, the Tina and Sunit Patel Professor in Molecular Nanotechnology and professor of chemical and biomolecular engineering, chemistry and civil and environmental engineering. "Our new approach offers a sustainable and highly effective alternative."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Breakthrough LDH Material That Works Fast&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The new approach is built around a layered double hydroxide (LDH) material made from copper and aluminum. Kim first identified this type of material while he was a graduate student at KAIST in 2021. As the team explored these compounds further, Chung found that a specific version containing nitrate could adsorb PFAS with unusually high performance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"To my astonishment, this LDH compound captured PFAS more than 1,000 times better than other materials," said Chung, a lead author of the study and now a fellow at Rice's WaTER (Water Technologies, Entrepreneurship and Research) Institute and Sustainability Institute. "It also worked incredibly fast, removing large amounts of PFAS within minutes, about 100 times faster than commercial carbon filters."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Researchers say the impressive results come from the material's internal design. Its ordered copper-aluminum layers, along with small charge imbalances, create a highly favorable surface where PFAS molecules can attach quickly and strongly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tested in River Water, Tap Water, and Wastewater&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To see how well the system could perform outside the lab, the team tested the LDH material in river water, tap water, and wastewater. Across all three, it remained highly effective. It also performed well in both static tests and continuous-flow setups, pointing to possible use in municipal water treatment systems and industrial cleanup.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="insertion_bottom"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Closing the Loop With PFAS Destruction and Reuse&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Capturing PFAS is only half the battle since the chemicals still need to be destroyed safely. Working with Rice professors Pedro Alvarez and James Tour, Chung developed a process to thermally decompose PFAS after they are captured on the LDH material. When the PFAS-loaded material was heated with calcium carbonate, the researchers removed more than half of the trapped PFAS without releasing toxic by-products. The same step also regenerated the LDH, making it possible to use the material again.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Early testing showed the material could go through at least six complete cycles of capture, destruction, and renewal. That makes it the first known eco-friendly, sustainable system for PFAS removal that combines rapid cleanup with repeated reuse.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;International Collaboration and Research Support&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"We are excited by the potential of this one-of-a-kind LDH-based technology to transform how PFAS-contaminated water sources are treated in the near future," Wong said. "It's the result of an extraordinary international collaboration and the creativity of young researchers."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A list of all the researchers involved in this study and their institutional affiliations can be found here. This research was supported by the Basic Science Research Program through the National Research Foundation of Korea funded by the Ministry of Education (2021R1A6A3A14044449, RS-2023-00242795), grants from the National Convergence Research of Scientific Challenges and the Sejong Science Fellowship through the National Research Foundation of Korea and funding from the Ministry of Science (NRF-2022M3C1C8094245) and ICT (RS-2024-00395438). This work was also funded by Saudi Aramco-KAIST CO2 Management, Nanosystems Engineering Research Center for Nanotechnology-Enabled Water Treatment (NEWT), the U.S. Army Corps of Engineers' Engineering Research and Development Center grant (W912HZ-21-2-0050), Rice Sustainability Institute and Rice WaTER Institute.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

					&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceDaily</author><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 06:46:33 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMib0FVX3lxTE1KN0pYLW5VMEM2T2I2R2phaU9RVEZLZEVPa210YXAtNnJQZWxTcUZGUGZRYXRtRTBBUElXWFZ2VUxfLXozVkowZHhOQzBTYjhWWDlPN0JVa1JDZG9COVpaNy1CT1hDUFE3bEp6a1pLOA</guid></item><item><title>医生回答：如何治疗流感和无用的药物- Ynetnews</title><link>https://www.ynetnews.com/health_science/article/bjplqrfmwg</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div data-contents="true"&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="7qbk7" data-offset-key="3rd6n-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="3rd6n-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="3rd6n-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;This year’s flu season began early, with five children dying from complications of the disease and hospitalizations on the rise. Family doctors are warning that influenza is not a mild winter illness, outlining its symptoms, identifying who is truly at risk and explaining how it should, and should not, be treated.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="7qbk7" data-offset-key="6etn1-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="6etn1-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="6etn1-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;“Influenza is a viral disease characterized by complications of the respiratory system,” says Dr. Zehava Alon, a family medicine specialist with Clalit Health Services’ Central District. She describes it as a severe illness that typically lasts about a week and is marked by very high fever and serious respiratory symptoms, including cough, pneumonia, sinus infections, shortness of breath and bouts of bronchitis, along with body aches and profound weakness. Unlike common cold viruses, which usually cause mild symptoms and resolve within days, influenza can worsen significantly. “Patients die from the complications, when the underlying cause is influenza,” she says, noting the deaths of five children this year and severe outcomes among older adults.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure data-block="true" data-editor="7qbk7" data-offset-key="63c9c-0-0" contenteditable="false"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="7qbk7" data-offset-key="cudbb-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="cudbb-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="cudbb-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;Dr. Adam Reiter, a family medicine specialist with Maccabi Healthcare Services, echoed her remarks. “Generally speaking, influenza is a viral disease of the respiratory tract. In most cases it begins and remains in the upper respiratory tract, meaning the nose and throat, but it can, God forbid, worsen and spread to the lower respiratory tract — the lungs. That is why it has the potential, like any viral illness and perhaps more so than other viruses, to cause significant respiratory disease with lung involvement.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure data-block="true" data-editor="7qbk7" data-offset-key="ai7j8-0-0" contenteditable="false"&gt;&lt;div class="ArticleImageComponenta wrapped"&gt;&lt;div class="ArticleWrappedImageComponenta"&gt;&lt;img id="ReduxEditableImage_ArticleWrappedImageData.rkx003ERYQbg" src="https://ynet-pic1.yit.co.il/cdn-cgi/image/format=auto/picserver6/crop_images/2025/12/21/H1gRB7qHm11l/H1gRB7qHm11l_142_528_697_930_0_medium.jpg" alt='ד"ר זהבה אלון, רופאת משפחה, כללית' title="Dr. Zehava Alon " aria-hidden="false"&gt;&lt;span disabled class="caption" contenteditable="false"&gt;Dr. Zehava Alon&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="7qbk7" data-offset-key="5i9be-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="5i9be-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="5i9be-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;One of the most common misconceptions about influenza and other winter illnesses is whether they are caused by a virus or a bacterium — a distinction that is critical for treatment.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="7qbk7" data-offset-key="4md5g-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="4md5g-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="4md5g-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;“Not everyone understands the difference between a virus and a bacterium,” says Dr. Reiter. “Both can make us sick, but the key difference is practical: what medicine can do.” Bacterial infections can be treated with antibiotics, he explains, while viral illnesses cannot. “There are no drugs that kill viruses, so treatment for viral diseases is supportive and aimed at relieving symptoms. That is why people with fever or worsening symptoms should be examined, so we can determine whether the illness is viral or bacterial.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure data-block="true" data-editor="7qbk7" data-offset-key="fff2j-0-0" contenteditable="false"&gt;&lt;div class="ArticleImageComponenta wrapped"&gt;&lt;div class="ArticleWrappedImageComponenta"&gt;&lt;img id="ReduxEditableImage_ArticleWrappedImageData.SJgvtB0KXWx" src="https://ynet-pic1.yit.co.il/cdn-cgi/image/format=auto/picserver6/crop_images/2025/12/21/BkAr7crmWg/BkAr7crmWg_511_94_619_826_0_medium.jpg" alt='ד"ר אדם רייטר, רופא משפחה, מכבי' title="Dr. Adam Reiter (Photo: Ofer Hajayov) " aria-hidden="false"&gt;&lt;span disabled class="caption" contenteditable="false"&gt;Dr. Adam Reiter&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span disabled class="credit" contenteditable="false"&gt;Photo: Ofer Hajayov&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="7qbk7" data-offset-key="2svm5-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="2svm5-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="2svm5-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;The confusion often leads patients to expect antibiotics even when they have influenza. “Influenza does not respond to antibiotics. It is a viral disease,” says Dr. Alon. “Antibiotics are sometimes given only for complications, such as pneumonia — not to treat the flu itself, but to treat a secondary infection that develops when the immune system is weakened.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure data-block="true" data-editor="7qbk7" data-offset-key="1ejg5-0-0" contenteditable="false"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="7qbk7" data-offset-key="ed4i-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="ed4i-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="ed4i-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;Influenza does not affect everyone the same way. While many recover within days, others can deteriorate quickly and develop serious complications, including pneumonia, severe respiratory failure requiring ventilation and even death.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="7qbk7" data-offset-key="6s07i-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="6s07i-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="6s07i-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;“When someone has a viral illness, the immune system is already weakened, which allows bacterial infections to develop on top of it,” says Dr. Reiter. “If there is no improvement, it is important to seek medical evaluation.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="7qbk7" data-offset-key="b8g74-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="b8g74-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="b8g74-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;These warnings are especially relevant for high-risk groups — people whose immune systems may struggle to fight a viral infection. They include the very old and the very young, people with underlying medical conditions and those taking medications that suppress the immune system, for whom vaccination is particularly important. Dr. Alon adds that nearly everyone carries some level of risk, particularly people in close, ongoing contact with children, such as teachers and preschool staff.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure data-block="true" data-editor="7qbk7" data-offset-key="2lqqo-0-0" contenteditable="false"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="7qbk7" data-offset-key="9gg97-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="9gg97-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="9gg97-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;Treatment for influenza is not the same for everyone and depends largely on the severity of symptoms, a person’s overall health and whether the illness is mild and self-limiting or requires medical evaluation.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="7qbk7" data-offset-key="9q6n7-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="9q6n7-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="9q6n7-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;“It very much depends on the individual, their medical background, whether they are in a high-risk group, and how the illness presents,” says Dr. Reiter.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="7qbk7" data-offset-key="c0ke3-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="c0ke3-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="c0ke3-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;“There is a big difference between a bit of coughing and a sore throat and a significant illness with high fever and breathing difficulty. The individual situation determines whether testing is needed. If symptoms are mild and within a day, two or three there is improvement, there is no need to seek medical care. But if the illness is severe, with high fever and significant symptoms, a medical evaluation is necessary. We have to rule out worsening, a secondary bacterial infection or lung involvement from influenza.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="7qbk7" data-offset-key="1pelu-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="1pelu-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="1pelu-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;In recent years, home test kits sold at pharmacies have also become available, allowing for rapid diagnosis of influenza and in some cases combined testing for influenza and COVID-19. These kits can help in cases of mild symptoms and guide initial management at home.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="7qbk7" data-offset-key="5a4t1-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="5a4t1-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="5a4t1-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;“In general, we always recommend looking first at the child’s overall condition,” says Dr. Efrat Wechsler, head of primary care and a pediatrician at Meuhedet Health Services. “The first step is to bring the fever down. When the fever drops, the child usually recovers somewhat — plays, eats and drinks. If there is no shortness of breath, you can wait through the first 48 hours and see how things develop.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure data-block="true" data-editor="7qbk7" data-offset-key="5ndfr-0-0" contenteditable="false"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="7qbk7" data-offset-key="2cnij-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="2cnij-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="2cnij-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;If the fever lasts more than two days, especially if it is very high, as is typical of the current wave, or if other concerning signs appear, including decreased alertness, reduced eating or drinking, breathing difficulties, a troubling cough or unusual rashes — the child should be examined, she says. “These can be signs of a secondary infection or another condition that requires treatment. Of course, this is not treatment of the illness itself, but of possible complications. Some complications are rare but can be very dangerous, such as inflammation of the heart muscle.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="7qbk7" data-offset-key="2our4-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="2our4-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="2our4-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;Dr. Alon adds that with any illness, preventing further spread is essential. “It’s important not to go to work for two days while sick and then collapse, after having already infected everyone. People who are ill should stay home, wear a mask, drink plenty of fluids, eat appropriately and rest. Grandma used to say chicken soup — but above all, hydration, light food and rest are key.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="7qbk7" data-offset-key="63l74-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="63l74-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="63l74-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;Fever reducers can be used, she adds. “There is also a medication given in severe cases, called Tamiflu, but it is prescribed only in serious cases and only in hospitals.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="7qbk7" data-offset-key="6kank-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="6kank-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="6kank-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;Dr. Reiter stresses the importance of basic hygiene. “Wash hands, cough into your elbow and keep distance from people in high-risk groups, such as infants, older adults and those with weakened immune systems.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="7qbk7" data-offset-key="fjnm0-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="fjnm0-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="fjnm0-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;Alongside treating the illness itself, one of the main ways to reduce infection and complications is prevention — foremost through the influenza vaccine.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="7qbk7" data-offset-key="2rui1-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="2rui1-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="2rui1-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;“There are two types of flu vaccines,” says Dr. Reiter. “There is a live attenuated vaccine given as a nasal spray, and the familiar injected vaccine, which is inactivated. The live vaccine may cause very mild illness, but not significant disease, while the inactivated vaccine should not cause illness at all. Both are very similar in terms of effectiveness and the protection they provide.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure data-block="true" data-editor="7qbk7" data-offset-key="5vdo6-0-0" contenteditable="false"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="7qbk7" data-offset-key="76jvc-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="76jvc-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="76jvc-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;The vaccine, he says, is safe and recommended for all residents of Israel starting at 6 months of age and should be taken once a year ahead of the winter flu season. “This is especially important for people in high-risk groups. For them, vaccination can truly mean the difference between severe illness and hospitalization and a mild illness that passes easily.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="7qbk7" data-offset-key="2iv-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="2iv-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="2iv-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;“This year alone, more than 800,000 people have already been vaccinated through Clalit, and that is not enough,” adds Dr. Alon. “At most, the inactivated vaccine can cause muscle aches for a day. Beyond that, there are no side effects. It does not cause the flu or complications. People remember the COVID-19 vaccines, which were developed quickly due to an emergency, but this is not the same. This is a vaccine that has existed for decades — safe and without side effects. Personally, I have been getting vaccinated for more than 25 years. As soon as vaccines are available, I am first in line.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="7qbk7" data-offset-key="9n92e-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="9n92e-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="9n92e-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;She notes that the vaccine is available as a nasal spray for children and as an injection for the rest of the population, with a formulation for older adults and nursing home residents that contains additional virus strains.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Ynetnews</author><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 03:37:34 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiakFVX3lxTE1tcmptQldLWWp5Q0R5V0hzREZZWWFYc0RUM0N5Nm5DU29fTmVxcy1YLUtyOFRDQXJTY3NDSWh5REZSUl9WdE55WENwUkx1VUg2QzFRakE2VGJ0TVVGTERLcU1UdHZRMjZaREE</guid></item><item><title>骨科专家分享5种食物，以预防维生素D缺乏症，并在阳光不足的冬季保持骨骼健康|健康-印度斯坦时报</title><link>https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/orthopaedic-experts-share-5-foods-to-prevent-vitamin-d-deficiency-and-maintain-bone-health-during-sun-deprived-winters-101766582027818.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="detail " dataid="/lifestyle/health/orthopaedic-experts-share-5-foods-to-prevent-vitamin-d-deficiency-and-maintain-bone-health-during-sun-deprived-winters-101766582027818.html"&gt; &lt;div class="storyParagraphFigure"&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Reduced sunlight exposure during winters quietly pushes a large section of the population toward &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/can-vitamin-d-levels-affect-colon-cancer-risk-florida-gastroenterologist-explains-the-link-between-the-two-101765888189094.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="vitamin D"&gt;vitamin D &lt;/a&gt;deficiency. While the issue is often underestimated, its consequences are far-reaching - ranging from bone pain and muscle weakness to &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/5-ortho-experts-share-the-top-5-joint-issues-people-faced-in-2025-back-pain-knee-osteoarthritis-and-tech-neck-101765884132221.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="joint"&gt;joint &lt;/a&gt;stiffness and increased fracture risk. Medical experts warn that during winter months, diet becomes a critical tool to maintain adequate Vitamin D levels.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;figure class=""&gt; &lt;span class=""&gt; &lt;picture&gt; &lt;source media="(max-width:767px)" srcset="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/12/24/550x309/vitd_1766582537962_1766582550017.png" alt="Try out Dr Vaish and Dr Rathi's recommendations to optimise your vitamin D levels during winter!(Image generated via Google Gemini)" title="Try out Dr Vaish and Dr Rathi's recommendations to optimise your vitamin D levels during winter!(Image generated via Google Gemini)"&gt;&lt;/source&gt; &lt;img src="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/12/24/550x309/vitd_1766582537962_1766582550017.png" alt="Try out Dr Vaish and Dr Rathi's recommendations to optimise your vitamin D levels during winter!(Image generated via Google Gemini)" title="Try out Dr Vaish and Dr Rathi's recommendations to optimise your vitamin D levels during winter!(Image generated via Google Gemini)"&gt; &lt;/picture&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;figcaption&gt;Try out Dr Vaish and Dr Rathi's recommendations to optimise your vitamin D levels during winter!(Image generated via Google Gemini)&lt;/figcaption&gt; &lt;/figure&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;p id="readMoreFTUser"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Also Read | &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/fitness-trainer-warns-women-are-at-greater-risk-of-muscle-loss-in-winter-shares-4-tips-to-prevent-101766327891932.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="Fitness trainer reveals women are at greater risk of muscle loss in winter; shares 4 tips to prevent"&gt;Fitness trainer reveals women are at greater risk of muscle loss in winter; shares 4 tips to prevent&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="mt-10 mb-10 htEchoRecirculationWidget"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="mt10 mb10 htEchoArticlePromo"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="predictorShow mb20" data-vars-predictor="true" data-vars-quiz="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="quizShow mb20" data-vars-minimized="false" data-vars-predictor="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="highlight"&gt;HT Lifestyle reached out to two orthopaedic experts - Dr Abhishek Vaish, Orthopaedic, Joint Replacement and Sports Injury Specialist at Apollo Hospital, and Dr Akhilesh Rathi, Director of Robotics, Joint Replacement and Orthopaedics at Sri Balaji Action Medical Institute and founder of Rathi Orthopedic and Spine Clinic - to discuss wintertime vitamin D deficiency and the most effective ways to optimise levels through diet.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;&lt;span&gt;Vitamin D and winters&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;As daylight hours and sun exposure decline during winter, vitamin D levels in many people tend to drop as well. Dr Vaish highlights, “We routinely see patients complaining of unexplained &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/mumbai-orthopaedic-surgeon-explains-why-knee-pain-worsens-in-winter-shares-causes-symptoms-and-easy-tips-to-manage-it-101765811662475.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="knee pain"&gt;knee pain&lt;/a&gt;, backache, and muscle fatigue during winter. In many cases, the underlying cause turns out to be Vitamin D deficiency aggravated by lack of sun exposure.”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;He explains that vitamin D is essential for calcium absorption and bone mineralisation. When sunlight-driven synthesis drops, nutritional sources play a compensatory role - and a thoughtful winter diet can significantly help prevent deficiency.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;&lt;span&gt;Fatty fishes&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;According to Dr Vaish, salmon, mackerel, sardines and tuna are among the richest natural sources of vitamin D. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="highlight"&gt;He recommends including them regularly in your diet - at least two to three times a week - as this can help support bone density and muscle strength.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;He notes, “Vitamin D from fatty fish is highly bioavailable and supports joint health, particularly in individuals with early arthritis or age-related bone loss.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;&lt;span&gt;Egg yolks&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Dr Rathi emphasises that egg yolks are often the most overlooked source, but they provide a steady amount of vitamin D, along with essential fats. For non-vegetarians, eggs are an easy addition to winter meals.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;He explains, “Egg yolks are nutritionally dense and help improve vitamin D intake without major dietary changes. When consumed sensibly, they benefit immunity and musculoskeletal health.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;figure class="inlineIMG"&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;img data-src="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/12/24/original/photo-1699892726871-22e77ee1b75b_1766582217747.jpg" class="lazy" src="https://images.hindustantimes.com/default/550x309.jpg" alt="Egg yolks are a great source of vitamin D.(Unsplash)" title="Egg yolks are a great source of vitamin D.(Unsplash)"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;figcaption&gt;Egg yolks are a great source of vitamin D.(Unsplash)&lt;/figcaption&gt; &lt;/figure&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;span&gt;Fortified foods&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Fortified milk, yoghurt, cereals, and plant-based milk alternatives have emerged as practical vitamin D sources, especially for vegetarians. These foods are widely recommended during winter.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Dr. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="highlight"&gt;Rathi notes, “Fortified foods are extremely useful for people who spend most of their day indoors - office workers, students, and elderly individuals - who get minimal sun exposure.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;&lt;span&gt;UV-exposed and sun-dried mushrooms&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;According to Dr Rathi, certain mushrooms naturally produce vitamin D when exposed to ultraviolet light, making them another great source. Sun-dried mushrooms can be incorporated into curries, soups, and stir-fries.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;He explains, “This is one of the few plant-based natural Vitamin D options and works well for those avoiding animal products.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;&lt;span&gt;Cod liver oil and select dairy products&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Dr Vaish highlights that cod liver oil remains one of the most concentrated dietary sources of vitamin D. Cheese and butter contribute smaller amounts but can support daily intake when eaten as part of a balanced diet. He cautions, “While food helps maintain levels, individuals with deficiency may still require medical supplementation after proper testing.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;In a season when sunlight is limited, informed dietary planning and expert advice remain the most effective tools to safeguard long-term health. Both doctors stress that persistent bone pain, muscle cramps, fatigue, or frequent infections during winter should not be ignored. Dr Vaish concludes, “Timely screening, dietary correction, and guided supplementation can prevent long-term bone and joint complications.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="highlight"&gt;Adding to this, Dr Rathi emphasises a preventive approach, stating, “Vitamin D deficiency is not just a bone issue - it impacts immunity, energy levels, and overall well-being.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="highlight"&gt;Winter should be seen as a time to proactively support the body through nutrition, testing when required, and medical guidance rather than waiting for symptoms to appear.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Note to readers: This article is for informational purposes only and not a substitute for professional medical advice. Always seek the advice of your doctor with any questions about a medical condition.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Hindustan Times</author><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 01:31:23 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilgJBVV95cUxOaHU3OFFESTVFZloyaTJSX1BGeHh2Mk9uQU1QSEl5QWhab2lIWktpNHkySkVmTXozVDNNTWJFZkxSak9yQ3RQMTZxbHhOOEUtaGJOdjRTbllqcHhyNnZjU0xsYk5TemRBNnQ2aW9CbEpKODNoWWN2czRyNmtnNTgxTjM2aGJqdzN6ckd2X20wRHhrcEltYzlmZF9GajV1MVdHVWFrUmxONHJmaDJoNmc4M2VjQlZIQWNxbnpDRDVwblFNbWdGN0M0MHBOZU40elZvYXBWajRMc2dfQ29mMV90dGNhVWd5NlNqb0R6Y2p5aE9UMlR0bng2RE9LMk1heEZubk5KY2xlVDRrdUswN000ZmhKYmxIQdIBmwJBVV95cUxNTkFVNWoyNEFIeU5scG5uajRRdlJVZWFiR29JNXJhQ3BGRjJnNFQ5NUlqVFJuemlyRjNWOFg0aHZWa0tPZkxhZU4tQTBxalFZWWZQMUFBT2t4QlV0d3dIMmNqRVBmMmNxUTFkdzFlQjBuSnA0Um5Kc1VGMDBPRE00c0VpTE1UUGp4Nl85UVpKa2tUTU15cl9aSVdaemx1U3JHaUdha0hrWk5LR3FNV2pRSlhqTzVxY1ptcU1WVmM2ME11dURCcTR2NFVvTE03WDlnYm1xb2dKcEdWaTQ5SjJQdmVMRVNwVnE3c04xTkJKblJBRFhCaG9SOTdrRWY2Y1pxVm1kYnlDeGoxcldheDFZTmtxQUh3QUFWalhV</guid></item><item><title>Mark Damon -频道3000</title><link>https://www.channel3000.com/obituaries/mark-damon/article_9c04abc2-5bc3-4bd5-a09e-ce8f100abfdb.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="article-body" itemprop="articleBody" class="asset-content  subscriber-premium" false&gt;
                                &lt;meta itemprop="isAccessibleForFree" content="true"&gt;
                                
                                
                                &lt;p&gt;Mark James Damon, age 61, passed away on Tuesday, December 9, 2025, at his home in Madison, Wisconsin. Mark was born on November 26, 1964, grew up in Stoughton, and attended LaFollette High School in Madison, graduating in 1984. Mark was a dedicated State of Wisconsin employee for over 35 years, delivering mail and pharmaceutical supplies throughout Central Wisconsin Center with courtesy, humor, and a movie-star smile.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Living with cerebral palsy that affected his arms and legs, Mark mastered the operation of a series of motorized wheelchairs outfitted with chin and foot controls for ignition, gear-shifting, and steering, and he pushed these vehicles to their limits. He had a strong bent for mechanics, an eagle eye for detail, and an unflagging enthusiasm for creative problem-solving. Generations of occupational, vocational, and social work professionals owe a debt of gratitude to Mark for being willing to experiment with new devices and systems such as a foot-controlled computer mouse and door openers; mouth-held tools for use with keyboards and dial pads; and voice-activated appliances.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mark was also a skilled instructor, patiently training countless aides and attendants on the intricacies of his assistive technology, as well as food preparation, household maintenance, and daily care.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="tncms-region-article_instory_top" class="tncms-region hidden-print"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mark was always up for adventure, exploring new trails and seeing where they might lead. Some favorite spots included Camp Wawbeek in Wisconsin Dells, his sister Bev’s house in Tacoma, Washington, and the annual Mad City Model Railroad Show.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mark will be sorely missed: his kindness, intelligence, courage, humor, and friendship brought light and joy to the lives of many, many people. He was preceded in death by his loving foster parents, Ruth and Harry Kirby, and his dear friend Audrey. He leaves behind many foster brothers, sisters, nephews, and nieces; long-time friend and roommate Kevin Danz; and scores of other friends and colleagues.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="tncms-region-article_instory_middle" class="tncms-region hidden-print"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many thanks are owed to the staff at Lakeview Supported Living Services, Community Work Services, FA, Inc., My Choice Wisconsin, UW Health, Unity Point Health – Meriter Hospital, and St. Croix Hospice for the care and support they provided to Mark.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A memorial gathering for Mark will be held at Ryan Funeral Home, 2418 N. Sherman Drive, Madison, Wisconsin on Friday, January 9, from 4 to 6 p.m.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In lieu of flowers, donations in Mark’s memory may be made to one of Mark’s favorite organizations, Easterseals Wisconsin, to support Camp Wawbeek and Respite Camp, using their Online Giving Form | Easterseals Wisconsin or by mailing contributions to Easterseals Wisconsin at 1468 N. High Point Rd., Ste. 202, Middleton, WI 53562. To view his obituary and leave a memory, please visit: &lt;a href="https://www.ryanfuneralservice.com/" rel="noopener noreferrer nofollow" target="_blank"&gt;www.ryanfuneralservice.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;​COPYRIGHT 2025 BY CHANNEL 3000. ALL RIGHTS RESERVED. THIS MATERIAL MAY NOT BE PUBLISHED, BROADCAST, REWRITTEN OR REDISTRIBUTED.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="tncms-region-article_instory_bottom" class="tncms-region hidden-print"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
                                
                                
                            &lt;/div&gt;

                            

                            
    


                            
    


                            
                                &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Channel 3000</author><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 22:40:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMioAFBVV95cUxOZEdCREZxY2RsVk03VVZ1b25ydGM4NklaOFUtREJDQy1oYlpIakdGSkw1T2NmSVNSWTE5YlZOQm9JNTh4MnFyVnRfYzROWDk0OXJaQ3JkNXBNS1B6RjZtSkFndmNCc2ljMXdLVGlwc3N3Qk9NMk5YWHNENnRDRmJ4MlRKTlFMcG9GSUQyRXBaSFFKdzRWQTNpaGpfWWdSendl</guid></item><item><title>小鼠研究表明，挑鼻子与阿尔茨海默氏症有令人惊讶的联系- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/mouse-study-suggests-nose-picking-has-a-surprising-link-with-alzheimers</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;A study published in 2022 found a tenuous but plausible link between picking your nose and an increased risk of developing dementia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In cases where picking at your nose causes internal tissue damage, critical species of bacteria have a clearer path to the brain, which responds to their presence in ways that resemble signs of  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/go/IaO" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73015" data-postid="182682" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;Alzheimer's&lt;/a&gt; disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There are numerous caveats here, not the least of which is that the supporting research so far is in mice rather than humans, but the findings are definitely worth further investigation – and could improve our understanding of how Alzheimer's disease starts, which remains something of a mystery.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/a-simple-new-compound-reverses-alzheimers-symptoms-in-rats"&gt;Simple New Compound Reverses Alzheimer's Symptoms in Rats&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A team of researchers led by scientists from Griffith University in Australia ran tests with a bacterium called &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Chlamydia_pneumoniae"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Chlamydia pneumoniae&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, which can infect humans and cause  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/pneumonia" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73057" data-postid="182682" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;pneumonia&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;C. pneumoniae&lt;/em&gt; has &lt;a href="https://link.springer.com/article/10.1007/s004300050071"&gt;also been discovered&lt;/a&gt; in the majority of human brains affected by late-onset dementia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The video below has a summary of the study's findings:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was demonstrated that in mice, the bacteria could travel up the olfactory nerve (joining the nasal cavity and the brain).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What's more, when there was damage to the nasal epithelium (the thin tissue along the roof of the nasal cavity), nerve infections got worse.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This led to the mouse brains depositing more of the amyloid-beta protein – a protein that is released in response to infections.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Plaques (or clumps) of this protein are also found in significant concentrations in &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/study-shows-how-alzheimer-s-causes-cells-to-overheat-and-fry-like-eggs"&gt;people with Alzheimer's disease&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/newsletter?utm_source=promo_generic_health"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-642x273.jpg" alt="Subscribe to ScienceAlert's free fact-checked newsletter" class="alignnone wp-image-182810 size-medium" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-642x273.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-768x326.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-600x255.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final.jpg 850w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We're the first to show that &lt;em&gt;Chlamydia pneumoniae&lt;/em&gt; can go directly up the nose and into the brain where it can set off pathologies that look like Alzheimer's disease," &lt;a href="https://news.griffith.edu.au/2022/10/28/new-research-suggests-nose-picking-could-increase-risk-for-alzheimers-and-dementia/"&gt;said neuroscientist James St John&lt;/a&gt; from Griffith University in Australia, when the study was published in October 2022.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We saw this happen in a mouse model, and the evidence is potentially scary for humans as well."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The scientists were surprised by the speed at which &lt;em&gt;C. pneumoniae&lt;/em&gt; took hold in the central nervous system of the mice, with infection happening within 24 to 72 hours. It's thought that bacteria and  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/virus" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73053" data-postid="182682" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;viruses&lt;/a&gt; see the nose as a quick route to the brain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While it's not certain that the effects will be the same in humans, or even that &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/researchers-have-a-new-theory-about-what-causes-alzheimers-and-its-not-plaque"&gt;amyloid-beta plaques are a cause of Alzheimer's&lt;/a&gt;, it's nevertheless important to follow up promising leads in the fight to understand this common neurodegenerative condition.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_148468" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-148468" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/01/amyloid_plaques_642.jpg" alt="Mouse Study Suggests Surprising Link Between Alzheimer's And Nose-Picking" class="wp-image-148468 size-full" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/01/amyloid_plaques_642.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/01/amyloid_plaques_642-600x327.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-148468" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Illustration of amyloid-beta protein plaques, in orange. (&lt;a href="https://www.flickr.com/photos/nihgov/38686503251"&gt;NIH/Flickr/PD&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We need to do this study in humans and confirm whether the same pathway operates in the same way," &lt;a href="https://news.griffith.edu.au/2022/10/28/new-research-suggests-nose-picking-could-increase-risk-for-alzheimers-and-dementia/"&gt;said St John&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It's research that has been proposed by many people, but not yet completed. What we do know is that these same bacteria are present in humans, but we haven't worked out how they get there."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/nasal-spray-may-slow-alzheimers-disease-study-in-mice-suggests"&gt;Nasal Spray May Slow Alzheimer's Disease, Study in Mice Suggests&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nose picking isn't exactly a rare thing. In fact, it's possible &lt;a href="https://www.medicalnewstoday.com/articles/nose-picking"&gt;as many as 9 out of 10 people&lt;/a&gt; do it… not to mention a bunch of other species (&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/weve-caught-aye-aye-using-its-wacky-long-finger-for-something-pretty-gnarly"&gt;some a little more adept&lt;/a&gt; than others).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While the benefits aren't clear, studies like this one should give us pause before picking.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Future studies into the same processes in humans are planned – but until then, St John and his colleagues suggest that picking your nose and plucking your nose hair is "not a good idea" because of the potential damage it does to protective nose tissue.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We don't want to damage the inside of our nose and picking and plucking can do that," &lt;a href="https://news.griffith.edu.au/2022/10/28/new-research-suggests-nose-picking-could-increase-risk-for-alzheimers-and-dementia/"&gt;warned St John&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"If you damage the lining of the nose, you can increase how many bacteria can go up into your brain."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_148469" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-148469" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/01/child_picking_nose_642.jpg" alt="child picking their nose" class="wp-image-148469 size-full" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/01/child_picking_nose_642.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/01/child_picking_nose_642-600x327.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-148469" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Nose picking: not just a habit for small children. (&lt;a href="https://pixabay.com/photos/kid-fruit-nose-picking-picnic-6589472/"&gt;Jupi Lu/Pixabay&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;One outstanding question that the team will be looking to answer is whether or not the increased amyloid-beta protein deposits are a natural, healthy immune response that can be reversed when the infection is fought off.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/scientists-reveal-how-nose-picking-could-increase-risk-of-alzheimers"&gt;A 2024 review further advanced the hypothesis&lt;/a&gt; that nose picking could play a role in increasing the risk of developing Alzheimer's disease – revealing more about how the process could unfold.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/the-cause-of-alzheimers-may-be-coming-from-within-your-mouth"&gt;The Cause of Alzheimer's May Be Coming From Within Your Mouth&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alzheimer's is an incredibly complicated disease, as is clear from the &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/alzheimers-might-not-actually-be-a-brain-disease-expert-says"&gt;sheer number of studies&lt;/a&gt; into it and the &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/scientists-have-identified-four-distinct-types-of-alzheimer-s"&gt;many different angles&lt;/a&gt; scientists are taking in trying to understand it – but each piece of research brings us a little bit closer to finding a way to stop it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Once you get over 65 years old, your risk factor goes right up, but we're looking at other causes as well, because it's not just age – it is environmental exposure as well," &lt;a href="https://news.griffith.edu.au/2022/10/28/new-research-suggests-nose-picking-could-increase-risk-for-alzheimers-and-dementia/"&gt;said St John&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"And we think that bacteria and viruses are critical."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The research was published in &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41598-022-06749-9"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Scientific Reports&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;An earlier version of this article was published in November 2022.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 22:22:05 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiogFBVV95cUxQMy02dnBUVmVOWWhrcWp5cWpTanpiNVJoaDJ6aVp0SFBnY0lpSGxvSklNSW1oTzd0eDRQZXlpYnZPXzZIalZydXR6aUJNU2hvWWxobGpLUVdhdkYyU0Y4Tks1dG12MU5NR1BkQWYzZ2VkbmxqZkthbWMwWFo2NmQ4emp2eXFySk1rRm81YVliVVh1VXUza0Z1QzRPN3ZOcUpsTUE</guid></item><item><title>艰难的爱：我是否与我的反Vax兄弟断绝了联系？ -新闻自由</title><link>https://www.thefp.com/p/tough-love-do-i-sever-ties-with-my</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div dir="auto" class="body markup"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;Welcome back to Tough Love with Abigail Shrier, the new advice column from The Free Press! Every Thursday, our contributing editor will address your conundrums, with no hesitation and no sugarcoating—just straight-up Tough Love. This week, Abigail answers a question from Julia (that’s not her real name), who’s considering severing ties with her brother because he won’t vaccinate his kids. To receive Tough Love directly in your inbox, every week, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.thefp.com/s/tough-love-with-abigail-shrier" rel&gt;sign up here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Dear Abigail,&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;I’m struggling with a painful family dilemma and I don’t know what’s left to try. My brother and his wife refuse to vaccinate their children—unless they’re forced to, like when their kids were kicked out of school for being unvaccinated, specifically for not having the measles, mumps, and rubella (MMR) jab. We’ve tried to be nonjudgmental in our questions and suggested compromises on ways we can interact, but every conversation feels like we’re speaking different languages.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This is part of a broader pattern of unsafe choices that make it hard to spend time together. My brother and his wife have driven more than once on the highway without putting their infant in a car seat because “he cries too much.” They also brought their kids, who had fevers, to our 100-year-old grandfather’s birthday party. Moments like these leave me feeling anxious, angry, and unsure whether I can trust them around my own family (I have three young children).&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;I love my brother, and I’ve always believed family should matter. But the disconnect in our values and basic safety standards feels enormous, and I’m starting to wonder if the healthiest choice is to step back. We don’t have a cool uncle willing to intervene; otherwise, I would go that route. So what do I do? Do I sever ties? Should I keep trying to reconcile or is it okay to accept that not all relationships can be fixed?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;How do I navigate the guilt, the love, and the need to protect my own family?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Julia&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Julia,&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The first time I lost my little brother, he was 4. We were in our local Lord &amp;amp; Taylor, where he’d crept inside a fountain of racked clothing and ducked down so I wouldn’t see him. I tore through the racks, crying his name, until I found him smiling, thinking he had won this round of hide-and-seek.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Free Press</author><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 21:43:42 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiakFVX3lxTE5xbWQ2a3R1ZGNjUzNwaFpRcWVXRDMzZkwzNFBhVFRsNzJGaEtyMFQteVBJb0prZzgzdVZkS0R0R3hkNndCaTVwODU5aHNFaVdJNkE4LUw1UWVKakFvdlplQ2xEd0MyVE9iSUE</guid></item><item><title>波士顿、威斯特伯勒可能有麻疹暴露，官员警告-《波士顿环球报》</title><link>https://www.bostonglobe.com/2025/12/24/metro/massachusetts-measles-alert/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="body | gutter_16--desktop gutter_16--tablet paywalled_content
              "&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;The Massachusetts Department of Public Health is working with the US Centers for Disease Control and Prevention and local partners to identify and notify those who may have been exposed, officials said. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;“Measles is a highly contagious, airborne disease, which has increased significantly in the United States because of the unfortunate decrease in vaccination rates. It is also a preventable disease,” Public Health Commissioner Dr. Robbie Goldstein said in a statement. “This current situation serves as an important reminder of the critical role vaccination plays in protecting our communities.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;While Massachusetts has not had a measles case this year, the United States has seen the highest number of nationwide cases in more than a decade – nearly 2,000 in 44 jurisdictions, which included three confirmed deaths from measles, Goldstein said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;“Fifteen years ago, measles had been considered eliminated in the United States, but that tremendous progress is at risk,” Goldstein said. “Vaccines are one of the most important public health interventions ever – they are safe, effective, and lifesaving.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Officials said the exposures may have occurred at Logan Airport Terminal B on Dec. 11 from 2:30 p.m. to 4:45 p.m.; at the DoubleTree hotel in Westborough from 3:30 p.m. on Dec. 11 to 9 p.m. on Dec. 12; and at Logan Airport Terminal C from 6 p.m. to 11:30 p.m. on Dec. 12.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;“Those who could have been exposed and begin to develop symptoms of measles should call their healthcare provider before visiting an office, clinic, or emergency department,” public health officials said in the statement. “Visiting a healthcare facility may put others at risk and should be avoided if possible.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Those who have had measles in the past or have received two doses of the Measles, Mumps, and Rubella (MMR) vaccine are unlikely to develop measles even if they were exposed, officials said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Boston Public Health Commissioner Dr. Bisola Ojikutu also encouraged people to get vaccinated for measles.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;“With multiple measles outbreaks across the country and increased travel around the holidays, now is an important time to ensure that you and your family are protected,” she said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Ojikutu said two doses of MMR vaccine are 97 percent effective at preventing measles and provide protection against mumps and rubella. Children should receive the vaccine at 12-15 months of age and again before kindergarten, she said. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Children who are at least 6 months old and traveling internationally or to areas of the US with active outbreaks should receive an early dose of vaccine before traveling, Ojikutu said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;“It is never too late for children or adults to get the measles vaccine even if they are past the recommended age,” Ojikutu said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Early symptoms of measles occur one to three weeks after exposure and may resemble a cold, with symptoms fever, cough, runny nose, and red eyes. A rash occurs on the skin two to four days after the initial symptoms develop and usually appears first on the head, officials said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;People with measles may be contagious up to four days before the rash appears and for four days after the rash starts, officials said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;State public health officials are urging anyone who has not been vaccinated or doesn’t know their measles immunization status to contact their healthcare provider to get vaccinated with at least one dose of the MMR vaccine. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;“Measles vaccine given within 72 hours of exposure may prevent measles disease,” officials said in the statement. “Vaccination beyond this window will provide protection from subsequent exposures.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr class="tagline_hr | border_foreground border_half gutter_20_28--mobile
               margin_none text_align_left width_100px"&gt;&lt;p class="tagline | font_primary inline_block  margin_top_32"&gt;Emily Sweeney can be reached at &lt;a href="mailto:emily.sweeney@globe.com" class="" target="_blank"&gt;emily.sweeney@globe.com&lt;/a&gt;. Follow her &lt;a href="https://www.twitter.com/emilysweeney" class="" target="_blank"&gt;@emilysweeney&lt;/a&gt; and on Instagram &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/emilysweeney22" class="" target="_blank"&gt;@emilysweeney22&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Boston Globe</author><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 19:48:59 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMifkFVX3lxTE1OeVREUmk0Rl94TFdHYUFmSEJvazZtQUp6Rm5Rc1NZU2ZmUHFTMlUwcm1PWWQtX3NNS041TEpzR3dUQktKazZYMlgwT21tUnhsNlR5V21pdDVJTzk0NTJIV2hwSGw1dkxpZV9Fa2cxREotdFB5ZWhaam1SdFYzQQ</guid></item><item><title>心脑连接：国际研究揭示迷走神经在保持心脏年轻方面的作用- Medical Xpress</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-12-heart-brain-international-reveals-role.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="success-screen" id="successScreen"&gt;
            &lt;p class="success-icon"&gt;✓&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;h2 class="success-title"&gt;Verification Complete&lt;/h2&gt;
            &lt;p class="success-subtext"&gt;This page will redirect in a moment...&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Medical Xpress</author><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 19:48:33 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiigFBVV95cUxNUW11ejRfd1hkeG1sNUM0SFJDV0l4eE1iMTU2bjZJRWZmR2tsZS1QZTlKaHQwU2FYSWpjcU5VZ0FVVWM0OTVydkFsNVFFVHdxSl9YMVlnN002NTBKdGE3a3ZNU3lKTmdsclMwRnN1MXJrb2RsY0l6T0t5eFhWWUo0Z01WeGNHV3NDSVE</guid></item><item><title>科学家意外地在实验室中创造了一种新材料，从而发现黄金是一种“反应性金属” - Earth.com</title><link>https://www.earth.com/news/discovery-that-gold-is-reactive-metal-by-creating-gold-hydride-in-lab-experiment/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="page_content__AwOj6"&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a high-pressure lab experiment, scientists accidentally created a new compound called gold hydride. This particular hydride formed when thin gold foil met dense hydrogen at pressures hundreds of thousands of times Earth’s atmosphere and blazing temperatures.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The discovery challenges gold’s reputation as a nearly inert metal and shows how extreme conditions can push familiar materials into unfamiliar forms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;By creating &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/hunan-geologists-discover-a-deposit-of-more-than-1000-tons-of-gold/"&gt;gold&lt;/a&gt; hydride in the lab, researchers opened a way to study dense hydrogen like that inside giant planets and fusing stars.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-creating-gold-hydride"&gt;Creating gold hydride&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The work was led by Mungo Frost, a staff scientist at Stanford Linear Accelerator Center (&lt;a href="https://www6.slac.stanford.edu/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;SLAC&lt;/a&gt;) whose research probes materials under extreme pressures and temperatures.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gold is usually chosen for experiments like this because it barely reacts, serving as a passive X ray absorber that heats surrounding material.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gold was expected to remain inert during the experiment, since it is normally chemically unreactive and is routinely used as an X-ray absorber for that reason.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That accidental reaction produced the first confirmed solid compound made solely of gold and hydrogen atoms in any laboratory experiment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-lab-built-to-study-diamonds"&gt;Lab built to study diamonds&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The experiment was originally designed to clock how long simple hydrocarbons take to turn into diamond under crushing pressure and searing heat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Researchers squeezed tiny drops of hydrocarbon between the tips of a diamond anvil cell, a device that traps samples at immense static pressures.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Laser heating inside such cells lets scientists study materials at extreme pressures, as shown in a recent &lt;a href="https://www.mdpi.com/2504-4494/6/5/111" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;review&lt;/a&gt; of diamond anvil work.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At the &lt;a href="https://www.xfel.eu/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;European XFEL&lt;/a&gt; in Germany, X-ray pulses hit a thin &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/metal-detectorist-finds-the-oldest-celtic-gold-coin-ever-recorded/"&gt;gold&lt;/a&gt; foil in the sample, which then heated the surrounding hydrocarbons.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The team cranked the pressure until it rivaled Earth’s lower mantle, then blasted the sample with trains of X-ray pulses.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Under those conditions, the study reports gold hydride forming at temperatures above 3,500 degrees Fahrenheit and at pressures far beyond &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/geologists-found-gigantic-fortresses-deep-beneath-the-earths-crust-in-the-mantle/"&gt;Earth’s mantle&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;X-ray scattering patterns confirmed that carbon atoms snapped into the tidy &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/doped-diamonds-discovery-may-reshape-quantum-computing/"&gt;lattice of diamond&lt;/a&gt;, matching what the researchers expected from earlier work.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Signals in the data revealed hydrogen atoms entering the gold lattice, forming gold hydride that altered how the metal scattered X-rays.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-gold-hydride-and-planet-formation"&gt;Gold hydride and planet formation&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Under pressure and heat, hydrogen became superionic, a state where atoms move like a liquid inside a solid, making the gold hydride conductive.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hydrogen usually barely scatters X-rays, so the team watched changes in the &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/man-with-a-cheap-metal-detector-finds-a-huge-piece-of-gold/"&gt;gold&lt;/a&gt; lattice to deduce how the light atoms were moving.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Simulations and measurements indicate that hydrogen diffuses rapidly through the hexagonal gold lattice at high temperature but separates when the sample cools.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Interior &lt;a href="https://agupubs.onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/full/10.1002/2016JE005080" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;models&lt;/a&gt; of Jupiter suggest a shell of metallic hydrogen surrounding a dense core, with pressures beyond anything on Earth’s surface.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In those environments, hydrogen is compressed so tightly that it behaves more like a dense, electrically conducting fluid than a simple gas.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Recent &lt;a href="https://link.aps.org/doi/10.1103/PhysRevLett.128.035702" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;research&lt;/a&gt; has shown that superionic states in silica water and silica hydrogen mixtures could help explain magnetic fields in giant planets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gold hydride offers a controlled environment where dense hydrogen’s structure and motion can be measured, giving theorists a clearer target for planetary calculations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-new-lens-on-fusion-research"&gt;New lens on fusion research&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stars like the Sun shine because gravity squeezes hydrogen until nuclei fuse, and fusion researchers try to recreate conditions in experiments on Earth.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Accurate models of dense hydrogen, hydrogen compressed to extraordinary pressures and densities, are vital for understanding fusion fuel behavior.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Simulations indicate that even small uncertainties in hydrogen’s behavior at high-density can significantly change fusion predictions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;By pinning how hydrogen moves through gold at given pressures and temperatures, the measurements give fusion modelers a benchmark to test their calculations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In everyday chemistry, gold is grouped with the noble metals that rarely form compounds, which is why jewelry stays bright for decades.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In these experiments, &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/scientists-discover-how-gold-reaches-earths-surface-from-the-mantle/"&gt;gold&lt;/a&gt; formed a hydride that held more hydrogen as pressure climbed, yet separated into plain gold again when conditions eased.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The findings indicate that extreme pressure and heat can enable forms of chemistry that do not occur under normal conditions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;High pressure work has shown unreactive elements like xenon can form compounds, so gold hydride underscores how chemistry changes when matter is squeezed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-high-tech-machines"&gt;High tech machines&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The experiments relied on the European XFEL, a powerful X-ray laser facility that delivers thousands of pulses each second to targets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Those pulses deposit energy in the gold foil, allowing scientists to heat the sample rapidly while the diamond-anvil cell maintains the pressure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;High-energy-density science, the study of matter under extreme pressures and temperatures, uses intense X-ray lasers together with diamond anvil cells.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As these tools improve, from tougher diamond anvils to brighter X-ray sources, researchers can probe states of matter once considered purely theoretical.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-gold-hydrides-and-other-exotic-phases"&gt;Gold hydrides and other exotic phases&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/proposed-highway-route-went-through-a-lost-celtic-town-full-of-gold-silver-and-amber/"&gt;Gold&lt;/a&gt; hydride joins a catalog of exotic phases, including superionic water and silica compounds, that appear only when atoms are squeezed and heated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many of these phases vanish once pressure or temperature drops, yet their existence helps explain how planets move heat and generate magnetic fields.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Because hydrides of other metals already show properties like superconductivity, understanding gold hydride could one day help design new electronic materials.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gold hydride’s appearance under stress shows that even familiar elements in lab samples can behave unexpectedly when scientists push conditions beyond normal experience.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-lessons-from-gold-hydride"&gt;Lessons from gold hydride&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The simulation framework that captured superionic hydrogen in &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/metal-detectorist-finds-the-oldest-celtic-gold-coin-ever-recorded/"&gt;gold&lt;/a&gt; can predict how other elements behave when infused with hydrogen at different pressures and temperatures.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Future experiments can swap gold for other metals or mixtures that resemble planetary materials more closely, letting researchers test whether strange hydrides emerge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Each compound uncovered at such extremes expands the periodic table of high-pressure phases and clarifies how ordinary elements behave when pushed hard.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study is published in the &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40755070/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;&lt;em&gt;National Library of Medicine&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;—–&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Like what you read? &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/subscribe/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Subscribe to our newsletter&lt;/a&gt; for engaging articles, exclusive content, and the latest updates.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Check us out on &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/earthsnap/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;EarthSnap&lt;/a&gt;, a free app brought to you by &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/author/eralls/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Eric Ralls&lt;/a&gt; and Earth.com.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;—–&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Earth.com</author><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 18:33:16 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMirAFBVV95cUxQSUJBc0pWVTR1WmF6TDdDcnlGRjU0eFppYW8ya1drQlRsRUduQVRhaERrTWYxaVotT0k1MmpVYkdoMFJpSThaRkcwYW00VmFXN1R1bG5iSzJUOUZPa21RejFGSTdYQnlXNWNoYTNmeTQ3Vm5VN0poaE13V0RQOG5jcnRzUHBsb2FGakxGY2pOQ3pSTGRxLXJEcVFTczcxZlNOWnk5SmlVeWh2QUxv</guid></item><item><title>复活的组织：在广泛损伤后实现再生的机制解决了一个有50年历史的谜团- Phys.org</title><link>https://phys.org/news/2025-12-resurrected-tissue-mechanism-enables-regeneration.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="success-screen" id="successScreen"&gt;
            &lt;p class="success-icon"&gt;✓&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;h2 class="success-title"&gt;Verification Complete&lt;/h2&gt;
            &lt;p class="success-subtext"&gt;This page will redirect in a moment...&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Phys.org</author><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 18:30:02 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijAFBVV95cUxNUkpNS2xPVjZYVTVxWlVhdnJXMEQ3c3hvTkVNdWV3Zmwyamcya0d1OVlTdE5sNGZGc2RfUzd5Q3NJQ1FKQWo3RUJ3Q29xZkxLTzdsR2NHQzZ4VFFuNTB1cWlGOTNkWnNQVmRrR0ZiMFRuSlc4OFhYZjRTRG43clN2ZExiQ0tiaHl2dksxeA</guid></item><item><title>常见ADHD药物的功能与科学家此前认为的不同- PsyPost</title><link>https://www.psypost.org/common-adhd-medications-function-differently-than-scientists-previously-thought/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="content-inner "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Prescription stimulants are among the most widely used psychiatric medications in the world. For decades, the prevailing medical consensus held that drugs like methylphenidate treat attention deficit hyperactivity disorder by targeting the brain’s executive control centers. A new study challenges this long-held dogma, revealing that these medications act primarily on neural networks responsible for wakefulness and reward rather than attention. The study was published in the journal &lt;a href="https://www.cell.com/cell/fulltext/S0092-8674(25)01373-X"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Cell&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Medical textbooks have traditionally taught that stimulants function by enhancing activity in the prefrontal cortex. This region of the brain is often associated with voluntary control, planning, and the direction of focus. The assumption was that by boosting activity in these circuits, the drugs allowed patients to filter out distractions and maintain concentration on specific tasks. However, the precise neural mechanisms have remained a subject of debate among neuroscientists.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Earlier research into these medications often produced inconsistent results. Some studies suggested that stimulants improved motivation and reaction times rather than higher-level reasoning. Furthermore, behavioral experiments have shown that the drugs do not universally improve performance. They tend to help individuals who are performing poorly but offer little benefit to those who are already performing well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To resolve these discrepancies, a research team led by neurologist Benjamin P. Kay at Washington University School of Medicine in St. Louis undertook a massive analysis of brain activity. Working with senior author Nico U.F. Dosenbach, Kay aimed to map the effects of stimulants across the entire brain without restricting their focus to pre-determined areas. They sought to understand which specific brain networks were most altered when a child took these medications.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers utilized data from the Adolescent Brain Cognitive Development Study. This large-scale project tracks the biological and psychological development of thousands of children across the United States. The team selected functional magnetic resonance imaging scans from 5,795 children between the ages of eight and eleven.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kay and his colleagues compared the brain scans of children who had taken prescription stimulants on the day of their MRI against those who had not. They employed a technique known as resting-state functional connectivity. This method measures how different regions of the brain communicate and synchronize with one another when the person is not performing a specific task.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The analysis did not rely on small, isolated samples. The researchers used a data-driven approach to look at the whole connectome, which is the complete map of neural connections in the brain. They controlled for various factors that could skew the results, such as head motion during the scan and socioeconomic status.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The findings contradicted the traditional “attention-centric” view of stimulant medication. The researchers observed no statistical difference in the functional connectivity of the dorsal or ventral attention networks. The drugs also did not produce measurable changes in the frontoparietal control network, which is usually linked to complex problem-solving.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Instead, the most substantial changes occurred in the sensorimotor cortex and the salience network. The sensorimotor cortex is traditionally associated with physical movement and sensation. However, recent discoveries suggest this area also plays a major role in regulating the body’s overall arousal and wakefulness levels.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The salience network is responsible for determining what is important in the environment. It helps the brain calculate the value of a task and decides whether an action is worth the effort. The study found that stimulants increased connectivity between these reward-processing regions and the motor systems.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This shift in connectivity suggests that the drugs work by altering the brain’s calculation of effort and reward. By boosting activity in the salience network, the medication makes tedious activities feel more rewarding than they otherwise would. This reduces the urge to switch tasks or seek stimulation elsewhere.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Essentially, we found that stimulants pre-reward our brains and allow us to keep working at things that wouldn’t normally hold our interest — like our least favorite class in school, for example,” Dosenbach said. This explains the paradox of why a stimulant can help a hyperactive child sit still. The drug removes the biological drive to fidget by satisfying the brain’s need for reward.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To verify that these findings were not an artifact of the pediatric data, the team conducted a separate validation study. They recruited five healthy adults who did not have attention deficits. These volunteers underwent repeated brain scans before and after taking a controlled dose of methylphenidate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The results from the adult trial mirrored the findings in the children. The medication consistently altered the arousal and reward networks while leaving the attention networks largely unchanged. This replication in a controlled setting provides strong evidence that the drugs act on basic physiological drivers of behavior.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study also uncovered a distinct relationship between stimulant medication and sleep. The researchers compared the brain patterns of medicated children to those of children who reported getting a full night of sleep. The functional connectivity signatures were remarkably similar.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stimulants appeared to mimic the neurological effects of being well-rested. Children who were sleep-deprived showed specific disruptions in their sensorimotor and arousal networks. When sleep-deprived children took a stimulant, those disruptions disappeared.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This “rescue” effect extended to cognitive performance as well. The researchers analyzed school grades and test scores for the children in the study. As expected, children with attention deficits performed better when taking medication. However, the data revealed a nuance regarding sleep.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stimulants improved the grades and test scores of children who did not get enough sleep. In fact, the medication raised the performance of sleep-deprived children to the level of their well-rested peers. Conversely, for children who did not have attention deficits and already got sufficient sleep, the drugs provided no statistical benefit to performance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“We saw that if a participant didn’t sleep enough, but they took a stimulant, the brain signature of insufficient sleep was erased, as were the associated behavioral and cognitive decrements,” Dosenbach noted. The medication effectively masked the neural and behavioral symptoms of fatigue.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This finding raises important questions about the use of stimulants as performance enhancers. The data suggests that the drugs do not make a well-rested brain smarter or more attentive. They simply counteract the drag of fatigue and lack of motivation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The authors of the study advise caution regarding this sleep-masking effect. While the drugs can hide the immediate signs of sleep deprivation, they do not replace the biological necessity of sleep. Chronic sleep loss is linked to cellular stress, metabolic issues, and other long-term health consequences that stimulants cannot fix.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kay highlighted the clinical implications of these findings for doctors and parents. Symptoms of sleep deprivation often mimic the symptoms of attention deficit hyperactivity disorder, including lack of focus and irritability. Treating a sleep-deprived child with stimulants might mask the root cause of their struggles.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Not getting enough sleep is always bad for you, and it’s especially bad for kids,” Kay said. He suggested that clinicians should screen for sleep disturbances before prescribing these medications. It is possible that some children diagnosed with attention deficits are actually suffering from chronic exhaustion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study also provides a new framework for understanding the brain’s motor cortex. The researchers noted that the changes in the motor system align with the recently discovered Somato-Cognitive Action Network. This network integrates body control with planning and arousal, further cementing the link between movement and alertness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Future research will need to investigate the long-term effects of using stimulants to override sleep signals. The current study looked at a snapshot in time, but the cumulative impact of masking fatigue over years remains unknown. The researchers also hope to explore whether these arousal mechanisms differ in various subtypes of attention disorders.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;By shifting the focus from attention to arousal and reward, this research fundamentally alters the understanding of how psychostimulants function. It suggests that these drugs are not “smart pills” that boost intelligence. Instead, they are endurance tools that help the brain maintain effort and wakefulness in the face of boredom or fatigue.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study, “&lt;a href="https://www.cell.com/cell/fulltext/S0092-8674(25)01373-X"&gt;Stimulant medications affect arousal and reward, not attention&lt;/a&gt;,” was authored by Benjamin P. Kay, Muriah D. Wheelock, Joshua S. Siegel, Ryan Raut, Roselyne J. Chauvin, Athanasia Metoki, Aishwarya Rajesh, Andrew Eck, Jim Pollaro, Anxu Wang, Vahdeta Suljic, Babatunde Adeyemo, Noah J. Baden, Kristen M. Scheidter, Julia Monk, Nadeshka Ramirez-Perez, Samuel R. Krimmel, Russel T. Shinohara, Brenden Tervo-Clemmens, Robert J. M. Hermosillo, Steven M. Nelson, Timothy J. Hendrickson, Thomas Madison, Lucille A. Moore, Óscar Miranda-Domínguez, Anita Randolph, Eric Feczko, Jarod L. Roland, Ginger E. Nicol, Timothy O. Laumann, Scott Marek, Evan M. Gordon, Marcus E. Raichle, Deanna M. Barch, Damien A. Fair, and Nico U.F. Dosenbach.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>PsyPost</author><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 17:36:51 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipwFBVV95cUxPZ1R2R1llaDlFNXQwT01hdmxjWlpqLURNV1JvTVF5V0dLYXIzZUtaYVhMUVVacGhqVGQzaExBUjZ6NS1BX0syYUhBbjA4cGlZZm1DOVRCQjJrdWU1amgyV1ZIdVJEUVZfWnM2V1FnNzdRZERfY1MxUkRpT2diczI4ajBOcmp2aTdaQTM4M1UwaGlZcHV6cVgtaVZsYWkwXzFNOC1MUDE3Yw</guid></item><item><title>性建议：自从我们有了孩子，我妻子就说有一部分性行为是禁止的。这没有道理。-石板</title><link>https://slate.com/advice/2025/12/sex-advice-baby-wife-off-limits.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article__content" itemprop="mainEntityOfPage"&gt;
          &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="18" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjhh3ynj0012j6m2jups7zvm@published"&gt;&lt;em&gt;How to Do It is Slate’s sex advice column. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Have a question? &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLSdx34-uOijrCIKqMdw5hnyYahSJBKa4AaSzDCu1nfcpmd3IjA/viewform"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Send it to Stoya and Rich here.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt; It’s anonymous!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="5" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjhh5jte00143b79nl3xmywh@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dear How to Do It,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

    


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="39" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjhh5esz000o3b79ovij47bn@published"&gt;My wife and I used to attend sex parties all the time. Ever since she got pregnant, that came to a halt. Our son is now nearly a year old, and I’m really eager to return to the scene.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="59" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjhm50pl003q3b797fkwyevp@published"&gt;However, she says that because we have a kid now, that chapter of our lives needs to remain closed. It’s not like we would be hosting parties at our place, and the fact that we have a kid seems neither here nor there in terms of going back to what we were doing. How can I ease her hang-ups?&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="4" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjhh5evg000p3b799n7ygoke@published"&gt;—Ready to Party On&lt;/p&gt;

  

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="5" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjhh5ey7000q3b792kppr3a4@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dear Ready to Party On,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="99" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjhh5f0r000r3b79ijey3535@published"&gt;Regardless of the fact that you’ll likely creep into coercion territory, convincing a person to have sex they aren’t comfortable with is a recipe for destroying your relationship. You don’t ease your wife’s hang-ups. You respect her current boundaries. Where you’re saying your son is nearly a year old, I’m seeing a woman who is not even a year out from giving birth for the first time. Your wife’s position might change again if you can exercise patience. If you push the subject, though, you’re likely to create distance, resentment, and a rigid and eternal “no” on this practice.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="160" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjhh5f3b000s3b7911mq45mp@published"&gt;It feels telling that you omit any mention of what your wife’s reasons are for her decision. OK, yes, because the two of you have a child, but is this about fear of STIs? Does the fact of motherhood mean a change in the boundaries of what she considers acceptable conduct? Has something about the physical and hormonal process of pregnancy changed her relationship to her body or her desires? Is it that time with your infant, or protecting precious sleep, is a higher priority, and sex parties interfere with that? It doesn’t seem like you have this information, and it does seem like you’ve assumed one (probably not the actual case) reason and immediately dismissed it. If you do want to understand your wife’s reasoning, ask her with genuine curiosity. Those answers are likely to help you come to terms with this particular manifestation of the fact that your lives are profoundly different now, because they need to be.&lt;/p&gt;

  


  


  


  


  
  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="109" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjhh5f71000t3b792o5njz2e@published"&gt;It also might help to understand what you’re missing about these parties. What are the emotional needs that were being met? Excitement? Novelty? Attention? Can you come up with potential ways to satisfy those desires while staying within your wife’s boundaries? This can be a second conversation. If you’re able to really hear your wife, and she’s able to feel that you’re hearing her, there will probably be at least some room for compromise and negotiation. This has to be collaborative, though, and you’ll be wise to proceed cautiously, gently, and with grace extended regarding how she may be reacting to the massive life experience she’s just been through.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="1" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjhhdmad001f3b79sd9hiwbs@published"&gt;&lt;span class="slate-paragraph--tombstone"&gt;—Jessica&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;h3 class="subhead subhead--none" data-uri="slate.com/_components/subhead/instances/cmjhhdri100213b79v620jyzs@published"&gt;
&lt;p class="subhead__marker"&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
More Advice From Slate

&lt;/h3&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="69" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjhhdohb001q3b794pdcv7ox@published"&gt;Recently, my long-term boyfriend got me a new dildo. It’s pale green, fairly large, and has stylized eyes painted onto it. I thought it looked freaky, but he thought it was funny and it went to live on the rack with most of our other sex toys near the bed. It’s never actually been used for any sexual activity, &lt;a href="https://slate.com/human-interest/2022/04/haunted-dildo-sex-advice.html"&gt;but I thought I’d try it under the right circumstances…&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;section class="newsletter-signup   " data-list="Advice" data-uri="slate.com/_components/newsletter-signup/instances/cmjhh3ynj0015j6m2efdcih95@published"&gt;


    &lt;p class="newsletter-signup__intro"&gt;
        &lt;svg class="newsletter-signup__arrow"&gt;
          &lt;use xlink:href="/media/components/newsletter-signup/sprite.svg#arrow"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;
        &lt;/svg&gt;
&lt;h1 class="newsletter-signup__headline"&gt;Never miss new Slate Advice columns&lt;/h1&gt;
      &lt;span class="newsletter-signup__description"&gt;Get the latest from Prudie and our columnists in your inbox each weekday, plus special bonus letters on Saturdays.&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;
    



&lt;/section&gt;

  

&lt;/div&gt;

      &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Slate</author><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMieEFVX3lxTE9oTjNXVGZPVzZCRnF1VlIzaXB3MGUycVE3Y1duMmRreHd5alp1MVYtcktjUUVKVmVWRFR0clY2QW5WeG1mVDFEZ0lhRUtwZHZYbU1pMTBaTzlkaGx5QTBlc1hiZnF4UDRXQTlndllKQXg4SUIxWmFQZg</guid></item><item><title>“这完全失控” ：科学家警告禽流感可能在2026年引发人类大流行-英国广播公司科学焦点杂志</title><link>https://www.sciencefocus.com/news/bird-flu-2026-analysis</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div _ngcontent-pxp-c1839238051 class="purple-inner-container purple-content-body-inner"&gt;&lt;p&gt;When a highly pathogenic strain of bird flu strain of avian influenza (H5N1) began sweeping across wild birds and poultry in 2020, it already looked concerning. Five years on, the picture has grown darker and stranger than most would have imagined. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The virus has infected hundreds of millions of farm animals, spilled into mammals at an unprecedented scale, devastated wildlife, and – in the United States – established itself in dairy cattle, a species no one expected to see implicated.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Human cases remain rare. But virologists say the trajectory is troubling, the data patchy and the future uncertain.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It’s now a global problem,” says &lt;a href="https://www.gla.ac.uk/schools/infectionimmunity/staff/edwardhutchinson/"&gt;Dr Ed Hutchinson&lt;/a&gt;, professor of molecular and cellular virology at the University of Glasgow. “As a disease of wild animals, it’s completely out of control. It’s raging around the world, and there’s no feasible containment method other than just watching it infect huge populations of animals.” &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;How quickly has the virus spread?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The current lineage of H5N1 emerged in Asia in the late 1990s and has since swept from continent to continent. Since 2020, a particularly aggressive branch of the virus – known to scientists as clade 2.3.4.4b – has spread explosively through wild birds.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;More than &lt;a href="https://www.aphis.usda.gov/livestock-poultry-disease/avian/avian-influenza/hpai-detections/commercial-backyard-flocks"&gt;180 million poultry&lt;/a&gt; have been infected in the US alone, and over &lt;a href="https://www.aphis.usda.gov/livestock-poultry-disease/avian/avian-influenza/hpai-detections/hpai-confirmed-cases-livestock"&gt;1,000 dairy farms&lt;/a&gt; have reported outbreaks. Egg prices have soared, and the US government has spent more than &lt;a href="https://www.congress.gov/crs-product/R48518"&gt;$1.19bn&lt;/a&gt; (£881m) reimbursing farmers for losses.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For now, the human toll remains limited: only &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/bird-flu/situation-summary/index.html"&gt;71 confirmed cases&lt;/a&gt; in the US, resulting in two deaths. Historically, though, H5N1 has been far deadlier: since 2003, &lt;a href="https://cdn.who.int/media/docs/default-source/wpro---documents/emergency/surveillance/avian-influenza/ai_20250131.pdf"&gt;almost half&lt;/a&gt; of all known human infections globally have proved fatal.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Even so, something unprecedented has happened. In early 2024, H5N1 was found in dairy cattle in the United States. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“This was to everyone’s astonishment,” Hutchinson says, “You now have a situation where a large proportion of consumer milk in the US at any given time contains genetic material from these highly pathogenic viruses.” &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thankfully, pasteurisation destroys the virus. But raw milk, along with close contact for workers on dairy farms, still poses significant risks of infection.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure class="wp-block-image size-large"&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" decoding="async" src="https://c02.purpledshub.com/uploads/sites/41/2025/12/eggs.jpg?webp=1&amp;amp;w=1200" alt="A customer, holding a carton of eggs, is seen during shopping at a supermarket as packages of eggs are seen on the shelves of the egg aisle in New York City, United States on December 20, 2024." class="wp-image-210606"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="wp-element-caption"&gt;Average egg prices in the US peaked at more than $6 (£4.40 approx) per dozen in March 2025 as swathes of flocks of hens were culled due to bird flu infections - Photo credit: Getty&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That unexpected species jump – along with growing evidence of infection in mammals from seals to foxes to bears – increases opportunities for the virus to change and adapt. Flu viruses are unusually good at evolving because their genome is segmented. If two different strains infect the same host cell, their gene segments can mix and match, producing a new hybrid virus.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This process, known as genome reassortment, has played a key role in sparking past pandemics, and many experts are concerned the same could happen if a person infected with a human influenza were also infected with bird flu. This may, for example, allow the virus to gain the ability to transmit effectively in humans, while maintaining a structure which is alien and undetectable to our immune systems. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“In a sense,” Hutchinson says, “the question about reassortment is not ‘When is it going to happen?’, but ‘Why isn't it happening all the time?’ Because there are so many influenza variants out there, and we don't really know the barriers to it taking off.” &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Beyond farms and factories, the outbreak has become a wildlife crisis. In South America, mass die-offs have struck &lt;a href="https://eswi.org/education-hub/pacific-and-atlantic-sea-lion-mortality-caused-highly-pathogenic-avian-influenza" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;sea lions&lt;/a&gt;. And on the Antarctic coast, almost half of the world’s female breeding population of southern elephant seals may already have been killed, according to a recent &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s42003-025-09014-7"&gt;study&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;The US: epicentre and outlier&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The US today is one of the most active hotspots for avian influenza transmission. Yet the national response is fragmented. Farm biosecurity measures remain the primary line of defence, even as&lt;a href="https://www.propublica.org/article/bird-flu-airborne-usda-pandemic"&gt; evidence grows&lt;/a&gt; that the virus may be travelling between farms on the wind – a mode that fences, disinfectant and clean boots cannot stop.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Meanwhile, virologists say monitoring and reporting are weakening. US surveillance varies dramatically between states, complicating assessments of how widespread H5N1 infections really are. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.kent.ac.uk/biosciences/people/1028/rossman-jeremy"&gt;Dr Jeremy Rossman&lt;/a&gt;, honorary senior lecturer in virology at the University of Kent, says effective containment hinges on broad, coordinated surveillance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“This requires extensive surveillance of infection in multiple animal populations, as well as monitoring and testing for animal workers at these farms,” he says. “This can allow for management of any infected flocks or herds, rapid identification of human spillover cases and early detection of new mutations in the virus that may affect transmissibility.” &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But in the US, Rossman argues, that isn’t happening consistently. “The response is more limited and variable from state to state and farm to farm,” he says. “Without strategic and coordinated surveillance and containment, the risks of a human transmissible H5N1 virus will steadily rise, with unknown, but potentially critical consequences.”  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hutchinson shares this concern. Not only are human and animal infections rising, he says, but data sharing has become patchier and harder to interpret, raising the risk that early warning signs could be missed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The good news is that effective vaccines already exist to protect both humans and animals – and the US is thought to have &lt;a href="https://www.unmc.edu/healthsecurity/transmission/2025/01/22/the-us-has-bird-flu-vaccines-heres-why-you-cant-get-one/"&gt;millions of doses stockpiled&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;How successful is vaccination? France adopted poultry vaccination in 2023 and saw outbreaks fall by&lt;a href="https://avinews.com/en/france-avian-influenza-nearly-eradicated-thanks-to-vaccination/#:~:text=France%20has%20achieved%20a%20major,vaccination%20campaign%20in%20October%202023."&gt; 96 per cent&lt;/a&gt; in two years, which is impressive. But progress elsewhere has been slow.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the US, poultry producers and lawmakers have opposed vaccination on trade grounds, warning that it could harm export markets and cost the chicken industry &lt;a href="https://www.congress.gov/crs-product/R48518"&gt;$10bn&lt;/a&gt; (£7.4bn) if other countries ban US meat.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is despite the outbreak already costing the country billions of dollars, not least ordinary people whose grocery bills have risen as egg prices &lt;a href="https://fred.stlouisfed.org/series/APU0000708111"&gt;soared 300 per cent&lt;/a&gt; in 2 years.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure class="wp-block-image size-large"&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" decoding="async" src="https://c02.purpledshub.com/uploads/sites/41/2025/12/bird-flu-virus.jpg?webp=1&amp;amp;w=1200" alt="Colorised transmission electron micrograph of avian influenza A H5N1 virus particles (gold)." class="wp-image-210607"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="wp-element-caption"&gt;This transmission electron micrograph shows avian influenza A H5N1 particles (gold), grown in a cell culture (blue) - Credit: Getty&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;So how worried should we be?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The central fear is human-to-human transmission. So far, it has not happened in any sustained way. But influenza evolves fast, and every new infected host is another throw of the genetic dice.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rossman warns that high levels of circulation across species increase the odds “of the virus evolving into a strain that has both high transmissibility and high lethality. Given the catastrophic implications if it did, tracking and mitigating the spread of H5N1 virus is of critical importance.” &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are reasons for optimism: vaccines and antivirals should be effective against avian influenza, and the world is far better prepared thanks to lessons learned from COVID, particularly in diagnostics and global surveillance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But there are caveats too. Scaling vaccines to a global population would take time; antiviral resistance has already appeared in poultry in Canada, and our immunity to H1 and H3 seasonal flu offers little protection against H5 strains.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Perhaps the sharpest warning comes from computer modelling of an outbreak. A 2025 &lt;a href="https://link.springer.com/article/10.1186/s12889-025-25358-5"&gt;study&lt;/a&gt; from Indian researchers found that once a pandemic strain began spreading in humans, the window for effective containment could be just 2 to 10 detected cases. Beyond that, containment would become almost impossible.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;What happens next&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As 2026 begins, H5N1 is circulating in more species, across more continents, than ever before. It is entrenched in global wildlife. It has destabilised farming. It is mutating, spreading and defying prediction.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hutchinson’s message is clear: vigilance, not panic. “There are reasons to hope as well as reasons to be alarmed,” he says. “But there’s definitely no reason to be relaxed about this one.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What scientists want next is simple: more surveillance, more transparency, more vaccination and more urgency, especially in the United States, where the virus is spreading rapidly, and surveillance remains uneven. Whether they’ll get their wishes, however, remains to be seen.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Read more:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BBC Science Focus Magazine</author><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiZ0FVX3lxTE5HcjlNTGlSdFhVcEhYbzB0cTdkNFIySFpnV3MtVmV4MTFHaFE3bkpqOUxBNmlpZWdvNWpaTnhzZkt1U3dUcGxWa2U4b2JydUpqUkdlOHBocWZzaVEyNDhRYk5QSzlnQWc</guid></item><item><title>兴奋剂ADHD药物的工作方式与以前认为的不同- Medical Xpress</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-12-adhd-medications-differently-previously-thought.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="success-screen" id="successScreen"&gt;
            &lt;p class="success-icon"&gt;✓&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;h2 class="success-title"&gt;Verification Complete&lt;/h2&gt;
            &lt;p class="success-subtext"&gt;This page will redirect in a moment...&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Medical Xpress</author><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 16:51:37 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilgFBVV95cUxNQkFJanpRTkVTN0RUSnBtOEx2REczdjIza1BYNEExZVAtU3phemMwdGZYLW9kUGgwcnhGbGQ5eXVoTGRTaDRLSFNJbHpaamx2TUdVblNtWUo1em41S1F0UlJJUGhlU0h4NmpnRVBSQ1g1NHItRVg1b2dsNjNVY3FrTTBLQUVYYlBfdUVHLVZoaWtOdkJpZ3c</guid></item><item><title>阿拉巴马州流感爆发让男孩在圣诞节为生命而战：休伊镇祈求奇迹- AL.com</title><link>https://www.al.com/news/2025/12/alabama-flu-outbreak-leaves-boy-fighting-for-his-life-at-christmas-hueytown-praying-for-a-miracle.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content   "&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="3CXGONLGDJG2FE3M7UE7BZXQMM"&gt;A Hueytown boy diagnosed with the flu is battling for his life on Christmas Eve in critical condition at Children’s of Alabama.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-1" data-gaid="inarticle-1"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="2ASAC4Q2EFDB3AYLXRXPWRHRV4"&gt;Jace Watkins, 11, was sick on Thursday, visited a doctor Friday, then had a seizure on Saturday, his family said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-2" data-gaid="inarticle-2"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="UFSA3ZPEAZD7XL5BCZFS3I3RBQ"&gt;A crowd including family and friends gathered in Hueytown City Park on Tuesday night to pray for Jace.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-3" data-gaid="inarticle-3"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="YHT2MPCPLVHYFJXLYH3RMMMPGA"&gt;“God hears our prayers,” said Amanda Aloia, a friend of the family who organized the prayer vigil. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-4" data-gaid="inarticle-4"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="IC7UFFP7VRBF5GA733CPTVLGAQ"&gt;“Tonight, we’re here to pray for his healing, that he receives a huge miracle, that he wakes up and he is refreshed and new and God heals every broken part of him, he wakes up with no negative side effects from this, and that his family receives some peace and comfort during this hard time.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-5" data-gaid="inarticle-5"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="TWJCZ6GYORC2JJOWWNXMYJMQWY"&gt;Jace’s life hangs in the balance as he’s on a ventilator in the Intensive Care Unit at Children’s.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-6" class="middleParagraph" data-gaid="inarticle-6"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="RECDXWTKE5F6PDZRHDVMU5KVM4"&gt;“They didn’t know if he’s going to make it,” the boy’s aunt, Sabrina Parsons, &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=z2o-acEp43g" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=z2o-acEp43g"&gt;told Fox 6&lt;/a&gt;. “The doctors did say if he did not have any brain activity in the next couple days, that he would be brain dead.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-7" data-gaid="inarticle-7"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="FSIWB3H6KRELFNCDNAZMX5ZT6I"&gt;New &lt;a href="https://www.al.com/news/2025/12/flu-season-is-here-just-in-time-for-christmas-these-areas-in-alabama-are-getting-hit-hardest.html" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://www.al.com/news/2025/12/flu-season-is-here-just-in-time-for-christmas-these-areas-in-alabama-are-getting-hit-hardest.html"&gt;cases of the flu have been doubling &lt;/a&gt;during the holidays, state officials say.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-8" data-gaid="inarticle-8"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="JT2OCRPKQJEFLA6HLH2ENCME7Y"&gt;The &lt;a href="https://www.alabamapublichealth.gov/data/respiratory.html" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://www.alabamapublichealth.gov/data/respiratory.html"&gt;Alabama Department of Public Health&lt;/a&gt; reports roughly 2.7% of emergency room visits in the week ending Dec. 3 were for flu-like illness. That’s more than twice the rate from the previous week.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-9" data-gaid="inarticle-9"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="EE22KCWN3NE75NC4FNAIYRCJNE"&gt;“ADPH is monitoring influenza activity statewide through our routine surveillance systems, and we are seeing increased flu activity consistent with the seasonal trend,” Ryan Easterling, director of health media and communications at ADPH said in an email to AL.com this week. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-10" data-gaid="inarticle-10"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-enter:VMO724EMTBEZLDSKN7S4N4NCFE" data-fusion-component="VMO724EMTBEZLDSKN7S4N4NCFE"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-exit:VMO724EMTBEZLDSKN7S4N4NCFE" data-fusion-component="VMO724EMTBEZLDSKN7S4N4NCFE"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-11" data-gaid="inarticle-11"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>AL.com</author><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 16:41:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMizwFBVV95cUxPVlI1S2lXTV9rT3hFenRkaWYwdFFVVV85RGFYeVlNNzNiVTBRTHdHckpHWldyY3R6SXdISHAxdlVGOGxXX3B0UDdoeE5TTWhhU3VOZHJFaHRLVmotMm1KUElNU3BhUzNaclNxYnl6cWJ1V0lzelZxQmRsd2pLV1hUUF9PTGpsRGh1emtRZE11UnZpem1EcmZlR0JrX1dKTW9GWDlVb0lESlBRMXdtRHdub1NxNHQzWlVhYXBJUVM4Z0l2OUt1dUliNTNoQUx4ZmfSAeMBQVVfeXFMTl9oOGdobVZNUHBBMXZFSTdyZl8yN0JMcVlUUFl0NnVtUFpxOHU2NGhfT3FyTm9iS3FOZkdkRUl3c21uY3E5dHE4Sm55QkJ4RWNqYldCTHJxcXNYVE5jeVRvSEVnRlJhLTJBTWVSOEVVQ0JpM21KSTZPNkVkSlVfRmJxaldiLVAwdGNLc2k5QU9pYkV0bllpQ0VwT1BzUHNYV3BvMklUelB4VGZ4Zjg1aHVicTNERXc5SXNZWDhaU2JmVHhEMnNkc1N2RHc5SWZ5UGJBaFZTRXpXV3pNRTMyU1czNmM</guid></item><item><title>卫生官员在最近暴露后确认弗吉尼亚州中部的麻疹病例- WSET</title><link>https://wset.com/news/local/health-officials-confirm-case-of-measles-in-central-virginia-after-recent-exposure-campbell-county-virginia-department-of-health-december-2025</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;h2 class="StoryPage_headline__AP3j8"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Health officials confirm case of measles in Central Virginia after recent exposure&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;div class="ByLineContainer_storyBylineContainer__0JNT7" id="js-Story-Byline-0"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="ByLine_storyByLineText__cze7l"&gt;by &lt;span class="ByLine_byLineWord__0Gbfn"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://wset.com/station/people/sam-becker"&gt;Sam Becker&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class="ByLine_byLineWord__0Gbfn"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="ByLineContainer_storyDatelineText__yS9e8"&gt;Wed, December 24, 2025 at 11:31 AM&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="ByLineContainer_storyDatelineText__yS9e8"&gt;&lt;span class="ByLineContainer_updatedText__0D6FY"&gt;Updated &lt;/span&gt;Wed, December 24, 2025 at 2:10 PM&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;button class="UserWayButton_userWayButton__h8S9a ByLineContainer_userWayButton___vCFL"&gt;&lt;img alt="UserWay icon for accessibility widget" src="/resources/defaults/news_3.0/icons/accessibility/userway-transparent.svg"&gt;&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>WSET</author><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 16:32:02 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi_wFBVV95cUxNU3J3dUtpU1ZPNlNXU25VU0RtODNKTGtkME9FSUNxZWhaS0Fvd0F0Yk41eGkxN2c4N0dMQkxNa1pieGxheWN0XzZFYUJyMERoS2lFWGdyNEp2Si1yck5ZSG4wdXRHT1RVVUdyY3dtQ3dNZUhuR24weUNRUDZfZkFmNzRyOERZUHR5T2tQNWEtU1BkY2hScTg1eXozQzZpOUZzQ3l4Vk8yaEZJSXE0eTVsdjZuLWJkckEtYkh5cHV4Z1hyUl9ybVU3bjVNNzh6NzkzQXlNVWpSM0p2ajFpZ1lqOHdOMjg4V090YmttamNtWFBfMmNrcHQyNTEteVZFU2c</guid></item><item><title>健康日志：父母的秘密武器-拼车之间</title><link>https://betweencarpools.com/the-health-log-a-parents-secret-weapon/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content"&gt;
&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;They say a mother’s intuition is key – but a mother’s information may help you do the best job possible when advocating for your child.&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;A while back, I shared &lt;a href="https://betweencarpools.com/one-trick-make-sure-never-forget-dose-antibiotics/"&gt;this medicine hack&lt;/a&gt; that was recently discovered by my much younger sister-in-law, who found it to be a game-changer for her and her friends. As I was discussing another parenting and medical idea with her, she encouraged me to share it with the BCP readers. Thanks, Tzipora, for being my cheerleader!&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="has-prata-font-family"&gt;In my experience, navigating Western medicine requires us to be our own advocates.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Fortunately, with the convenience of urgent care centers and late hours, we often find ourselves in various medical offices with our children. However, this can also mean that no one is keeping track of our kids’ medical history for us.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;That’s why I started a note on my phone called “The Family Health Log.” I listed my children’s names and underlined them, then created bullets for each medical episode, including the treatment and sometimes a brief note. This simple hack has helped me stay organized and informed, and I hope it can do the same for you.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;This is a sneak peak at what a segment of my log looks like : &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;[Child’s Name]&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;•⁠  ⁠March 16th, 2020: Strep (rapid positive) – Cephalexin for 10 days&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;•⁠  ⁠May 27th, 2020: Strep (overnight positive) – Amoxycillin (switched to Duricef after 4 days)&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;•⁠  ⁠Feb 25th, 2021: Toe infection – Cephalexin&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;•⁠  ⁠April 26th, 2021: Strep (positive after multiple cultures and behavioral issues) – Duricef&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;•⁠  ⁠July 15th, 2021: Toe infection – Duricef&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;This tool is especially valuable for young parents who travel frequently, perhaps between Eretz Yisroel, their childhood home for Bain Hazmanim, and their in-laws in another city. With their baby experiencing recurring ear infections in different locations, it can be challenging to keep track of treatments and dates.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;This smart tool allows a responsible mom to maintain a detailed list of dates and treatments, making it easier to share with an ENT specialist and determine the best course of action. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;figure class="wp-block-image size-full"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" data-pin-url="https://betweencarpools.com/the-health-log-a-parents-secret-weapon/?tp_image_id=83702" data-pin-title="The Health Log: A Parent’s Secret Weapon" src="https://cdn.betweencarpools.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/shutterstock_1677873781-scaled.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-83702" srcset="https://cdn.betweencarpools.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/shutterstock_1677873781-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://cdn.betweencarpools.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/shutterstock_1677873781-300x200.jpg 300w, https://cdn.betweencarpools.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/shutterstock_1677873781-1024x683.jpg 1024w, https://cdn.betweencarpools.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/shutterstock_1677873781-768x512.jpg 768w, https://cdn.betweencarpools.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/shutterstock_1677873781-1536x1024.jpg 1536w, https://cdn.betweencarpools.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/shutterstock_1677873781-2048x1366.jpg 2048w, https://cdn.betweencarpools.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/shutterstock_1677873781-150x100.jpg 150w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Here’s another example of how the Health Log proved helpful. My nine-year-old was complaining of frequent headaches, and I couldn’t quite pinpoint the cause. I decided to track the occurrences, jotting down the date and time in his Health Log whenever he mentioned a headache. After a few weeks, a pattern emerged: his headaches always seemed to occur on Sunday evenings. Armed with this insight, we made a few adjustments – we shifted his bedtime on Motzai Shabbos and added an extra water bottle to his Sunday backpack. The headaches significantly decreased. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;mark class="has-inline-color"&gt;My camera roll has also been an empowering tracking tool, as long as it’s organized.&lt;/mark&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;I learned from BCP to caption photos and I’ve created and labeled albums to monitor specific issues. For example, track your teen’s acne journey for a couple of months to identify which creams or medicines are most effective, and have photos readily available to share with their dermatologist. I’ve used this hack to track my son’s eczema journey, and it’s been incredibly helpful.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="has-prata-font-family"&gt;While playing the big sister role,&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;I’d like to share a tip that seemed obvious to me until a great-grandmother told me she wasn’t aware of it. When you or your child take antibiotics, try to wait 2–3 hours before giving probiotics or a yogurt/probiotic snack. Don’t stress if the timing isn’t perfect – even 1.5 hours can make a difference. Waiting 2–3 hours helps protect against diarrhea, upset stomach, diaper rash, and yeast infections caused by antibiotics.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Just a heads up, sometimes kids can throw up after taking antibiotics. If that happens, definitely check with your pediatrician, but I’ve heard that if it’s more than 30 minutes after the dose, it’s probably absorbed and you don’t need to worry about giving another one. Best to get their advice, though!&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="has-prata-font-family"&gt;The last tip is one I’ve found incredibly helpful:&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;mark class="has-inline-color"&gt;I often ask a doctor for permission to record or film a visit.&lt;/mark&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Here’s why. When I’m with my infant and we’re at the ENT for a procedure like a tongue clip, I can’t focus on the nurse’s instructions while tending to my screaming baby. By filming the exercises, I can review them later at a calmer time. Similarly, when I take a child to a specialist and am hit with a lot of information or options, it’s hard to retain everything to discuss with my spouse later. Recording the consult (with the doctor’s permission) or taking notes on my phone helps me process the information and make informed decisions. This is especially useful if I’m seeking a second opinion and want to compare perspectives.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;I hope this share brings you and your family the same benefits it’s brought mine. Wishing you a winter filled with health, happiness, and fewer unexpected doctor visits!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="cp-load-after-post"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Between Carpools</author><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 16:11:30 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMidkFVX3lxTE5ieW9QQ2F2UnN3cWMtVnJLeUUzUFJyWktUSEtnMFMtZzVxdy1pV3o5a0ZMTXQwOTI4eFZfV19YVHBzOThDYWU2bXlvRGZ5alNHeGxNRm9IMmVKbTZIel9UVmlVeWdsNmpodUpXZnlqLWhGM2tKMFE</guid></item><item><title>医院计划因疾病日益严重而限制访客-《代顿每日新闻》</title><link>https://www.daytondailynews.com/local/hospitals-plan-on-restricting-visitors-due-to-growing-illnesses/5LNXXDPQFZAY3PRTGXYNVXNVLY/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="c-contentElements" data-start-index="0"&gt;&lt;p class="story-text " data-index="1"&gt;“Our hospitals are taking proactive, temporary steps to protect patient safety and maintain access to care for our community,” said Sarah Hackenbracht,&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;GDAHA president and CEO. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="story-text " data-index="2"&gt;The restrictions will be: &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="list b-margin-bottom-d40-m20"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;No visitation by anyone who is ill with any respiratory symptoms including coughing, fever, chills, headache, vomiting, sore throat, muscle aches or diarrhea.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;No visitation by anyone under age 14 even if they have received the seasonal influenza vaccine or receive the appropriate vaccine when it becomes available. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="story-text " data-index="4"&gt;“We know how important it is for patients to have the support of loved ones, and these decisions are not made lightly. These measures help reduce the spread of illness and support our health care teams as they care for patients across the region,” Hackenbracht said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="story-subscription__placeholder subscription-promo b-margin-bottom-d40-m20"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="story-text " data-index="6"&gt;Area hospitals and ambulatory care sites are currently seeing higher-than-normal volumes of patients with positive cases of respiratory illnesses, including influenza, COVID-19 and other seasonal viruses, according to GDAHA. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="story-nativo_placeholder--moap b-clear-both is-deferred"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="story-text " data-index="8"&gt;Statewide, hospitalizations for respiratory illnesses have been slowly increasing since November, but the latest week showed 752 hospitalizations for the week ending Dec. 13, according to the most recent data available from the Ohio Department of Health. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="story-text " data-index="9"&gt;Of those hospitalizations, 327 were for COVID-19 cases, 318 were for the flu and 107 for respiratory syncytial virus (RSV), according ODH data. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="story-text " data-index="10"&gt;The local breakdown for the most recent week of data shows:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="list b-margin-bottom-d40-m20"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;In Butler County, 10 hospitalizations for COVID-19, 19 for the flu and eight for RSV&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;In Clark County, four hospitalizations for COVID-19, seven for the flu and none for RSV&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;In Montgomery County, 32 hospitalizations for COVID-19, 37 for the flu and 18 for RSV&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="story-text " data-index="12"&gt;Limiting visitors for hospital patients when there is a higher risk of spreading contagious illnesses like respiratory viruses is a standard infection prevention practice, according to GDAHA. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="story-text " data-index="15"&gt;Hospitals are asking community members to postpone visiting if they are feeling unwell, especially if experiencing symptoms such as fever, cough, sore throat or congestion. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="story-text " data-index="16"&gt;For visitors who are permitted into area hospitals, GDAHA is encouraging them to follow all hospital guidance, including hand hygiene and masking when requested.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="story-text " data-index="17"&gt;Visitor restrictions are temporary and will be reviewed regularly based on illness trends and hospital conditions. Exceptions may be made for pediatric patients, labor and delivery, end-of-life care and other special circumstances, according to GDAHA. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="story-text " data-index="18"&gt;GDAHA is a member-service organization representing 29 hospitals and health systems in the Dayton region. GDAHA collaborates with its members to improve the delivery of health care services in Auglaize, Butler, Darke, Champaign, Clark, Greene, Miami, Montgomery, Preble, Shelby, and Warren counties in West Central Ohio.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Dayton Daily News</author><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 16:01:01 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiyAFBVV95cUxOQm9naE54QkhhTXJIRG9CUjZBMzdmUFlBY1Vfa3R3MUhpYlBCOWltcGpydFgtamdleTQ1Y3lOREVNRVFzTzg5ZzJXN1g1bVhzUlVISUpTLUpKMlhWZEZGdHBXSWtsUGhGanZvaGc3Z3hNQll5d3NaOFc1RHFLc2VGcXNVM09uaVpJTmlpdlduS0FydUxmZ3c4ZFNkWjdwTzFBTzVLbzdPT00wMG9sNlhBeTBpdDBaWnRWZmRSUHh1cG91ZWJqRHhlXw</guid></item><item><title>根据注册营养师的说法，每天早上吃燕麦片会发生什么-非常简单</title><link>https://www.realsimple.com/what-happens-when-you-eat-oatmeal-every-morning-11870872</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="realsimple-sc-page_1-0" class="comp realsimple-sc-page mntl-sc-page mntl-block structured-content" data-sc-sticky-offset="90" data-sc-ad-label-height="24" data-sc-ad-track-spacing="100" data-sc-min-track-height="250" data-sc-max-track-height="600" data-sc-breakpoint="50em" data-sc-load-immediate="4" data-sc-content-positions="[1, 1250, 1550, 1950, 2350, 2750, 3150, 3550, 3950]" data-bind-scroll-on-start="true"&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-block_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block realsimple-sc-block-callout--summary realsimple-sc-block-callout mntl-sc-block-universal-callout theme-summary" data-tracking-id="mntl-sc-block-callout" data-tracking-container="true"&gt; &lt;h3 class="mntl-sc-block-universal-callout__heading"&gt;Key Takeaways&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;div class="mntl-sc-block-universal-callout__body"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Eating oatmeal daily can boost steady energy, support healthy blood sugar, and improve digestion thanks to its soluble fiber—especially beta-glucan.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Long-term, a daily bowl may help lower cholesterol, strengthen gut health, and reduce disease risk, provided it’s not loaded with added sugar.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Pairing oats with protein, healthy fats, and fiber-rich toppings—like chia seeds, yogurt, and berries—creates a more balanced, satisfying breakfast.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_2-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Eggs, bagels, &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.realsimple.com/foods-you-shouldnt-eat-for-breakfast-8732229" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;cereal&lt;/a&gt;, toast—these are all classic breakfast foods you’re sure to find in most American kitchens. Some people like to mix it up every day, while others stick to what they know they enjoy. If you’re a creature of habit and find that oatmeal is your &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.realsimple.com/food-recipes/recipe-collections-favorites/healthy-meals/easy-healthy-breakfast-ideas" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;go-to breakfast&lt;/a&gt;, you’re probably someone who’s aware of its &lt;a href="https://www.realsimple.com/are-oats-good-for-you-8782060" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="3"&gt;many health benefits&lt;/a&gt;.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_3-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_4-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Sure, oats themselves are chock &lt;a href="https://www.realsimple.com/health/nutrition-diet/benefits-of-oatmeal" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;full of benefits&lt;/a&gt; and nutrients. Rich in &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.realsimple.com/dietitians-favorite-high-fiber-foods-11819806" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;dietary fiber&lt;/a&gt;, they’re good for your gut and heart health. They’re also known for providing &lt;a href="https://www.realsimple.com/grain-with-more-energy-boosting-power-than-quinoa-or-brown-rice-11760171" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="3"&gt;steady energy levels&lt;/a&gt;, stabilizing blood sugar, and reducing the risk of some diseases.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_5-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_6-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Clearly, oatmeal is a healthy food to eat daily…so long as it’s not the kind that’s filled with sugar. So what happens when you eat oatmeal for breakfast, day-in and day-out? We spoke to RDs to find out.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_7-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-oatmeal-nutrition"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_9-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block realsimple-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Oatmeal Nutrition &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_10-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; “Oatmeal is a nutrient powerhouse, packed with soluble fiber, especially beta-glucan, plus &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.realsimple.com/health/nutrition-diet/vitamin-b-foods" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;B-vitamins&lt;/a&gt;, iron, &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.realsimple.com/health/nutrition-diet/foods-high-in-magnesium" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;magnesium&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.realsimple.com/foods-with-more-antioxidants-than-blueberries-11773725" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="3" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;antioxidants&lt;/a&gt;,” says Brannon Blount, RDN, a registered dietitian in Danville, Virginia.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_11-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_12-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Here’s a closer look at the nutrient profile of 40 grams (about ½ cup dry) of rolled oats, according to USDA&lt;a href="https://fdc.nal.usda.gov/food-details/2346396/nutrients" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt; &lt;/a&gt;data:&lt;span data-cite="1" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Calories:&lt;/strong&gt; 153&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Carbohydrates:&lt;/strong&gt; 27.5 grams (g)&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fiber:&lt;/strong&gt; 4.16 g&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Beta-glucan:&lt;/strong&gt; 3.01 g&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Protein:&lt;/strong&gt; 5.4 g&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fat:&lt;/strong&gt; 2.36 g&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Iron:&lt;/strong&gt; 1.74 milligrams (mg)&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Magnesium:&lt;/strong&gt; 50.4 mg&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Vitamin B1 (Thiamine):&lt;/strong&gt; 0.162 mg&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Vitamin B9 (Folate):&lt;/strong&gt; 12.8 micrograms (µg)
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_13-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_14-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; These nutrients look great on paper, but they’re also associated with a variety of positive health effects. Many of them can be chalked up to the fiber content, particularly a type of fiber known as beta-glucan.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_15-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_16-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; “Oatmeal is a fabulous source of &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.realsimple.com/health/nutrition-diet/what-are-refined-carbs" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;complex carbohydrates&lt;/a&gt;, and contains fiber that helps to prevent blood sugar spikes and supports sustained energy between meals,” explains Jenny Finke, MS, RD, a registered dietitian who specializes in women’s and metabolic health in Greenwich, Connecticut. “One serving of oatmeal packs around 4 grams of fiber, specifically beta-glucan, a viscous, &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.realsimple.com/health/nutrition-diet/healthy-eating/soluble-fiber-vs-insoluble-fiber" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;soluble fiber&lt;/a&gt; known for various health benefits, including lowering cholesterol and improving blood sugar control.”
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_17-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_18-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; The research on oatmeal really says it all. In one trial, an oat beverage rich in beta-glucan was shown to significantly lower cholesterol &lt;em&gt;and &lt;/em&gt;heart disease risk&lt;span data-cite="2" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;. “Oatmeal offers cardiovascular benefits that are often overlooked,” Finke says. Additional research has demonstrated the anti-obesity&lt;span data-cite="3" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; and antioxidant&lt;span data-cite="4" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; properties of oats, much of which emphasizes the role of beta-glucan. Finally, oats are known for helping balance blood sugar levels, and these benefits can even be see in people with type 2 diabetes&lt;span data-cite="5" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_19-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_20-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Plus, the gut-friendliness of fiber can’t be ignored. &lt;a href="https://www.realsimple.com/high-fiber-foods-11690551" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;High-fiber foods&lt;/a&gt;, including &lt;a href="https://www.realsimple.com/food-recipes/recipe-collections-favorites/healthy-meals/healthiest-grains" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;whole grains&lt;/a&gt; like oats, are associated with improving a variety of GI issues, such as constipation and diarrhea&lt;span data-cite="6" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;. Since the majority of Americans currently don’t get enough fiber&lt;span data-cite="7" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;, oats are that much more attractive for those looking to increase their intake of this essential nutrient. Oats may also provide some protection against colorectal cancer, research suggests&lt;span data-cite="8" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_21-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_22-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; The fiber, namely beta-glucan, in oats is only scratching the surface. RDs also point out that it provides a plethora of micronutrients. “Oats are surprisingly rich in minerals for such an affordable &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.realsimple.com/healthy-shelf-stable-foods-11740097" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;pantry staple&lt;/a&gt;, including &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.realsimple.com/manganese-benefits-7568287" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;manganese&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.realsimple.com/foods-with-more-magnesium-than-almonds-11810536" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="3" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;magnesium&lt;/a&gt;, iron, &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.realsimple.com/foods-high-in-zinc-7511268" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="4" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;zinc&lt;/a&gt;, and copper,” Finke says. She adds that many of the nutrients in oats (e.g. fiber, iron, magnesium, etc.) are generally not consumed enough in the United States, further demonstrating how upping your oat intake could fill nutritional gaps.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_23-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_25-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_27-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-what-happens-when-you-eat-oatmeal-every-day"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_28-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block realsimple-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; What Happens When You Eat Oatmeal Every Day? &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_29-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; There’s a ton of research behind the nutrients in and benefits of oatmeal. In some contexts, oats are even considered a &lt;a href="https://www.realsimple.com/healthiest-superfoods-right-now-according-to-registered-dietitians-11740552" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;superfood&lt;/a&gt;. However, it’s one thing to &lt;em&gt;read &lt;/em&gt;about the perks of oats—it’s another to &lt;em&gt;incorporate &lt;/em&gt;them into your daily life, reaping the benefits one day at a time. Here’s what could happen over the short- and long-term if oats become your &lt;a href="https://www.realsimple.com/why-eating-the-same-breakfast-every-day-might-be-the-healthiest-choice-11859026" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;staple breakfast&lt;/a&gt;.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_30-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_31-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; When you first start eating oats daily, you may notice some of the effects fairly quickly. “Many people notice they &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.realsimple.com/how-to-start-eating-healthier-8425807" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;snack less&lt;/a&gt; and feel more sustained energy throughout the morning,” Blount says. At the same time, there may be an adjustment period if &lt;a href="https://www.realsimple.com/high-fiber-lunch-ideas-that-ll-help-power-you-through-your-work-day-8633615" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;fiber-rich foods&lt;/a&gt; aren’t the norm for you. “For some, the jump in fiber can cause bloating or gas—especially if they’re not used to whole grains,” Blount adds.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_32-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_33-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; What about the long-term effects of eating oatmeal daily? “Daily oatmeal can improve cholesterol levels, support &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.realsimple.com/gut-healthy-breakfast-ideas-8758625" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;gut health&lt;/a&gt;, regulate appetite, and stabilize blood sugar,” Blount says, adding that it’s perfectly safe for most adults to eat oatmeal every day. Some of these effects could also lead to a reduced risk of certain diseases, such as heart disease.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_34-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_35-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Finke is such a fan of daily oatmeal, she frequently recommends it to her clients &lt;em&gt;and &lt;/em&gt;eats it herself. However, not all bowls of oatmeal are equal. “When eating oatmeal daily, it’s important to choose minimally sweetened options to limit added sugars and preserve blood sugar benefits,” Finke explains. She also shares an important reminder that no one food provides &lt;em&gt;all &lt;/em&gt;the nutrients your body needs. This is why the ingredients you mix into and add on top of your oatmeal are also important.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_36-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_37-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; In case you need inspiration, Finke shared her very own oatmeal combo: “The breakfast I make as a dietitian specializing in metabolic health is a bowl of oatmeal mixed with protein powder and a couple of tablespoons of &lt;a href="https://www.realsimple.com/chia-seeds-vs-flax-seeds-11709668" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;chia seeds&lt;/a&gt;, then topped with a dollop of &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.realsimple.com/easy-ways-to-add-greek-yogurt-to-your-diet-11810883" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Greek yogurt&lt;/a&gt; and a handful of berries. This combination delivers complex carbohydrates from the oats, along with high-quality protein, calcium, &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.realsimple.com/foods-high-in-omega-3-11695043" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="3" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;omega-3 healthy fats&lt;/a&gt;, and plenty of fiber.”
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_38-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_39-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Real Simple</author><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 16:01:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiwFBVV95cUxQSEE4ZHNSV3U1Nks2and3ZE9pVHY4aTFfMUgycEpFX0QxLU1oYjFuVk9IdDVxOWh3aXZFUlcxNEZwSzV5WjlMaWpNMWN3alEzNTB3MVI5WHJMOXBLYWhQVjBSZ3M0YjZhUkptS1hBZzF3Y01oYmJfd0gzOHdXZ1I0SllaaDFLejhwdU13</guid></item><item><title>脑部扫描揭示多动症药物的惊喜- SciTechDaily</title><link>https://scitechdaily.com/brain-scans-reveal-a-surprise-about-adhd-medications/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>SciTechDaily</author><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 16:00:18 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihAFBVV95cUxNQ3NPUFdTOUx5Y1pIVnZvSF9MY1drRGdlQ1JsQU1mb1czSDVOSXNuUXEyaTRIWmhXQ2xtd2pxREYzYXA3ZFJJNGlyQzE0R2VvQVI4Z0l0ZzI5OUZhTXZYWVExT3J1MTMxRVdDeXROQjBYeFVVN09fSl9jS0l2LWFja1Z5cjY</guid></item><item><title>苏格兰流感病例下降超过三分之一--英国广播公司</title><link>https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/cd9z4y0xpkdo</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article&gt;&lt;p data-component="headline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 hNbOGD"&gt;&lt;h1 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 idLnWK"&gt;Flu cases in Scotland drop by more than a third&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 eRlINq"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="hero-image" class="sc-5340b511-1 cMIbKV"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20251210-151139-37baf2dfdd-web-2.36.1-1/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 gUePlo hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/6053/live/05e36680-b59c-11f0-99a1-9f4dd3d6a1a3.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/6053/live/05e36680-b59c-11f0-99a1-9f4dd3d6a1a3.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/6053/live/05e36680-b59c-11f0-99a1-9f4dd3d6a1a3.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/6053/live/05e36680-b59c-11f0-99a1-9f4dd3d6a1a3.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/6053/live/05e36680-b59c-11f0-99a1-9f4dd3d6a1a3.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/6053/live/05e36680-b59c-11f0-99a1-9f4dd3d6a1a3.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/6053/live/05e36680-b59c-11f0-99a1-9f4dd3d6a1a3.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/6053/live/05e36680-b59c-11f0-99a1-9f4dd3d6a1a3.jpg.webp" loading="eager" alt="Getty Images A young woman sits on her sofa, blowing her nose into a tissue" class="sc-5340b511-0 hLdNfA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 jVqbAn"&gt;Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The number of laboratory-confirmed flu cases in Scotland has dropped by more than a third, new figures show. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;&lt;a target="_blank" href="https://publichealthscotland.scot/news/2025/december/phs-urges-simple-steps-to-reduce-spread-of-flu-over-festive-period/" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;Public Health Scotland (PHS) data&lt;/a&gt; shows there were 1,297 confirmed cases in the week to 21 December - down from 1,994 in the previous week. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Provisional figures also suggest there were 679 flu-related hospital admissions across the country, down from 950 in the previous week. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;PHS said the latest figures were encouraging but warned there could be more than one wave of flu in a season and urged people to take steps to stop the virus spreading over the festive period. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Separate data from the National Records of Scotland also shows the increase in flu-related deaths is slowing down.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;There were a total of 73 deaths with flu listed as an underlying cause in the week to 15 December. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;This is &lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/articles/cq60jn2j068o" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;up from 67 in the week to 8 December&lt;/a&gt;, but the number of deaths had more than doubled the previous week.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="embed-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 djqsWD"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Scotland's flu season started earlier than usual, with a sharp rise in mid-November.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Experts warned at the start of November that a new variant of flu was spreading more easily across the UK and as a result there would be a long, drawn-out flu season.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Dr Kim Marsh from PHS said: "Following an early start to the season, the latest data suggests that flu cases and hospitalisations in Scotland continue to decrease. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"While each flu season is unique and peaks are not always predictable, we have now seen reassuring declines across a range of age groups and data systems, including reductions in case numbers in younger age groups."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="embed-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 djqsWD"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;But Dr Marsh warned that flu season is not yet over. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;She explained: "In some flu seasons there can be more than one wave of flu because different types of flu circulate at different times. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"At present, flu A is the main strain circulating. However, in Scotland we typically see flu B circulating in the first few months of the new year, and this can cause a second rise in flu cases.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"That's why it's so important to come forward if you're eligible for a flu vaccine this winter and haven't had it yet."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Health Secretary Neil Gray also urged anyone eligible for a flu vaccine to take up the offer. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;As of 21 December, more than 1.3 million adult vaccines had been administered  - more than 110,000 more than this time last winter, he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;He added: "Vaccination remains the best protection against the virus and I encourage everyone who is eligible to come forward for theirs if they have not yet done so."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 hNbOGD"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 gXmhTb"&gt;What can you do to help stop the spread of flu?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;PHS is urging people with flu symptoms, such as a cough or high temperature, to help reduce the spread of flu by taking the following steps:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class="sc-6f869981-0 diUlgm"&gt;&lt;li class="sc-734a601e-0 cRgahm"&gt;Stay off work and do not visit hospitals or care homes until you are feeling better&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="sc-734a601e-0 cRgahm"&gt;Limit contact with others, especially those at higher risk such as babies, the elderly and those with underlying health conditions&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="sc-734a601e-0 cRgahm"&gt;Cover your mouth and nose with a tissue when you cough or sneeze and bin them right away&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="sc-734a601e-0 cRgahm"&gt;Wash your hands regularly with soap and warm water&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="sc-734a601e-0 cRgahm"&gt;Consider wearing a face covering if you must go out&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;You can also find out how to get vaccinated at &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.nhsinform.scot/flu" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;nhsinform.scot/flu&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 hNbOGD"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 gXmhTb"&gt;Is it a cold, flu or Covid?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BBC</author><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 15:59:14 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiWkFVX3lxTE05aGR3aTFhbGJ0OEJFTV9BUzFiSDE0WFc1VWpLNXZVRTVtT1M3WVp6bHdwaFkwekxpV0MtV0JpX2hsZU9VWlNOMnBOT0owbWZoa25wUXA3RllhQdIBX0FVX3lxTFB4T3NmY0ZEaUdIM0h1T1d5RU9VTXNYeGVST05qWEZmaE9XdjBNYUJwRmFDS3VaZ0dpckVuYllNSEduX2I5YzRXNEttc3hDS05UUkI0RU5TdGdVZ1Y3ZlRJ</guid></item><item><title>卫生部召回血压药物--特立尼达和多巴哥新闻日报</title><link>https://newsday.co.tt/2025/12/24/health-ministry-recalls-blood-pressure-drug/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article class="article-content"&gt;


	&lt;a class="article-category" href="https://newsday.co.tt/category/news"&gt;News&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;header&gt;
	&lt;h1&gt;Health ministry recalls blood-pressure drug&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;/header&gt;



&lt;address class="article-author"&gt;
	&lt;a rel="author" href="https://newsday.co.tt/reporter/newsday_reporter"&gt;
		Newsday Reporter								
	&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/address&gt;



&lt;time class="date-time" pubdate datetime="2025-12-24" title="Wednesday 24 December 2025"&gt;2 Hrs Ago&lt;/time&gt;

&lt;figure id="article-featured-image" class="article-featured-image"&gt;&lt;img fetchpriority="high" src="https://newsday.co.tt/wp-content/uploads/2025/08/24251776-1024x754.jpg" alt="Health Minister Dr Lackram Bodoe "&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;Health Minister Dr Lackram Bodoe &lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The Ministry of Health, via its Chemistry, Food and Drug Division, has announced a voluntary recall affecting specific lots of bisoprolol fumarate and hydrochlorothiazide tablets, a generic medication used to treat hypertension.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The affected lots are 17232401 (expiring November 2025), 17232401 (expiring November 2025), 17232401 (expiring November 2025), 17240974 (expiring May 2026), 17240974 (expiring May 2026) and 17240974 (expiring May 2026).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The recall was initiated by Glenmark Pharmaceuticals Inc in coordination with the US Food and Drug Administration (FDA) after routine quality testing identified a potential cross-contamination issue. Trace amounts of another drug, ezetimibe, a medication used to treat high cholesterol, were detected in reserve samples of the product, which should not have been present in the blood-pressure medication.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A total of 11,136 bottles of these products have been affected by the recall.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While FDA’s classification of this recall is Class III, indicating that exposure to the trace contaminant is not likely to cause adverse health effects, the ministry is urging appropriate precaution.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="ad-manager-half-page-mobile-ad-300x600 ad-space-centered" id="div-gpt-ad-1550239531467-0"&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The ministry advised that people who may have purchased or are currently in possession of the affected products to discontinue use immediately and return the medication to the place of purchase.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It said anyone with health concerns should consult with their healthcare provider as patients should not abruptly stop antihypertensive medication without professional guidance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Additional information can be obtained by contacting the Office of the Director of the Chemistry, Food and Drugs Division via email at cfdd@health.gov.tt or phone at 217-4664 ext 13101.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/article&gt;



&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Trinidad and Tobago Newsday</author><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 15:44:37 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigwFBVV95cUxNT1NBTTM2Umg1WVl2eHotTUdYM2hrQUlkZUdHX3BfYWdzMW4yNlJDV25KRkNJYThrVTByeFl5QTNOUHU0YlJEd0dTZG9iQVNIN0tGdlQ3VTFUaFplcjhOME9qRFhSNDNkczR5eDdncm9pQVpPc013eWVpOS03ZGd5R2NYcw</guid></item><item><title>科学家逆转小鼠阿尔茨海默氏症并恢复记忆- ScienceDaily</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/12/251224032354.htm</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p id="first" class="lead"&gt;A study reveals that restoring the brain's energy balance may not just slow Alzheimer's -- but actually reverse it.&lt;/p&gt;

						&lt;div id="text"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;    &lt;li&gt;For more than a century, Alzheimer's disease has been widely viewed as permanent and untreatable once it begins. As a result, most research has focused on preventing the disease or slowing its progression rather than attempting to reverse it.&lt;/li&gt;    &lt;li&gt;By studying multiple mouse models of Alzheimer's alongside human Alzheimer's brain tissue, researchers identified a critical biological problem at the center of the disease. They found that the brain's inability to maintain healthy levels of a vital cellular energy molecule called NAD+ plays a major role in driving Alzheimer's.&lt;/li&gt;    &lt;li&gt;In animal models, maintaining normal brain NAD+ levels prevented Alzheimer's from developing. Even more striking, restoring NAD+ balance after the disease was already advanced allowed the brain to repair damage and fully restore cognitive function.&lt;/li&gt;    &lt;li&gt;These results suggest that treatments aimed at restoring the brain's energy balance could potentially move Alzheimer's therapy beyond slowing decline and toward meaningful recovery.&lt;/li&gt;    &lt;li&gt;The findings also open the door to further research, including the exploration of complementary strategies and carefully designed clinical trials to determine whether these results can translate to patients.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A Longstanding View of Alzheimer's Is Being Questioned&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For more than 100 years, Alzheimer's disease (AD) has been widely viewed as a condition that cannot be undone. Because of this belief, most scientific efforts have focused on preventing the disease or slowing its progression, rather than attempting to restore lost brain function. Even after decades of research and billions of dollars in investment, no drug trial for Alzheimer's has ever been designed with the goal of reversing the disease and recovering cognitive abilities.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That long-held assumption is now being challenged by researchers from University Hospitals, Case Western Reserve University, and the Louis Stokes Cleveland VA Medical Center. Their work set out to answer a bold question: can brains already damaged by advanced Alzheimer's recover?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;New Study Targets Brain Energy Failure&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The research was led by Kalyani Chaubey, PhD, of the Pieper Laboratory and published on December 22 in &lt;em&gt;Cell Reports Medicine&lt;/em&gt;. By examining both human Alzheimer's brain tissue and multiple preclinical mouse models, the team identified a key biological failure at the center of the disease. They found that the brain's inability to maintain normal levels of a critical cellular energy molecule called NAD+ plays a major role in driving Alzheimer's. Importantly, maintaining proper NAD+ balance was shown to not only prevent the disease but also reverse it in experimental models.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;NAD+ levels naturally decline throughout the body, including the brain, as people age. When NAD+ drops too low, cells lose the ability to carry out essential processes needed for normal function and survival. The researchers discovered that this decline is far more severe in the brains of people with Alzheimer's. The same pattern was seen in mouse models of the disease.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="insertion_middle"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How Alzheimer's Was Modeled in the Lab&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Although Alzheimer's occurs only in humans, scientists study it using specially engineered mice that carry genetic mutations known to cause the disease in people. In this study, researchers used two such models. One group of mice carried multiple human mutations affecting amyloid processing, while the other carried a human mutation in the tau protein.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Amyloid and tau abnormalities are among the earliest and most significant features of Alzheimer's. In both mouse models, these mutations led to widespread brain damage that closely mirrors the human disease. This included breakdown of the blood-brain barrier, damage to nerve fibers, chronic inflammation, reduced formation of new neurons in the hippocampus, weakened communication between brain cells, and extensive oxidative damage. The mice also developed severe memory and cognitive problems similar to those seen in people with Alzheimer's.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Testing Whether Alzheimer's Damage Could Be Reversed&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After confirming that NAD+ levels dropped sharply in both human and mouse Alzheimer's brains, the team explored two possibilities. They tested whether maintaining NAD+ balance before symptoms appeared could prevent Alzheimer's, and whether restoring that balance after the disease had already progressed could reverse it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This approach built on the group's earlier work published in Proceeding of the National Academy of Sciences USA, which showed that restoring NAD+ balance led to both structural and functional recovery after severe, long-lasting traumatic brain injury. In the current study, the researchers used a well-characterized pharmacologic compound called P7C3-A20, developed in the Pieper laboratory, to restore NAD+ balance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="insertion_bottom"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Full Cognitive Recovery Observed in Advanced Disease&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The results were striking. Preserving NAD+ balance protected mice from developing Alzheimer's, but even more surprising was what happened when treatment began after the disease was already advanced. In those cases, restoring NAD+ balance allowed the brain to repair the major pathological damage caused by the genetic mutations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Both mouse models showed complete recovery of cognitive function. This recovery was also reflected in blood tests, which showed normalized levels of phosphorylated tau 217, a recently approved clinical biomarker used to diagnose Alzheimer's in people. These findings provided strong evidence of disease reversal and highlighted a potential biomarker for future human trials.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Researchers Express Cautious Optimism&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"We were very excited and encouraged by our results," said Andrew A. Pieper, MD, PhD, senior author of the study and Director of the Brain Health Medicines Center, Harrington Discovery Institute at UH. "Restoring the brain's energy balance achieved pathological and functional recovery in both lines of mice with advanced Alzheimer's. Seeing this effect in two very different animal models, each driven by different genetic causes, strengthens the idea that restoring the brain's NAD+ balance might help patients recover from Alzheimer's."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dr. Pieper also holds the Morley-Mather Chair in Neuropsychiatry at UH and the CWRU Rebecca E. Barchas, MD, DLFAPA, University Professorship in Translational Psychiatry. He serves as Psychiatrist and Investigator in the Louis Stokes VA Geriatric Research Education and Clinical Center (GRECC).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A Shift in How Alzheimer's Is Viewed&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The findings suggest a fundamental change in how Alzheimer's could be approached in the future. "The key takeaway is a message of hope -- the effects of Alzheimer's disease may not be inevitably permanent," said Dr. Pieper. "The damaged brain can, under some conditions, repair itself and regain function."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dr. Chaubey added, "Through our study, we demonstrated one drug-based way to accomplish this in animal models, and also identified candidate proteins in the human AD brain that may relate to the ability to reverse AD."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why This Approach Differs From Supplements&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dr. Pieper cautioned against confusing this strategy with over the counter NAD+-precursors. He noted that such supplements have been shown in animal studies to raise NAD+ to dangerously high levels that promote cancer The method used in this research relies instead on P7C3-A20, a pharmacologic agent that helps cells maintain healthy NAD+ balance during extreme stress, without pushing levels beyond their normal range.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"This is important when considering patient care, and clinicians should consider the possibility that therapeutic strategies aimed at restoring brain energy balance might offer a path to disease recovery," said Dr. Pieper.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Next Steps Toward Human Trials&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The research also opens the door to additional studies and eventual testing in people. The technology is currently being commercialized by Glengary Brain Health, a Cleveland-based company co-founded by Dr. Pieper.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"This new therapeutic approach to recovery needs to be moved into carefully designed human clinical trials to determine whether the efficacy seen in animal models translates to human patients," Dr. Pieper explained. "Additional next steps for the laboratory research include pinpointing which aspects of brain energy balance are most important for recovery, identifying and evaluating complementary approaches to Alzheimer's reversal, and investigating whether this recovery approach is also effective in other forms of chronic, age-related neurodegenerative disease."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

					&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceDaily</author><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 15:15:25 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMib0FVX3lxTFBHa0hNTVpyWXRzR1lTTmpiSUtsdTg2M0tLb3daWGF4LUNFdWlvdlFrQlBYeXI4ekNpeFgzSkJfWTJxdHhYWGtPdmNMNmFfLUtVczRSNWxNVnRnV3lBSTVhaWdYRFF5cTN5Q3otek0tVQ</guid></item><item><title>糖尿病可以逆转吗？医生揭示了哪些生活方式的改变实际上在血糖控制中起作用-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/can-diabetes-be-reversed-doctor-reveals-what-lifestyle-changes-actually-work-in-blood-sugar-control/articleshow/126161934.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;div class="MwN2O"&gt;&lt;div class="vdo_embedd"&gt; &lt;div class="T22zO"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Imagine your body as a complex orchestra with insulin as the conductor that keeps every section in harmony. In diabetes, it is like the conductor that goes off-beat and the music turns chaotic. Everyone wants to “reverse” that disorder and restore perfect harmony but doctors say that it is more like retuning the orchestra than flipping a switch.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="3"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="4"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What diabetes reversal actually means&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="5"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;When endocrinologists talk about remission rather than reversal, they mean a state where blood glucose levels return to non-diabetic ranges without the need for medications but the underlying susceptibility remains. If lifestyle support is lifted, blood glucose can climb again. This distinction is important and backed by emerging clinical research.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="10"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="12"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="lOvcW vdo_embedd"&gt;&lt;div class="k7lcu"&gt;&lt;p class="efT4r"&gt;Diabetes Management Made Simple: 5 Yoga Asanas That Work&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="15"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Remission is possible in type 2 diabetes with intensive lifestyle change. According to a &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jama/fullarticle/1389816" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="_blank" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;2012 study published in JAMA&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, “Intensive lifestyle intervention resulted in significantly greater remission of type 2 diabetes compared with standard diabetes support and education.” This landmark study from the US looked at people with type 2 diabetes undergoing a structured lifestyle program with calorie control and increased physical activity. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The lifestyle group experienced significantly higher rates of diabetes remission compared with the control group, highlighting that how you live matters tremendously.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="21"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="23"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div data-pos="0" class="id-r-component QbQNS undefined  
        "&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;img alt="Forget 'Reversal': Doctors Reveal the Truth About Managing Diabetes Through Lifestyle" msid="126162509" width="" title="Forget 'Reversal': Doctors Reveal the Truth About Managing Diabetes Through Lifestyle " placeholdersrc="https://static.toiimg.com/photo/83033472.cms" imgsize="23456" resizemode="4" offsetvertical="0" placeholdermsid="" type="thumb" src="https://static.toiimg.com/photo/83033472.cms" class="" data-src="https://static.toiimg.com/photo/imgsize-23456,msid-126162509/forget-reversal-doctors-reveal-the-truth-about-managing-diabetes-through-lifestyle.jpg" data-api-prerender="true"&gt;&lt;p class="q3gJl"&gt;Forget 'Reversal': Doctors Reveal the Truth About Managing Diabetes Through Lifestyle &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="26"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Weight loss directly improves insulin sensitivity. A &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://diabetesjournals.org/diabetes/article/64/10/3300/34408/Effects-of-Intentional-Weight-Loss-on-Mechanisms" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="_blank" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;2015 study in Diabetes journal&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; found, “Modest weight loss was associated with improved insulin sensitivity, β-cell function, and metabolic outcomes.” This study shows that even modest weight loss, as little as 5% of body weight, can significantly improve key physiological processes involved in type 2 diabetes. These include insulin sensitivity and how the body manages blood glucose, which supports remission efforts even when medications remain part of care.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="32"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sleep quality, stress and glucose regulation. As per a &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://jcsm.aasm.org/doi/10.5664/jcsm.6476" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="_blank" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;2017 study in Journal of Clinical Sleep Medicine&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; established, “Poor sleep quality and short sleep duration are associated with impaired glucose metabolism and increased risk of type 2 diabetes.” This review highlights an often-neglected piece of the diabetes puzzle: sleep. Poor sleep disrupts hormonal regulation, including insulin sensitivity, demonstrating that lifestyle inputs beyond diet and exercise, like sleep quality and stress reduction, meaningfully influence diabetes outcomes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="38"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="39"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What experts say about diabetes reversal&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="40"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Is it possible to reverse diabetes or is remission a more realistic goal? With diabetes rates ever increasing across the world, many people are questioning if intensive lifestyle changes can significantly improve blood sugar levels and even lessen the need for drugs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="43"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Even when talking about diabetes reversal, we must be precise in our terminology," Dr Usha Ayyagari, Endocrinologist at Apollo Clinic in Chennai, shared in an interview with the Times of India. "Remission is a more accurate term, not reversal."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="45"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to her, remission is possible-albeit mainly possible with early type 2 diabetes and very patient specific. The population of people who enjoy the best results usually see:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="47"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="48"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Significant and sustained weight loss&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Short duration of diabetes&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Less age&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Good blood sugar control prior to intervention&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Not required (or not previously required) insulin&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;"This will dramatically improve the chances of going into remission," Dr Ayyagari implied.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="51"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Talking about what type of diabetes can benefited most from lifestyle changes, Dr Ayyagari said that all types of diabetes need lifestyle management but type 2 diabetes, in particular, has the greatest responsiveneness to lifestyle based interventions. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="53"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Insulin resistance is a hallmark of type 2 diabetes, and it can improve significantly with lifestyle change," explained Dr Ayyagari. "This makes blood sugar control much easier than type 1 diabetes, where the body cannot produce insulin."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="56"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="58"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div data-pos="0" class="id-r-component QbQNS undefined  
        "&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;img alt="Can You Really 'Reverse' Diabetes? Experts Weigh In on Remission and Lifestyle Changes" msid="126162519" width="" title=" Can You Really 'Reverse' Diabetes? Experts Weigh In on Remission and Lifestyle Changes" placeholdersrc="https://static.toiimg.com/photo/83033472.cms" imgsize="23456" resizemode="4" offsetvertical="0" placeholdermsid="" type="thumb" src="https://static.toiimg.com/photo/83033472.cms" class="" data-src="https://static.toiimg.com/photo/imgsize-23456,msid-126162519/can-you-really-reverse-diabetes-experts-weigh-in-on-remission-and-lifestyle-changes.jpg" data-api-prerender="true"&gt;&lt;p class="q3gJl"&gt; Can You Really 'Reverse' Diabetes? Experts Weigh In on Remission and Lifestyle Changes&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="61"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;When asked what is the most important consideration, diet, exercise, sleep, or stress management, Dr Ayyagari noted that the habits don't work in isolation; all of them are just as important, she says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="63"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Her suggestions are as follows -&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="65"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="66"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Diet:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; It’s important to eat at appropriate times, amounts and your calorie range.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Exercise:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; It’s best to incorporate cardio and strength training, the amount of time should be suitability to your goals.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sleep: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;Insufficient sleep increases insulin resistance, weight gain and complicates diabetes and high blood pressure management.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Stress: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;Stress can affect both mental and physical health to the extent that it directly affects blood sugar.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Regarding how much weight loss makes a difference, Dr Ayyagari said that even small changes matter. “I just need to go back to mention that as little as 5% weight loss can begin improving blood pressure and blood glucose,” said Dr Ayyagari. However, other diabetes-related complications will often require a greater weight loss: &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="68"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="69"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Sleep apnoea&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fatty liver disease&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;“In those cases, a minimum of 15% weight loss, and sometimes more, will be needed,” Dr Ayyagari indicated. Discontinuing medication is not guaranteed but improvements are much more likely. This depends on the same remission factors, said Ayyagari and added that even if a person can’t stop their medicine, there will be improvements in control and these can allow for: &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="71"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="72"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fewer medicines&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Lower doses&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Less frequent insulin injections&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Or a lesser dose of insulin&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;In some cases, patients will be able to terminate certain medications but they will still need to undergo a treatment program. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="75"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="76"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Bottom line&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="77"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Although diabetes is not reversible, remission is an achievable and evidence-based target, particularly in individuals with early-type 2 diabetes. The most effective tools remain the fundamentals of eating well, exercising on a regular basis, sleeping well, managing stress and reduce their weight and maintain it. Dr Ayyagari concluded, "Lifestyle is the cornerstone of diabetes management - but the health benefits extend beyond blood glucose management."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="81"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong em" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Note: The information provided in this article is for educational purposes only and is not intended as medical advice. Always consult with a qualified healthcare professional before starting any new medication or treatment and before changing your diet or supplement regimen.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 15:10:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipgJBVV95cUxQTXFVYjZpZzM0WDBVSTFGdHRlcjB1Ujg3ckpjODBSaXVxY0NvbkxhSzV0S2tENmhQUUh1T0VrVXdoNjFjNnlHSkMzWklsb285dzNZNjN6Y2gtSkIxSGhsNHM2MDcxSzBwVzJBaTlneWhQRXZwcG1mR2VaUmhtM2VFTmJwTmdJTWg5dHJkZXhGTy05MnU0M2FoMGR3bmd3ZzNJazNPSTY0akdxdklHUWRpWjNHS2dJRGtqT1NzYmhpMVRYM09YUkxLS2E3YzRCeXlVRnZQc3FxREdEaDhjY242ZnFyM1I2eHdwRHdwS083RHhsRzU1b1VqYjBOdlBaMDRRSXBMWmNBY2hLYzhBQ3VxT1hNZ3JEVS1ZWk1vZkhrOFZROXZQVmfSAasCQVVfeXFMT2d0U1ZvMXlYZWxjb0NvYTEzSWFlWV9yZDJIVDFUcFY2LU1McEZhcTNGYkFld2lpZ2hzYVJVbTR0TXluZTJTRGF0Z3Faa2F1WHBFeUYxZ3FYdlFHUl96Q3Z3ek1OT04tRXg1dEM2Vnl6UDRXell3dDh3ZWl4M0J3M1YwVktmOUhlSEFyeG9fazRRRjMwNk9DRGhLR2pLTkRhYVdMZlVJMEhwb3BSZEpaV3lSbE54WHZmMWtVYXJKQ2xUakw2LVQzTGQxVXdqeE5uWm1TMEEyWkxjNV9GRDI3WEc5dW84T1pNWTl3SnFTbmJFOGoycXdzMjBUWkZBSDhWSkhGMTFjR2ZMeHpEMXdUcHJGU2JHSUJra1hPTzBXdnNrSDJwSURjVDFyZDA</guid></item><item><title>专家说，圣诞节前流感病例下降-英国广播公司</title><link>https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/c3e0qpxzwe7o</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article&gt;&lt;p data-component="headline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 hNbOGD"&gt;&lt;h1 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 idLnWK"&gt;Flu cases falling ahead of Christmas, experts say&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="byline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="byline" class="sc-573fa0e8-0 bWRWzH"&gt;&lt;span data-testid="byline-contributors" class="sc-573fa0e8-11 cOQNNv"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="byline-contributors-contributor-0" class="sc-573fa0e8-5 gXJgDY"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="sc-573fa0e8-7 gqeTMs"&gt;Nick Triggle&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-testid="byline-contributors-contributor-0-role-location" class="sc-573fa0e8-8 bIfajQ"&gt;Health correspondent&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 eRlINq"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="hero-image" class="sc-5340b511-1 cMIbKV"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20251210-151139-37baf2dfdd-web-2.36.1-1/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 gUePlo hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/a145/live/7c53aff0-e0e4-11f0-a8dc-93c15fe68710.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/a145/live/7c53aff0-e0e4-11f0-a8dc-93c15fe68710.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/a145/live/7c53aff0-e0e4-11f0-a8dc-93c15fe68710.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/a145/live/7c53aff0-e0e4-11f0-a8dc-93c15fe68710.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/a145/live/7c53aff0-e0e4-11f0-a8dc-93c15fe68710.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/a145/live/7c53aff0-e0e4-11f0-a8dc-93c15fe68710.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/a145/live/7c53aff0-e0e4-11f0-a8dc-93c15fe68710.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/a145/live/7c53aff0-e0e4-11f0-a8dc-93c15fe68710.jpg.webp" loading="eager" alt="Getty Images A female doctor wearing a stethoscope standing in a hospital " class="sc-5340b511-0 hLdNfA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 jVqbAn"&gt;Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The amount of flu circulating has started to fall in England, &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.gov.uk/government/statistics/national-flu-and-covid-19-surveillance-reports-2025-to-2026-season/national-flu-and-covid-19-surveillance-report-24-december-2025-week-52" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;latest data suggests&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The UK Health Security Agency (UKHSA) said it was encouraging news heading into Christmas, but warned the virus could always bounce back in the new year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The UKHSA uses a range of different measures to monitor flu rates, including sample testing in hospitals and in GP practices.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The latest data covers last week up to Sunday with the UKHSA concluding the virus was circulating "at medium levels".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Similar trends are being seen elsewhere in the UK. Public Health Scotland said it had seen two weeks of cases decreasing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The fall in England comes after the agency said last week that the spread was stabilising after several weeks of rises.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;This year's flu season started early, driven by a mutated strain of the virus, which prompted concern about the pressure that could be placed on hospitals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;NHS England data for the total number of people in hospital is not being published this week.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;But there are signs in UKHSA's sample testing that the numbers being admitted to hospital are beginning to fall, suggesting the projections of record numbers of patients ending up in hospital with the virus over the festive period will not be realised.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="embed-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 djqsWD"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Dr Jamie Lopez-Bernal, an infectious diseases expert at UKHSA, said it was "encouraging news".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;But he added: "The virus is still very much with us and everyone, especially those most vulnerable to winter bugs, needs to take care to protect themselves or help not to spread these viruses to others.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"This is particularly important over Christmas as families come together to celebrate. So if you have any cold or flu-like symptoms you should try to minimise contact with others."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;He said there were simple steps we can all take to protect one another when mixing indoors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"Washing hands regularly and ensuring indoor spaces are well ventilated helps, and we advise those who have symptoms and need to go out, to consider wearing a face covering in indoor public spaces. These simple measures can help make a difference to reduce the spread.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"Flu is always unpredictable, is still circulating and could bounce back even further in the new year as we have seen in past years," he warned. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BBC</author><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 15:01:56 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiWkFVX3lxTE05WmROMjFHR2hpQkkxV3lDaGZfNGczNXdzUzN6YTA0RFE1VU1mTHo5WFlRS0RPZWRBQklZZktqdHJHZk9nNmVTQW5qRGU4LTBkc09RMkZrMVBiZ9IBX0FVX3lxTE9scVZ0YzhZTmpaSU4zZG9USmotTENaYmZGNk9jX0tOWXlWRjdUMmZvQUtjRWVXMFppOExqb2lNTktOQjlydmlrOEI5XzJtMV9ua1g4bWh2RWNNa1N6ci1j</guid></item><item><title>官员警告波士顿地区可能接触麻疹- WCVB</title><link>https://www.wcvb.com/article/measles-boston-westborough-massachusetts-texas-visitor/69857705</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-content--body-inner"&gt;
										&lt;div class="mobile"&gt;
													



																		&lt;div class="mobile"&gt;
							

&lt;section class="article-headline"&gt;
	
			&lt;p class="article-headline--title"&gt;Health officials warn about potential exposure to measles in Boston, Westborough&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;/section&gt;


							&lt;div class="article-branding"&gt;
						&lt;img data-src="https://kubrick.htvapps.com/htv-prod-media.s3.amazonaws.com/htv_default_image/site_branding/wcvb.png" class="lazyload lazyload-in-view branding" alt="WCVB logo"&gt;
								&lt;p class="article-headline--publish-date border-left"&gt;
			Updated: 11:17 AM EST Dec 24, 2025
		&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;a href="/article/hearst-television-news-policy-statements/14471973" class="editorial-standards border-left"&gt;Editorial Standards &lt;span class="info-icon"&gt;ⓘ&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;

							

&lt;p class="article-authors"&gt;
		&lt;/p&gt;


						&lt;/div&gt;
					&lt;/div&gt;
	
						
					&lt;p class="article-content--body-teaser"&gt;
						
					&lt;/p&gt;
	
					&lt;p class="article-content--body-text-raw"&gt;
						Massachusetts health officials issued a warning Wednesday about possible exposure to measles in locations visited by an infected tourist earlier this month. According to the Department of Public Health, a visitor from Texas arrived in the area on Dec. 11 on Airlines flight 2384, and departed on JetBlue flight 117 on Dec. 12. Potential exposures to the infected traveler may have occurred at:Logan Airport Terminal B, Boston, MA, 2:30 p.m.-4:45 p.m., Thursday, Dec. 11DoubleTree by Hilton Hotel Boston-Westborough, Westborough, MA, between 3:30 p.m., Thursday, Dec. 11, and 9 p.m., Friday, Dec. 12Logan Airport Terminal C, Boston, MA, 6 p.m.-11:30 p.m., Friday, Dec. 12Anyone who may have been exposed and begins to develop symptoms is advised to  call their healthcare provider before visiting an office, clinic, or emergency department."Measles is very contagious," DPH officials wrote in a statement. "However, the risk to most people in Massachusetts is low because the vaccination rate in the state is high. People who are not immune and visited any of the locations on the following dates and times may be at risk for developing measles."Video below: Expert 'On the Record' about vaccinesEarly symptoms may occur from one to three weeks after exposure and may resemble a cold. A skin rash follows a few days later. "This case is a reminder that everyone should be vaccinated against measles to protect themselves and others from this highly infectious disease. With multiple measles outbreaks across the country and increased travel around the holidays, now is an important time to ensure that you and your family are protected. Two doses of MMR vaccine are 97% effective at preventing measles and provides protection against mumps and rubella infection," said Dr. Bisola Ojikutu, Commissioner of Public Health for the City of Boston.
					&lt;/p&gt;
	
					&lt;div class="article-content--body-text"&gt;
						&lt;strong class="dateline"&gt;BOSTON —&lt;/strong&gt; 													&lt;p&gt;Massachusetts health officials issued a warning Wednesday about possible exposure to measles in locations visited by an infected tourist earlier this month. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to the Department of Public Health, a visitor from Texas arrived in the area on Dec. 11 on Airlines flight 2384, and departed on JetBlue flight 117 on Dec. 12. Potential exposures to the infected traveler may have occurred at:&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Logan Airport Terminal B, Boston, MA, 2:30 p.m.-4:45 p.m., Thursday, Dec. 11&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;DoubleTree by Hilton Hotel Boston-Westborough, Westborough, MA, between 3:30 p.m., Thursday, Dec. 11, and 9 p.m., Friday, Dec. 12&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Logan Airport Terminal C, Boston, MA, 6 p.m.-11:30 p.m., Friday, Dec. 12&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Anyone who may have been exposed and begins to develop symptoms is advised to  call their healthcare provider before visiting an office, clinic, or emergency department.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Measles is very contagious," DPH officials wrote in a statement. "However, the risk to most people in Massachusetts is low because the vaccination rate in the state is high. People who are not immune and visited any of the locations on the following dates and times may be at risk for developing measles."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Video below: Expert 'On the Record' about vaccines&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p id="cream-inline-rec" class="cream-inline hidden"&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Early symptoms may occur from one to three weeks after exposure and may resemble a cold. A skin rash follows a few days later. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"This case is a reminder that everyone should be vaccinated against measles to protect themselves and others from this highly infectious disease. With multiple measles outbreaks across the country and increased travel around the holidays, now is an important time to ensure that you and your family are protected. Two doses of MMR vaccine are 97% effective at preventing measles and provides protection against mumps and rubella infection," said Dr. Bisola Ojikutu, Commissioner of Public Health for the City of Boston.&lt;/p&gt;

							
											&lt;/div&gt;
	
	
						
						
														&lt;/div&gt;
	
																&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>WCVB</author><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilwFBVV95cUxNMW1IWEFDTU5xZE9QSGo3NEJhX2dYN09zUUMyUzNHdzFjbWIwVko4NWJZRGZINV9jZzA2eVRUcW1hdkVrbUhUcUFzTmtWWS1HMkVLaXUxakRiWDBfMko0WGpSUGxDWmZ0bHd6Ti1SV3ZsZXZqRTZzQWlKSF9HYWxRYnFTZEh5Z0pXTFdHU3pWcUpKYk94NWtz</guid></item><item><title>如何提高握力- gq.com</title><link>https://www.gq.com/story/how-to-improve-your-grip-strength</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="body__inner-container"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Unless you’re deep into the &lt;a href="https://www.gq.com/story/im-done-optimizing"&gt;world of optimization&lt;/a&gt;, you might not know how to improve your grip strength, or why that's even important. Sure, toting around your grocery bags can be testing if you’re struggling to remember where you parked, but otherwise, you're probably not picking things up and thinking ‘Wow, I wish I gripped that a bit harder.’&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yet, as UK-based physical trainer Ben Dillon (founder of the &lt;a data-offer-url="https://www.facebook.com/themyoroom/" class="external-link" data-event-click='{"element":"ExternalLink","outgoingURL":"https://www.facebook.com/themyoroom/"}' href="https://www.facebook.com/themyoroom/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Myo Room&lt;/a&gt; and an expert at &lt;a data-offer-url="https://exercisewithstyle.com/" class="external-link" data-event-click='{"element":"ExternalLink","outgoingURL":"https://exercisewithstyle.com/"}' href="https://exercisewithstyle.com/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Exercise With Style&lt;/a&gt;) explains, there’s more to grip strength than you’d think.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What does ‘grip strength’ really mean?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Grip strength is defined as the force exerted by the muscles in the hand and forearm to hold onto an object,” explains Dillon. Those muscles include the &lt;a href="https://www.gq.com/story/best-biceps-exercises"&gt;biceps&lt;/a&gt; brachii and brachioradialis; triceps brachii, the flexor carpi radialis and flexor carpi ulnaris; extensor carpi radialis and extensor carpi ulnaris muscles. But what does this motley collection of muscle fibers actually do?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Container-VgtPr ekoLDG"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“These &lt;a href="https://www.gq.com/story/how-to-actually-build-muscle-when-you-work-out-3"&gt;muscles&lt;/a&gt; work together to control the hand’s ability to grip and hold objects of different shapes and sizes, from small objects such as coins to large objects such as a basketball,” says Dillon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why is grip strength important in the gym?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;In short, grip strength is important during your workout so that you don’t injure yourself. Deadlifts, pull-ups and kettlebell swings (for example) might not go so well if you’re not able to hold them tight. But good grip strength is also crucial for improving performance and increasing overall strength for exercises like deadlifts, pull-ups, chin-ups, and rows.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Stronger grip strength allows for better control and stability when performing exercises that place stress on the hands, wrists, and forearms, reducing the risk of overuse injuries or strains,” he says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How can good grip strength help with your daily routine?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Having good grip strength can have a positive impact on day-to-day activities, as it allows for better control and stability in many everyday tasks, including carrying objects, opening jars and bottles, DIY tasks, typing, and general outdoor activities such as gardening,” says Dillon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dillon goes on to point out that a strong grip allows for better control when carrying objects. reducing the risk of dropping or spilling items and can reduce the risk of hand and wrist strain from extended computer use (you know who you are). “Using hand tools, painting, or hanging pictures, with good grip strength will help reduce the risk of hand fatigue and injury,” he adds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>gq.com</author><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiakFVX3lxTE8xVVdlcmFRcUt5X0V0bWhRaU9jRzZJem03blF1Z2dTWTFrbzRDYTNEb3RTRTI3dVlsWmRBekxuc2FFNEI5THJ2LVFYTW1aMF9hczVzMG9CSDNCX1J2a1hRVkRvOVRITnhaZVE</guid></item><item><title>科学家促进线粒体燃烧更多卡路里- Phys.org</title><link>https://phys.org/news/2025-12-scientists-boost-mitochondria-calories.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="success-screen" id="successScreen"&gt;
            &lt;p class="success-icon"&gt;✓&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;h2 class="success-title"&gt;Verification Complete&lt;/h2&gt;
            &lt;p class="success-subtext"&gt;This page will redirect in a moment...&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Phys.org</author><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 14:59:42 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMifkFVX3lxTE1tN0xSOXhYNzh1MW1BcWJzcUtTTm9rQUxGUkxGRk5OZ3VXSmxPYUhYTVR4SklsZmxScmpTdjRqRVpUeHA4NFh3N2NUdUpxengxdjhqSjV6OGhuZTZwNl9EbXZHMlNtV3I4SHc3T3NRcEt5NUNCNlBweVg2R1MwQQ</guid></item><item><title>州公共卫生官员提醒居民在多个地点可能接触麻疹- Mass.gov</title><link>https://www.mass.gov/news/state-public-health-officials-alert-residents-about-potential-exposure-to-measles-in-multiple-locations-0</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="ma__rich-text " dir="auto"&gt;
                      &lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="ma__rich-text__flame"&gt;Boston&lt;/span&gt; — The Massachusetts Department of Public Health (DPH) confirmed today that an out-of-state adult visitor who spent time in Boston and Westborough earlier this month was diagnosed with measles and was present in a number of locations. This could have resulted in other people being exposed to measles virus.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On December 11 at 2:39 p.m., the visitor arrived at Boston Logan Airport on American Airlines flight 2384 from Dallas-Fort Worth, TX. The visitor stayed at the DoubleTree by Hilton Hotel Boston-Westborough in Westborough and departed the state on December 12 via Logan Airport at 9:19 p.m. on JetBlue flight 117 to Las Vegas, NV.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;DPH is working with the US Centers for Disease Control and Prevention (CDC) and local partners to identify and notify those who may have been exposed to measles from this individual.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Measles is a highly contagious, airborne disease, which has increased significantly in the United States because of the unfortunate decrease in vaccination rates. It is also a preventable disease,” said &lt;strong&gt;Public Health Commissioner Robbie Goldstein, MD, PhD&lt;/strong&gt;. “This current situation serves as an important reminder of the critical role vaccination plays in protecting our communities. While Massachusetts has not had a measles case this year, 2025 saw the highest number of nationwide cases in more than a decade – nearly 2,000 in 44 jurisdictions, and sadly, three deaths. Fifteen years ago, measles had been considered eliminated in the United States, but that tremendous progress is at risk. Vaccines are one of the most important public health interventions ever – they are safe, effective, and lifesaving.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Measles is very contagious. However, the risk to most people in Massachusetts is low because the vaccination rate in the state is high. People who are not immune and visited any of the locations on the following dates and times may be at risk for developing measles.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Exposures to this individual may have occurred at the following locations and times:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Logan Airport Terminal B, Boston, MA, &lt;strong&gt;2:30 p.m.-4:45 p.m., Thursday 12/11&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;DoubleTree by Hilton Hotel Boston-Westborough, Westborough, MA, &lt;strong&gt;between 3:30 p.m., Thursday 12/11 and 9 p.m., Friday 12/12&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Logan Airport Terminal C, Boston, MA, &lt;strong&gt;6 p.m.-11:30 p.m., Friday 12/12&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Those who could have been exposed and begin to develop symptoms of measles should call their healthcare provider before visiting an office, clinic, or emergency department. Visiting a healthcare facility may put others at risk and should be avoided if possible. Anyone who has had measles in the past or has received two doses of the Measles, Mumps, and Rubella (MMR) vaccine is unlikely to develop measles even if exposed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Early symptoms of measles occur 7 to 21 days after exposure and may resemble a cold (with fever, cough, runny nose, and red eyes). A rash occurs on the skin 2 to 4 days after the initial symptoms develop. The rash usually appears first on the head and then moves downward. The rash typically lasts a few days and then disappears in the same order.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;People with measles may be contagious up to four days before the rash appears and for four days after the rash appears.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“This case is a reminder that everyone should be vaccinated against measles to protect themselves and others from this highly infectious disease. With multiple measles outbreaks across the country and increased travel around the holidays, now is an important time to ensure that you and your family are protected. Two doses of MMR vaccine are 97% effective at preventing measles and provides protection against mumps and rubella infection,” said &lt;strong&gt;Dr.&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Bisola Ojikutu, MD, MPH, FIDSA, Commissioner of Public Health for the City of Boston&lt;/strong&gt;. “Children should receive the vaccine at 12-15 months of age and again before kindergarten to ensure strong immunity. Children who are at least 6 months old who are traveling internationally or to areas of the US with active outbreaks should receive an early dose of vaccine before traveling. It is never too late for children or adults to get the measles vaccine even if they are past the recommended age.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to the CDC, as of December 23, a total of 1,988 measles cases have been &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/measles/data-research/index.html"&gt;reported&lt;/a&gt; in 44 jurisdictions across the United States in 2025. The majority were unvaccinated or had unknown vaccination status (93 percent), 3 percent had one dose of the MMR vaccine, and 4 percent had two doses. There have been three confirmed deaths in the US from measles this year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Due to the increase in measles cases nationally, DPH urges anyone who has not been vaccinated or does not know their measles immunization status to contact their healthcare provider to get vaccinated with at least one dose of the MMR vaccine. Measles vaccine given within 72 hours of exposure may prevent measles disease. Vaccination beyond this window will provide protection from subsequent exposures.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Health care providers who suspect measles should call DPH at 617-983-6800 immediately for recommendations and testing guidance. Providers in Boston should call the Boston Public Health Commission at 617-534-5611.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="/info-details/measles"&gt;Learn more about measles on DPH’s website.&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;
              &lt;p&gt;###&lt;/p&gt;          
        &lt;/div&gt;
                                    
                              &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Mass.gov</author><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 14:48:45 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiywFBVV95cUxPMzZ3ZWVpTzQxZkc5T2lwcHItRjZJeFBQa1BMNFZkdE52NHd4WkdxVGhwSHRQeU1hMFNlRDZVX2xOVVVpVVU0eGtUY1hvdlZsaF9yN19uUjhVdC1MM010X1pkV3haX2xTeDJnTzFRbXZMVVJvMGZRUVZkVEhSaXhOb2MyTkxfMV9SSjQxM3N0OGp1ME5kWU1rTnpUcWVwZTNWWVQtWlZxQURBLUlJYmlaX0VkZGJnU2cwaVRMT2FsQkVtV0N6NzEycjBsOA</guid></item></channel></rss>