<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>GNews Health</title><link>https://news.google.com/</link><description></description><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>根据心理学， 9种日常习惯比任何补充剂都能更好地保护您的大脑- VegOut</title><link>https://vegoutmag.com/lifestyle/z-t-9-daily-habits-that-protect-your-brain-better-than-any-supplement-according-to-psychology/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="page__content mt-4"&gt;
							&lt;p&gt;There’s no shortage of supplements claiming to boost focus, sharpen memory, or keep your brain young.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But here’s the truth. No pill can replace what real daily habits do for your mind.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Your brain isn’t a static organ. It’s constantly adapting, responding, and reshaping itself based on what you do, eat, think, and feel. Research in psychology shows that lifestyle choices have far greater effects on brain health than any supplement ever could.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you want to protect your brain long-term, start with these nine powerful habits.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;1) Get consistent, quality sleep&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sleep is your brain’s nightly reset.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When you rest, your brain clears out waste, stores memories, and repairs connections that keep your thinking sharp. Skipping rest doesn’t just make you tired. It slows down attention, weakens focus, and makes emotional regulation harder.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Studies from the &lt;a href="https://www.nhlbi.nih.gov/health/sleep-deprivation/health-effects" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;National Institutes of Health&lt;/a&gt; show that even one night of poor sleep affects how your brain processes information. Over time, chronic sleep loss can contribute to cognitive decline.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, treat sleep as non-negotiable. Aim for seven to eight hours every night. Keep your room dark, avoid screens before bed, and go to sleep at the same time each evening.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Good sleep is free medicine for your brain.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;2) Move your body every day&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Exercise is one of the best things you can do for mental clarity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When you move, your brain receives more oxygen and nutrients. Movement also releases neurochemicals that boost mood, sharpen focus, and help create new brain connections.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You don’t have to train like an athlete. Even &lt;a href="https://vegoutmag.com/things-to-do/k-if-you-commit-to-these-5-weekly-activities-youll-age-better-than-95-of-your-peers/"&gt;moderate activities&lt;/a&gt; like brisk walking, yoga, or cycling help your brain perform better.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Personally, I’ve found that going for a run in the morning clears mental fog faster than coffee. The rhythm of movement resets my thoughts and sets the tone for the day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Exercise isn’t just about muscles or fitness. It’s brain fuel.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;3) Feed your brain nutrients it actually needs&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What you eat has a direct impact on how you think and feel.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Research consistently links diet quality with &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s44220-024-00226-0" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;brain health&lt;/a&gt;. The Mediterranean diet, for instance, is rich in omega-3s, antioxidants, and plant-based foods that protect brain cells from inflammation and oxidative stress.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Eat more foods that support long-term brain health:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Leafy greens like spinach and kale&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Berries for antioxidants&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Nuts and seeds for healthy fats&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Whole grains for steady energy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Legumes for protein and fiber&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As someone who eats vegan, I’ve seen how clean energy from whole foods keeps my mind focused throughout the day. Processed foods, sugar, and alcohol, on the other hand, can make your brain sluggish.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You don’t have to overhaul your diet overnight. Just make more choices that feed your mind instead of depleting it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;4) Keep learning new things&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The brain loves novelty.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learning strengthens neural pathways and increases plasticity, which helps your mind stay flexible and creative. It doesn’t have to mean going back to school. Try reading new subjects, learning an instrument, or practicing a language.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When &lt;a href="https://vegoutmag.com/lifestyle/gen-8-signs-youre-far-more-capable-than-you-give-yourself-credit-for-according-to-psychology/"&gt;you challenge yourself&lt;/a&gt; to learn, your brain forms fresh connections. This process keeps it strong well into older age.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’ve mentioned before that when I started diving into behavioral psychology, it completely changed how I viewed human decision-making. That mental challenge reignited my curiosity and made me realize how important lifelong learning really is.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Every time you learn something new, your brain literally upgrades itself.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;5) Spend time in nature&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-65565" src="https://vegoutmag.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/08/es-50.png" alt="" srcset="https://vegoutmag.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/08/es-50.png 1600w, https://vegoutmag.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/08/es-50-300x158.png 300w, https://vegoutmag.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/08/es-50-1024x538.png 1024w, https://vegoutmag.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/08/es-50-768x403.png 768w, https://vegoutmag.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/08/es-50-1536x806.png 1536w, https://vegoutmag.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/08/es-50-1200x630.png 1200w, https://vegoutmag.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/08/es-50-857x450.png 857w, https://vegoutmag.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/08/es-50-900x473.png 900w, https://vegoutmag.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/08/es-50-420x221.png 420w, https://vegoutmag.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/08/es-50-840x441.png 840w" sizes="(max-width: 1600px) 100vw, 1600px"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Your brain wasn’t designed to stare at screens all day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nature helps it recharge. The sounds, colors, and movement of natural environments soothe the nervous system and improve focus.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Researchers have found that even short &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0272494425002713#:~:text=A%20consistent%20body%20of%20evidence,et%20al.%2C%202015)." target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;exposure to nature&lt;/a&gt; reduces stress hormones and restores attention. Just 20 minutes outdoors can improve cognitive performance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I like to grab my camera and head to the nearest park when I need a reset. Observing light, trees, and patterns in nature always brings me back to the present moment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You don’t need a mountain trail to get the benefits. A walk around your block or sitting under a tree works just fine.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;6) Practice mindfulness or meditation&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A wandering mind is an anxious mind.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mindfulness trains your brain to stay in the present, reducing stress and increasing clarity. Regular meditation strengthens the prefrontal cortex, which handles focus, decision-making, and self-awareness.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You don’t need to meditate for hours. Even five to ten minutes of quiet breathing or paying full attention to what you’re doing can make a difference.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you find traditional meditation difficult, try mindful walking, cooking, or simply taking a pause before responding to something stressful.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Calm attention is one of the most powerful habits for long-term brain health.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;7) Nurture real social connections&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Human beings are wired for connection.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Strong relationships don’t just make you happier; they protect your brain. &lt;a href="https://news.harvard.edu/gazette/story/2017/04/over-nearly-80-years-harvard-study-has-been-showing-how-to-live-a-healthy-and-happy-life/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Research from Harvard’s&lt;/a&gt; long-term adult development study shows that meaningful social ties are one of the strongest predictors of both happiness and cognitive longevity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Loneliness, on the other hand, has been linked to memory loss and depression.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Make time for friends, family, or even small daily interactions with neighbors or coworkers. The conversations you have, the laughter you share, and the empathy you give all stimulate your brain’s social and emotional circuits.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I make a point to call a friend or grab coffee with someone at least once a week. It’s not about networking or small talk. It’s about staying human.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Your brain thrives when it feels connected.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;8) Manage your stress&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Stress is unavoidable, but chronic stress is harmful to your brain.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Long-term exposure to cortisol, the body’s stress hormone, can damage neurons in the hippocampus, which is responsible for memory and learning.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://vegoutmag.com/lifestyle/gen-the-art-of-staying-calm-7-habits-of-people-who-never-lose-their-cool/"&gt;Managing stress&lt;/a&gt; doesn’t mean eliminating challenges. It means giving your brain space to recover.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Try breathwork, physical activity, time outdoors, or any routine that helps you slow down. I like to end my evenings by putting my phone away, having tea, and reading a few pages of a good book. It tells my brain it’s time to wind down.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Balance is what keeps your brain resilient.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;9) Get comfortable with boredom&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In a world full of constant stimulation, boredom has become rare. Yet it’s one of the healthiest states for creativity and problem-solving.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When your brain isn’t flooded with information, it activates what neuroscientists call the “&lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/topics/neuroscience/default-mode-network" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;default mode network&lt;/a&gt;,” which helps you process experiences and form new insights.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some of your best ideas come when you stop trying to have them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So resist the urge to reach for your phone every time you feel restless. Sit in silence. Let your mind wander.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Boredom gives your brain space to connect dots you didn’t even know were there.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Final thoughts&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You don’t need supplements to protect your brain. You need consistency.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These nine habits might sound simple, but they work because they align with how your brain naturally thrives. Sleep, movement, learning, calmness, and connection — these are what keep your mind strong for life.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When you care for your brain daily, you’ll notice the difference not just in how well you think, but in how fully you live.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Take it one day at a time, and your brain will thank you for decades to come.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="vegou-quiz-after-article" id="vegou-3593601358"&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;What’s Your Plant-Powered Archetype?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ever wonder what your everyday habits say about your deeper purpose—and how they ripple out to impact the planet?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This 90-second quiz reveals the plant-powered role you’re here to play, and the tiny shift that makes it even more powerful.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;12 fun questions. Instant results. Surprisingly accurate.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;						&lt;/div&gt;
					&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>VegOut</author><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 17:03:22 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMixAFBVV95cUxPT3F4b3E1WjBhMGRkd0EyWlBtZnRpQWRTSXItdWwxcnRRLXJWbzFmLUhIYmdGUDdnMlEyOEczVFZNTDRudlZRM1VBVEtXLUhNMWdfODdkYjhxSDE0aVRWT3lLU1FTQWRUY3JZX2tPdmxvN0xBLW5sQTFLSnFEYzgyRV9KdnJCT2ZqSUJRYk5TTXFrOEFWZnIyOE5XZTJSaXlZeURSWGwtVm1NdVBCcHZyLVBpb2NuX3psWXNyVWg0ZmE5ai15</guid></item><item><title>关于难以发现的快速上升的乳腺癌形式的须知- GhanaWeb</title><link>https://www.ghanaweb.com/GhanaHomePage/NewsArchive/What-to-know-about-a-rapidly-rising-form-of-breast-cancer-that-s-hard-to-detect-2006662</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-left"&gt;
&lt;p class="article-image"&gt;&lt;a href="What-to-know-about-a-rapidly-rising-form-of-breast-cancer-that-s-hard-to-detect-2006662?gallery=1"&gt;&lt;img src="https://cdn.ghanaweb.com/imagelib/pics/195/19572610.295.jpg" alt="File photo of breast cancer awareness" title="File photo of breast cancer awareness"&gt; &lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class="image_caption"&gt;&lt;span&gt;File photo of breast cancer awareness&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="article-content-area"&gt;&lt;p id="article-123"&gt;Rates of one type of breast cancer — invasive lobular carcinoma — have been rising in the United States more than three times faster than those of all other breast cancers combined over the past decade, according to a new study.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
This elusive breast cancer that’s hard to spot in routine mammograms is behind more than 1 in 10 cases nationwide.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
The research, published in Cancer, the journal of the American Cancer Society, analyzed national data from 2012 to 2021 and found that rates of invasive lobular carcinoma increased by about 2.8% each year, while rates of all other breast cancer rose by about 0.8% a year.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
What exactly is invasive lobular carcinoma, and how common is it? How is it diagnosed, and why can it be more difficult to find during screenings? Who is most at risk? What are the treatment options? And what should women know about reducing their risk of developing this and other types of breast cancer?&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
To help us with these questions, I spoke with CNN wellness medical expert Dr. Leana Wen, an emergency physician and adjunct associate professor at the George Washington University. Wen previously served as Baltimore’s health commissioner.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;b&gt;CNN: What is invasive lobular carcinoma, and how common is it?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Dr Leana Wen&lt;/b&gt;: Invasive lobular carcinoma, also known as ILC or lobular breast cancer, is a type of breast cancer that begins in the milk-producing glands of the breast, called lobules, and then spreads into nearby tissue. These malignant tumors are often hormone receptor-positive, meaning the cancer cells grow in response to estrogen or progesterone.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
ILC is the second most common type of breast cancer, after invasive ductal carcinoma, and accounts for 10% to 15% of all new breast cancer diagnoses, according to the National Cancer Institute. About 47,500 ILC cases are diagnosed in the US each year, and more women are diagnosed with it than with brain, kidney, liver, pancreatic or ovarian cancer.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;b&gt;CNN: Why is ILC often more difficult to find with routine mammograms?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Wen&lt;/b&gt;: This type of tumor tends to grow in a way that doesn’t change the breast’s structure as much as other cancers. Instead of forming a defined mass, the cancer cells spread through the tissue in thin strands that appear more like normal breast tissue on imaging. Because of this, mammograms may show only subtle changes, or sometimes none at all. Women may also be less likely to feel a distinct lump during a breast self-exam, which can delay detection.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;b&gt;CNN: What other imaging is used to diagnose ILC?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Wen&lt;/b&gt;: A breast ultrasound can help spot areas of thickened tissue that don’t show up on a mammogram, and a breast MRI provides a more detailed view that can reveal cancers hidden in dense breast tissue.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
These tests aren’t routinely recommended for everyone. Mammography remains the standard screening tool for most women. But those at higher risk, including women with dense breasts and those with a strong family history of breast cancer or known genetic mutations, may be advised to have an ultrasound or MRI in addition to regular mammograms.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;b&gt;CNN: What does this study show in terms of the rise of cases and who is most at risk?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Wen&lt;/b&gt;: Researchers found that ILC has been increasing across every racial and ethnic group, but the steepest rise was seen among Asian American and Pacific Islander women, whose incidence grew by about 4.4% each year in the study period. Age is also a risk factor, as women 65 and older are more likely to be diagnosed with ILC than with invasive ductal carcinoma. About 70% of new ILC cases were diagnosed in women 60 and older; the median age of diagnosis is 66.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;b&gt;CNN: How do the study authors explain the rise especially in this type of breast cancer?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Wen&lt;/b&gt;: Several factors may be driving this greater increase. Because ILC is strongly linked to hormones, changes in hormone exposure over time could be part of the reason. Rising rates of obesity and alcohol use, along with changes in childbearing and menopause patterns, may also contribute to the steady increase.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Improvement in diagnosis and greater awareness of ILC may be leading to more accurate identification. Some lobular cancers may have been misclassified as ductal cancers in the past, so part of the rise may reflect better recognition. In addition, more women are living longer after menopause, which can increase the likelihood of developing ILC compared with other types of breast cancer.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;b&gt;CNN: What are the treatment options for ILC?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Wen&lt;/b&gt;: Treatment is similar to that for other breast cancers. Surgery to remove the tumor, followed by radiation, is common, as is hormonal therapy, since most tumors grow in response to estrogen or progesterone. Chemotherapy may be used in some cases. For advanced disease, newer targeted drugs combined with hormonal therapy can help slow progression and improve outcomes. However, ILC may have greater resistance to treatment, especially in more advanced disease, and tends to carry a poorer prognosis once it has spread.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;b&gt;CNN: How can women reduce their risk of developing ILC and other types of breast cancer?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Wen&lt;/b&gt;: Some risk factors can’t be changed, such as age or family history, but many lifestyle choices can make a difference. Quitting smoking, limiting alcohol, maintaining a healthy weight and staying physically active all help lower the risk of breast cancer. Eating a balanced diet rich in fruits, vegetables and whole grains supports overall health and may reduce inflammation linked to cancer.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Regular screening and knowing what’s normal for your breasts are key for early detection. Talk with your doctor about your risk factors and decide together when you should begin screening and whether you need tests in addition to a mammogram.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Finally, pay attention to changes in your breasts, such as thickening, swelling, nipple discharge, different colors or new areas of fullness, and seek medical evaluation as soon as something looks or feels different.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>GhanaWeb</author><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 15:37:16 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi1AFBVV95cUxQYldXWlJuZ0J5SlhfSnRIckVvUE5IRU1SbHprQjZoaWJFMXZMeEJ1bmNySlZua3N3V3ZYZW1rN0RIQkVYM3dmbk1zaWNDMXRZMFdLTkpPVTFqdW4zbHR4VWlrRVhLV0VIU29XTWZ2d0dMbWJUUUVpbWktUm51WU5jeUl0dnUtU1c1Ny1GbFFGekRrWWxvaXE3dGVhWEV2b1Z6RDJDUXdRMDh5aTZEQXJsNzdUeThJX3F6dGM2bEFQelFYSHFqOFlPd0RReGNfQjVNR1ZyZg</guid></item><item><title>科学家们刚刚发现了白发与癌症之间令人惊讶的联系-科学日报</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/10/251025084553.htm</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p id="first" class="lead"&gt;Throughout life, our cells are continually exposed to both internal and external influences that can harm DNA. This DNA damage is a well-known factor in the development of aging and cancer, yet scientists have long struggled to understand the exact link -- especially how DNA-damaged stem cells affect tissue health over time.&lt;/p&gt;

						&lt;div id="text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Melanocyte stem cells (McSCs) are specialized cells that give rise to melanocytes, the pigment-producing cells responsible for the color of our hair and skin. In mammals, these stem cells are found in a region of the hair follicle known as the bulge-sub-bulge area. Here, they exist as immature melanoblasts, ensuring that hair and skin maintain their color through repeated cycles of regeneration.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Discovering How DNA Damage Drives Hair Graying&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Published online on October 6, 2025, in &lt;em&gt;Nature Cell Biology&lt;/em&gt;, a study led by Professor Emi Nishimura and Assistant Professor Yasuaki Mohri at The University of Tokyo explored how McSCs react to different types of DNA damage. Using long-term lineage tracing and gene expression profiling in mice, the researchers discovered that when McSCs experience DNA double-strand breaks, they undergo a process known as senescence-coupled differentiation (seno-differentiation). In this state, the stem cells permanently mature and are eventually lost, which leads to hair turning gray. The process is controlled by the activation of the p53-p21 signaling pathway.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When McSCs are exposed to certain carcinogens, including 7,12-dimethylbenz(a)anthracene or ultraviolet B radiation, they do not follow the same protective path. Even with DNA damage present, these cells avoid seno-differentiation and continue to renew themselves. They expand clonally instead, aided by KIT ligand signals released from surrounding tissue and the epidermis. These niche-derived signals block the protective differentiation response, pushing the stem cells toward a cancer-prone state.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Opposing Cellular Fates: Graying or Cancer&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;According to Nishimura, "These findings reveal that the same stem cell population can follow antagonistic fates -- exhaustion or expansion -- depending on the type of stress and microenvironmental signals." She adds, "It reframes hair graying and melanoma not as unrelated events, but as divergent outcomes of stem cell stress responses."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The researchers emphasize that their findings do not imply that developing gray hair prevents cancer. Instead, seno-differentiation appears to serve as a stress-triggered defense mechanism that removes damaged stem cells before they can become harmful. When this safeguard fails or is bypassed, those damaged cells can survive and potentially lead to melanoma.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="insertion_middle"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Linking Aging, Cancer, and Cellular Self-Destruction&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By uncovering the molecular pathways that determine whether stem cells undergo protective exhaustion or dangerous expansion, this study connects the biology of tissue aging with cancer formation. It also highlights the value of naturally removing compromised stem cells through "senolysis," a biological process that helps prevent cancer by sacrificing cells that could otherwise become malignant.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;E.K.N. is supported by a JSPS Grant-in-Aid for Scientific Research (S) (25H00439), an AMED CREST Project (JP22gm1710003-JP25gm1710003), an AMED Project for Elucidating and Controlling Mechanisms of Ageing and Longevity (JP17gm5010002-JP21gm5010002), an AMED SCARDA Japan Initiative for World-leading Vaccine Research and Development Centers (JP223fa627001), a JSPS Grant-in-Aid for Scientific Research (A) (20H00532), and a JSPS Grant-in-Aid for Scientific Research on Innovative Areas 'Stem Cell Aging and Disease' (26115003), International Joint Research Projects Selected for FY 2025 (No: K25-1185).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yasuaki Mohri is supported by a JSPS Grant-in-Aid for Young Scientists (18K15114) and a JSPS Grant-in-Aid for Scientific Research (C) (25K10315).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jun Seita is supported by an AMED Project for Elucidating and Controlling Mechanisms of Ageing and Longevity (JP19gm5010003, JP20gm5010003) and a JSPS Grant-in-Aid for Scientific Research (C) (18K08377).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

					&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Science Daily</author><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 15:29:51 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMib0FVX3lxTFBta2lUcHdtOW5CVjR5QjZkamY0a0w3T2VCWnlsWGxJNnYtY09wMkp5MGtOOUMtSlJ3ZGZxMkFnSFJBR0JUc0RYaktqNllNUGE5ZDZVV0ZFeGM0c1RsV3B3ejZSY01JaUhVeFJsQnhvYw</guid></item><item><title>得益于斯坦福新技术SFGATE ，这些患者恢复了视力</title><link>https://www.sfgate.com/bayarea/article/patients-get-vision-stanford-tech-21116556.php</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article class="rel"&gt;&lt;figure class="rel f m0 fdc -mx20 sm:-mx40 lg:-mx56 x100vw sm:cw-80 lg:cw-112 mb32"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="mediaCaptionAria" class="f fdc g2 rel pt8 px20 sm:px0 rel"&gt;&lt;span class="photoCaption c-gray700 block ya"&gt;&lt;div data-server-side-rendered="true" class="r12zgbl0 ruduv2y"&gt;&lt;p&gt;The prototype glasses have a camera attached. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="photoCredit c-gray600 block rel z1 mt2 mr48"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Science Corporation&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://med.stanford.edu/profiles/daniel-palanker" data-link="native" class=""&gt;Daniel Palanker&lt;/a&gt;, a professor of ophthalmology at Stanford University, first envisioned a way to reverse blindness two decades ago — and this week, he finally shared the successful invention with the world. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;With new wireless chips implanted behind their eyes and high-tech glasses, around 30 people with advanced age-related macular degeneration — a &lt;a href="https://www.hopkinsmedicine.org/health/conditions-and-diseases/agerelated-macular-degeneration-amd" data-link="native" class=""&gt;common&lt;/a&gt; eye disease — have regained their ability to read again. The device is the first of its kind to bring back functional sight, albeit blurry and only black and white, to patients with this type of incurable vision loss. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="pt16 sy16 bb bt b-gray300 mb32"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="uiTextSmall f aic jcc"&gt;Article continues below this ad&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-block-type="ad" data-small-id="A300" data-large-id="Inline-1" data-unit="hnp-sfgate.com/article_dtc" class="f jcc mnh250px sm:mnh600px ais lg:f lg:jcc lg:mnh250px lg:pb16 lg:aic"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Palanker and his international colleagues &lt;a href="https://www.nejm.org/doi/full/10.1056/NEJMoa2501396" data-link="native" class=""&gt;published the results&lt;/a&gt; from their clinical trial on Oct. 20 in the New England Journal of Medicine. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;“We were surprised that patients could see so well — that was unpredictable,” Palanker told SFGATE. “Until this implant, people tried retinal prosthetics many times, resulting in just light perception but not form vision.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure class="rel f m0 fdc -mx20 sm:mx0 x100vw sm:x100 mb32"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="mediaCaptionAria" class="f fdc g2 rel pt8 px20 sm:px0 rel"&gt;&lt;span class="photoCaption c-gray700 block ya"&gt;&lt;div data-server-side-rendered="true" class="r12zgbl0 ruduv2y"&gt;&lt;p&gt;A scientist examines the prototype glasses in the lab. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="photoCredit c-gray600 block rel z1 mt2 mr48"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Science Corporation&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;The advanced form of macular degeneration, called geographic atrophy, causes people to lose sight over time. It’s most commonly found in &lt;a href="https://www.mayoclinic.org/diseases-conditions/geographic-atrophy/symptoms-causes/syc-20582973" data-link="native" class=""&gt;people over 60&lt;/a&gt; and can cause irreversible blindness, affecting over &lt;a href="https://www.nejm.org/doi/full/10.1056/NEJMoa2501396" data-link="native" class=""&gt;5 million people&lt;/a&gt; worldwide — and an &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC11695844/#:~:text=BACKGROUND%3A,in%20at%20least%201%20eye." data-link="native" class=""&gt;estimated 1 million&lt;/a&gt; in the U.S. The condition destroys photoreceptor cells in the retina, the neural tissue in the back of the eye responsible for transforming light into electrical signals for the brain. Many people keep their peripheral vision, though they often become &lt;a href="https://afb.org/blindness-and-low-vision/eye-conditions/low-vision-and-legal-blindness-terms-and-descriptions" data-link="native" class=""&gt;legally blind&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="md:pt16 md:sy16 md:bb md:bt b-gray300 mb32"&gt;&lt;div class="vh y0 mb0 md:vv md:y100 md:mb16"&gt;&lt;p class="uiTextSmall f aic jcc"&gt;Article continues below this ad&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-block-type="ad" data-small-id="NTV7ARD" data-large-id="Inline-2" data-unit="hnp-sfgate.com/article_dtc" class="lg:f lg:jcc lg:mnh250px lg:pb16 lg:aic"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;The new device has two parts that talk to each other: an implanted chip and special glasses. The glasses — a prototype which Palanker admits is a “little awkward-looking” —  have an attached camera that captures images and then projects them, via infrared light, to the chip. Meanwhile, the 2-by-2-millimeter chip — implanted into the patients’ damaged retinas — converts those images into electrical stimulation, restoring sight. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure class="rel f m0 fdc -mx20 sm:mx0 x100vw sm:x100 mb32"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="mediaCaptionAria" class="f fdc g2 rel pt8 px20 sm:px0 rel"&gt;&lt;span class="photoCaption c-gray700 block ya"&gt;&lt;div data-server-side-rendered="true" class="r12zgbl0 ruduv2y"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Compared to a household key, the chip pales in size. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="photoCredit c-gray600 block rel z1 mt2 mr48"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Science Corporation&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;There were 32 participants who completed the clinical trial — all older than 60 and with sight worse than &lt;a href="https://www.nvisioncenters.com/improve-eyesight/20-100-vision-and-up/" data-link="native" class=""&gt;20/320&lt;/a&gt; in at least one eye. Once they had the new technology, some could make out patterns immediately, while it took others months of training before their sight improved. A year after receiving the device, the vast majority — 27 people — had regained the ability to read, though they could only see a few letters at a time. With their artificial retinas, some could read with 20/42. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nineteen trial participants experienced side effects, such as pressure, tears and bleeding — though most of these issues resolved within two months. Two-thirds of the participants reported medium to high user satisfaction.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="pt16 sy16 bb bt b-gray300 mb32"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="uiTextSmall f aic jcc"&gt;Article continues below this ad&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-block-type="ad" data-small-id="Inline-1" data-large-id="Inline-3" data-unit="hnp-sfgate.com/article_dtc" class="f jcc mnh250px pb16 aic lg:f lg:jcc lg:mnh250px lg:pb16 lg:aic"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sheila Irvine, who is registered blind at age 70, expressed her joy at being able to read and do crosswords again to &lt;a href="https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/c0qpz39jpj7o" data-link="native" class=""&gt;the BBC&lt;/a&gt;: “It’s beautiful, wonderful. It gives me such pleasure.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;“This is certainly an important development,” said Dr. &lt;a href="https://ophthalmology.ucsf.edu/jacque-duncan-md/" data-link="native" class=""&gt;Jacque Duncan&lt;/a&gt;, a distinguished professor of ophthalmology and the department chair at UC San Francisco, who was not involved in this research. &lt;strong&gt;“&lt;/strong&gt;There are existing treatments to try and prevent vision loss — but once vision has been lost, there aren’t really any treatments to bring vision back for people with this disease.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;The scientists hope to make the new technology available outside of the lab. Science Corp., based in Alameda, recently bought the assets of Pixium Vision SA, which originally developed the device before going out of business. Science Corp. has submitted the paperwork necessary to sell the device in Europe. Palanker is also exploring a pathway to bring it to the U.S.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="pt16 sy16 bb bt b-gray300 mb32"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="uiTextSmall f aic jcc"&gt;Article continues below this ad&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-block-type="ad" data-small-id="Inline-2" data-large-id="Inline-4" data-unit="hnp-sfgate.com/article_dtc" class="f jcc mnh250px pb16 aic lg:f lg:jcc lg:mnh250px lg:pb16 lg:aic"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure class="rel f m0 fdc -mx20 sm:mx0 x100vw sm:x100 mb32"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="mediaCaptionAria" class="f fdc g2 rel pt8 px20 sm:px0 rel"&gt;&lt;span class="photoCaption c-gray700 block ya"&gt;&lt;div data-server-side-rendered="true" class="r12zgbl0 ruduv2y"&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is an up-close view of the implant. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="photoCredit c-gray600 block rel z1 mt2 mr48"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Science Corporation&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Palanker is not finished inventing, however. He is developing software that could enable patients to see not only black and white but also shades of gray — a key aspect of face recognition. He’s also working on the next generation of chips that would enable higher resolution vision, getting people closer to 20/20, and a pair with sleeker glasses. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;“There was huge excitement and relief, since I didn’t know what to expect until the clinical trial,” Palanker said. “I’m very happy to see that the results were consistent, with almost all patients having a very similar performance. It wasn’t a one-off.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="y1px x100 abs bgn top"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="y1px x100 abs bgn"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="y1px x100 abs bgn"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="y1px x100 abs bgn"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="y1px x100 abs bgn bottom"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>SFGATE</author><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 15:09:40 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijgFBVV95cUxQa1ZKRVFrXzEzVHlKWnQ3Q0UxMGtsLWdLTWFuZVkxbEJjSXUybVNzZVdILVVQOFoycUppSVVyQ2FJZE1SRnl3VVRyLV9pMTRTOTNwOHJQTFlBMEJMUFZvYThLTUVtbFh3MGRBcHo0aG1ScXRweTdpNGd1SXk0b1Z4Z3JWLVlMT2FEUEVScDhn</guid></item><item><title>每个女性在11月都需要的一种维生素- sofeminine.co.uk</title><link>https://www.sofeminine.co.uk/the-one-vitamin-every-woman-needs-more-of-in-november/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content clear" itemprop="text"&gt;

		
		&lt;p&gt;Grey mornings steal the colour from the sky, coats get heavier, and energy seems to drain faster than the daylight. Colds circle like gossip, nails snap, moods dip, and sleep feels less restorative than it should. There’s a quiet culprit behind so many November slumps.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The bus heater fogs the windows as a woman in a wool scarf taps her Oyster card and stares at the faint sun, a pale coin behind the cloud. In the office, she eats porridge by a screen that glows brighter than the day outside, then walks home under street lamps that flicker before five. Small aches, a steady tiredness, a sense that coffee does less than it used to. The clocks didn’t just shift time; they shifted her body’s chemistry, one missing light signal at a time. It’s the sunshine you can’t see.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-type="_mgwidget" data-widget-id="1874125"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;The invisible gap November brings&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Call it what it is: **vitamin D** is the thing many women are running short on in November. The sun sits low and the angle means UVB barely reaches you at all in the UK. Winter coats cover skin, commutes happen in the dark, and lunch breaks are swallowed by rain. Your bones, muscles, immune cells and even mood circuitry use this nutrient like a language. When it fades, life feels heavier than it should.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Take Priya, 34, who works in an NHS scheduling office in Lewisham. By mid-November she was skipping her evening Pilates because her legs felt leaden and her motivation fell off a cliff. Her GP, familiar with that seasonal pattern, suggested a blood test and a simple daily supplement. She felt steadier by January. In the background, the UK’s own data echoes her story: roughly one in five people have low vitamin D levels in winter and spring, with higher risk if you have darker skin or keep most of your skin covered.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-type="_mgwidget" data-widget-id="1874126"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There’s a clean logic to it. The north-of-50-degrees latitude means the sun’s UVB is too weak from roughly October to March for most people to make vitamin D in skin. Food helps, but not much: oily fish, egg yolks and fortified milks offer only small amounts, and vegetarian choices are slimmer still. Melanin reduces vitamin D synthesis, city living limits daylight, and desk jobs do the rest. The body tries to coast on summer stores, then—bang—November arrives and the tank runs low.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;iframe title="The #1 Vitamin Every Woman Needs for Hormonal Balance (Backed by Science!)" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/oQWQRotp2ss?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen&gt;VIDEO&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-type="_mgwidget" data-widget-id="1874128"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;How to top up without turning your life upside down&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The simplest play is boring, which is why it works: take **10 micrograms (400 IU)** of vitamin D daily through autumn and winter. That’s the UK guidance for adults, including women who are pregnant or breastfeeding. Put the bottle next to the kettle or toothbrush and swallow it with your main meal, as fat helps absorption. If you prefer plant-based, look for D3 from lichen; it’s vegan and widely available. Tiny habit, big return.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let’s be honest: nobody really does that every day. The trick is to lower the friction. Buy a three-month supply in one go. Set a phone reminder for the time you naturally pause, like after lunch. If you regularly forget, a weekly dose can be discussed with your GP or pharmacist. Don’t chase mega-doses on your own, and don’t exceed the UK’s safe upper limit of 100 micrograms (4,000 IU) a day. If you have kidney issues, take certain medications, or have a health condition affecting calcium, ask your clinician for personalised advice.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-type="_mgwidget" data-widget-id="1874129"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Food still counts, but think of it as a nudge, not the fix. A tin of sardines on toast, mushrooms exposed to UV light, fortified yoghurt or plant milks slipped into porridge. Your plate can support what the sky won’t. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“November is when vitamin D goes quiet in Britain,” says a London-based dietitian. “A small, consistent supplement bridges that silence for bone, immune and mood support.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Pick D3 where you can; vegan D3 exists and works well.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Anchor the tablet to a daily cue: kettle, keys, or toothbrush.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Eat oily fish once or twice a week if you enjoy it.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Look for “fortified with vitamin D” on milks and cereals.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If you cover most skin or have darker skin, speak to your GP about year-round needs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;What this means for your November&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We’ve all had that moment when the early dark feels like it’s winning. The good news is you can change the odds with a habit so small it barely dents your day. Think of vitamin D as a winter foundation—quiet, unflashy, stabilising—so your energy, focus, and sense of steadiness don’t rely on rare blue skies.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It won’t fix everything. It can shift the background, the slow hum your body runs on as you stack work, family, and the life you’d still like to live when the sun clocks off at four. If you share a house, make it a household ritual, like tapping the lights off at night or topping the fruit bowl. One tiny pill, the same time, each day. In the gloom of November, that kind of predictability feels like a small act of resistance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;table&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Point clé&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Détail&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Intérêt pour le lecteur&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Vitamin D drops in November&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;UK sunlight is too weak for skin synthesis&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Explains why energy and resilience feel lower&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Daily 10 µg works&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Matches national guidance for adults&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Clear, low-effort action to take now&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Food supports, doesn’t replace&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Oily fish, fortified milks, UV mushrooms&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Easy tweaks that stack with a supplement&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;FAQ :&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Can I get enough vitamin D from the sun in November in the UK?&lt;/strong&gt;Not realistically. The sun’s UVB angle is too low for most of the UK, even at midday. Short outdoor time is still great for mood and movement, but it won’t cover vitamin D.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Should I choose D2 or D3?&lt;/strong&gt;D3 tends to raise and maintain blood levels more effectively. Vegan D3 from lichen is widely available if you avoid animal products.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What’s the safest dose to take daily?&lt;/strong&gt;For most adults, **10 micrograms (400 IU)** daily through autumn and winter is advised in the UK. Don’t exceed 100 micrograms (4,000 IU) a day unless your clinician recommends it.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How soon might I feel a difference?&lt;/strong&gt;Some people notice steadier energy within a few weeks, while others simply avoid the slow slide they felt in past winters. The body is topping up a low reservoir, which takes time.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What if I’m pregnant, breastfeeding, or have a health condition?&lt;/strong&gt;Stick with 10 micrograms daily unless your midwife or doctor advises otherwise. If you have kidney problems, sarcoidosis, high calcium, or take certain medicines, get personalised guidance first.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p data-type="_mgwidget" data-widget-id="1874130"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

		
		
			&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>sofeminine.co.uk</author><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 14:15:30 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiwFBVV95cUxQNFZ3SHBmakVjYUJlaHkyX0FxVzZGSnBxMUZnZFp4RS1jUGRmOFJfRFdKVTV4ak9tVjRSam5rZVhlOVN4aHFtdGVqZTc2OHhEekl4N3dSRnRxZ2lvNDY3eWlSWWJUdWVRQ18xcG8wend2b3VLYjJFN2g2bXMtU19na2JDYWdxdDFlSHJV</guid></item><item><title>这些真菌生活在您的体内，它们可能会影响您的健康- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/these-fungi-live-inside-you-and-they-may-affect-your-health</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;The "gut microbiome" has become a popular health term in recent years. It's easy to see why, with an abundance of research showing how important the trillions of microbes living in our gut are for health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But what many people might not realize is that the microbiome doesn't only contain bacteria. It also contains other types of microbes – including fungi. The fungal component of the &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/topics/gut-microbiome-1624"&gt;microbiome&lt;/a&gt; is called the "mycobiome".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Although the mycobiome has been &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.3389/fped.2020.572538"&gt;less well studied&lt;/a&gt; than its bacterial counterpart, recent research shows it's &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1038/s41467-025-56743-8"&gt;sensitive to diet&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/S2666-5247(22)00203-8"&gt;may affect our health&lt;/a&gt;, too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/we-contain-a-variety-of-microbiomes-heres-a-look-at-a-few-of-the-most-important"&gt;We Contain a Variety of Microbiomes. Here's a Look at a Few of The Most Important.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_178405" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-178405" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/CandidaFungiSEM.jpg" alt="single-celled fungus that is commonly found on the skin and the mucous membranes of the mouth, digestive and respiratory tracts, and the vagina, where it is usually harmless" class="size-full wp-image-178405" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/CandidaFungiSEM.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/CandidaFungiSEM-600x351.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-178405" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Candida&lt;/em&gt; is infamous for causing thrush when the bacteria that usually keeps it in check is out of balance. (Science Photo Library/Getty Images)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;The best studied mycobiome is the one in our &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.cell.2024.04.043"&gt;intestines&lt;/a&gt;. It's composed of many fungal species. The &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1080/19490976.2024.2399360"&gt;most common fungal species&lt;/a&gt; found there, particularly in the Western world, belong to the &lt;a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/books/NBK560624/"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Candida&lt;/em&gt; family&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Candida&lt;/em&gt; are a type of yeast. For most of us, the &lt;em&gt;Candida&lt;/em&gt; population in our mycobiome is kept in check by our &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/26053625/"&gt;immune system and our gut bacteria&lt;/a&gt;. But changes to either of these can cause &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1080/21505594.2016.1247140"&gt;populations of &lt;em&gt;Candida&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; to expand in the mycobiome. This can be a problem, because &lt;em&gt;Candida&lt;/em&gt; may cause &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41577-022-00826-w"&gt;life-threatening infections&lt;/a&gt; in people with damaged immune systems.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For example, research found that hospital patients who are &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1097/ccm.0000000000000746"&gt;given antibiotics&lt;/a&gt; are more likely to develop &lt;em&gt;Candida&lt;/em&gt; infections.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is partly explained by the &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.mib.2011.07.015"&gt;effect of antibiotics&lt;/a&gt;, which kill off certain species of gut bacteria that compete with &lt;em&gt;Candida&lt;/em&gt; for space and resources within the intestine. Antibiotics have also been found to &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.chom.2022.04.013"&gt;directly alter our immune cells&lt;/a&gt; and how they fight fungal infections.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another study, which analyzed the &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1038/s41591-019-0709-7"&gt;mycobiome of cancer patients&lt;/a&gt;, found that those who developed serious &lt;em&gt;Candida&lt;/em&gt; infections had an overgrowth of the fungus in their mycobiome just before the infection started. Combined with the damaging effects of chemotherapy on the &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1007/s00210-023-02781-2"&gt;immune system&lt;/a&gt;, this made it harder for patients to fight off the infection.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Disruption in the mycobiome's &lt;em&gt;Candida&lt;/em&gt; balance has also been linked to several other diseases. For instance, &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1128/mBio.01361-14"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Candida&lt;/em&gt; levels are high&lt;/a&gt; in patients who are critically ill. This suggests that too much Candida in our guts is a sign of poor health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Changes in the fungal mycobiome have also been linked to &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1177/17562848211047130"&gt;several gut diseases&lt;/a&gt;, including inflammatory bowel disease. Research on &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1038/s41586-022-04502-w"&gt;Crohn's disease&lt;/a&gt; has also shown that patients have an overgrowth of &lt;em&gt;Candida&lt;/em&gt;. These fungi also produce toxins that irritate the gut lining, which could potentially explain some of the symptoms Crohn's patients experience.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;High levels of &lt;em&gt;Candida&lt;/em&gt; in the gut can activate immune cells as well, making them more inflammatory. This has been seen in patients with &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1038/s41590-023-01637-4"&gt;severe COVID-19&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Mycobiomes in the body&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The mycobiome isn't only found in our gut.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We also have a &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1080/21505594.2016.1249093"&gt;skin mycobiome&lt;/a&gt;. In fact, the skin &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1038/nature12171"&gt;between our toes&lt;/a&gt; contains a more diverse number of fungal species than any other skin mycobiome.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/37703811/"&gt;skin mycobiome&lt;/a&gt; is mostly dominated by a fungus called &lt;em&gt;Malassezia&lt;/em&gt;. This yeast has adapted to grow on the skin's surface.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/spark-into-space-comp"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro-642x272.jpg" alt="Win a $10,000 Space Coast Adventure Holiday" class="alignnone wp-image-177074 size-medium" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro-642x272.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro-768x326.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro-600x255.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro.jpg 844w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Malassezia&lt;/em&gt; can &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1080/21505594.2016.1249093"&gt;activate the immune cells&lt;/a&gt; that reside between the skin's layers. This may lead to inflammation linked to &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.jaad.2008.07.058"&gt;skin disorders&lt;/a&gt;, such as psoriasis and eczema.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_178397" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-178397" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/IllustrationOfPsoriasisExcessiveSkinCellGrowthFormingPlaques.jpg" alt="illustration of excessive skin cell growth in psoriasis forming plaques" class="wp-image-178397 size-full" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/IllustrationOfPsoriasisExcessiveSkinCellGrowthFormingPlaques.jpg 727w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/IllustrationOfPsoriasisExcessiveSkinCellGrowthFormingPlaques-642x424.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/IllustrationOfPsoriasisExcessiveSkinCellGrowthFormingPlaques-600x396.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 727px) 100vw, 727px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-178397" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Psoriasis is a skin condition where excessive growth of skin cells can lead to itchy, scaly, thickened patches (plaques) of skin which may become infected. (Nemes Laszlo/Science Photo Library/Getty Images)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Candida auris&lt;/em&gt; is also a cause for concern. This fungus is &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/S2666-5247(23)00114-3"&gt;resistant to many antifungal drugs&lt;/a&gt;, which is why it can be a problem if it grows on the skin's surface. In a hospital or emergency room, this could be dangerous – particularly to patients who have immune system problems.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Women also have a mycobiome within the vagina. Its balance with the bacterial communities living there can be a big determinant for vaginal health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One of the &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/s1473-3099(18)30103-8"&gt;most common fungal infections&lt;/a&gt; globally is vaginal candidiasis (thrush). It can &lt;a href="https://www.nhs.uk/pregnancy/related-conditions/common-symptoms/thrush"&gt;cause symptoms&lt;/a&gt; such as intense itching, pain and swelling. Many adult women will experience at least one thrush infection in their lifetime.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The source of thrush is another fungus from the Candida family: &lt;em&gt;Candida albicans&lt;/em&gt;. This is a common member of the vaginal mycobiome.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1073/pnas.1002611107"&gt;vagina's microbiome&lt;/a&gt; is normally dominated by the bacteria &lt;em&gt;Lactobacillus&lt;/em&gt; which help keep &lt;em&gt;Candida&lt;/em&gt; populations in check. But if the balance between bacteria and fungi gets disrupted (for example, by antibiotics), the fungus can &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1186/s12934-020-01464-4"&gt;overgrow or produce inflammatory molecules&lt;/a&gt; within the vagina. This inflammatory response is responsible for common thrush symptoms such as redness and itching.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Probiotics may help to restore the balance between fungi and bacteria to prevent vaginal yeast infections – although this has had &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1093/femsre/fuaf013"&gt;limited success so far&lt;/a&gt;. Some &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1126/scitranslmed.adi3363"&gt;new treatments&lt;/a&gt; that target inflammation-causing fungal molecules have shown promise in animal models and in small numbers of women.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There's good evidence to suggest we might also have a mycobiome in the &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/s2213-2600(18)30510-1"&gt;lungs&lt;/a&gt; and in &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.fgb.2019.03.008"&gt;breastmilk&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Controversially, some have even suggested that we may have small numbers of fungal cells in the brain – and these fungal cells may be linked with neurodegenerative disorders such as &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.7150/ijbs.42257"&gt;Parkinsons&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1038/srep15015"&gt;Alzheimer's&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.3389/fnagi.2018.00159"&gt;Autopsy studies&lt;/a&gt; have found evidence of fungi in the brains of people who died from brain disorders – but this doesn't prove the fungi caused their illness or that it was there during their life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cell.com/cell-reports/pdf/S2211-1247(23)01252-4.pdf"&gt;Experimental studies in mice&lt;/a&gt; have also shown that small numbers of fungal cells can survive in the brain for long periods of time – and the presence of these fungal cells was linked with &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1038/s41467-018-07991-4"&gt;reduced memory function&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1371/journal.pbio.3003020"&gt;Experiments in flies&lt;/a&gt; have also shown fungi may travel to the brain and affect function. This is the best evidence we currently have showing small numbers of fungi may get into the brain and survive long-term.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Whether this occurs in people, and if this would be considered a true mycobiome, remains to be proven.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There's still much we don't know about the mycobiome. But with continued research in this area we may soon better understand the mycobiome's importance in our health and how we can nurture and care for it.&lt;img loading="lazy" decoding="async" src="https://counter.theconversation.com/content/264545/count.gif?distributor=republish-lightbox-basic" alt="The Conversation" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade"&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/profiles/rebecca-a-drummond-1344962"&gt;Rebecca A. Drummond&lt;/a&gt;, Professor, Immunology and Immunotherapy, &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/institutions/university-of-birmingham-1138"&gt;University of Birmingham&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This article is republished from &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com"&gt;The Conversation&lt;/a&gt; under a Creative Commons license. Read the &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/the-fungi-living-in-the-body-play-an-important-role-in-health-heres-what-you-should-know-about-the-mycobiome-264545"&gt;original article&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 14:02:40 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikgFBVV95cUxPVERqeHVXanhpWm5xakZybmR3TWxCVWh6UlBlWEk4LVFMajFlWVpfdVJRLXNQOU9Lamt3OUUwYW9mQ1dmMkIyY3ZaV0ZBZjA5TkJMSmFCeUZCcDFFMERPTm9acUlENlV5aGZhczh3ZVQ2bng0bTF1ZE96SHllWlFVclp3S0NEMlZNU2J0a1FndENWZw</guid></item><item><title>霍乱正在迅速蔓延，但它可以被阻止。我们为什么不把它写进历史？ --《卫报》</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/global-development/2025/oct/25/cholera-global-spread-vaccine-production-africa-zambia</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body-commercial-selector article-body-viewer-selector dcr-hdpgoq"&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The last outbreak of cholera in Britain was in 1866; in the United States there has not been an outbreak since 1911.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;And yet today people are sick with this ancient disease in &lt;a href="https://www.who.int/publications/m/item/multi-country-outbreak-of-cholera--external-situation-report--30--26-september-2025" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;32 countries&lt;/a&gt;, with more than 6,800 deaths reported so far this year –already exceeding all of last year’s toll of &lt;a href="https://www.who.int/news/item/12-09-2025-cholera-kills-more-people-for-second-consecutive-year-while-prevention-and-treatment-available" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;6,000 deaths, which was itself a 50% increase on 2023&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="sign-in-gate"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The most severe outbreaks are in Africa, where conflict is accelerating the spread and hampering control efforts in some countries. &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/society/cholera" data-link-name="in body link" data-component="auto-linked-tag"&gt;Cholera&lt;/a&gt; is the definitive disease of deprivation. It persists not for lack of science or solutions, but because leaders have failed to act with the urgency and commitment the crisis demands.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;A consortium of more than 50 partners, led by the World Health Organization (WHO), is responding to these outbreaks through the &lt;a href="https://www.gtfcc.org/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;Global Task Force on Cholera Control&lt;/a&gt;– a partnership established in 1992 to enable access to essential supplies, as well as work on the detection, prevention and treatment of cholera and set global priorities to sustainably control the disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Complementing the work of the taskforce, in August the WHO and the &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/africa" data-link-name="in body link" data-component="auto-linked-tag"&gt;Africa&lt;/a&gt; Centres for Disease Control and Prevention launched a continental cholera emergency response plan.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="8b6c02be-b19e-4970-9fc8-43b3873fb026" data-spacefinder-role="richLink" data-spacefinder-type="model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.RichLinkBlockElement" class="dcr-47fhrn"&gt;&lt;gu-island name="RichLinkComponent" priority="feature" deferuntil="idle" props='{"richLinkIndex":5,"element":{"_type":"model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.RichLinkBlockElement","prefix":"Related: ","text":"Sudan cholera outbreak kills 40 in a week as health centres overwhelmed","elementId":"8b6c02be-b19e-4970-9fc8-43b3873fb026","role":"richLink","url":"https://www.theguardian.com/global-development/2025/aug/14/sudan-cholera-outbreak-water-health-medecins-sans-frontieres-msf-war-refugees"},"ajaxUrl":"https://api.nextgen.guardianapps.co.uk","format":{"design":8,"display":0,"theme":1}}'&gt;&lt;/gu-island&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Cholera is caused by a bacterium ingested in food or water contaminated with faeces from an infected person, and the only way to prevent it is by ensuring access to safe water and sanitation. This is why it is now practically unheard of in countries with those facilities, but thrives in communities afflicted by inequality, poverty, conflict, displacement and climate-related disasters.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The disease can be prevented with effective vaccines. An injectable vaccine was first developed in the late 19th century, and was superseded by oral vaccines in the 1980s.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;But because the disease afflicts almost exclusively the poorest countries and communities, the vaccine does not attract investment from developers, for whom it offers little market opportunity. There is currently only one manufacturer producing cholera vaccines at the scale needed for mass vaccination campaigns: EUBiologics, based in South Korea.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;To manage cholera outbreaks, the WHO and other partners established a global &lt;a href="https://www.who.int/groups/icg/cholera/stockpiles" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;cholera vaccine stockpile&lt;/a&gt; for outbreaks in 2013 under the International Coordinating Group on Vaccine Provision (ICG) to ensure rapid, equitable and effective access to vaccines in emergencies, especially in low-resource settings. Since then, the stockpile has distributed almost 255m doses of vaccine to 34 countries.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Almost 75% of those doses have been distributed since 2021, in response to the global resurgence of cholera. So far this year, the stockpile has disbursed more than 49m vaccine doses – already eclipsing the previous record for a single year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Given the increasing frequency and severity of outbreaks, vaccines from the stockpile can only be used to bring outbreaks under control, rather than to conduct preventive campaigns in areas at risk of cholera.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The stockpile is replenished every week but production cannot keep up with demand, and it is regularly below the &lt;a href="https://www.gavi.org/vaccineswork/everything-you-need-know-about-global-emergency-vaccine-stockpiles" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;recommended threshold&lt;/a&gt; of having 5m doses ready to respond to outbreaks at any time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;To stretch supplies further, the ICG suspended the standard two-dose vaccination regimen in 2022 in favour of a single dose.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure data-spacefinder-role="inline" data-spacefinder-type="model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.NewsletterSignupBlockElement" class="dcr-173mewl"&gt;&lt;a data-ignore="global-link-styling" href="#EmailSignup-skip-link-14" class="dcr-jzxpee"&gt;skip past newsletter promotion&lt;/a&gt;&lt;aside aria-label="newsletter promotion" class="dcr-av5vqf"&gt;&lt;div class="dcr-10et71f"&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-rsfwa"&gt;Sign up to &lt;span&gt;Global Dispatch&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-1xjndtj"&gt;Get a different world view with a roundup of the best news, features and pictures, curated by our global development team&lt;/p&gt;&lt;gu-island name="SecureSignup" priority="feature" deferuntil="visible" props='{"newsletterId":"global-dispatch","successDescription":"Get a different world view with a roundup of the best news, features and pictures, curated by our global development team"}'&gt;&lt;/gu-island&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-1eusqlu"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Privacy Notice: &lt;/strong&gt;Newsletters may contain information about charities, online ads, and content funded by outside parties. If you do not have an account, we will create a guest account for you on &lt;a data-ignore="global-link-styling" href="https://www.theguardian.com" rel="noreferrer" class="dcr-1rjy2q9"&gt;theguardian.com&lt;/a&gt; to send you this newsletter. You can complete full registration at any time. For more information about how we use your data see our &lt;a data-ignore="global-link-styling" href="https://www.theguardian.com/help/privacy-policy" rel="noreferrer" class="dcr-1rjy2q9"&gt;Privacy Policy&lt;/a&gt;. We use Google reCaptcha to protect our website and the Google &lt;a data-ignore="global-link-styling" href="https://policies.google.com/privacy" rel="noreferrer" class="dcr-1rjy2q9"&gt;Privacy Policy&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a data-ignore="global-link-styling" href="https://policies.google.com/terms" rel="noreferrer" class="dcr-1rjy2q9"&gt;Terms of Service&lt;/a&gt; apply.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;p id="EmailSignup-skip-link-14" tabindex="0" aria-label="after newsletter promotion" role="note" class="dcr-jzxpee"&gt;after newsletter promotion&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;This was based on evidence showing that a single dose provides protection, but it wanes faster than it would with a two-dose regimen. Single-dose vaccination is only therefore a temporary solution to scarce supplies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Demand shows no sign of abating, meaning supply must increase.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;In October 2024, &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/zambia" data-link-name="in body link" data-component="auto-linked-tag"&gt;Zambia&lt;/a&gt; signed a memorandum of understanding with China’s Jijia Medical Technology Company to establish a cholera vaccine-production facility in Lusaka. The planned production will still require rigorous quality assurance and clinical trials to confirm safety and efficacy before any locally manufactured doses can be approved by the WHO and deployed in mass vaccination campaigns.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;While expanding vaccine production in Africa is essential for preventing and responding to outbreaks of this historical disease, the only long-term solution is for governments to invest in safe drinking water and sanitation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;There are some diseases that cannot be completely prevented, such as Alzheimer’s and most cancers. But cholera is not one of them – it can be stopped. Cholera persists because poverty, inequality, conflict and displacement persist.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Stopping it is therefore not a scientific, medical or technical challenge; fundamentally, it’s a political one.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Guardian</author><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 13:38:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiswFBVV95cUxQNDZVMmVrdS1LWkNudG1oSkZNTTFibjBjcUM1VlYtbVloOTN0RU5iR242QzRyTi04ZHA0aHByYjNWWEhQT1pELTZBOS16QUNiZHRVbENBZ2JlQXRQeHdjb1dZM0Y3RXZBNDRHdkdMSExUSkEwV0FCQ1NSenR5NjUyNVJvZEpNb2oyN0VLeVlvSHhPMFRLZE11clRySnhtN1V4ZWdELVBDWU9nbElVaG5QZnMtRQ</guid></item><item><title>在刷牙之前或之后，您应该用牙线清洁牙齿吗？牙医揭示正确的技术- AOL.com</title><link>https://www.aol.com/floss-teeth-brush-them-dentists-103200640.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="caas-body"&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure align-caption-with-image"&gt;&lt;div class="no-margin"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="caption-wrapper"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption-collapse"&gt;&lt;span class="caption"&gt;Should You Floss Your Teeth Before You Brush?&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="photo-credit"&gt;PeopleImages - Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;i&gt;"Hearst Magazines and Yahoo may earn commission or revenue on some items through these links."&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You know you should brush teeth twice and floss once a day at a minimum to keep your teeth clean and breath fresh. But it turns out those two things may make a difference in both the cleanliness of your mouth and the health of your whole body.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“In addition to protecting your smile, maintaining excellent oral hygiene contributes to better overall health,” says &lt;a href="https://www.aae.org/patients/directory/people/steven-j-katz/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Steven J. Katz, DDS, MS;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Steven J. Katz, DDS, MS&lt;/a&gt;, the president of the American Association of Endodontists. &lt;strong&gt;“&lt;a href="https://www.amjmed.com/article/S0002-9343(23)00755-6/fulltext" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Research has shown;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Research has shown&lt;/a&gt; that people who take care of their teeth and gums also enjoy a lower risk of cardiovascular disease, improved control of diabetes, and even &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/pcd/issues/2025/25_0083.htm" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:better cognitive health;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;better cognitive health&lt;/a&gt; as they age.”&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To ensure you’re taking the best possible care of your teeth so you can reap those potential health benefits, you may want to rethink your dental care routine. We reached out to two dentists to find out if it makes a difference whether you brush your teeth first and floss after, or floss first and brush after. Apparently it does!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why do we need to floss our teeth?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Flossing entails sticking something thin (usually a special string) between your teeth and moving it around to help dislodge any matter that shouldn’t be there, which supports the health of our entire mouth. “Flossing is a simple yet crucial step in maintaining oral health, as it removes debris and plaque from areas your toothbrush can’t reach,” says &lt;a href="https://go.redirectingat.com?id=74968X1596630&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.aspendental.com%2Fproviders%2Fashley-boling%2F1265743710%2F&amp;amp;sref=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.goodhousekeeping.com%2Fhealth%2Fwellness%2Fa69000438%2Fshould-you-floss-your-teeth-before-or-after-you-brush%2F" data-i13n="elm:affiliate_link;elmt:premonetized" rel="sponsored" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Ashley Boling, DDS/DMD;elm:affiliate_link;elmt:premonetized;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Ashley Boling, DDS/DMD&lt;/a&gt;, a dentist and the owner of an Aspen Dental practice in Hixon, Tennessee. “This &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC7375740/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:reduces the risk;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;reduces the risk&lt;/a&gt; of cavities, gum disease and other dental issues.” As noted above, those dental problems can also put you at risk for additional whole-body health issues.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Should you floss before or after brushing your teeth?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;It might sound counterintuitive to put floss between teeth that you know are still dirty, but &lt;strong&gt;it’s best to floss first and brush second.&lt;/strong&gt; “Flossing first removes food particles and plaque from between the teeth — areas that a toothbrush simply can’t reach,” says Katz. &lt;strong&gt;“Clearing out those spaces not only reduces the risk of cavities and gum disease, but also allows the fluoride in your toothpaste to reach more surfaces of your teeth.&lt;/strong&gt; That means &lt;a href="https://www.ada.org/resources/community-initiatives/fluoride-in-water/fluoridation-faqs" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:stronger enamel;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;stronger enamel&lt;/a&gt;, healthier gums, and better protection against decay.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Boling agrees. “You can floss before or after brushing as long as you are doing it thoroughly and are reaching areas that your toothbrush can’t,” she says. &lt;strong&gt;“Flossing beforehand, however, can help dislodge food particles and plaque, making brushing more effective.”&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;When is the best time of day to floss?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The best time to floss your teeth is the time that you will stick to every day. “For many people, &lt;strong&gt;the easiest habit is to floss at night before brushing and right before bed,” says Katz. “That way, you go to sleep with a clean, healthy mouth.&lt;/strong&gt; Once flossing becomes part of your nightly routine, you’ll quickly notice that it feels incomplete when you skip it — almost like forgetting to wash your face or lock the door.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What’s the best flossing tool?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I find &lt;strong&gt;traditional string floss to be the most effective for scraping plaque from beneath the gumline, but tools like floss picks and water flossers are great alternatives,&lt;/strong&gt; especially for those with dexterity challenges or braces,” says Boling. “The key is consistency — the best flossing tool is the one you’ll use regularly!”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Pro 1000 Rechargeable Electric Toothbrush&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure align-caption-with-image"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class="link rapid-noclick-resp athena-button" href="https://www.amazon.com/dp/B003UKM9CO?tag=syn-yahoo-20&amp;amp;ascsubtag=%5Bartid%7C10055.a.69000438%5Bsrc%7Cyahoo-us" data-i13n="elm:affiliate_link;elmt:premonetized" rel="sponsored" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:$39.94 at amazon.com;elm:affiliate_link;elmt:premonetized;itc:0;sec:content-canvas"&gt;$39.94 at amazon.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;4100 Power Toothbrush&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure align-caption-with-image"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class="link rapid-noclick-resp athena-button" href="https://www.amazon.com/dp/B09LD7WRVS?tag=syn-yahoo-20&amp;amp;ascsubtag=%5Bartid%7C10055.a.69000438%5Bsrc%7Cyahoo-us" data-i13n="elm:affiliate_link;elmt:premonetized" rel="sponsored" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:$39.99 at amazon.com;elm:affiliate_link;elmt:premonetized;itc:0;sec:content-canvas"&gt;$39.99 at amazon.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;9900 Prestige Rechargeable Electric Power Toothbrush with SenseIQ&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure align-caption-with-image"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class="link rapid-noclick-resp athena-button" href="https://www.amazon.com/dp/B08YCVJKXV?tag=syn-yahoo-20&amp;amp;ascsubtag=%5Bartid%7C10055.a.69000438%5Bsrc%7Cyahoo-us" data-i13n="elm:affiliate_link;elmt:premonetized" rel="sponsored" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:$349.99 at amazon.com;elm:affiliate_link;elmt:premonetized;itc:0;sec:content-canvas"&gt;$349.99 at amazon.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The bottom line&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Consistent brushing and flossing, combined with regular dental visits, are the best way to maintain strong oral health and avoid complex dental procedures,” says Katz. If you want to make the most of your dental routine, &lt;strong&gt;it’s smart to floss your teeth before you clean them with a toothbrush so as much debris is removed as possible.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You Might Also Like&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>AOL.com</author><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 13:13:53 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMidEFVX3lxTE9PM1laZUxZT0hsWGRVMG1CbE5oZldtdWNNTmNoSURnYUdvYVNmbXhHSW02TWd2TnJSdlFVUEItMm1OaVJRUlYxU0JuWXg1SnVpaTlJMGpSODVabzFVSEFtSjNUYlVFSXJ0bFlVWGRTR09OYUNJ</guid></item><item><title>房客专栏|发霉的食物与癌症和神经损伤等严重健康问题有关-《华盛顿邮报》</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/wellness/2025/10/25/mold-toxins-old-food-health-risks/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="FGLST642LNAMFIKSK65AKORAVE" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;When you open your refrigerator and find a wedge of cheese flecked with green mold or a package of chicken that smells faintly sour, it can be tempting to gamble with your stomach rather than waste food.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 13:01:52 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijgFBVV95cUxNQmFRV2hpWFVBWGRtQVBKVWdzV0p5YlFaRW1ndXRPS05vdWx0WjdCSnphdzhHdkE3cUdOcWRsbXczOGZMZ2szVGx2T0lvNXN5Xy13aGJqWktzdzBXdDlMSjBVTzJ0VVFfbk9yZ1AtaFV6M2dxc09YeXEyV3Npb3loSnlVRzdBZThOUVZjWjVB</guid></item><item><title>根据毒理学家- CNN的说法，您对食物中铅的最佳防御</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2025/10/25/health/lead-in-food-wellness</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article__content" data-editable="content" itemprop="articleBody" data-reorderable="content"&gt;
                
    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmh5byblv000x26p5946d2zkw@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Lead shouldn’t be in your food, right?
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmh5bzrgp00083b6nnhjx8ahb@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Exposure to the substance has been linked to a wide range of health impacts, including developmental problems, nervous system damage and hearing problems in children; and high blood pressure, joint pain and reproductive problems in adults.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmh5bzrgp00093b6n7qi572xg@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            At the same time, reports continue to document high levels of lead in food products such as &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2024/09/12/health/lead-cinnamon-powder-spices-wellness"&gt;applesauce&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2024/02/06/health/cinnamon-applesauce-lead-fda"&gt;cinnamon powder&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2025/01/09/health/protein-powder-heavy-metals-wellness"&gt;protein powder&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2024/07/31/health/cacao-dark-chocolate-lead-heavy-metals-wellness"&gt;chocolate&lt;/a&gt;. This year, the US Food and Drug Administration established new guidance on limits of lead content in &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2025/01/06/health/lead-baby-food-fda-wellness"&gt;baby food&lt;/a&gt;.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmh5bzrgp000a3b6n6m8z26g8@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            It makes sense to ask: Why would there be lead in your diet at all?
    &lt;/p&gt;

  

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmh5bzrgp000b3b6nlasen1i4@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Lead is a naturally occurring metal found in our planet, and it has been used in products such as gasoline, paint, plumbing, cosmetics, ceramics and batteries, according to the &lt;a href="https://www.niehs.nih.gov/health/topics/agents/lead" target="_blank"&gt;National Institute of Environmental Health Science.&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmh5bzrgp000d3b6n6ruw1qpi@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Often, lead in food comes from the soil. “The most common reason is because lead, like other metals and heavy metals, is a naturally occurring part of the earth and the Earth’s crust,” said Dr. Joseph Zagorski, a toxicologist and assistant professor at Michigan State University’s Center for Research on Ingredient Safety.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmh5bzrgp000e3b6nvf1ymt37@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Some plants are more prone to absorbing the lead in the soil and storing them in their own tissue, he added. If crops are grown in areas with higher levels of lead in the environment, they may contain more of the metal.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmh5bzrgp000f3b6nkfv9s0sv@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            But not all the lead sources in the environment are natural, Zagorski said. Human activities such as smelting frequently lead to lead contamination, and there have been pesticides that contained lead, he added.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmh5bzrgp000g3b6nzq74qs5a@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Use of leaded gasoline can also lead to contamination of plants through the air, said Dr. Tasha Stoiber, a senior scientist for the Environmental Working Group. Lead has been phased out of gasoline for cars, but is &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2021/08/30/business/lead-gasoline-car-climate-change-intl"&gt;still used&lt;/a&gt; in some fuel types.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmh5bzrgp000h3b6nnnv7z60p@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Contamination also can occur through someone adding lead to food, as appeared to be &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2024/02/06/health/cinnamon-applesauce-lead-fda"&gt;the case in 2023&lt;/a&gt; with some applesauce pouches. But that is not usually the case.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmh5bzrgp000i3b6n78p346sc@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Because the heavy metal is found in the environment, people are unlikely to reach a point of zero lead exposure in our food or anywhere. However, lead –– even in small doses –– can have health impacts, Stoiber said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmh5bzrgp000j3b6nr1jnv2tk@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            For children, the concern is particularly great because their smaller bodies and metabolisms put them at a greater vulnerability for harms caused by exposure, according to the &lt;a href="https://www.fda.gov/food/environmental-contaminants-food/closer-zero-reducing-childhood-exposure-contaminants-foods" target="_blank"&gt;FDA.&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmh5bzrgp000k3b6nv1e5nozb@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The federal agency has been working to reduce dietary exposure to contaminants for children to as close to zero as possible. And no safe level of exposure to lead has been identified, according to the &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/lead-prevention/php/news-features/updates-blood-lead-reference-value.html" target="_blank"&gt;US Centers for Disease Control and Prevention.&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmh5bzrgp000l3b6n5gngssut@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            However, the &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/35690180/" target="_blank"&gt;FDA does use a benchmark&lt;/a&gt; of 2.2 micrograms per day of dietary lead exposure for children and 8.8 micrograms per day for women of childbearing age. Experts use those numbers to evaluate when an exposure is potentially a concern and a product needs to be alerted.&lt;s&gt;&lt;/s&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;

  

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmh5bzrgp000m3b6n3y4xir9h@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The guidelines on dietary lead exposure are hard to translate into practical use at home, and you likely won’t know exactly how much is in the food you are eating, Stoiber said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmh5bzrgp000n3b6n1dagwvtp@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            She recommends looking into brands that regularly test their food products for lead levels. And your best defense against lead –– and any other toxin –– is a diverse, nutritionally dense diet, Zagorski said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmh5bzrgp000o3b6n11bexvtw@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Eating a variety of foods can help in two ways. First, it reduces the likelihood that you are eating too much of one food that may be more likely to contain lead.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmh5bzrgp000p3b6nme5lm7c1@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            For example, earlier this year &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2025/01/09/health/protein-powder-heavy-metals-wellness"&gt;a report found lead&lt;/a&gt; in protein powders. Occasional use of those protein powders isn’t as concerning as a person making protein shakes three times a day.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmh5bzrgp000q3b6ntflm3vsk@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “Protein powder is intended to be a supplement and not a diet,” Zagorski said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmh5bzrgp000r3b6nelkccouc@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Second, a nutrient-dense and varied diet also can help with your body’s natural defenses against unwanted elements, he added. Your body prefers absorbing iron over lead — so if you have enough iron in your diet, your digestive system is more likely to let the lead pass through, he said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmh5bzrgp000s3b6nab5v9hbp@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “The dose makes the poison,” Zagorski said. “Your body is very good at taking care of itself and getting rid of toxins, so (make) sure that we are giving it the tools it needs and not overconsuming one thing.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

  
&lt;p data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/editor-note/instances/cmh5ggc7y00043b6n9c6k07n9@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="editor-note" class="editor-note-elevate vossi-editor-note_elevate inline-placeholder " data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
    Sign up for &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/newsletters/eat-but-better?source=nl-acq_article"&gt;CNN’s Eat, But Better: Mediterranean Style&lt;/a&gt;. Our eight-part guide shows you a delicious expert-backed eating lifestyle that will boost your health for life.
&lt;/p&gt;

              &lt;/div&gt;
                  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>CNN</author><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 13:00:01 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMia0FVX3lxTFB4ekxncU5ESGZBNWMtaXY2eHlVSXo4S0lSTjliV1lfLXhQVlE2anpXUTV4OFZDYlF1NUtfVXE1Nk5ldVFoTzVROW9YdHJwN0c2YU9yaUNQSkN6NGFyN2tfT3Rtc3NOdlpmaHU0</guid></item><item><title>COVID-19 mRNA疫苗可以触发免疫系统识别和杀死癌症，研究发现- Live Science</title><link>https://www.livescience.com/health/cancer/covid-19-mrna-vaccines-can-trigger-the-immune-system-to-recognize-and-kill-cancer-research-finds</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="article-body" class="text-copy bodyCopy auto paywall-locker"&gt;
&lt;p id="d5d2ee61-1cea-4820-a582-d16bffa5f21f"&gt;The &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.livescience.com/health/viruses-infections-disease/coronavirus" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.livescience.com/health/viruses-infections-disease/coronavirus"&gt;&lt;u&gt;COVID-19&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; mRNA-based vaccines that &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://doi.org/10.1001/jamahealthforum.2025.2223" target="_blank" data-url="https://doi.org/10.1001/jamahealthforum.2025.2223" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;saved 2.5 million lives globally&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; during the &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.livescience.com/tag/pandemic" data-auto-tag-linker="true" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.livescience.com/tag/pandemic"&gt;pandemic&lt;/a&gt; could help spark the immune system to fight &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.livescience.com/health/viruses-infections-disease/cancer" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.livescience.com/health/viruses-infections-disease/cancer"&gt;&lt;u&gt;cancer&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. This is the surprising takeaway of a new study that &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://doi.org/10.1038/s41586-025-09655-y" target="_blank" data-url="https://doi.org/10.1038/s41586-025-09655-y" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;we and our colleagues published in the journal Nature&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="ad-unit-1" class="ad-unit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While developing &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.livescience.com/health/medicine-drugs/what-are-mrna-vaccines-and-how-do-they-work" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.livescience.com/health/medicine-drugs/what-are-mrna-vaccines-and-how-do-they-work"&gt;&lt;u&gt;mRNA vaccines&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; for patients with brain tumors in 2016, our team, led by &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://directory.ufhealth.org/sayour-elias" target="_blank" data-url="https://directory.ufhealth.org/sayour-elias" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;pediatric oncologist Elias Sayour&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, discovered that mRNA can train immune systems to kill tumors — &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://doi.org/10.1038/s41551-025-01380-1" target="_blank" data-url="https://doi.org/10.1038/s41551-025-01380-1" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;even if the mRNA is not related to cancer&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a id="elk-seasonal" href="" data-url="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p id="d5d2ee61-1cea-4820-a582-d16bffa5f21f-2" class="paywall" aria-hidden="true"&gt;Based on this finding, we hypothesized that mRNA vaccines designed to target the SARS-CoV-2 virus that causes COVID-19 might also have antitumor effects.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="mid-article-leaderboard" class="ad-unit sm:hidden block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="110b7ed4-d6e7-4d6b-a874-7a23d84905ac"&gt;So &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://scholar.google.com/citations?user=AqVdPM4AAAAJ&amp;amp;hl=en" target="_blank" data-url="https://scholar.google.com/citations?user=AqVdPM4AAAAJ&amp;amp;hl=en" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;we looked at clinical outcomes&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; for more than 1,000 late-stage melanoma and lung cancer patients treated with a type of immunotherapy called &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.cell.2023.03.006" target="_blank" data-url="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.cell.2023.03.006" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;immune checkpoint inhibitors&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. This treatment is a common approach doctors use to train the immune system to kill cancer. It does this by blocking a protein that tumor cells make to turn off immune cells, enabling the immune system to continue killing cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="ad-unit-2" class="ad-unit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Remarkably, patients who received either the Pfizer or Moderna mRNA-based COVID-19 vaccine within 100 days of starting immunotherapy were more than twice as likely to be alive after three years compared with those who didn't receive either vaccine. Surprisingly, patients with tumors that don't typically respond well to immunotherapy also saw very strong benefits, with nearly fivefold improvement in three-year overall survival. This link between improved survival and receiving a COVID-19 mRNA vaccine remained strong even after we controlled for factors like disease severity and co-occurring conditions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To understand the underlying mechanism, &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://scholar.google.com/citations?user=E2q2tK8AAAAJ&amp;amp;hl=en" target="_blank" data-url="https://scholar.google.com/citations?user=E2q2tK8AAAAJ&amp;amp;hl=en" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;we turned to animal models&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. We found that COVID-19 mRNA vaccines act like an alarm, triggering the body's immune system to recognize and kill tumor cells and overcome the cancer's ability to turn off immune cells. When combined, vaccines and immune checkpoint inhibitors coordinate to unleash the full power of the immune system to kill cancer cells.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="youtube-video youtube-facade" data-nosnippet="" id="_D_Iz9s9Y6k"&gt;
&lt;div class="video-aspect-box"&gt;
&lt;div class="watch-on-iframe-_D_Iz9s9Y6k" data-yt-video-token="_D_Iz9s9Y6k" title="COVID-19 mRNA vaccine sparks immune response to fight cancer, study finds - YouTube"&gt;
&lt;span class="youtube-video-title"&gt;COVID-19 mRNA vaccine sparks immune response to fight cancer, study finds - YouTube&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;img src="https://img.youtube.com/vi/_D_Iz9s9Y6k/maxresdefault.jpg" alt="COVID-19 mRNA vaccine sparks immune response to fight cancer, study finds - YouTube" data-aspect-ratio="16/9" loading="lazy"&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;svg class="play-button" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 234.67 165.33"&gt;&lt;path fill="red" d="M229.763 25.817c-2.699-10.162-10.65-18.165-20.748-20.881C190.716 0 117.333 0 117.333 0S43.951 0 25.651 4.936C15.553 7.652 7.6 15.655 4.903 25.817 0 44.236 0 82.667 0 82.667s0 38.429 4.903 56.85C7.6 149.68 15.553 157.681 25.65 160.4c18.3 4.934 91.682 4.934 91.682 4.934s73.383 0 91.682-4.934c10.098-2.718 18.049-10.72 20.748-20.882 4.904-18.421 4.904-56.85 4.904-56.85s0-38.431-4.904-56.85"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path fill="#fff" d="m93.333 117.559 61.333-34.89-61.333-34.894z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;
&lt;a class="watch-on-youtube-_D_Iz9s9Y6k" href="https://youtu.be/_D_Iz9s9Y6k" target="_blank" data-url="https://youtu.be/_D_Iz9s9Y6k" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;Watch On &lt;svg class="youtube-logo" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 507.9 113.39"&gt;&lt;g fill="#fff"&gt;&lt;path d="M64.792 80.99V32.396l42.082 24.297zm93.803-63.285a20.285 20.285 0 0 0-14.32-14.32C131.642 0 80.99 0 80.99 0S30.337 0 17.705 3.385a20.286 20.286 0 0 0-14.32 14.32C0 30.338 0 56.693 0 56.693S0 83.049 3.385 95.68A20.285 20.285 0 0 0 17.705 110c12.632 3.386 63.285 3.386 63.285 3.386s50.652 0 63.285-3.386a20.284 20.284 0 0 0 14.32-14.32c3.385-12.632 3.385-38.988 3.385-38.988s0-26.355-3.385-38.988m94.473 74.326c.887-2.314 1.332-6.098 1.332-11.35V58.556c0-5.097-.445-8.822-1.332-11.178-.888-2.355-2.452-3.533-4.69-3.533-2.163 0-3.69 1.178-4.577 3.533-.888 2.356-1.332 6.081-1.332 11.178V80.68c0 5.25.424 9.035 1.275 11.35.848 2.318 2.392 3.475 4.633 3.475 2.239 0 3.803-1.157 4.691-3.475zm-17.953 11.122c-3.207-2.16-5.486-5.52-6.835-10.079-1.352-4.554-2.027-10.617-2.027-18.185v-10.31c0-7.644.771-13.784 2.316-18.417 1.544-4.633 3.956-8.011 7.24-10.135 3.282-2.123 7.587-3.186 12.916-3.186 5.251 0 9.459 1.082 12.626 3.243 3.165 2.162 5.482 5.542 6.95 10.136 1.466 4.595 2.2 10.715 2.2 18.36v10.31c0 7.567-.714 13.65-2.142 18.243-1.43 4.595-3.747 7.955-6.951 10.077-3.205 2.124-7.548 3.186-13.03 3.186-5.64 0-10.06-1.082-13.263-3.243m248.053-57.981c-.81 1.005-1.352 2.646-1.621 4.923-.272 2.278-.404 5.734-.404 10.367v5.097h11.697V60.46c0-4.555-.155-8.011-.463-10.367-.309-2.355-.868-4.014-1.678-4.98-.812-.966-2.067-1.449-3.766-1.449-1.7 0-2.954.503-3.765 1.506zm-2.025 29.886v3.591c0 4.557.132 7.974.404 10.251.269 2.279.828 3.94 1.68 4.982.849 1.041 2.16 1.564 3.938 1.564 2.392 0 4.035-.927 4.923-2.781.887-1.853 1.37-4.942 1.447-9.268l13.785.812c.077.62.116 1.469.116 2.548 0 6.565-1.795 11.47-5.387 14.712-3.589 3.242-8.669 4.865-15.232 4.865-7.876 0-13.398-2.47-16.564-7.414-3.168-4.94-4.75-12.586-4.75-22.935V63.589c0-10.657 1.641-18.436 4.924-23.342 3.281-4.903 8.9-7.355 16.854-7.355 5.482 0 9.691 1.004 12.626 3.012 2.933 2.01 5 5.137 6.197 9.383 1.197 4.247 1.796 10.117 1.796 17.607v12.163h-26.757m-284.953-1.33-18.187-65.68h15.869l6.37 29.77c1.623 7.339 2.82 13.594 3.591 18.766h.464c.54-3.706 1.738-9.922 3.591-18.65l6.603-29.886h15.869l-18.417 65.68v31.51h-15.754v-31.51M322.115 34.23v71.007h-12.511l-1.39-8.688h-.347c-3.399 6.564-8.496 9.845-15.291 9.845-4.71 0-8.185-1.543-10.425-4.633-2.24-3.087-3.359-7.915-3.359-14.48V34.23h15.985v52.126c0 3.168.348 5.426 1.043 6.776.695 1.353 1.853 2.027 3.475 2.027 1.39 0 2.722-.423 3.996-1.275 1.274-.849 2.22-1.928 2.838-3.241V34.229h15.986m81.995.001v71.007h-12.511l-1.391-8.688h-.345c-3.402 6.564-8.498 9.845-15.292 9.845-4.711 0-8.186-1.543-10.426-4.633-2.24-3.087-3.358-7.915-3.358-14.48V34.23h15.985v52.126c0 3.168.347 5.426 1.041 6.776.696 1.353 1.855 2.027 3.476 2.027 1.391 0 2.723-.423 3.996-1.275 1.275-.849 2.22-1.928 2.839-3.241V34.229h15.985"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="M365.552 20.908h-15.87v84.329h-15.637v-84.33h-15.869V8.05h47.376v12.858m76.811 53.636c0 5.174-.215 9.229-.639 12.162-.424 2.937-1.139 5.021-2.143 6.255-1.004 1.236-2.357 1.854-4.053 1.854a7.404 7.404 0 0 1-3.65-.927c-1.12-.618-2.026-1.544-2.722-2.78V50.796c.54-1.93 1.467-3.513 2.78-4.749 1.313-1.234 2.74-1.853 4.285-1.853 1.623 0 2.876.637 3.766 1.91.886 1.275 1.505 3.418 1.853 6.43.348 3.011.523 7.297.523 12.857zm14.652-28.964c-.967-4.478-2.531-7.721-4.692-9.73-2.163-2.007-5.136-3.011-8.919-3.011-2.935 0-5.676.83-8.224 2.49a16.926 16.926 0 0 0-5.908 6.545h-.117l.001-37.416h-15.405v100.777h13.204l1.622-6.717h.347c1.235 2.393 3.088 4.285 5.56 5.675 2.47 1.39 5.213 2.085 8.225 2.085 5.404 0 9.382-2.491 11.931-7.471 2.548-4.982 3.823-12.76 3.823-23.341V64.23c0-7.953-.484-14.17-1.448-18.65"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/g&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;a id="elk-f81a0f95-4252-41bd-b055-18efdd53e6e2" class="paywall" aria-hidden="true" href="" data-url="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;h2 id="why-it-matters-3"&gt;Why it matters&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="9126cac2-27e6-4442-a69c-7c673f20ee40"&gt;Immunotherapy with immune checkpoint inhibitors has &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.cell.2023.03.006" target="_blank" data-url="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.cell.2023.03.006" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;revolutionized cancer treatment&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; over the past decade by producing cures in many patients who were previously considered incurable. However, these therapies are ineffective in patients with &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.cancer.gov/publications/dictionaries/cancer-terms/def/cold-tumor" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.cancer.gov/publications/dictionaries/cancer-terms/def/cold-tumor" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;"cold" tumors&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; that successfully evade immune detection.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div id="slice-container-newsletterForm-articleInbodyContent-UkaQPY7j3SYFwCapiP6V3Q" class="slice-container newsletter-inbodyContent-slice newsletterForm-articleInbodyContent-UkaQPY7j3SYFwCapiP6V3Q slice-container-newsletterForm"&gt;&lt;div data-hydrate="true" class="newsletter-form__wrapper newsletter-form__wrapper--inbodyContent"&gt;&lt;div class="newsletter-form__container"&gt;&lt;section class="newsletter-form__main-section"&gt;&lt;p class="newsletter-form__strapline"&gt;Get the world’s most fascinating discoveries delivered straight to your inbox.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Our findings suggest that mRNA vaccines may provide just the spark the immune system needs to turn these "cold" tumors "hot." If validated in our upcoming clinical trial, our hope is that this widely available, low-cost intervention could extend the benefits of immunotherapy to millions of patients who otherwise would not benefit from this therapy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a id="elk-13185a60-4cd5-49ca-89db-46af8135339a" class="paywall" aria-hidden="true" href="" data-url="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;h2 id="what-other-research-is-being-done-3"&gt;What other research is being done&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="d3879fbc-7791-438b-9a65-91492b549592"&gt;Unlike vaccines for infectious diseases, which are used to prevent an infection, &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://theconversation.com/modernas-experimental-cancer-vaccine-treats-but-doesnt-prevent-melanoma-a-biochemist-explains-how-it-works-197003" target="_blank" data-url="https://theconversation.com/modernas-experimental-cancer-vaccine-treats-but-doesnt-prevent-melanoma-a-biochemist-explains-how-it-works-197003" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;therapeutic cancer vaccines&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; are used to help train the immune systems of cancer patients to better fight tumors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We and many others are &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://theconversation.com/modernas-experimental-cancer-vaccine-treats-but-doesnt-prevent-melanoma-a-biochemist-explains-how-it-works-197003" target="_blank" data-url="https://theconversation.com/modernas-experimental-cancer-vaccine-treats-but-doesnt-prevent-melanoma-a-biochemist-explains-how-it-works-197003" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;currently working hard&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; to make &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://theconversation.com/customizing-mrna-is-easy-and-thats-what-makes-it-the-next-frontier-for-personalized-medicine-a-molecular-biologist-explains-216127" target="_blank" data-url="https://theconversation.com/customizing-mrna-is-easy-and-thats-what-makes-it-the-next-frontier-for-personalized-medicine-a-molecular-biologist-explains-216127" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;personalized mRNA vaccines&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; for &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://theconversation.com/brain-cancer-in-children-is-notoriously-hard-to-treat-a-new-mrna-cancer-vaccine-triggers-an-attack-from-within-228666" target="_blank" data-url="https://theconversation.com/brain-cancer-in-children-is-notoriously-hard-to-treat-a-new-mrna-cancer-vaccine-triggers-an-attack-from-within-228666" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;patients with cancer&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. This involves taking a small sample of a patient's tumor and using machine learning algorithms to predict which proteins in the tumor would be the &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://doi.org/10.1038/s41392-022-01270-x" target="_blank" data-url="https://doi.org/10.1038/s41392-022-01270-x" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;best targets for a vaccine&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. However, this approach can be &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://doi.org/10.1038/s41392-023-01674-3" target="_blank" data-url="https://doi.org/10.1038/s41392-023-01674-3" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;costly and difficult to manufacture&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In contrast, COVID-19 mRNA vaccines do not need to be personalized, are already widely available at low or no cost around the globe, and could be administered at any time during a patient's treatment. Our findings that &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://doi.org/10.1038/s41586-025-09655-y" target="_blank" data-url="https://doi.org/10.1038/s41586-025-09655-y" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;COVID-19 mRNA vaccines have substantial antitumor effects&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; bring hope that they could help extend the anti-cancer benefits of mRNA vaccines to all.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a id="elk-0360b2b0-5aa7-4d73-a110-c8a0c9134676" class="paywall" aria-hidden="true" href="" data-url="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;h2 id="what-s-next-3"&gt;What's next&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="cabb8cd4-853e-4687-98b2-c182965eefd3"&gt;In pursuit of this goal, we are preparing to test this treatment strategy in patients with a nationwide clinical trial in people with lung cancer. People receiving an immune checkpoint inhibitor will be randomized to either receive a COVID-19 mRNA vaccine during treatment or not.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="03558f35-9487-44d0-904f-6a34a842406c"&gt;This study will tell us whether COVID-19 mRNA vaccines should be included as part of the standard of care for patients receiving an immune checkpoint inhibitor. Ultimately, we hope that this approach will help many patients who are treated with immune therapy, and especially those who currently lack effective treatment options.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This work exemplifies how a tool born from a global pandemic may provide a new weapon against cancer and rapidly extend the benefits of existing treatments to millions of patients. By harnessing a familiar vaccine in a new way, we hope to extend the lifesaving benefits of immunotherapy to cancer patients who were previously left behind.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This edited article is republished from &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="http://theconversation.com/" target="_blank" data-url="http://theconversation.com/" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Conversation&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt; under a Creative Commons license. Read the &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://theconversation.com/covid-19-mrna-vaccines-could-unlock-the-next-revolution-in-cancer-treatment-new-research-258992" target="_blank" data-url="https://theconversation.com/covid-19-mrna-vaccines-could-unlock-the-next-revolution-in-cancer-treatment-new-research-258992" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;em&gt;original article&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a id="elk-b04dac75-7394-41a8-89a6-76ad4bd94625" class="paywall" aria-hidden="true" href="" data-url="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Live Science</author><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi1AFBVV95cUxOZGpyLVBmTVhkLUZSQXV1Zk15R0psNVlXTzBaaHhkWHNmTVZUVmVKTnVXcjUtTWg4YjZISWh0bUc5QXg0WkxVTjZWWmF2bzJRdUhLLUxUc0kwYlctZk15Y3FHckdHQ0tCYW9xbW9OTVNzOTI4bkpkbWdPcHBMZWRVaDRPWU5lbmJyRUVsd2JVRkotc056dC1GbWxnX3g2dkw0YzIzaXpvZjJjWTR5OVBPa0hxNFpHV3dWLS16R1RDcmNqZzlsZzZNbVdHNEJmbDI4SHlGbw</guid></item><item><title>随着癌症在年轻人中上升，专家解释了如何降低风险-《华盛顿邮报》</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/health/2025/10/25/young-cancer-risk-breast-colorectal/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="topper-text-elems" class="wpds-c-kebnqj wpds-c-kebnqj-iPJLV-css"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="article-topper" class="wpds-c-cBzrLX wpds-c-cBzrLX-cmVlgk-isCenterNS-false wpds-c-cBzrLX-iyHTpF-useUATStyles-true wpds-c-cBzrLX-ieuxqEo-css"&gt;&lt;h1 id="main-content" data-qa="headline" data-testid="headline" class="wpds-c-eRlesA wpds-c-eRlesA-dHdMuz-isOnSplitTopper-false wpds-c-eRlesA-bAbYzz-isStyle-false wpds-c-eRlesA-iPJLV-css"&gt;As cancer rises among young adults, experts explain how to lower risk&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;p data-qa="subheadline" data-testid="subheadline" class="wpds-c-ckOSsQ wpds-c-ckOSsQ-iPJLV-css"&gt;Not only are more young people being diagnosed with breast and colorectal cancer, but the diseases are leading to more deaths. Here’s what you can actually do about it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-testid="timestamp" class="wpds-c-bEimne wpds-c-bEimne-dyECYW-theme-default"&gt;&lt;time datetime="2025-10-25T09:00:00.000Z" class="wpds-c-gRBhEF wpds-c-gRBhEF-idbzzBd-css overrideStyles"&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-eUMOSL"&gt;&lt;span data-testid="published-date" class="wpds-c-bASIGw wpds-c-bASIGw-ilmVsQY-css overrideStyles"&gt;October 25, 2025 at 5:00 a.m. EDT&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-testid="relative-date" class="wpds-c-bASIGw wpds-c-bASIGw-idUCtvg-css overrideStyles"&gt;Today at 5:00 a.m. EDT&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 12:01:48 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijgFBVV95cUxNLUtNVmpYN3dOVEdiTnpXaWhtQnpCVkNDTlZWZUlrbEhhbG93ZW0ySk1TcUU3REpmanhQWmc5Znh0eXNURWMxUlN6TDRsOWUybTgwMGRLS0RRbWNFMFB0NFJWMnhTU0NmR3BkUlNCZnFSandiZVFOWjdtVVVOWVlSVngzMGFWRnUwSVhvVGhR</guid></item><item><title>我们每周在父母家见面，共进家庭晚餐。但我妈妈拒绝遵守我对家人的简单规则。-石板</title><link>https://slate.com/advice/2025/10/parent-advice-family-dinners-rules.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article__content" itemprop="mainEntityOfPage"&gt;
          &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="16" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmh5q2fpj0051fgm6kx8q7kd9@published"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Care and Feeding is Slate’s parenting advice column. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Have a question for Care and Feeding? &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://forms.gle/4BXEw8Wtcd7aAyXh9"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Submit it here&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="4" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmh5qa61b001l3b79whcwyquy@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dear Care and Feeding,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="26" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmh5qa2nj00173b79bh3kenil@published"&gt;My parents are in their 70s and live around the corner. About once a week, we go to my parents’ house for family time and dinner.&lt;/p&gt;



  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="56" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmh5qjqh100333b79c509rvqg@published"&gt;My daughter is almost 2 and has a pretty strict bedtime; it becomes more difficult to get her to sleep if she goes past it. Here’s the problem: No matter how hard I try, I can’t get my mom to get dinner on the table early enough for us to get home in time for bedtime!&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="100" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmh5segc000053b79lut1mtw2@published"&gt;I try to help her plan and make dinner, but even then, she’ll get out the ingredients and just wait before she starts cooking. She works full-time and has always been bad at coming home on time, so getting the whole evening together to start sooner is not possible. She blames &lt;em&gt;me&lt;/em&gt; for not adjusting our schedule (i.e., not letting our daughter stay up later “just” one night a week or so). She has now declared that we just can’t come over for dinner anymore, which is sad to me. Do you have a recommendation for solving this frustrating problem?&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="3" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmh5qa2rt00193b79h262jyfw@published"&gt;—Routines Are Important!&lt;/p&gt;

  

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="2" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmh5qa2tj001a3b79bb9tsav3@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dear Routines,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="96" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmh5qa2vv001b3b79qmjw167n@published"&gt;I sympathize (very much) with your desire to keep your toddler’s bedtime at an hour that works best for getting her to go to sleep. (Indeed, I’m delighted for you that you have found the magic bullet for a stress-free bedtime! May it ever be so.) What you cannot do is make others, even your own mother, adhere to your schedule. This is unreasonable. (Yes, you are her daughter; you are also a guest in her house when you go over for dinner. Dinner guests do not get to dictate the time dinner will be served.)&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="75" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmh5qa2xx001c3b79ze45d454@published"&gt;But your mother, too, is being unreasonable if she demands that you push back her granddaughter’s bedtime for her sake (thus making &lt;em&gt;your&lt;/em&gt; life more difficult). My generous interpretation of her putting off the start of cooking is that she doesn’t want to miss that “family time” that occurs before dinner. Still: Why invite you to dinner, knowing that she won’t get said dinner on the table until an hour that’s too late for you?&lt;/p&gt;

  


  


  


  


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="78" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmh5qa30c001d3b79t5aa28ov@published"&gt;All of the above is why I am 99 percent certain this conflict isn’t actually about dinner, but about 1) who’s in charge;  2) your mother’s disapproval—I’m just guessing, but I’ll eat my hat if I’m wrong—of your adherence to a strict routine for your child; and 3) your wanting her to prove that she trusts and supports you in your role as a parent. (And probably some other stuff I don’t have enough information to guess at.)&lt;/p&gt;

  

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="161" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmh5qa32e001e3b79xfac05yy@published"&gt;In any case, when it comes to the particular concrete issue you’re dealing with (if not the sources of it, which I recommend also dealing with, forthrightly), you have three choices, as I see it: You can invite your parents to your house for dinner once a week, making and serving the meal on your schedule; you can propose to your mother that instead of her cooking for your family once a week, she allow you to bring a meal—either home-cooked or picked up from a restaurant—over to her house, and that she further allow &lt;em&gt;you&lt;/em&gt; to serve it, so that dinner will be had on time; or you can dispense with a weekly extended family dinner altogether and instead invite your parents to join you for another activity once a week or so, perhaps during the day on the weekend, at a time that is convenient for you and works with your daughter’s (also pretty strict, I imagine?) nap schedule.&lt;/p&gt;

  


  


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="73" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmh5qa349001f3b79xalln1yy@published"&gt;You might even give your mom the choice between the three options—or mix it up a bit and rotate among the three, week to week, depending on what works for all concerned. This would require both you and your mom to be more flexible than either of you has so far been inclined to be—but perhaps this would be a good thing for all of you (including, in the long term, your daughter).&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="1" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmh5qcqll001r3b796qtwzci0@published"&gt;&lt;span class="slate-paragraph--tombstone"&gt;—Michelle&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;h3 class="subhead subhead--none" data-uri="slate.com/_components/subhead/instances/cmh5qd0jw002a3b79rpe6qsml@published"&gt;
&lt;p class="subhead__marker"&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
More Advice From Slate

&lt;/h3&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="68" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmh5qcy4v00233b79pr0lfppt@published"&gt;How do teachers really feel about kids missing school for a vacation? My kids range in age from upper elementary school to middle school. For years, I’ve watched families visit Disney World in the dead of winter to beat the long lines, or take advantage of lower airfare during nonpeak travel periods to head off somewhere warm. I’m envious. &lt;a href="https://slate.com/human-interest/2018/11/ask-teacher-vacation-absence.html"&gt;I’m a rule-follower and feel like school is school…&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;section class="newsletter-signup   " data-list="Advice" data-uri="slate.com/_components/newsletter-signup/instances/cmh5q2fpj0054fgm6xtkpgysi@published"&gt;


    &lt;p class="newsletter-signup__intro"&gt;
        &lt;svg class="newsletter-signup__arrow"&gt;
          &lt;use xlink:href="/media/components/newsletter-signup/sprite.svg#arrow"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;
        &lt;/svg&gt;
&lt;h1 class="newsletter-signup__headline"&gt;Never miss new Slate Advice columns&lt;/h1&gt;
      &lt;span class="newsletter-signup__description"&gt;Get the latest from Prudie and our columnists in your inbox each weekday, plus special bonus letters on Saturdays.&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;
    



&lt;/section&gt;

  

&lt;/div&gt;

      &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Slate</author><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMifEFVX3lxTFBWaHpyNWJ5X1lKQ3RpSkdrRGdrWElTZTROWlp3bWpjckNYVHVBVXcxd1QycXpZZUU1cURWcGl5VUthbTRJVTg5c2FaU1M2X1JVUUpvVDRzY19MYk5jVU9aYkptREo5eTdETHM3MTRIYW55VUhWMlQyaDg0blg</guid></item><item><title>一名男子在埃尔克哈特县（ Elkhart County ）的树上猛烈撞击后受伤- WSBT</title><link>https://wsbt.com/news/local/crash-accident-man-injured-tree-hit-fire-flames-smoke-police-investigation-ambulance-hospital-injuries-county-road-15-40-elkhart-indiana</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="StoryText_storyText__C3hWI StoryText_storyText__C3hWI"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="dateline"&gt;ELKHART COUNTY, Ind. (WSBT) — &lt;/span&gt;A man was taken to the hospital early Saturday morning after a fiery crash in Elkhart County.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It happened just after 12:45 a.m. on County Road 15, north of County Road 40.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="ImageEmbed_imageEmbed__5mYLo"&gt;&lt;img alt="A man was sent to the hospital after he hit a tree early Saturday morning on County Road 15 (WSBT 22)" class="ImageEmbed_image__qZBo_" src="/resources/media2/16x9/1280/986/center/90/ff7f381c-ecbb-4d62-845c-01036db7bff3-elkhartcountycrash.png"&gt;&lt;p class="ImageEmbed_caption__gAtoE"&gt;A man was sent to the hospital after he hit a tree early Saturday morning on County Road 15 (WSBT 22)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Police say a 25-year-old Nappanee man was heading south on County Road 15 when he drove off the road and hit a tree.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;His vehicle then burst into flames.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He was taken to the hospital for his injuries. His condition is not known at this time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;An investigation is underway.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>WSBT</author><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 11:39:50 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi9wFBVV95cUxOOXo0T2JRNVI3SzZwZmhNb0Z6ZnFlRGdTbkRGMFVweFJDdXg5LWRPakFVemJYUVhsT3JWeVVBLTBfRDNhTldzXzNTWDJiYlI0elVJZkpaeFJTU2VvWk45czhtZWoxbXEtTVgzczhVME5YaEpGSjk5VGVjRmY2VF9McTloRGVwYUFjTnVwZ1ZtVUpPLU81ZFJ1OXNENnlONTQ0anlrMnZfUEpERVg0QjBWTjRzaXRhTFEzb2haTWxfUzZpN1lnSmxabHFGUWFQYmpyU09YZjBNZlh1bTN2aUxnLWxRcXU2RGZfQjVua1Zad0QzNWVWdXNv</guid></item><item><title>研究发现更年期会导致可能影响记忆、情绪的大脑变化- MedicalNewsToday</title><link>https://www.medicalnewstoday.com/articles/study-menopause-structure-brain-changes-affect-memory-mood-thinking</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div data-testid="tabbed-article-section" class="css-12va8w7"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;figure class="css-yhe8zq"&gt;&lt;span class="css-rwmw5v"&gt;&lt;span class="css-mjp0j9"&gt;&lt;picture class="css-16pk1is"&gt;&lt;source srcset="https://media.post.rvohealth.io/wp-content/uploads/sites/3/2025/10/rainbow-womans-face-1296x728-header-1024x575.jpg 750w" media="(min-width: 1190px)"&gt;&lt;/source&gt;&lt;source srcset="https://media.post.rvohealth.io/wp-content/uploads/sites/3/2025/10/rainbow-womans-face-1296x728-header-1024x575.jpg 750w" media="(min-width: 990px)"&gt;&lt;/source&gt;&lt;source srcset="https://media.post.rvohealth.io/wp-content/uploads/sites/3/2025/10/rainbow-womans-face-1296x728-header-1024x575.jpg 879w" media="(min-width: 768px)"&gt;&lt;/source&gt;&lt;img loading="eager" src="https://media.post.rvohealth.io/wp-content/uploads/sites/3/2025/10/rainbow-womans-face-1296x728-header-1024x575.jpg" alt="A prism of light and rainbow colours shine on a woman's face wearing glasses" class="css-1jytyml"&gt;&lt;/picture&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;hl-share-overlay class="css-1mqo1cs"&gt;&lt;a class="icon-hl-pinterest css-11oz8gb" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer nofollow" data-event="Any Page|Image Pinterest Click|Icon Clicked" data-element-event="OPEN|CONTENTBLOCK|Any Page|Article Body|BUTTON|Image Widget Pinterest Click|" href="https://www.pinterest.com/pin/create/button/?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.medicalnewstoday.com%2Farticles%2Fstudy-menopause-structure-brain-changes-affect-memory-mood-thinking&amp;amp;media=https%3A%2F%2Fmedia.post.rvohealth.io%2Fwp-content%2Fuploads%2Fsites%2F3%2F2025%2F10%2Frainbow-womans-face-1296x728-header-1024x575.jpg&amp;amp;description=Menopause%3A%20Study%20finds%20structural%20brain%20changes%20during%20transition" title="Share on Pinterest" data-pin-custom="true" data-share-url="https://media.post.rvohealth.io/wp-content/uploads/sites/3/2025/10/rainbow-womans-face-1296x728-header-1024x575.jpg"&gt;&lt;span class="css-z1zfa"&gt;Share on Pinterest&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/hl-share-overlay&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;figcaption class="css-13b3g0x"&gt;A new study aims to explain how menopause restructures the brain. Pawel Wewiorski/Getty Images&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A research team from Puerto Rico carried out a literature review to compile findings on how menopause may reshape the brain.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;They reviewed studies published from 2020 to 2025 to get a better understanding of neuroanatomical changes during menopause. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The researchers identified consistent patterns that may help explain the changes in thinking, mood, and overall health that often occur during the menopause transition.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;The menopause transition can be a difficult part of a person’s life. &lt;a href="https://menopause.org/patient-education/menopause-topics/hot-flashes" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;Hot flashes&lt;/a&gt; are a common symptom, but the effects of hormonal changes can run much more deeply and affect everyday life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;The research team of the new literature review, affiliated with BRAVE Lab at Ponce Health Sciences University, noted patterns in brain changes caused by hormones that may help explain many menopause-related symptoms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;The team will present their &lt;a href="https://dx.doi.org/10.1097/GME.0000000000000002541" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;findings&lt;/a&gt; at the 2025 Annual Meeting of The Menopause Society.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-testid="tabbed-article-section" class="css-1avyp1d"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Considering the impact menopause transition can have, especially throughout a decade or more of a woman’s life, the researchers of the new review wanted to review existing studies to see what links they could find between menopause and brain structure changes. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;To do this, they searched various databases for studies published within the past five years related to menopausal symptoms and brain structure. They focused on the most recent research and only included peer-reviewed studies in their review. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;After going through the studies, the researchers compiled the links they found between menopause and brain structure. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;One pattern the review noted was that gray matter volume in the brain decreased. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gray matter is &lt;hl-trusted-source source="PubMed Central" rationale="Highly respected database from the National Institutes of Health"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/books/NBK553239/#article-36416.s2" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;significant&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/hl-trusted-source&gt; in terms of day-to-day functioning, and a decrease in gray matter is associated with cognitive decline. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;While this may sound concerning, the researchers said some studies suggest that gray matter volume may partially recover in postmenopause. This indicates that the brain may adapt and reorganize itself over time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The research team also noticed a pattern in findings related to menopause and white matter hyperintensities. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;These spots can affect everyday thinking, memory, and mood, and may signal an increased vulnerability to certain neurological conditions over time. The hyperintensities were more pronounced in women who went through early menopause and who had &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC3185243/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;frequent vasomotor symptoms&lt;/a&gt; (also known as hot flashes and include night sweats).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Overall, the findings suggest menopause may lead to measurable changes in brain structure, which may impact memory, thinking, and mood.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="css-zya54r"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-testid="tabbed-article-section" class="css-1avyp1d"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.mayo.edu/research/faculty/faubion-stephanie-s-m-d-m-b-a/bio-20199366" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;Stephanie Faubion&lt;/a&gt;, MD, medical director for the Menopause Society, spoke with &lt;em&gt;Medical News Today&lt;/em&gt; about the review. She cautioned against becoming overly concerned about some of the links found between menopause and gray matter volume loss. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;“While we know that menopause is related to some structural brain changes, we don’t have a clear understanding of whether these structural changes cause functional changes or cognitive decline,” said Faubion. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Faubion added that women who experience forgetfulness or trouble concentrating during the menopause transition should not assume it signals something more serious. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Indeed, there is no evidence that symptoms of ‘brain fog’ during the menopause transition are associated with later risk of dementia, which is reassuring,” Faubion pointed out. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://cleopatrarx.com/rhonda-r-voskuhl/#:~:text=Voskuhl%20sees%20menopausal%20women%20with,Back%20To%20Team" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;Rhonda R. Voskuhl&lt;/a&gt;, MD, Professor of Neurology at UCLA and Inventor of CleopatraRX, also spoke with &lt;em&gt;MNT&lt;/em&gt; about the review and discussed the importance of hormone replacement therapy (HRT) during menopause.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;“Early treatment with estrogen for menopause is better than later treatment,” said Voskuhl. “Women are thought to become less responsive to estrogen treatment over the years.” &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Voskuhl also touched on long-term cognitive concerns for women who experience brain fog during menopause. She pointed out that “not all menopausal women get Alzheimer’s disease,” but it does &lt;a href="https://www.alz.org/alzheimers-dementia/facts-figures" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;affect women&lt;/a&gt; disproportionately. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Loss of neuroprotective estrogen during menopause may contribute to susceptibility to getting Alzheimer’s disease 10 to 20 years later,” commented Voskuhl. She said that this would have to be further studied, including treating menopausal women with HRT to determine whether a “cause and effect relationship” exists.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-testid="tabbed-article-section" class="css-1avyp1d"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;hl-trusted-source source="World Health Organization" rationale="Highly respected international organization"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.who.int/news-room/fact-sheets/detail/menopause" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;Menopause occurs&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/hl-trusted-source&gt; when an individual hasn’t had a period for one full year, a signal that the ovaries have stopped producing most of their estrogen and progesterone. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;The time leading up to menopause is called perimenopause, or the menopause transition, which can last for a decade or more. The average age of menopause is 51 to 52.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, some people may reach menopause earlier, and those who undergo treatment for certain cancers or have their ovaries removed will reach medical menopause without going through perimenopause.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;During this time, people experience physical and emotional changes resulting from shifting hormone levels. The symptoms of menopause can vary in intensity from mild to more disruptive.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.medicalnewstoday.com/articles/hot-flash-causes" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;hot flashes&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;night sweats&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;irregular or missed periods (before they stop completely)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;mood swings&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;fatigue and low energy &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another symptom that people report is brain fog or &lt;hl-trusted-source source="PubMed Central" rationale="Highly respected database from the National Institutes of Health"&gt;&lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/38888619/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;cognitive difficulties&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/hl-trusted-source&gt;. These cognitive changes may include difficulty remembering things and concentrating, which can lead to frustration, &lt;a href="https://www.medicalnewstoday.com/articles/323454" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;anxiety&lt;/a&gt;, and depressive feelings. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;There are some ways to &lt;hl-trusted-source source="Department of Health and Human Services" rationale="Governmental authority"&gt;&lt;a href="https://womenshealth.gov/menopause/menopause-treatment" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;treat&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/hl-trusted-source&gt; the symptoms caused by menopause. Doctors can prescribe &lt;a href="https://www.medicalnewstoday.com/articles/do-different-types-hormone-therapy-affect-memory-after-menopause" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;hormone therapy&lt;/a&gt;, which can provide some relief for hot flashes, night sweats, and vaginal dryness. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, not everyone is a candidate for hormone therapy during menopause. Each individual can discuss their options with a doctor.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="css-zya54r"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>MedicalNewsToday</author><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 11:37:30 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMirgFBVV95cUxOelNRSWFOMkRBZ3k3OV95V0l2dm93czdudUFkaWFGQ3BMWS1mQnUxTXlwZUxaaUExU1M2Q21nN054bExZdVZkRkpLQ2hNWFh5T3RkYjhMeHJHNFFWb0FHay1oUnBLbXFZVGRCMzlibWZFVUdITVR2cWtyYURENU0xMkN2ektBSjByY0JORFJCdk9FbjRVZk5YRng3REIzU1pPMEc3MGp1a05tTTFPUlE</guid></item><item><title>根据资深泌尿科医生的说法， 5种可能会“破坏”肾脏的早晨习惯-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/5-morning-habits-that-can-ruin-the-kidneys-according-to-senior-urologist/photostory/124803657.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="COQxt" data-ua-type="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Our kidneys are one of the most important organs of the body, that performs many key functions! Apart from filtering blood, kidneys also help in fluid elimination, and remove waste. Over time, our kidneys can grow weak, and suffer from impaired function. While diabetes, alcohol consumption, and obesity etc, are well-known causes of Chronic Kidney Disease (CKD), do you know that there are some morning habits, that too can ruin your kidneys? Dr. Venkatsubramaniam, a senior urologist in Chennai lists these 5 habits….&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 11:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi8AFBVV95cUxPMjNmdVN0UEh1dFZqMkI4REFBVVdEMkFwYUJRTUZIX1BNQW5vaTdrdmhZWDhwZWZrTmZuNDdKS0w2NGN0UHpTQmFwekg2VGg3SEZhaDFYb0RxOGFBYkoxVWVpQ25Zb1k4dkVuLUZGQ0dRQkQ0RG9WcjMyZ0ctbk9JV3FvVjR3ZVBtbC1uY3RzNEdtU19GX3dselN3Y1A3NzZtUzFDTUJ2Y1BiRmJERk1fdWhRbV93Q2VOLW1ZS2oxS01yV1MyLUhXUE93LVplLVRJQTFFYXVrR0hSQTM1MVlQU0t6MWoxY1pzZzdYS1JtR2bSAfgBQVVfeXFMUHE1eWVpcVhPblBEbjYxMDlfMUF2U0xCR3M2em9Cc3JiM1dzeEcyTEtwTXJpRzRvcU9GSkNGbFVHMGhNZ3pxQ2hfX3J0ekFiWVY0cW9CQkduaHNqNlVVaFJ3cFNJZWdqRW9rOHdPZjdHWWMwNlBOcHZtaFZseHNZTS1sZk84SnJLVldtQjZ3RVF4TkxVNTRiT1ExQ2JmWWNSbWhnZ3VhTXppT1d1VUQ5ekJQdUxTZG5DZml3aFlhaDdIYUhBY2ttdnpsM0ZVTHdIOHpLaF91LTRmMnpsNXo3VzJHclNIcDBSdWpqZTNKZUxZV1lDalVoUno</guid></item><item><title>应用程序使用人工智能来帮助患者记住预约信息- BBC</title><link>https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/cy0ydgd89ndo</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;An app designed to help people remember and summarise information from medical appointments using artificial intelligence (AI) has launched.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Created by Oxford-based company Aide Health, the Mirror app records appointments and gives a summary afterwards that the patient can refer back to and share with carers and family.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Creator Ian Wharton said the platform was a "really modern application of AI to solve a challenge that is this hidden risk in every healthcare consultation that we have".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;He said he came up with the idea to help his dad, who has early-stage Alzheimer's, to ensure he did not miss information from doctors appointments.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"It was the vast majority of information that was given to him that he just couldn't recall, and my biggest fear was not being by his bedside when he was told something important," he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"They're moments of quite often intense information, which are very very brief for you to digest often high-stakes news."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The Mirror app listens into medical appointments, and produces a detailed summary of what has been said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Janette Alfrey was one of the first people to use the platform, and said it left her "quite stunned".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"It had given me a heading as to why I was there, and then it had talked about what was about to happen and why they were doing it, and what was going to happen when they did the next operation," she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"When friends and colleagues phoned up over the next couple of days asking what was going to happen, I could just send them a screenshot of what I was told.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"It saved me having to go through everything again."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Mr Wharton said patients' data recorded by the app was "theirs, we don't do anything with it - we don't sell it, we don't give it to third parties".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;He said the current version, which can only be used during in-person consultations, was "just the beginning".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"Right now our app is passive - it listens and summarises for you - but in the future it will be your advocate, it will chirp, it will speak out it if it thinks there's something you should ask," he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"That's where this technology is going, and this is absolutely where we're going in how we manage our health."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BBC</author><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 06:51:26 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiWkFVX3lxTE1iYkQzbUhGdDFCLUxuXzJybTFLbElENFZOWDVWdVB6T1EwM3dMeW5DbUt6elZiWGhOTjZaU0ZISi0tZ0VDUnZGLXlEOWc2TU5tdXVmNVZocXNSUdIBX0FVX3lxTFA5b0V3Rk5hZlRxQ294X3BPcmVfdUtra1FDM1JqZ1NfOHp6U203anBqcEtyN2J1cXg2czBGMVRaUWRxQXlyclNaVGJ3WU9LUkRJZW10VnRCaGdrTWdwaDdj</guid></item><item><title>《耶路撒冷邮报》（ The Jerusalem Post ）为您提供保健指南</title><link>https://www.jpost.com/health-and-wellness/article-871519</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Jerusalem Post</author><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 06:44:36 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiZ0FVX3lxTE8xUTExakVWVXFrT0xubjgwOFB4Y05KMEFjcEZXbkRJSDRMYlpTWUtIMk9rai1ldFEwMEtFekk3NkhOQUhTckZIVnNjTmFFSjh4RmIxMUctalhsOWQwWWJhWExKVkM2dTg</guid></item><item><title>新一波具有健身意识的人们正在使用葡萄糖监测仪来获得关于健康的令人大开眼界的见解-《波士顿环球报》</title><link>https://www.bostonglobe.com/2025/10/25/lifestyle/glucose-monitor-mass-general-weight-loss-diabetes/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="body | gutter_16--desktop gutter_16--tablet paywalled_content
              "&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0 text_align_left"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;“I noticed spikes in my blood sugar cause crashes and really impacted my mood. It changed how I started my day, because what I eat at 11 a.m. affects how I feel at 7 p.m.,” said Berardi, 43. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0 text_align_left"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Continuous glucose monitors have become hugely popular and a billion-dollar business. While still a small percent of the overall market, the over-the-counter segment is nonetheless expected to grow to $2 billion by 2034, from $370 million in 2024, according to research firm  Global Market Insights. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0 text_align_left"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Brand leaders such as Stelo from Dexcom and Lingo from Abbott are sold over the counter for adults not using insulin for about $80 each, or less with subscriptions. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0 text_align_left"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Devices typically last about 2 weeks, and a subscription can cover replacements as well as access to data and other analysis through a mobile app. Costs vary depending on the length of the subscription; Abbott, for example, advertises a 12-week Lingo plan for $249&lt;b&gt;.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0 text_align_left"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;New brands targeting weight-loss monitors, such as Signos, offer promotions that include a subscription, two devices, and the mobile app for $130 a month. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0 text_align_left"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Yet despite their widespread use, researchers have only a limited understanding of how they might benefit people without diabetes. Proponents say the monitors can help people make healthier lifestyle choices. But some experts caution that without more thorough vetting, the data can be misinterpreted and should not be used as a replacement for the routine pre-diabetic screening doctors perform at annual exams. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0 text_align_left"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;A new study from researchers at Mass General Brigham suggests that the usefulness of continuous glucose monitors in tracking blood sugar varies depending on a person’s level of diabetes risk.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0 text_align_left"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;The team examined how a lab test, hemoglobin A1c, which measures average blood sugar over several months, compared with eight different measures from glucose monitors, which record blood sugar levels every 5 minutes. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0 text_align_left"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Researchers analyzed data from nearly 1,000&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;adults ages 40 or older, including those with and without diabetes. The data was provided by patients who wore the G6 monitor from Dexcom. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0 text_align_left"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Participants’ readings for type 2 diabetes closely matched their A1c test results. However, the correlation was weaker for people with prediabetes and those with normal blood sugar, even when researchers accounted for factors such as body mass index, according to the study.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0 text_align_left"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Dr. Jorge Rodriguez, a co-author of the study, hypothesized that in people without diabetes, short glucose spikes from meals don’t last long enough to affect the three-month averages of an A1c test. But among diabetics, glucose levels stay elevated longer, so data recorded by the monitors align better with A1c tests.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0 text_align_left"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;“As a physician, it is important to me to be able to advise all patients who may increasingly use these monitors,” said Rodriguez, an internal medicine hospitalist at Brigham and Women’s Hospital and assistant professor at Harvard Medical School. “In those without diabetes, [continuous glucose monitors] may be useful as behavioral ‘biofeedback’ tools that can provide insight into how food and activity impact real-time blood sugar levels, but they do not directly reflect longer-term blood sugar control.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0 text_align_left"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;The devices, which track blood sugar through a tiny sensor placed just beneath the skin, have helped people with type 1 diabetes prevent dangerous overnight drops and improve glucose control for those who rely on insulin. About 1 in 10 Americans has diabetes, and nearly half of those with Type 1 diabetes wear a continuous glucose monitor, according to the National Institutes of Health.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0 text_align_left"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Rodriguez said they launched the study last year as the FDA approved the first over-the-counter continuous glucose monitors. Around a half-dozen companies now market them, including Dexcom and Levels, which Trump’s Surgeon General co-founded. Rodriguez said there’s a need for more research into how well the devices predict someone’s risk of developing diabetes or dying of cardiovascular disease.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0 text_align_left"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;“These tools could still be powerful at a personalized level and add value by seeing the impact of sugar, identifying it, and helping you make different choices... like what you chose to eat for lunch,” Rodriguez said. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0 text_align_left"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Sharam Fouladgar-Mercer, founder of Signos, a health platform promoted to non-diabetics, said the technology offers a glimpse into how bodies process energy and coaches people toward better health. Signos is the first over-the-counter continuous glucose monitoring system to be cleared by the FDA specifically for weight management.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0 text_align_left"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;“What works for one person doesn’t necessarily work for another, and the technology offered the only glimpse into how our bodies were processing the energy we intake,” said Fouladgar-Mercer, who said he was obese before using a glucose monitor. “We built a solution that helps people connect with what they eat, how they move, the way they feel with the data on the screen, so you don’t have to wait to see the number on the scale move.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0 text_align_left"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Rodriguez said rapid changes in glucose could have downstream effects on hearts and kidneys, which is “normally seen in people with diabetes, but there’s a gap in understanding how it could impact those without diabetes. There’s still research to be done,” he said. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0 text_align_left"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Berardi noticed that even modest periods of movement — walking after eating — made a measurable difference in her blood sugar.&lt;i&gt; &lt;/i&gt;But after acquiring what she called “enough insight,” she stopped using the device, citing the cost as a barrier. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0 text_align_left"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;“Food is so powerful, and [glucose monitors] empower people to really see how it impacts all those biomarkers,” she said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0 text_align_left"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;According to the American Diabetes Association, normal blood glucose levels for an adult without diabetes are below 100 mg/dL when fasting and below 140 mg/dL two hours after meals.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0 text_align_left"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Rodriguez said he and his colleagues launched a separate study with around 10 participants to extend the findings and explore if people are changing their behaviors based on the readings of their continuous glucose monitors.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0 text_align_left"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Dr. Samir Malkani, an endocrinologist and diabetes specialist at UMass Memorial Medical Center, called the use of blood-sugar monitors by non-diabetics “uncharted territory.”  &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0 text_align_left"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;“Why are we so worried about people who are in the normal range? The main advantage of monitors is to flag when things are out of range,” he said. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0 text_align_left"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Berardi is glad she tried&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;the device and thinks more people will start using continuous glucose monitors to track their wellness.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0 text_align_left"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;“I’m happy I did because this is a proactive approach to good metabolic health, versus the reactive, symptomatic approach that I think we’re so used to,” she said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr class="tagline_hr | border_foreground border_half gutter_20_28--mobile
               margin_none text_align_left width_100px"&gt;&lt;p class="tagline | font_primary inline_block  margin_top_32"&gt;Sarah Rahal can be reached at &lt;a href="mailto:sarah.rahal@globe.com" class="" target="_blank"&gt;sarah.rahal@globe.com&lt;/a&gt;. Follow her on X &lt;a href="https://www.twitter.com/SarahRahal_" class="" target="_blank"&gt;@SarahRahal_&lt;/a&gt; or Instagram &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/sarah.rahal" class="" target="_blank"&gt;@sarah.rahal&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Boston Globe</author><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMioAFBVV95cUxPMmIyUVV4dVl0WFc1Q3Y2T2VVOHhwU2JhYlRzdl9nel9zQUVJY0xQZnY1Sm1Nd3NZcUxNcnJidlJLbVZHMmFTTkFUblVNdDlfaFNoTEFqOHVraC16dnhULWZOZFM0d3o1ZHNKd0xKZVpjYkFpd3RSdTVrSFlJZ1VHYTFQeElCd2I5aFo1VThIQVhYVFdVaVB1cEEwRlZpUUJH</guid></item><item><title>“没有人应该死于心脏病发作；”顶级心脏病专家揭示了应该出现心脏病的警告信号-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/no-one-should-die-of-a-heart-attack-top-cardiologist-reveals-warning-signs-of-heart-trouble-one-should-not-ignore/articleshow/124799897.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Heart disease is the number one cause of death globally, and despite immense advancements in treatment, millions get diagnosed with it each year. While heart disease is not reversible, and is fairly progressive, it is entirely preventable and manageable (if detected early). Dr Evan Levine, a board certified cardiologist in US, lists out few tell-tale signs of heart disease that no one should ignore, even if they are otherwise ‘healthy.’&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="3"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Chest pressure and shortness of breath&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="5"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr. Levine identifies chest pressure as a primary indicator, which people experience when they have coronary artery disease. People who have coronary artery disease experience chest pressure which they describe as tightness, heaviness, squeezing, or pressing sensation in their chest region, mostly described as “an elephant sitting on the chest.” According to Dr Levine, it could occur anytime, such as ‘walking, shoveling, or even at rest.’ Dr. Levine states that heart muscle blood flow reduction produces this chest pressure, which requires immediate medical attention. This pressure, says Dr Levine, can even radiate to the arms, shoulder, and jaw. Even though it is more common in the left side of the body, Dr Levine says it “can occur in both arms.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="10"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="lOvcW vdo_embedd"&gt;&lt;div class="k7lcu"&gt;&lt;p class="efT4r"&gt;Chest pain is the only sign of heart attack - Myth of Fact? Expert explains&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="12"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="14"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Shortness of breath&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="16"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another symptom that patients with coronary artery disease experience is shortness of breath (different from chest pressure). &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This occurs, because the heart requires oxygen-rich blood to function properly, but narrowed arteries in CAD patients restrict blood flow, which results in breathing difficulties, during physical activity. Dr. Levine explains that CAD can cause shortness of breath, even when chest pain is absent, particularly among patients who have high blood pressure or diabetes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="21"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Fatigue, nausea, and heartburn in women&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="23"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr. Levine explains that women with coronary artery disease tend to experience slightly different symptoms than men do. Women with coronary artery disease experience different symptoms than men because they develop atypical signs, which includes fatigue and nausea and heartburn symptoms. The symptoms often lead doctors to miss the correct diagnosis, because they resemble other less severe medical conditions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="27"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="29"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Women who have coronary artery disease experience fatigue which causes them to feel extremely tired or exhausted, after doing minimal physical work. This occurs because heart muscle fails to receive sufficient blood flow, which produces nausea and heartburn symptoms that resemble gastrointestinal problems. Dr. Levine warns women to seek medical help when they experience consistent heartburn symptoms, because these could indicate CAD, when combined with other warning signs or risk factors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="33"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Why awareness matters&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="35"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="36"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr. Levine emphasises that prompt identification of these symptoms becomes essential because coronary artery disease advances without noticeable symptoms, until it results in heart attack or heart failure. Women and other patients need to understand all possible heart disease symptoms because they do not always experience the typical chest pain symptoms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="40"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;People who experience unexplained chest pressure, shortness of breath or unusual fatigue, nausea or heartburn, should immediately visit a doctor for medical evaluation. The prompt diagnosis and treatment of heart conditions, leads to better patient results and helps prevent dangerous heart-related complications.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="43"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Prevention of Heart Disease&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="45"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The development of coronary artery disease results from plaque accumulation in arteries, which stems from unhealthy lifestyle choices. Dr. Levine and other heart health experts, provide multiple essential methods which help people prevent heart disease. They are:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="47"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Healthy diet&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="49"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;A heart-healthy diet serves as the base for all heart health initiatives. A diet rich in fruits, vegetables, whole grains and lean proteins helps people lower their cholesterol levels, and reduce inflammation in their bodies. The Mediterranean diet and DASH diet, serve as two evidence-based eating plans, which focus on plant-based foods and olive oil as their main components. People should restrict their consumption of saturated fats, trans fats, excessive sugar and salt, because these substances raise blood pressure and damage arteries.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="53"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Exercise&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="55"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Physical exercise at least 150 minutes per week through moderate activities like walking, swimming or cycling helps build heart strength and improves blood flow, while maintaining weight at a healthy level. Regular exercise helps people lower their risk for developing high blood pressure, diabetes and obesity, which are all factors that increase the risk of coronary artery disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="59"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Quitting smoking&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="61"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Quitting smoking stands as the most important step, because tobacco consumption causes blood vessel damage and accelerates plaque formation. The exposure to secondhand smoke, creates an increased risk for developing cardiovascular diseases. Heart health benefits from stress management through relaxation methods, proper sleep and social connections, because these practices help control dangerous hormones that affect the heart.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="65"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Regular check ups&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="67"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Regular health screenings help doctors track blood pressure, cholesterol and blood sugar levels, to identify potential health issues before they become serious. Doctors will prescribe medication to control risk factors when necessary to stop disease advancement. The implementation of these prevention methods leads to significant health benefits. As Dr Levine says, “No one should die of a heart attack”, hence it is important to take precautions beforehand.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="69"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr. Levine explains that regular small changes in lifestyle will help people lower their risk of coronary artery disease while creating better health outcomes and longer life expectancy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="71"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Key takeaways&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="73"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="74"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;• Chest pressure or tightness stands as a primary dangerous indicator, which people experience when they have coronary artery disease.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;• Shortness of breath which occurs during physical activity, should be considered as an essential warning indicator for heart disease.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;• Women tend to experience fatigue, nausea and heartburn symptoms instead of traditional chest pain, when their hearts are under stress.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;• Any unusual body sensation requires immediate medical evaluation because it might indicate heart disease.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;• Preventing heart disease requires people to eat healthily while exercising regularly, quitting smoking, controlling their stress levels and scheduling routine medical check-ups.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="76"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="77"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 05:39:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiuAJBVV95cUxNMko1TnhjRktUUjI3QjVhTnY1OHNZUzhFdmJidkZCMnc4VVhMV2N2MDlMUXhMaEN3WDhTQ1g4UUFqQWlUZHBqV1B5bWdWeW5QbzE3QzZlbnllT19aeWl2dWdUczJCalU1Zzg2Ry1XNmMtN2tQazBhX1NXNG1Yek9LTXEtSEc3WHN2WDl5VFF4QTB6X0phSnB1OW1mY0ttSThGYTY2OC1IYTg3WXBBaVpQMXptRzdNZTRFS1BMUWtiMUVXWUFVT1J2NGVvY3UzbHJWbUFYOU5vTnBnOXFSbVJBUlZQb2ZsN1RlSlFqVmM4RkhpRE9raGIyc1J2WWdXRkl0cE9SUWNWZk91OHdleGtsOWdtM0NhMV9RbWJSQUN4b0M0cUFPOGtrb29jY3I2ZGxCejJtV09fblE</guid></item><item><title>在抗击疟疾的斗争中，一个意想不到的—和紧密的-盾牌-纽约时报</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/10/25/health/insecticide-treated-baby-wraps-carriers-malaria.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The New York Times</author><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 04:01:05 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimgFBVV95cUxNRjJFeWtXTU1XMEg3bXdrWkNRSmN4Z0hDdGxsTlQwamVLOFBVQWtMQ0RSY2tZdzdoQ0dyUWtGRURseUtFMzhDMGFvMjdDT1RlVDktZEhTZ0ROdU5DVm5ZNXJEdFVqbkpvS2FTbC02MkY3TWhYZWdPS3I2X2hmNHBVcFRycnViemlpR1hGVEdhaElnaXJvVHg4Rjh3</guid></item><item><title>拿破仑不幸的1812年军队的DNA揭示了可能导致士兵死亡的原因- WVTM</title><link>https://www.wvtm13.com/article/napoleon-1812-invasion-army-diseases-dna/69151987</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-content--body-inner"&gt;
										&lt;div class="mobile"&gt;
													



																		&lt;div class="mobile"&gt;
							

&lt;section class="article-headline"&gt;
	
			&lt;p class="article-headline--title"&gt;DNA from Napoleon’s ill-fated 1812 army reveals what likely led to the soldiers’ demise&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;/section&gt;


							&lt;div class="article-branding"&gt;
						&lt;img data-src="https://kubrick.htvapps.com/htv-prod-media.s3.amazonaws.com/htv_default_image/site_branding/cnn.png" class="lazyload lazyload-in-view branding" alt="CNN logo"&gt;
								&lt;p class="article-headline--publish-date border-left"&gt;
			Updated: 9:34 PM CDT Oct 24, 2025
		&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;a href="/article/hearst-television-news-policy-statements/14471973" class="editorial-standards border-left"&gt;Editorial Standards &lt;span class="info-icon"&gt;ⓘ&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;

							




						&lt;/div&gt;
					&lt;/div&gt;
	
						
					&lt;p class="article-content--body-teaser"&gt;
						
					&lt;/p&gt;
	
					&lt;p class="article-content--body-text-raw"&gt;
						Near the end of his reign, French emperor Napoleon Bonaparte led an army of over half a million men in an invasion of Russia in 1812. Six months later, after the army was forced to retreat, an estimated tens of thousands of his soldiers made it back to France.Known as one of the costliest wars in history, the death of hundreds of thousands of soldiers has been attributed to battle, as well as starvation, cold and a typhus epidemic that broke out.Now, researchers have found evidence in the DNA remains of the soldiers that there may have been multiple diseases that devastated the army, including two previously undetected types of bacteria. The study was published Friday in the journal Current Biology.“Previously, we just thought that there was one infectious disease that decimated the Napoleon army — the typhus,” said lead author Rémi Barbieri, a former postdoctoral fellow at the Institut Pasteur in Paris who currently holds a postdoctoral position at Estonia’s University of Tartu. Instead, the researchers found something unexpected, opening the door to potentially uncovering other infectious diseases that could have contributed to the soldiers’ deaths, he added.The researchers found the pathogens — Salmonella enterica and Borrelia recurrentis, bacteria that cause paratyphoid fever and relapsing fever, respectively — by analyzing teeth from the fallen soldiers who were found in a mass grave uncovered in 2001 in Vilnius, Lithuania.The new findings not only give a clearer picture of a significant historical event, but they highlight how technology has advanced and opened the door to understanding historical circumstances, researchers say.Mixing pot of diseaseWhen Napoleon and his troops reached Moscow, they weren’t met with Russian soldiers. Instead, the city was abandoned, with burnt crops and no supplies available, such as safe food to eat or clean clothing. As the harsh winter months approached, the French army was forced to retreat, but not without facing many hardships.Rickettsia prowazekii, the bacterium responsible for typhus, was first detected in the teeth of Napoleon’s soldiers during a 2006 study, but the research was limited by the technology at that time. To find out if typhus was the sole culprit for the demise of soldiers, the authors of the new study used a method known as high-throughput sequencing, which can sequence millions of DNA fragments at a time. It allows for highly degraded DNA to be identified, such as the genome fragments extracted from samples more than 200 years old.“This is something that can be only done with these machines that are very powerful to go and sequence a lot of high quantity of DNA,” said study coauthor Nicolás Rascovan, supervisor of the research and head of the Microbial Paleogenomics Unit at the Institut Pasteur. “This sort of analysis, these kinds of projects, can really give a much clearer picture about the landscape of infectious disease in the past … and how (historical events) have also shaped the landscape of infectious diseases today.”The study authors looked at 13 samples and found no traces of typhus, but their work does not discredit the findings of the 2006 study, the researchers noted. The study sample is also too small to know the exact impact the diseases had on Napoleon’s army. “What changes (with) our study is the fact that now we have direct evidence there were several different infectious diseases present in this site,” Rascovan said. It is likely that more diseases were at play that have yet to be detected, he added.Cecil Lewis, an ancient DNA researcher who studies the human microbiome, said the results were not particularly surprising, but he called it a meaningful contribution to “our understanding of the demise of Napoleon’s army.” Lewis, vice president of academics at the Oklahoma School of Science and Mathematics, was not involved with the study.“We are now in a period where ancient DNA studies can contribute more nuance to the understanding of such historic events, which is exciting,” Lewis said in an email. “Studying historical and ancient pathogens, their place in history, offers a glimpse into the evolutionary paths organisms have taken, some now extinct, others forming the foundation of present-day pathogens. These data help us better understand the possibilities for how pathogens can impact lives, evolve, and persist, which is crucial for anticipating and managing future threats.”Paratyphoid fever and relapsing fever are still around today, but are not as common or as deadly. Napoleon survived the retreat, but his dwindling army ultimately contributed to his fall from power a few years later.“Something that is quite impressive is how, in so little time, since 2006 with the first study to today, the technologies have been developed so much that we can do things that were impossible to even conceive a few years ago and now are possible,” Rascovan said. “So I am very excited to think what is going to be next in terms of technological developments.”
					&lt;/p&gt;
	
					&lt;div class="article-content--body-text"&gt;
																			&lt;p&gt;Near the end of his reign, French emperor Napoleon Bonaparte led an army of over half a million men in an invasion of Russia in 1812. Six months later, after the army was forced to retreat, an estimated&lt;a href="https://www.britannica.com/event/Napoleonic-Wars/The-retreat-from-Moscow" rel="nofollow"&gt; tens of thousands&lt;/a&gt; of his soldiers made it back to France.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Known as one of the costliest wars in history, the death of hundreds of thousands of soldiers has been attributed to battle, as well as starvation, cold and a typhus epidemic that broke out.&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Now, researchers have found evidence in the DNA remains of the soldiers that there may have been multiple diseases that devastated the army, including two previously undetected types of bacteria. The &lt;a href="https://www.cell.com/current-biology/fulltext/S0960-9822(25)01247-3" rel="nofollow"&gt;study was published&lt;/a&gt; Friday in the journal Current Biology.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Previously, we just thought that there was one infectious disease that decimated the Napoleon army — the typhus,” said lead author Rémi Barbieri, a former postdoctoral fellow at the Institut Pasteur in Paris who currently holds a postdoctoral position at Estonia’s University of Tartu. Instead, the researchers found something unexpected, opening the door to potentially uncovering other infectious diseases that could have contributed to the soldiers’ deaths, he added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers found the pathogens — &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/topics/immunology-and-microbiology/salmonella-enterica" rel="nofollow"&gt;Salmonella enterica&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/topics/medicine-and-dentistry/borrelia-recurrentis" rel="nofollow"&gt;Borrelia recurrentis&lt;/a&gt;, bacteria that cause paratyphoid fever and &lt;a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/books/NBK441913/" rel="nofollow"&gt;relapsing fever&lt;/a&gt;, respectively — by analyzing teeth from the fallen soldiers who were found in a mass grave uncovered in 2001 in Vilnius, Lithuania.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The new findings not only give a clearer picture of a significant historical event, but they highlight how technology has advanced and opened the door to understanding historical circumstances, researchers say.&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;h2 class="body-h2" id="mixing-pot-of-disease"&gt;Mixing pot of disease&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="cream-inline-rec" class="cream-inline hidden"&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When Napoleon and his troops reached Moscow, they weren’t met with Russian soldiers. Instead, the city was abandoned, with burnt crops and no supplies available, such as safe food to eat or clean clothing. As the harsh winter months approached, the French army was forced to retreat, but not without facing many hardships.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/books/NBK448173/" rel="nofollow"&gt;Rickettsia prowazekii&lt;/a&gt;, the bacterium responsible for typhus, was first detected in the teeth of Napoleon’s soldiers during a 2006 study, but the research was limited by the technology at that time. To find out if typhus was the sole culprit for the demise of soldiers, the authors of the new study used a method known as high-throughput sequencing, which can sequence millions of DNA fragments at a time. It allows for highly degraded DNA to be identified, such as the genome fragments extracted from samples more than 200 years old.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“This is something that can be only done with these machines that are very powerful to go and sequence a lot of high quantity of DNA,” said study coauthor Nicolás Rascovan, supervisor of the research and head of the Microbial Paleogenomics Unit at the Institut Pasteur. “This sort of analysis, these kinds of projects, can really give a much clearer picture about the landscape of infectious disease in the past … and how (historical events) have also shaped the landscape of infectious diseases today.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study authors looked at 13 samples and found no traces of typhus, but their work does not discredit the findings of the 2006 study, the researchers noted. The study sample is also too small to know the exact impact the diseases had on Napoleon’s army. “What changes (with) our study is the fact that now we have direct evidence there were several different infectious diseases present in this site,” Rascovan said. It is likely that more diseases were at play that have yet to be detected, he added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cecil Lewis, an ancient DNA researcher who studies the human microbiome, said the results were not particularly surprising, but he called it a meaningful contribution to “our understanding of the demise of Napoleon’s army.” Lewis, vice president of academics at the Oklahoma School of Science and Mathematics, was not involved with the study.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“We are now in a period where ancient DNA studies can contribute more nuance to the understanding of such historic events, which is exciting,” Lewis said in an email. “Studying historical and ancient pathogens, their place in history, offers a glimpse into the evolutionary paths organisms have taken, some now extinct, others forming the foundation of present-day pathogens. These data help us better understand the possibilities for how pathogens can impact lives, evolve, and persist, which is crucial for anticipating and managing future threats.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/typhoid-fever/about/index.html#:~:text=Where%20illness%20is%20common,be%20poor%2C%20including%20parts%20of:" rel="nofollow"&gt;Paratyphoid fever and relapsing fever&lt;/a&gt; are still around today, but are not as common or as deadly. Napoleon survived the retreat, but his dwindling army ultimately contributed to his fall from power a few years later.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Something that is quite impressive is how, in so little time, since 2006 with the first study to today, the technologies have been developed so much that we can do things that were impossible to even conceive a few years ago and now are possible,” Rascovan said. “So I am very excited to think what is going to be next in terms of technological developments.”&lt;/p&gt;

							
											&lt;/div&gt;
	
	
						
						
																			

																				&lt;/div&gt;
	
																&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>WVTM</author><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 02:34:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihwFBVV95cUxNM3F6VkhGcW5XTnVlNTBxMGItckVHN2x1cGJoQUduU0ppcWNBcF9SeGN3TjJYdTZYWVV5OGhsS19aZVJYa09mUER0QVJHS01WMjhjOGNnZ2tHeHVPZUFPU2drRjJfZlg0MlFxZ1JvYkpyazc5bUJQNEUtei0zOW1na1RyVVBqbFE</guid></item><item><title>拿破仑不幸的1812年军队的DNA揭示了可能导致士兵死亡的原因- WMTW</title><link>https://www.wmtw.com/article/napoleon-1812-invasion-army-diseases-dna/69151987</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-content--body-inner"&gt;
										&lt;div class="mobile"&gt;
													



																		&lt;div class="mobile"&gt;
							

&lt;section class="article-headline"&gt;
	
			&lt;p class="article-headline--title"&gt;DNA from Napoleon’s ill-fated 1812 army reveals what likely led to the soldiers’ demise&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;/section&gt;


							&lt;div class="article-branding"&gt;
						&lt;img data-src="https://kubrick.htvapps.com/htv-prod-media.s3.amazonaws.com/htv_default_image/site_branding/cnn.png" class="lazyload lazyload-in-view branding" alt="CNN logo"&gt;
								&lt;p class="article-headline--publish-date border-left"&gt;
			Updated: 10:34 PM EDT Oct 24, 2025
		&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;a href="/article/hearst-television-news-policy-statements/14471973" class="editorial-standards border-left"&gt;Editorial Standards &lt;span class="info-icon"&gt;ⓘ&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;

							




						&lt;/div&gt;
					&lt;/div&gt;
	
						
					&lt;p class="article-content--body-teaser"&gt;
						
					&lt;/p&gt;
	
					&lt;p class="article-content--body-text-raw"&gt;
						Near the end of his reign, French emperor Napoleon Bonaparte led an army of over half a million men in an invasion of Russia in 1812. Six months later, after the army was forced to retreat, an estimated tens of thousands of his soldiers made it back to France.Known as one of the costliest wars in history, the death of hundreds of thousands of soldiers has been attributed to battle, as well as starvation, cold and a typhus epidemic that broke out.Now, researchers have found evidence in the DNA remains of the soldiers that there may have been multiple diseases that devastated the army, including two previously undetected types of bacteria. The study was published Friday in the journal Current Biology.“Previously, we just thought that there was one infectious disease that decimated the Napoleon army — the typhus,” said lead author Rémi Barbieri, a former postdoctoral fellow at the Institut Pasteur in Paris who currently holds a postdoctoral position at Estonia’s University of Tartu. Instead, the researchers found something unexpected, opening the door to potentially uncovering other infectious diseases that could have contributed to the soldiers’ deaths, he added.The researchers found the pathogens — Salmonella enterica and Borrelia recurrentis, bacteria that cause paratyphoid fever and relapsing fever, respectively — by analyzing teeth from the fallen soldiers who were found in a mass grave uncovered in 2001 in Vilnius, Lithuania.The new findings not only give a clearer picture of a significant historical event, but they highlight how technology has advanced and opened the door to understanding historical circumstances, researchers say.Mixing pot of diseaseWhen Napoleon and his troops reached Moscow, they weren’t met with Russian soldiers. Instead, the city was abandoned, with burnt crops and no supplies available, such as safe food to eat or clean clothing. As the harsh winter months approached, the French army was forced to retreat, but not without facing many hardships.Rickettsia prowazekii, the bacterium responsible for typhus, was first detected in the teeth of Napoleon’s soldiers during a 2006 study, but the research was limited by the technology at that time. To find out if typhus was the sole culprit for the demise of soldiers, the authors of the new study used a method known as high-throughput sequencing, which can sequence millions of DNA fragments at a time. It allows for highly degraded DNA to be identified, such as the genome fragments extracted from samples more than 200 years old.“This is something that can be only done with these machines that are very powerful to go and sequence a lot of high quantity of DNA,” said study coauthor Nicolás Rascovan, supervisor of the research and head of the Microbial Paleogenomics Unit at the Institut Pasteur. “This sort of analysis, these kinds of projects, can really give a much clearer picture about the landscape of infectious disease in the past … and how (historical events) have also shaped the landscape of infectious diseases today.”The study authors looked at 13 samples and found no traces of typhus, but their work does not discredit the findings of the 2006 study, the researchers noted. The study sample is also too small to know the exact impact the diseases had on Napoleon’s army. “What changes (with) our study is the fact that now we have direct evidence there were several different infectious diseases present in this site,” Rascovan said. It is likely that more diseases were at play that have yet to be detected, he added.Cecil Lewis, an ancient DNA researcher who studies the human microbiome, said the results were not particularly surprising, but he called it a meaningful contribution to “our understanding of the demise of Napoleon’s army.” Lewis, vice president of academics at the Oklahoma School of Science and Mathematics, was not involved with the study.“We are now in a period where ancient DNA studies can contribute more nuance to the understanding of such historic events, which is exciting,” Lewis said in an email. “Studying historical and ancient pathogens, their place in history, offers a glimpse into the evolutionary paths organisms have taken, some now extinct, others forming the foundation of present-day pathogens. These data help us better understand the possibilities for how pathogens can impact lives, evolve, and persist, which is crucial for anticipating and managing future threats.”Paratyphoid fever and relapsing fever are still around today, but are not as common or as deadly. Napoleon survived the retreat, but his dwindling army ultimately contributed to his fall from power a few years later.“Something that is quite impressive is how, in so little time, since 2006 with the first study to today, the technologies have been developed so much that we can do things that were impossible to even conceive a few years ago and now are possible,” Rascovan said. “So I am very excited to think what is going to be next in terms of technological developments.”
					&lt;/p&gt;
	
					&lt;div class="article-content--body-text"&gt;
																			&lt;p&gt;Near the end of his reign, French emperor Napoleon Bonaparte led an army of over half a million men in an invasion of Russia in 1812. Six months later, after the army was forced to retreat, an estimated&lt;a href="https://www.britannica.com/event/Napoleonic-Wars/The-retreat-from-Moscow" rel="nofollow"&gt; tens of thousands&lt;/a&gt; of his soldiers made it back to France.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Known as one of the costliest wars in history, the death of hundreds of thousands of soldiers has been attributed to battle, as well as starvation, cold and a typhus epidemic that broke out.&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Now, researchers have found evidence in the DNA remains of the soldiers that there may have been multiple diseases that devastated the army, including two previously undetected types of bacteria. The &lt;a href="https://www.cell.com/current-biology/fulltext/S0960-9822(25)01247-3" rel="nofollow"&gt;study was published&lt;/a&gt; Friday in the journal Current Biology.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Previously, we just thought that there was one infectious disease that decimated the Napoleon army — the typhus,” said lead author Rémi Barbieri, a former postdoctoral fellow at the Institut Pasteur in Paris who currently holds a postdoctoral position at Estonia’s University of Tartu. Instead, the researchers found something unexpected, opening the door to potentially uncovering other infectious diseases that could have contributed to the soldiers’ deaths, he added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers found the pathogens — &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/topics/immunology-and-microbiology/salmonella-enterica" rel="nofollow"&gt;Salmonella enterica&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/topics/medicine-and-dentistry/borrelia-recurrentis" rel="nofollow"&gt;Borrelia recurrentis&lt;/a&gt;, bacteria that cause paratyphoid fever and &lt;a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/books/NBK441913/" rel="nofollow"&gt;relapsing fever&lt;/a&gt;, respectively — by analyzing teeth from the fallen soldiers who were found in a mass grave uncovered in 2001 in Vilnius, Lithuania.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The new findings not only give a clearer picture of a significant historical event, but they highlight how technology has advanced and opened the door to understanding historical circumstances, researchers say.&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;h2 class="body-h2" id="mixing-pot-of-disease"&gt;Mixing pot of disease&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="cream-inline-rec" class="cream-inline hidden"&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When Napoleon and his troops reached Moscow, they weren’t met with Russian soldiers. Instead, the city was abandoned, with burnt crops and no supplies available, such as safe food to eat or clean clothing. As the harsh winter months approached, the French army was forced to retreat, but not without facing many hardships.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/books/NBK448173/" rel="nofollow"&gt;Rickettsia prowazekii&lt;/a&gt;, the bacterium responsible for typhus, was first detected in the teeth of Napoleon’s soldiers during a 2006 study, but the research was limited by the technology at that time. To find out if typhus was the sole culprit for the demise of soldiers, the authors of the new study used a method known as high-throughput sequencing, which can sequence millions of DNA fragments at a time. It allows for highly degraded DNA to be identified, such as the genome fragments extracted from samples more than 200 years old.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“This is something that can be only done with these machines that are very powerful to go and sequence a lot of high quantity of DNA,” said study coauthor Nicolás Rascovan, supervisor of the research and head of the Microbial Paleogenomics Unit at the Institut Pasteur. “This sort of analysis, these kinds of projects, can really give a much clearer picture about the landscape of infectious disease in the past … and how (historical events) have also shaped the landscape of infectious diseases today.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study authors looked at 13 samples and found no traces of typhus, but their work does not discredit the findings of the 2006 study, the researchers noted. The study sample is also too small to know the exact impact the diseases had on Napoleon’s army. “What changes (with) our study is the fact that now we have direct evidence there were several different infectious diseases present in this site,” Rascovan said. It is likely that more diseases were at play that have yet to be detected, he added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cecil Lewis, an ancient DNA researcher who studies the human microbiome, said the results were not particularly surprising, but he called it a meaningful contribution to “our understanding of the demise of Napoleon’s army.” Lewis, vice president of academics at the Oklahoma School of Science and Mathematics, was not involved with the study.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“We are now in a period where ancient DNA studies can contribute more nuance to the understanding of such historic events, which is exciting,” Lewis said in an email. “Studying historical and ancient pathogens, their place in history, offers a glimpse into the evolutionary paths organisms have taken, some now extinct, others forming the foundation of present-day pathogens. These data help us better understand the possibilities for how pathogens can impact lives, evolve, and persist, which is crucial for anticipating and managing future threats.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/typhoid-fever/about/index.html#:~:text=Where%20illness%20is%20common,be%20poor%2C%20including%20parts%20of:" rel="nofollow"&gt;Paratyphoid fever and relapsing fever&lt;/a&gt; are still around today, but are not as common or as deadly. Napoleon survived the retreat, but his dwindling army ultimately contributed to his fall from power a few years later.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Something that is quite impressive is how, in so little time, since 2006 with the first study to today, the technologies have been developed so much that we can do things that were impossible to even conceive a few years ago and now are possible,” Rascovan said. “So I am very excited to think what is going to be next in terms of technological developments.”&lt;/p&gt;

							
											&lt;/div&gt;
	
	
						
						
																			

																				&lt;/div&gt;
	
																&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>WMTW</author><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 02:34:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihAFBVV95cUxOZGhRWTBQX0h5SUtDaUxFUGw3MF9SbUo5VEFHUnZWdlk1MHVxUXFsbVFINTcwU09yYmFHZDd6V0d1UXppRUFpVUNxWXFNZTFnblNidkRseEV4Q1VOSldUbjVxSFVaVXlET0E0SWhjeHZBazk4RHVDRjNtaThjT0dXcG53UmY</guid></item><item><title>七个巴拿马地区报告了Oropouche病毒病-巴拿马新闻室</title><link>https://newsroompanama.com/2025/10/24/oropouche-virus-disease-reported-across-seven-panama-regions/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content"&gt;
        
&lt;p&gt;Since the first cases of Oropouche virus disease (OROV) were detected in Panama at the end of 2024 and the beginning of this year, a total of 613 confirmed cases have been reported across seven regions in Panama during 2025.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;According to Panama’s health ministry, OROV crossed the southern border from Colombia and is now found in Panamá Metro, Los Santos, Herrera, Panamá Norte, Veraguas, Panamá Oeste, Coclé, Darién, and Panamá Este (East Panama).&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;This disease is primarily spread by the bites of infected biting midges (small flies) and mosquitoes.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Ministry of Health recommends that residents living in areas with active virus transmission use repellent, wear long-sleeved shirts and long pants, and install mosquito nets or wire mesh on doors and windows. They are also urged to avoid traveling to areas with active virus transmission.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Blas Armién, national head of Epidemiology at the Ministry of Health, explained in a media release on October 22, 2025, “Of the 15 health regions, at least seven have identified the circulation of OROV in the human population.”&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Armién added the most common symptoms of Oropouche include sudden onset of high fever, intense headache with photophobia, muscle and joint pain, and, in some cases, skin rashes (exanthemas).&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In this regard, Armién warned that infection during the first trimester of pregnancy can cause genetic alterations in the fetus, such as hydrocephalus. He also emphasized the importance of attending prenatal checkups, as a case of vertical transmission (from mother to child) has been reported in Panama.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Regarding neurological disorders, he mentioned that cases of Guillain-Barré syndrome and flaccid paralysis may occur.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Because it presents symptoms similar to those of dengue, a specific diagnostic algorithm is used to distinguish the two diseases.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;To alert international travelers of this health risk, the U.S. CDC reissued a Level 1 – Practice Usual Precautions, Travel Health Notice in September 2025. The CDC has included countries such as Brazil and Cuba in this warning.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The CDC says, given the limited information on the risk of possible spread through sex, including the unknown of whether the virus may be present in vaginal fluid, travelers and their partners concerned about possible sexual transmission of Oropouche virus can consider using condoms or not having sex during travel and for 6 weeks after returning from travel.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;As of late October 2025, no preventive vaccines targeting OROV are available.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="post-views content-post post-71894 entry-meta load-static"&gt;
				&lt;span class="post-views-icon dashicons dashicons-chart-bar"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="post-views-label"&gt;Post Views:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="post-views-count"&gt;1,270&lt;/span&gt;
			&lt;/p&gt;                    
               
        
	&lt;nav class="navigation post-navigation" aria-label="Continue Reading"&gt;
		&lt;h2 class="screen-reader-text"&gt;Continue Reading&lt;/h2&gt;
		
	&lt;/nav&gt;            &lt;/div&gt;


                                &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Newsroom Panama</author><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 01:53:47 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMioAFBVV95cUxOeG9VUVg2cVEyb2R1c29QX05TbmRQckM1VzVENDBGUjR0b2g3N2c2ZTV5YjAwbTczY3hfRFZ2MEV0WkpMTVYtM2xyaVFxenMxcEVqbFdnQnlpYnRlR1NHZHJ4TXdfVElIeldRVjRGUk9mNlhxcm5BUDF2bUpaQW5nSHVCY2ZvQ1dQbFh4U0ZCQWdnWVZ2cGRMczdFeTdmZ082</guid></item><item><title>科学家说，在你的日常生活中添加一些日常食物可以帮助你的大脑保持年轻-食物和葡萄酒</title><link>https://www.foodandwine.com/green-tea-walnuts-delay-brain-aging-11824925</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-page_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-page mntl-block structured-content" data-sc-sticky-offset="90" data-sc-ad-label-height="24" data-sc-ad-track-spacing="100" data-sc-min-track-height="250" data-sc-max-track-height="600" data-sc-breakpoint="50em" data-sc-load-immediate="4" data-sc-content-positions="[1, 1250, 1550, 1950, 2350, 2750, 3150, 3550, 3950]" data-bind-scroll-on-start="true"&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-block_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block foodandwine-sc-block-callout--summary mntl-sc-block-universal-callout--tips mntl-sc-block-universal-callout theme-summary callout--bordered" data-text="Key Points" data-tracking-id="mntl-sc-block-callout" data-tracking-container="true"&gt;
&lt;div class="mntl-sc-block-universal-callout__body"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;A new 18-month study found that adults following a calorie-restricted “green-MED” diet — rich in green tea, walnuts, and the leafy plant mankai — showed signs of slower brain aging compared to those on standard healthy-eating or traditional Mediterranean diets.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Researchers connected decreases in certain blood proteins related to brain aging, especially galectin-9, to the green-MED group’s diet high in polyphenols and low in red and processed meats.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;While the findings show correlation rather than causation, scientists say the results could eventually support simple blood tests to monitor brain health and cognitive aging.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_2-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Scientists just gave us another reason to enjoy a cup of green tea today, because it turns out, it might help your brain age more slowly.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_3-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_4-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; In October, a team of international researchers, including those from Ben-Gurion University of the Negev in Israel, Harvard University in Massachusetts, and the University of Leipzig in Germany, published the results of their 18-month secondary analysis of brain aging in the journal &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.clinicalnutritionjournal.com/article/S0261-5614%2825%2900235-3/fulltext" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1" rel="nofollow"&gt;Clinical Nutrition&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_5-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_6-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; The team followed nearly 300 adults who participated in the &lt;a href="https://clinicaltrials.gov/study/NCT03020186" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;DIRECT PLUS trial,&lt;/a&gt; where each was randomly assigned to one of three diets: one based on "general" healthy-eating guidelines; another following the calorie-restricted Mediterranean diet (with 1,500–1,800 calories a day for men and 1,200–1,400 calories for women); and the last adhering to a “green-MED” diet that was also calorie-restricted but higher in polyphenols and lower in red and processed meats (replacing beef and lamb with poultry and fish). It turns out that the last one might be the secret to better brain aging.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_7-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_8-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; As the paper explained, the Green-MED group consumed a daily serving of walnuts (28 grams, to be exact), drank between three and four cups of green tea, and had a mankai shake each day — derived from a green leafy plant that supplies complete proteins. All participants, regardless of their diet group, had access to a gym and guidance on physical activity.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_9-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_11-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_12-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Over the 18 months, the researchers combined MRI scans taken before and after the experiment with a machine-learning model to estimate each participant's brain age. They then calculated a "brain age gap" by comparing the MRI-estimated brain age with the person's actual chronological age. A positive gap indicated accelerated brain aging, while a negative gap suggested the brain is aging more slowly than the person's chronological age (i.e., it is "younger" than the person's birthday would indicate).
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_13-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_14-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; At the start of the study, participants whose brains appeared younger than their actual age tended to share a few traits: they weighed less, had smaller waistlines, lower blood pressure, and healthier blood sugar levels. When researchers examined blood samples before the diet changes, two proteins also stood out: galectin-9 (Gal-9) and decorin (DCN). Higher levels of either were tied to an “older” brain. In their discussion, the authors also cited prior research showing that high levels of decorin in cerebrospinal fluid are associated with early Alzheimer’s changes. And for both proteins, particularly GAL-9, diet choices played an essential role in brain health over time.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_15-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_16-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block foodandwine-sc-block-embed mntl-sc-block-universal-embed "&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_17-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_18-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Blood markers for these proteins shifted depending on which diet participants followed, with the green-MED group showing the most significant changes. These participants showed the greatest reduction in GAL-9 protein, followed by the Mediterranean group, which showed slight reductions. The markers of the healthy guideline group went essentially unchanged.  
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_19-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_20-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; "Studying the circulating proteins in blood allows us to observe, in a real-life setting, how the brain’s aging processes are influenced by lifestyle and dietary changes," Dr. Anat Yaskolka-Meir, postdoctoral research fellow at Harvard and the co-first author of the paper, &lt;a href="https://www.eurekalert.org/news-releases/1098285" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;shared&lt;/a&gt;. "This approach gives us a dynamic window into brain health, helping to reveal biological changes long before symptoms may appear. By mapping these protein signatures, we gain powerful new insight into how interventions, such as diet, may help preserve cognitive function as we age.”
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_21-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_23-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_24-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; The researchers noted some significant limitations in their study, notably that about 90% of the participants were men who initially had abdominal obesity. The machine learning model's ability to predict the brain age gap was also limited, and although the study found a link between the green-MED diet and decreased brain aging, they cannot yet establish causation. Nevertheless, these findings and their recommendations for brain health contribute to an increasing body of research suggesting that consuming more polyphenol-rich foods like green tea and walnuts, along with reducing processed and red meats, could offer substantial health benefits.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_25-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_26-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; And perhaps most importantly, the authors suggest their findings could someday enable medical and scientific professionals to better understand brain health.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_27-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_28-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; “In this study, we are taking a small step toward a new possibility," Dafna Pachter, a Ph.D. student and the first author of the paper, said. "A simple, accessible, and affordable blood test that could, in the future, provide an indication of brain status by analyzing omics layers in the blood." &lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Food &amp; Wine</author><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 01:14:10 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMifEFVX3lxTFA1Tl9oRFcxdDhSYmt1WnJLU3RLX2hGdzR1am5NZ3pDeVJLV2NERndtM0xyNU9VTnFubGJNZWlla0NZV2JDZ2ZIM3gzdmt2b0RmT2xLaDFlOWN3U3pQSlpZaWVYUTJUaVlqT2VSdHZVNDZBT2pGR2Q3dlY2Q2Y</guid></item><item><title>新的突破性治疗方法用光安全地杀死癌细胞- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/new-breakthrough-treatment-safely-kills-cancer-cells-with-light</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/cancer" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73077" data-postid="178808" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;Cancer&lt;/a&gt; treatment has come a long way, but many of today's therapies still come with steep costs: not just financial, but physical and emotional too. Chemotherapy and radiotherapy remain vital tools, yet they often damage healthy cells alongside cancerous ones, leaving patients exhausted and vulnerable to long-term side effects.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Around the world, researchers are searching for &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/topics/cancer-treatment-7080"&gt;treatments&lt;/a&gt; that are both effective and gentle, able to target tumors precisely while sparing the rest of the body.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Now, US researchers have introduced a promising new &lt;a href="https://news.utexas.edu/2025/10/09/led-light-blasts-cancer-cells-and-spares-healthy-ones/"&gt;light-based treatment&lt;/a&gt; that could transform the way cancer is treated. Their discovery combines near-infrared LED light with nanoscopic flakes of tin oxide, known as &lt;a href="https://utaustinportugal.org/"&gt;SnOx nanoflakes&lt;/a&gt;, to kill &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/topics/cancer-cell-8247"&gt;cancer cells&lt;/a&gt; while leaving healthy ones unharmed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/study-suggests-covid-mrna-vaccines-help-fight-cancer-too"&gt;Study Suggests COVID MRNA Vaccines Help Fight Cancer Too&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_178822" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-178822" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/LEDSystemActivatesSnOxNanoflakesToNeutraliseCancerCell.jpg" alt="Illustration of LED system used to fight cancer" class="wp-image-178822 size-full" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/LEDSystemActivatesSnOxNanoflakesToNeutraliseCancerCell.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/LEDSystemActivatesSnOxNanoflakesToNeutraliseCancerCell-600x450.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-178822" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;The researchers' custom near-infrared LED heating system activates SnOx nanoflakes that heat and neutralize cancer cells (green: live cells; red: cells killed by photothermal therapy). (&lt;a href="https://news.utexas.edu/2025/10/09/led-light-blasts-cancer-cells-and-spares-healthy-ones/"&gt;The University of Texas at Austin&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;This marks an important advance in &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40169560/"&gt;photothermal therapy&lt;/a&gt;, a technique that uses light to heat and destroy tumors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In this case, the process relies on inexpensive, accessible LED systems rather than specialized lasers. The approach reduces damage to surrounding tissues and could one day offer a safer and less invasive alternative &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/topics/chemotherapy-588"&gt;to chemotherapy&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/topics/radiation-therapy-39517"&gt;or radiotherapy&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At the core of the innovation is a simple concept: using light to create localized heat that targets and kills cancer cells. The team designed the SnOx nanoflakes to absorb near-infrared light efficiently, a wavelength that can safely penetrate biological tissue.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When illuminated, these nanoflakes act like microscopic heaters, producing enough warmth to disrupt cancer cell membranes and proteins, ultimately causing cell death. Healthy tissues remain largely unaffected because they are less sensitive to heat and because the nanoflakes can be directed specifically toward malignant cells.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41571-020-0410-2"&gt;targeted heating process&lt;/a&gt;, known as &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41392-025-02140-y"&gt;photothermal therapy&lt;/a&gt;, relies on a physical rather than chemical mechanism. This means it can avoid many of the systemic side effects typically seen with chemotherapy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Traditional photothermal systems use lasers because they can focus light precisely deep within tissue. However, that same intensity can also damage healthy cells, requires costly equipment, and limits use to highly specialized facilities.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In this study, the researchers replaced lasers with light-emitting diodes (LEDs), which emit a gentler, broader spectrum of light. LEDs produce more uniform heating and are far less likely to burn or harm healthy tissue. They are also inexpensive and portable, making them well suited for clinical or even at-home use.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In &lt;a href="https://pubs.acs.org/doi/10.1021/acsnano.5c03135"&gt;laboratory studies&lt;/a&gt;, the LED light combined with SnOx nanoflakes destroyed up to 92 percent of skin cancer cells and 50 percent of colorectal cancer cells within 30 minutes. Healthy human skin cells were unaffected.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This level of selectivity makes the technique particularly promising for cancers such as melanoma and basal cell carcinoma, which can be treated directly through light exposure. Such precision is rare among photothermal technologies, which often risk harming surrounding tissue.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The underlying science is equally significant. Tin oxide is a stable, biocompatible material already used in electronics.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;By converting tin disulfide (SnS₂) into oxygenated tin oxide nanoflakes, the researchers created structures that absorb near-infrared light much more effectively.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This transformation improves photothermal performance and allows the nanoflakes to be made using water-based, non-toxic synthesis methods. The process avoids harmful solvents and expensive manufacturing steps, making it scalable, sustainable and suitable for medical applications.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/spark-into-space-comp"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro-642x272.jpg" alt="Win a $10,000 Space Coast Adventure Holiday" class="alignnone wp-image-177074 size-medium" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro-642x272.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro-768x326.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro-600x255.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro.jpg 844w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The team envisions compact LED devices that could be applied directly to the skin after surgical tumor removal to destroy any remaining malignant cells and reduce the risk of recurrence.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For example, after removing a melanoma or basal cell carcinoma, a patch-like LED device could deliver focused light to activate the nanoflakes at the surgical site. This type of portable, home-based treatment could make post-surgical cancer care safer, more convenient and &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40170176/"&gt;less dependent&lt;/a&gt; on hospital visits.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The innovation also opens the door to combination therapies. Photothermal treatment can make cancer cells more vulnerable to other forms of therapy, such as &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC9760263/"&gt;immunotherapy&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S2452262725000285"&gt;targeted drugs&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Heat generated by light can weaken tumor cells, make their membranes more permeable and trigger immune responses that help the body identify and destroy cancer. Integrating LED-based photothermal therapy with other approaches could make treatment plans more precise, effective and less toxic.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Although still in the early stages, the researchers are refining the technology and exploring new applications. They are studying how different wavelengths and exposure times affect outcomes and investigating whether other materials similar to tin oxide could reach deeper tissues, such as those affected by breast or colorectal cancers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another area of development is implantable nanoflake systems: tiny biocompatible devices that could provide ongoing photothermal control inside the body.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The potential for accessibility is one of the most exciting aspects of this work. Because LED-based devices are inexpensive to manufacture and simple to operate, they could be used in low-resource regions where access to cancer care is limited.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/38571427/"&gt;This could democratize&lt;/a&gt; advanced treatment by extending it beyond major hospitals. For superficial cancers detected early, LED therapy might even be incorporated into outpatient or cosmetic procedures, reducing recovery time and improving quality of life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Safety is another major advantage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chemotherapy damages rapidly dividing healthy cells across the body, and radiotherapy can harm normal tissue and cause fatigue or scarring. Photothermal therapy, by contrast, confines its effects to the illuminated site. It produces no systemic toxicity, no cumulative organ damage and minimal discomfort.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This high &lt;a href="https://www.science.org/doi/10.1126/sciadv.adx6350"&gt;precision&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40802759/"&gt;stems&lt;/a&gt; from both the optical targeting and the biological selectivity of the nanoflakes, which preferentially heat cancer cells due to their altered metabolism and greater sensitivity to thermal stress.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The next step is to translate these laboratory findings into preclinical and, eventually, human trials. While much work remains, LED-driven photothermal therapy could represent a shift in how we treat cancer, making therapies more precise, affordable and humane.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Light, one of nature's simplest energies, could become a powerful medical tool for &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC8002224/"&gt;selectively destroying tumors&lt;/a&gt; without harming healthy tissue. With innovations such as SnOx nanoflakes, the vision of non-invasive, localized, patient-friendly cancer treatment is coming steadily closer to reality.&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://counter.theconversation.com/content/267556/count.gif?distributor=republish-lightbox-basic" alt="The Conversation" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" loading="lazy"&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/profiles/justin-stebbing-1405462"&gt;Justin Stebbing&lt;/a&gt;, Professor of Biomedical Sciences, &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/institutions/anglia-ruskin-university-1887"&gt;Anglia Ruskin University&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This article is republished from &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com"&gt;The Conversation&lt;/a&gt; under a Creative Commons license. Read the &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/how-a-new-light-based-cancer-treatment-could-destroy-tumours-without-harming-healthy-cells-using-leds-267556"&gt;original article&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 01:02:32 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilwFBVV95cUxQVElPWFdjcFkzQ3JfS3RHaXFlT01PVGcwSEMzc1dzc2dqX05FcVlFWVd0bzMyVWhnNVZydVJOYzNVOTAwVnR4TjNYQzJ0b3NiQndzd3hJTGZUU0t0c283Q1ZGVmprRWZKRE1qMTV0Qmg2eHFVTkFVRTk5bXpiU2pHcWVJNHVpOGV4azRRbmxlRDhnbHVqNFdr</guid></item><item><title>乔治王子学校对手足口病高峰发出警告- WTOP</title><link>https://wtop.com/prince-georges-county/2025/10/warnings-about-a-spike-in-hand-foot-and-mouth-disease-in-pgcps/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="schema-summary"&gt;A warning has gone out to parents of Prince George's County Public Schools students about a spike in hand, foot and mouth disease. So far, students in over 40 schools have reported cases of the virus.&lt;/p&gt;

            &lt;div id="Entry-content" class="entry-content Entry-content "&gt;
                                                
                                
                &lt;p&gt;A warning has gone out to parents of Prince George’s County Public Schools students about a spike in &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/hand-foot-mouth/about/index.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;hand, foot and mouth disease.&lt;/a&gt; So far students in more than 40 schools have reported cases of the virus, impacting students from preschool to high school, since the school year began in late August.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It is a communicable disease,” said Dr. Traci Jones, who is the supervisor for the Office of School Health for Prince George’s County Public Schools. “It is not a life-threatening communicable disease, but it is a communicable disease that is easily transmitted.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She said kids should be properly washing their hands and staying home if they have symptoms, such as fever or open blisters.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The school system said the very early symptoms are similar to that of a cold: fever, lack of appetite, a sore throat and the other signs of a cold. Those appear about one to two days before blisters appear on the palms and feet, and sores develop in the mouth.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You can spread it and have it for up to a week, and then usually one to two days before the blisters come, that’s when you get your most infectious,” Jones said. “But you don’t know that you’re infectious at the time, because you feel perfectly fine.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That’s why she repeatedly stressed the need for parents and kids to wash their hands.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“One of the things I see people do now is they’re wearing gloves all the time, trying not to get it,” she said. “But if you come in contact with it and it’s on your gloves, all you’re going to do is spread it to others. So that is not an answer — to put gloves on — but hand washing is a big way of curtailing it.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jones also asked parents to thoroughly and repeatedly wipe down toys and other things that kids might put their hands or mouths on.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Schools are increasing our cleaning protocols so that we can help curtail the spread of it. We have crews coming in after hours to clean,” she said. “We have instructed our cleaning crews to — what they would normally wait until at the end of the day to clean — do it twice a day in our attempts to curtail it as much as possible. We’re also going to start increasing hand washing for our students, making sure that’s done more frequently.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Any child who does get the virus is being told to stay home until they’ve been fever free for 24 hours and all blisters on their hands have crusted over. Mouth sores that can cause a child to drool also need to be closed up.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Our goal is to try to prevent the spread of this as much as possible,” said Jones.&lt;/p&gt;
                
                
                &lt;p class="After-content"&gt;
                                    &lt;/p&gt;

            &lt;p class="single-page__signature bottom"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Get breaking news and daily headlines delivered to your email inbox by signing up &lt;a href="https://wtop.com/newsletter-signup/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="single-page__signature bottom"&gt;© 2025 WTOP. All Rights Reserved. This website is not intended for users located within the European Economic Area.&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;/div&gt;
            &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>WTOP</author><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 01:01:06 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMirwFBVV95cUxNUWN1M050dEhfRGRvZFlxX1N2NU9ER2tiR2YxVk1wLWZVS2JPdTdkQ2lfR3Y1YzI0VXJXWFMtWmV3bVBMMnZhS3MzZ0lYZmo3TzZPc21scnlXclUxSXYxaFVkSklyWTg4aXlTNDZlQU41TzRXU0I1VnJUWWZKUFVkTkYxZS15ZEF1MXJndDlxX3E3ZmNva2R4WWcyNXhXbXoyLUZ0MHhlTndvVTlLek1J</guid></item><item><title>卫生专家对新出现的更致命的mpox形式表示担忧- Queerty</title><link>https://www.queerty.com/health-experts-express-concern-over-new-deadlier-form-of-mpox-that-has-emerged-20251024/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="cf-column"&gt;
            &lt;h2 data-translate="blocked_why_headline"&gt;Why have I been blocked?&lt;/h2&gt;

            &lt;p data-translate="blocked_why_detail"&gt;This website is using a security service to protect itself from online attacks. The action you just performed triggered the security solution. There are several actions that could trigger this block including submitting a certain word or phrase, a SQL command or malformed data.&lt;/p&gt;
          &lt;/div&gt;

          &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Queerty</author><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMisgFBVV95cUxOMlNRUFlDbk9XUlBTcWc4bGhaS00xakdmU3hPSldEUlR3UDBSSk5JNTUzZHNtVUpvUWxFNVF4eHh5RnNnbndCWllOOU9oX0d1Q19VRnlnaFRwN0VIaVZGVEc4MGNFR0dKTVFQcHJWMUJJT2FrUjBQT2puZmdwNHNvVzduLWFSMUhIODhVWDVPX3lQS0NXZV9qbFA3eDUxODRKU2pTQ09FdUlsOUswODhENjRR</guid></item></channel></rss>