<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>GNews Health</title><link>https://news.google.com/</link><description></description><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>这两位疫苗专家说，这是你应该接种新冠疫苗和流感疫苗的时候--《华盛顿邮报》</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/health/2025/10/19/covid-vaccine-flu-shot-timing/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="7WUICWJJ4FFCXJFWXHEEQUTTH4" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Flu season is here. The summer wave of the coronavirus has receded, but the winter uptick is likely around the corner. Shots &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/health/2025/09/19/cdc-covid-vaccine-vote-acip/" target="_blank"&gt;are available&lt;/a&gt; for both respiratory viruses, raising questions about the best time to get these shots if you haven’t gotten one already.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:04:26 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihgFBVV95cUxOYVI2MHdsMG5zQUlZRUpFRG5LNHNMSVd6bjBvNHM3dGR4ZTVtLTVvVXV6VkhlYWNRclVkYlFIY1ljXzVSb1lpd2xSajJRTlI2ektVZ0R5d0RiU3lpLWV4WXhoVG1yYmVMUmlBM1g3c3AzWDlhcHI4RndZZmFBR2VTZmhlMmNJQQ</guid></item><item><title>您的牙刷充满了细菌- BBC</title><link>https://www.bbc.com/future/article/20251017-why-you-might-want-to-clean-your-toothbrush-more</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="sc-85f9acf9-0 kySSTS"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;But Hartmann sees this as less of a concern for people who do live together. "People who live together share a &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://elifesciences.org/articles/00458" class="sc-f9178328-0 jZoZnB"&gt;higher proportion of the microbes&lt;/a&gt; in their mouth &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41586-022-05620-1" class="sc-f9178328-0 jZoZnB"&gt;than people who don't&lt;/a&gt;," she says. "I doubt this is driven by such an indirect route as storing toothbrushes close by, as opposed to the more direct route of kissing or less indirect route of sharing." (It's worth noting that dog owners will often &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://elifesciences.org/articles/00458" class="sc-f9178328-0 jZoZnB"&gt;share many of the same microbes as their pets&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Indeed, some of the viruses found on toothbrushes could in fact be working in our favour – Hartmann and her team found that &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.frontiersin.org/journals/microbiomes/articles/10.3389/frmbi.2024.1396560/full" class="sc-f9178328-0 jZoZnB"&gt;toothbrushes host thriving communities&lt;/a&gt; of viruses known as bacteriophages, which infect bacteria rather than humans and can help to control their numbers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 fsBZby"&gt;&lt;span id="what's-the-risk?" class="sc-d16436d-0 cVoAro"&gt;&lt;b id="what's-the-risk?" class="sc-d16436d-0 kPzeuB"&gt;What's the risk?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span id="" class="sc-d16436d-0 cVoAro"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;In most cases the risk from pathogens is small, agrees Zinn, but it could be more of a concern for those whose immune systems are compromised, meaning they are more prone to infections. &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.mdpi.com/2076-2607/8/9/1379" class="sc-f9178328-0 jZoZnB"&gt;Zinn's research&lt;/a&gt;, along with other similar studies that have &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0964339721001099" class="sc-f9178328-0 jZoZnB"&gt;sequenced bacterial DNA from toothbrushes&lt;/a&gt;, have found that at least some of these bacteria carry genes that make them resistant to antibiotics. This means that if they do cause infections they are harder to treat. But Zinn adds that in his study these genes were at "at relatively low levels" and so only present "a moderate concern from a public health perspective". One study of 50 toothbrushes from students in Italy, however, found all of them carried bacteria that were &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://journalmrji.com/index.php/MRJI/article/view/304" class="sc-f9178328-0 jZoZnB"&gt;resistant to multiple drugs&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Some toothbrushes come infused with &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0300571206001990" class="sc-f9178328-0 jZoZnB"&gt;antimicrobial treatments&lt;/a&gt; that are marketed as being a way to keep the bacteria living on your brush under control. But most studies seem to indicate that these treatments &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://aap.onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/abs/10.1902/jop.2003.74.3.312" class="sc-f9178328-0 jZoZnB"&gt;do little&lt;/a&gt; to limit the &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0300571206001990" class="sc-f9178328-0 jZoZnB"&gt;number of bacteria living on your brush&lt;/a&gt;, and may even lead to an &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.liebertpub.com/doi/10.1089/mdr.2006.12.83" class="sc-f9178328-0 jZoZnB"&gt;increase in antimicrobial-resistant species&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;In fact, allowing your toothbrush simply to &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.dentalhealthcareeoe.nhs.uk/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/supervised-toothbrushing-guidelines-final-20.9.pdf" class="sc-f9178328-0 jZoZnB"&gt;air dry at room temperature in an upright position&lt;/a&gt; after use can be a simple way of reducing the microbes living there. Many viruses, including &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://link.springer.com/article/10.1007/s00784-022-04530-w" class="sc-f9178328-0 jZoZnB"&gt;influenza and coronaviruses&lt;/a&gt;, break down as they dry out. Bacteria such as &lt;i id="streptococcus-mutans" class="sc-d16436d-0 gbdkAi"&gt;Streptococcus mutans&lt;/i&gt;, which are a major contributor to tooth decay, can remain viable on toothbrush bristles for up to eight hours but by &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.ingentaconnect.com/content/aapd/jodc/2008/00000075/00000001/art00007" class="sc-f9178328-0 jZoZnB"&gt;12 hours they begin to die off&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BBC</author><pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 09:00:48 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilwFBVV95cUxNbEptRFhGRk96LUs2dlc5VGVvZHBmZ3AwTFFGbzkta2M5QjVHdkU2YW9wRk4tUTdsejJsOWxFNlRnX2RCNi1JY25yOEN0M0hTcExiSHBENjhXSVFvWXI5MExWTjN1c3haaFJMdU82c3VYYWNHblJQQnhDQmxhMDhvTml0LW00cGRYekotd0liTlpQVU05Smd3</guid></item><item><title>一位专业力量训练师说，衰老的秘诀不仅仅是举重，以下是他的建议- Fit&amp;Well</title><link>https://www.fitandwell.com/exercise/cardio-strength-workouts/an-expert-strength-trainer-says-the-secret-to-aging-well-isnt-just-lifting-weights-heres-what-he-recommends</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="article-body" class="article__body "&gt;
&lt;p id="5f62931a-2b88-4172-88cc-517d1629c629"&gt;I spend a lot of time looking at fitness trends, but one constant has been strength training, and for good reason.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="ad-unit-1" class="ad-unit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Recently, however, the concept of lifting weights for long-term health and longevity has featured repeatedly in my social feeds, on my favorite websites and in my daily conversations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a id="elk-seasonal" href="" data-url="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p id="5f62931a-2b88-4172-88cc-517d1629c629-2"&gt;However, when I put this to &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://onepeloton.pxf.io/c/221109/1493570/17622?subId1=fitandwell-gb-1440825047931391567&amp;amp;sharedId=fitandwell-gb&amp;amp;u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.onepeloton.com%2F" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.onepeloton.com/" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" rel="sponsored noopener" data-hl-processed="hawklinks" data-placeholder-url="https://onepeloton.pxf.io/c/221109/1493570/17622?subId1=hawk-custom-tracking&amp;amp;sharedId=hawk-prefix&amp;amp;u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.onepeloton.com%2F" data-google-interstitial="false" data-merchant-name="Peloton" data-merchant-id="317344" data-merchant-network="ImpactRad" data-merchant-url="onepeloton.com"&gt;Peloton&lt;/a&gt;’s expert strength training instructor, &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.instagram.com/benjaminalldis/?hl=en" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.instagram.com/benjaminalldis/?hl=en" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;Ben Alldis&lt;/a&gt;, he said that while strength training is important, it’s not the only&lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt;thing that matters if you want to age well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“To live a long, healthy, happy life, adding variety to your training is where the magic happens,” he says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="ad-unit-2" class="ad-unit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a id="elk-mix-strength-training-with-cardio-and-stretching" href="" data-url="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;h2 class="article-body__section" id="section-mix-strength-training-with-cardio-and-stretching"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Mix strength training with cardio and stretching&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="f21a7159-b026-417e-9df2-d85d0145b521"&gt;Alldis emphasizes that strength training should still be a big component of your weekly workouts, because it can help you maintain the muscle you need for everyday activities and support healthy aging.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC4035379/" target="_blank" data-url="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC4035379/" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;Research&lt;/a&gt; even shows that older people with higher muscle mass have a lower risk of dying from all major causes. But that doesn’t mean lifting weights is all you need to do.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cardiorespiratory fitness is also strongly linked to longevity, so it’s important to incorporate some exercises that improve your heart and lung health—like brisk walking, jogging, cycling or swimming—too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div id="slice-container-newsletterForm-articleInbodyContent-HYovotBKuQL7ZtxD9TJHZ7" class="slice-container newsletter-inbodyContent-slice newsletterForm-articleInbodyContent-HYovotBKuQL7ZtxD9TJHZ7 slice-container-newsletterForm"&gt;&lt;div data-hydrate="true" class="newsletter-form__wrapper newsletter-form__wrapper--inbodyContent"&gt;&lt;div class="newsletter-form__container"&gt;&lt;section class="newsletter-form__main-section"&gt;&lt;p class="newsletter-form__strapline"&gt;Start your week with achievable workout ideas, health tips and wellbeing advice in your inbox.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I would always suggest getting a good mixture of cardio, strength and stretching in your routine,” says Alldis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This well-rounded approach ticks all the boxes for a strong heart, functional muscle and mobile joints.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a id="elk-prioritize-consistency" href="" data-url="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;h2 class="article-body__section" id="section-prioritize-consistency"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Prioritize consistency &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="2d7fc781-c5f2-4bbe-b9de-3529f3d6fd09"&gt;I asked Alldis how to split your weekly workouts if you’re new to exercise and want to follow this approach. His advice was to prioritize building a consistent habit first.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I think a good goal is always to aim for three days a week,” he says. “I would probably recommend just sticking with cardio or strength to begin with.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Once you’ve built this routine, he suggests adding 15-20 minutes of stretching to the end of your sessions to improve mobility and aid recovery.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When you’re on a roll with this, you can start tweaking your program to make sure it aligns with the &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://odphp.health.gov/our-work/nutrition-physical-activity/physical-activity-guidelines/current-guidelines" target="_blank" data-url="https://odphp.health.gov/our-work/nutrition-physical-activity/physical-activity-guidelines/current-guidelines" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;national recommendations&lt;/a&gt;, which include:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul id="4d8078aa-ba13-467b-bd88-e50f72c16dbd"&gt;&lt;li&gt;150 minutes of moderate-intensity aerobic exercise or 75 minutes of vigorous aerobic exercise every week.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Two additional sessions of muscle-strengthening exercise that work the major muscles of the body every week.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Fit&amp;Well</author><pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 06:05:55 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi_AFBVV95cUxNZWNkeGpQdTVoZFhlZnpEY1E3NVJ2VnNLdkwwM1VjODA2YmJzYkhHYUpMaFd6MjZBZ3NIWFNyVkNlQjdKcDRLaTFya0t4TEFyd3BkY0N6RXdsVm9lY3VWODBpVldfbWNtTFprU2hYbDNlNTdoWVFQZEV2cmZJV0Rwc01yTWpURmRyaHBLalNIVC0yRGZNNkpLUWluUXQxdzN2ZTFETkNuTGJWQmdOdFFHcS03V0p4bjRPSGt4NGhtZFVzVk55VGlGUHk0bXoyQldkb0QzRS05VlJYbmR5T0x1Smp3X1pza1E5WVRFTUtnZnVEUWFIRGFRUzJVRVY</guid></item><item><title>突破性癌症疗法在不损害健康细胞的情况下阻止肿瘤生长-《科学日报》</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/10/251018102122.htm</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p id="first" class="lead"&gt;Scientists at the Francis Crick Institute and Vividion Therapeutics have discovered chemical compounds that can precisely prevent the cancer-driving gene RAS from connecting with a key pathway responsible for tumor growth.&lt;/p&gt;

						&lt;div id="text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The potential treatment is now moving into its first human clinical trial. If proven safe and effective, it could become a way to treat a wide range of cancers while minimizing harm to healthy cells.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The RAS gene plays a central role in controlling how cells grow and divide, but mutations in this gene occur in roughly one in five cancers. When mutated, RAS becomes permanently active, continually sending signals that push cells to keep growing and multiplying.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Inside the cell, RAS sits on the membrane and acts as the starting signal in a chain of growth processes. Completely shutting down RAS or the enzymes it controls has proven difficult, because these same pathways are essential for normal cell function. One of the enzymes linked to RAS, called PI3K, also helps regulate blood sugar through insulin. Blocking PI3K entirely can lead to side effects such as hyperglycemia.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In their study, published on October 9 in &lt;em&gt;Science&lt;/em&gt;, the team combined chemical screening with biological testing to identify compounds that stop RAS and PI3K from interacting, while leaving normal cell activity intact.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Researchers at Vividion Therapeutics pinpointed a set of small molecules that permanently attach to the surface of PI3K near the spot where RAS would normally bind. Using an assay created by the Crick researchers, they confirmed that these compounds successfully blocked the RAS-PI3K interaction but still allowed PI3K to perform its other roles, including those related to insulin signaling.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Crick team and their collaborators at Vividion then tested one of the compounds in mice with RAS-mutated lung tumors. The treatment stopped tumor growth, and the researchers found no signs of elevated blood sugar levels.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="insertion_middle"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Next, they tried combining the new compound with one or two additional drugs that target enzymes within the same pathway. Together, the treatments produced stronger and longer-lasting tumor suppression than any of the drugs used alone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The scientists also tested the compound in mice with tumors carrying mutations in another cancer-linked gene, HER2, which is often overactive in breast cancer and also connects with PI3K. Tumor growth was again halted, even though the effect did not rely on RAS. This finding suggests that the new compound could potentially help stop the growth of a broader range of cancers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The drug has now entered the first clinical trial in humans to test for safety and side effects in people with both RAS and HER2 mutations. The trial will also assess if the potential treatment is more effective in combination with other drugs targeting RAS.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Julian Downward, Principal Group Leader of the Oncogene Biology Laboratory at the Crick, said: "Given the RAS gene is mutated across a wide range of cancers, we've been exploring how to stop it interacting with cell growth pathways for many years, but side effects have held back the development of treatments.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Our collaborative effort has overcome this challenge by targeting the PI3K and RAS interaction specifically, leaving PI3K free to bind with its other targets. It's exciting to see these clinical trials starting, highlighting the power of understanding chemistry and fundamental biology to get to something with potential to help people with cancer."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"This discovery is a great example of how new discovery approaches can open up completely novel ways to tackle cancer," said Matt Patricelli, Ph.D., Chief Scientific Officer of Vividion. "By designing molecules that stop RAS and PI3K from connecting, while still allowing healthy cell processes to continue, we've found a way to selectively block a key cancer growth signal. It's incredibly rewarding to see this science now progressing in the clinic, where it has the potential to make a real difference for patients."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

					&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Science Daily</author><pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 05:53:03 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMib0FVX3lxTE5PT2Q2NzRUQi1yNjVsbEtWMFN3eFFOeTdzZjN1R3FjSGhkNXBxbFRUYTM1RUFwVHRXVENZM3lBcGtIS1kwdUw2MUdrOEdHN2dGQ0UzQXA1RndfR1pMMVVEUUlBWkNDd0pNRDdYYmtVUQ</guid></item><item><title>​4种可与胡芦巴种子结合调节血糖的食物-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/food-news/4-foods-to-combine-with-fenugreek-seeds-to-regulate-blood-sugar/photostory/124605188.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="COQxt" data-ua-type="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;As per experts, curcumin in turmeric reduces inflammation and improves insulin action. According to a study titled&lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC3857752/"&gt; Curcumin and Diabetes: A Systematic Review&lt;/a&gt;, curcumin could favorably affect most of the leading aspects of diabetes, including insulin resistance, hyperglycemia, hyperlipidemia, and islet apoptosis and necrosis. In addition, curcumin could prevent the deleterious complications of diabetes.&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How to consume: &lt;/strong&gt;It is suggested that one can combine methi seeds with turmeric and warm milk or water for added benefits. One can add them to curries as well for effective results, supporting digestion, reducing inflammation, regulating blood sugar, and enhancing overall metabolic health naturally.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All Images Courtesy: istock&lt;br&gt;Disclaimer: The information provided in this article is meant for general knowledge only and should not be taken as medical advice. Always talk to your doctor before starting any new routine.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 03:40:14 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi3gFBVV95cUxPZDlhNUdwcEhDZ0E5azQ2c3J3UzFCRExTSjltQlE3eFFUN3FwZHBac2QwbzRPamx4blhpRFJJSVhQaGJCemRGcjFnMzVfZUY1MFJ1WExXQndVcFRycVRnY1NwU0htTjNrc0piLVZYYXNhNHJqNTJQSzlGTFBFOURMVTBVWWNoWWMtOHJxclJIMnVWWkk5dXliVW9nQXdWcTVENGYwLU9ab2pCQkFDOU5KMW9kSExEbF82eG9KM1ZZMGdybHMtY05BU09qdVdPZ1BvRWd2Tl9fdDVZQldOVlHSAeYBQVVfeXFMTnMxcWczeFB0V0xValBqN3p6LVBlZ2luZ0pRZE1qeVhsR3dKWjQwT2JEX3JpaGoyY3ZTV2xGV2VYT1hPMDFjVFkydHlpSlhmR2ppRkx2eTd5SDdrRDVXMno4QldSS1J5X29Sc01fdzVZM0d2MmE4RFJsQmIxVDNwWHZldGpZQlpQS0NzTzVkRUdrb1p4a2c4aFZoLWM5NjlEMENjMHk2UUhjWnU1c1pEMDFIQVR1TVlHZHFfNkgtQ01YME5WWFhNZk14bGdZVkJhcmpRdG00clJieVNldUZrVjljeHU5UlE</guid></item><item><title>新的血液检测实际上可以检测到我/CFS吗？以下是我们所知道的- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/can-a-new-blood-test-actually-detect-me-cfs-heres-what-we-know</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Scientists in the United Kingdom &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/society/2025/oct/08/scientists-say-they-have-first-blood-test-to-diagnose-chronic-fatigue-syndrome-me"&gt;say they have developed&lt;/a&gt; a blood test that can diagnose  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/chronic-fatigue-syndrome" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73056" data-postid="177505" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;myalgic encephalomyelitis&lt;/a&gt;/ &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/chronic-fatigue-syndrome" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73056" data-postid="177505" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;chronic fatigue syndrome&lt;/a&gt; (ME/CFS) &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1186/s12967-025-07203-w"&gt;with 96 percent accuracy&lt;/a&gt; – the first of its kind.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For many who live with the debilitating condition, this will be exciting news.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Despite affecting &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1186/s12967-020-02269-0"&gt;millions of people worldwide&lt;/a&gt;, this condition remains poorly understood. It is characterized by unrelenting fatigue that doesn't improve with rest, and post-exertional malaise – &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1111/j.1365-2796.2011.02428.x"&gt;a worsening of symptoms&lt;/a&gt; after even minor physical or mental activity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/massive-study-links-8-genetic-signals-to-chronic-fatigue-syndrome"&gt;Massive Study Links 8 Genetic Signals to Chronic Fatigue Syndrome&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yet with no reliable test, many people wait years for a diagnosis. This usually depends on symptoms meeting certain clinical criteria. But &lt;a href="https://emerge.org.au/diagnosis/"&gt;diagnostic criteria can be controversial as they vary worldwide&lt;/a&gt;, and many are outdated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;An accurate blood test could be a game-changer for diagnosis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So, how excited should we get? Here's what we know.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;How diagnosis works without a test&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Currently, you can only receive a diagnosis if you experience disabling fatigue – one of the &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1300/J092v11n01_02"&gt;key symptoms&lt;/a&gt; according to most clinical criteria – for at least six months, accompanied by post-exertional malaise.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But people with the condition often experience &lt;a href="https://www.healthdirect.gov.au/chronic-fatigue-syndrome-cfs-me"&gt;a wide range of other symptoms&lt;/a&gt;, including headaches, muscle or joint pain, sleep disturbances, dizziness, a racing heart, and problems with memory, thinking, and decision making.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So, clinicians must also rule out other conditions with overlapping symptoms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This means diagnosis relies heavily on clinicians' knowledge of ME/CFS and their willingness to listen to the patient's complex symptom history. This process can &lt;a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/books/NBK284892/#:%7E:text=Diagnosing%20ME/CFS%20in%20the,2014;%20ProHealth%2C%202008"&gt;take years&lt;/a&gt; – and the delay in diagnosis has real consequences.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Evidence suggests early intervention is key to recovery. Rest during the early stages of the illness likely results in better long-term outcomes, as has been suggested for the clinically similar disease &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1371/journal.pone.0264331"&gt;long COVID&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One study showed a &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.3390/diagnostics12102540"&gt;delayed ME/CFS diagnosis&lt;/a&gt; was linked to poorer outcomes, meaning recovery was less likely and the chance of developing more severe symptoms increased.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Without a definitive diagnosis, patients regularly face disbelief about their illness and have limited access to information, health-care services, and medical benefits.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Frequent delays in diagnosis may contribute to the condition's low recovery rate, which is &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.3390/diagnostics12102540"&gt;estimated at just 1–10 percent&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What the new study looked at&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;To develop a diagnostic test, the new study identified biomarkers that may be specific to people with this condition.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In this case, the biomarkers relate to  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/epigenetic-changes" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73027" data-postid="177505" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;epigenetics&lt;/a&gt; – changes in the structure of a person's chromosomes, influencing which genes can be turned on or off.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These changes occur due to environmental influences such as stress, infection, and exercise. So, when someone develops ME/CFS, the illness may change the structure of their chromosomes – but until now researchers hadn't identified what this would look like.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/spark-into-space-comp?utm_source=promo_astro"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro-642x272.jpg" alt="Mid Article Promo Astro" class="alignnone wp-image-177074 size-medium" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro-642x272.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro-768x326.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro-600x255.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro.jpg 844w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers examined blood samples from people they knew had ME/CFS and identified around 200 such biomarkers. These changes formed a distinct biological "signature" that was not present in the blood of healthy participants in the comparison group.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This signature was very accurate in correctly identifying which samples were from people with the condition and which were from the comparison group.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to the researchers, the test's sensitivity was 92 percent – this is the probability a positive result will show when someone has the condition. It had a specificity of 98 percent, meaning the probability it can rule out negative cases.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This combined to an overall diagnostic accuracy of 96 percent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;So, is this a breakthrough?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;This research is promising, but it's still very early days. It was a proof-of-concept study, meaning small-scale research to initially test whether an idea might work.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In this case, researchers explored the idea that structural changes in chromosomes could be used as biomarkers of ME/CFS. Their results suggest they can.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, there were several limitations. The study involved a relatively small number of people: 47 participants with severe ME/CFS and 61 in the healthy "control" group.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The ME/CFS group had more females, and its participants were so severely affected they were housebound. So they presumably had lower activity levels than the control group.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We know a person's &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.tig.2020.06.016"&gt;sex&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.3390/biomedicines10010126"&gt;activity levels&lt;/a&gt; can influence these chromosomal changes, so this may have affected the results.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To develop a diagnostic test that can be used widely, several crucial steps remain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;How much a person's sex and exercise levels influence these biomarkers needs to be determined. The biomarkers will also need to be validated in larger, more diverse groups, which include people with less and more severe symptoms than in this study and those from different backgrounds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To confirm these biomarkers are truly specific to ME/CFS, they need to be compared with other conditions that share similar symptoms, such as multiple sclerosis and fibromyalgia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Finally, it's also important that a test, if developed, should be affordable and accessible.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;ME/CFS remains a severely underdiagnosed condition, and the lack of a reliable test continues to delay care and worsen outcomes. Identifying biomarkers, as this study aimed to do, is a promising first step.&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://counter.theconversation.com/content/267099/count.gif?distributor=republish-lightbox-basic" alt="The Conversation" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" loading="lazy"&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/profiles/sarah-annesley-1397560"&gt;Sarah Annesley&lt;/a&gt;, Senior Postdoctoral Research Fellow in Cell and Molecular Biology, &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/institutions/la-trobe-university-842"&gt;La Trobe University&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This article is republished from &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com"&gt;The Conversation&lt;/a&gt; under a Creative Commons license. Read the &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/can-a-new-blood-test-really-detect-me-cfs-an-expert-unpacks-new-research-267099"&gt;original article&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 01:01:27 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilgFBVV95cUxPTUNOYmo1R0c1QmxKQkx2NHpnLWZQMXc0NnZkWFk4ajNxeVhSV0lmcUVmNWxsWFpUdmhtTG1GcjlWdzVNTDdfY3B1Z2NhcmkyRVZaWVBuWXM1SE5BS2VkMTNmcllzZXhuZGpQNUpDX2toTm1RUXBzQmpqWE0zMnFza0JrUTlQY3NROFdxNTNTMjAwTXhHVGc</guid></item><item><title>“姑娘，吃你的疯狂药丸吧！ ’抗抑郁药重塑为热门生活方式配饰- wsj.com</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/health/wellness/anti-depressants-lifestyle-accessory-3b66027d</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>wsj.com</author><pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 01:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiAFBVV95cUxNSGNIandtTG1Xd01ycC1wVnFaVmh4VGVmcHUwbnlUQVZxX1VwOHp1RFpub1JJQkFzSG5kQmtsYlpOc0hHOHlhTktRNUduclFidWJCeUcwVUdNY1VIdWpmVFp5OEd6clFkQnJSMm9fcVZFcnF5ZnFkSS15VXotT25ablQxU2xfSzY2</guid></item><item><title>让退休生活感觉像是人生最美好时光的10个爱好- VegOut</title><link>https://vegoutmag.com/things-to-do/d-t-10-hobbies-that-make-retirement-feel-like-the-best-years-of-your-life/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="page__content mt-4"&gt;
							&lt;p&gt;Retirement isn’t an ending.&lt;br&gt;
It’s a schedule you finally get to design around energy, curiosity, and connection.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you want it to feel like the best chapter yet, pick hobbies that compound—skills and friendships that get better with time.&lt;br&gt;
Here are ten that do exactly that, plus simple ways to start.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;1) Walking—on purpose&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Walking sounds basic, but it’s a Swiss Army knife for retired life.&lt;br&gt;
You get movement, sunlight, and conversation—without special gear or sore joints.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Turn it into a practice, not just a pastime.&lt;br&gt;
Choose a daily loop and give it a theme: birds one day, architecture the next, neighborhood history on Fridays.&lt;br&gt;
Invite one friend each week and talk phone-free.&lt;br&gt;
If you like structure, join or start a local walking club (libraries and parks departments are underrated hubs).&lt;br&gt;
Track steps if that motivates you, but don’t let metrics outrun joy. The win is consistency and company.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On my side, “camera walks” changed everything. When I bring a lightweight mirrorless camera, I notice textures, colors, small street moments. The walk becomes a &lt;a href="https://vegoutmag.com/things-to-do/r-research-says-these-7-activities-can-make-you-instantly-happier/"&gt;mindfulness exercise&lt;/a&gt; I actually look forward to.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;2) Community gardening&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you’ve never pulled a sun-warm tomato from a vine you tended, you’re missing a quiet kind of magic.&lt;br&gt;
Community plots give you fresh produce, real conversations, and a rhythm to the year.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Start simple: salad greens, herbs, cherry tomatoes, and one “just-for-fun” plant like shishito or lemon cucumbers.&lt;br&gt;
If you’re plant-based or plant-curious, the garden also nudges your menu in that direction without forcing it—basil practically begs to become pesto, and mint turns water into something you actually crave.&lt;br&gt;
Bonus dividends: dirt therapy, vitamin D, and neighbors you’ll know by first name by August.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Not into bending and kneeling? Build two standing-height beds and use lightweight fabric pots. Your back will thank you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;3) Playing music again&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Did you abandon the piano in 8th grade? Guitar in your 20s?&lt;br&gt;
Retirement is the perfect time to pick it up with zero performance anxiety.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Find a teacher who gets adults. They’ll prioritize songs you love over drills you hate.&lt;br&gt;
Set a tiny commitment—ten minutes a day, five days a week.&lt;br&gt;
Join a low-pressure jam circle, ukulele club, or community choir. (Choirs are secret wellness machines: breathing, posture, focus, new friends.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A neat trick: keep the instrument out, not in a case. Visibility beats &lt;a href="https://vegoutmag.com/lifestyle/gen-12-signs-youre-more-disciplined-than-90-of-people-even-if-you-dont-feel-like-it/"&gt;discipline&lt;/a&gt;. When my guitar leans by the couch, I end up strumming during ad breaks and call that a win.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;4) Volunteering with a clear role&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Volunteering adds purpose, but it’s easy to overcommit.&lt;br&gt;
The sweet spot is a specific task on a predictable cadence: food bank packing on Thursday mornings, trail maintenance the first Saturday, literacy tutoring every other week.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Think of it like a part-time job you actually want.&lt;br&gt;
Ask for a role description, a point person, and an end date you can renew.&lt;br&gt;
You’ll show up more, feel useful, and &lt;a href="http://www.webmd.com/mental-health/signs-resentment#:~:text=Use%20self%2Dcompassion,pain%20with%20mindfulness%20and%20kindness." target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;avoid resentment&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If food is your thing, soup kitchens and community fridges always need steady help. There’s something grounding about chopping onions next to someone you wouldn’t have met otherwise and leaving with tired hands and a full heart.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;5) Photography—story first, gear second&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You don’t need a pro setup to capture the &lt;a href="https://vegoutmag.com/lifestyle/8-signs-youre-living-according-to-your-values-instead-of-societys-expectations/"&gt;life you’re living&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br&gt;
Smartphone cameras are incredible, and the best camera is the one you carry.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Give yourself projects that force you to look closer: “One doorway a day,” “Faces of the farmers market,” “Morning light for 30 days.”&lt;br&gt;
Learn just three controls—exposure, focus, and composition (rule of thirds and leading lines carry you far).&lt;br&gt;
Share small: a private album with family, a monthly photo email to friends, prints on your fridge.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This hobby also pairs perfectly with travel and walking. You’ll remember the texture of the trip—the way steam rose from ramen in a rainy alley—long after the itinerary fades.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;6) Cooking clubs (with a theme)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-60994" src="https://vegoutmag.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/06/flourish-after-retirement.png" alt="" srcset="https://vegoutmag.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/06/flourish-after-retirement.png 1600w, https://vegoutmag.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/06/flourish-after-retirement-300x158.png 300w, https://vegoutmag.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/06/flourish-after-retirement-1024x538.png 1024w, https://vegoutmag.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/06/flourish-after-retirement-768x403.png 768w, https://vegoutmag.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/06/flourish-after-retirement-1536x806.png 1536w, https://vegoutmag.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/06/flourish-after-retirement-1200x630.png 1200w, https://vegoutmag.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/06/flourish-after-retirement-857x450.png 857w, https://vegoutmag.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/06/flourish-after-retirement-900x473.png 900w, https://vegoutmag.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/06/flourish-after-retirement-420x221.png 420w, https://vegoutmag.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/06/flourish-after-retirement-840x441.png 840w" sizes="(max-width: 1600px) 100vw, 1600px"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cooking hits the retirement trifecta: creativity, community, and health.&lt;br&gt;
Starting a monthly cooking club is an easy way to turn eating into a social ritual.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Pick a theme structure so it doesn’t fizzle:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;“Country of the Month” (Lebanon, Mexico City street food, Korean temple cuisine)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;“One Ingredient, Five Ways” (cauliflower steaks, aloo gobi, roasted florets, soup, tacos)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;“Plant-Forward Classics” (bolognese with lentils and mushrooms, jackfruit tacos, tofu katsu)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rotate homes, cap prep at 60 minutes, and keep recipes in a shared folder.&lt;br&gt;
If you’re exploring more &lt;a href="https://www.ncoa.org/article/cooking-with-plant-based-protein-5-tasty-options-to-try/#:~:text=Swap%20cooked%20lentils%20for%20meat,and%20heartier%20with%20cooked%20lentils." target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;plant-based meals&lt;/a&gt;, clubs make it fun; skepticism drops when the food is genuinely good and there’s laughter around the table.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One pragmatic trick from restaurant life: mise en place. Prep and portion ingredients before you turn on the heat. Stress drops, flavor goes up.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;7) Strength and mobility that you’ll actually do&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The goal isn’t a six-pack; it’s freedom—getting off the floor, carrying groceries, traveling without fear of stairs.&lt;br&gt;
Two to three short strength sessions a week plus daily mobility will change how your whole life feels.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Keep it minimal: squats, push/pull, hinge, carry.&lt;br&gt;
A kettlebell, resistance bands, and a bath towel for shoulder mobility can handle most of it.&lt;br&gt;
If classes keep you accountable, try Pilates, tai chi, gentle yoga, or water aerobics.&lt;br&gt;
Measure what matters: “Can I get up from the floor without using my hands?” “Can I balance on one foot while I brush my teeth?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I track “streaks” for &lt;a href="https://www.fitandwell.com/features/a-trainer-says-this-10-minute-full-body-mobility-routine-is-a-non-negotiable-for-people-with-tight-hips-back-and-shoulders" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;ten-minute mobility&lt;/a&gt;. When I hit seven days, my back stops complaining and my sleep improves. That feedback is addictive in a good way.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;8) Mentoring and tutoring&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You’ve got decades of scar tissue and wisdom. Someone out there needs it.&lt;br&gt;
Mentoring is a high-leverage hobby: your one hour can bend a young person’s trajectory.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Choose a lane: reading buddies in elementary schools, résumé coaching at the library, mock interviews at a community college, entrepreneurship programs for teens, or industry mentoring through your old professional network.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Set boundaries up front (frequency, platforms, preferred times).&lt;br&gt;
Remember: your job isn’t to fix; it’s to ask good questions, reflect patterns, and celebrate progress.&lt;br&gt;
And yes, reverse mentoring is real—let the 20-year-old show you how they actually use the internet in 2025. You’ll trade value both ways.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;9) Micro-adventures and slow travel&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Travel doesn’t have to mean airports and time zones.&lt;br&gt;
A micro-adventure—one night somewhere new within 90 minutes of home—scratches the novelty itch with almost no logistics.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Pick a theme: historic inns on old highways, small-town diners with a vegan option, train day trips, mid-week coastal walks.&lt;br&gt;
For bigger trips, aim for slow travel: longer stays, fewer moves, neighborhood markets, local transit, easy mornings.&lt;br&gt;
House swaps are an underused option that make long stays affordable and interesting. Two retired couples swapping cities for a month? Everyone wins.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bring a simple ritual. I journal five lines a day—what I tasted, the best conversation, one small surprise. Later, that one page brings the entire place back.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;10) Making things with your hands&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There’s a specific satisfaction in finishing something tangible—pottery that holds your morning coffee, a stool you built, a quilt that keeps a grandkid warm.&lt;br&gt;
It anchors your days and gives your brain a restorative “focus mode.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Test-drive skills through beginner classes: pottery studios, community makerspaces, woodworking shops, textile labs.&lt;br&gt;
Start with small, useful projects to bank wins: a hand-thrown bowl, a cutting board, a sewn tote, a cyanotype print from leaves you gathered on a walk.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The secret is to iterate. “Same project, better each time.” It lowers the learning curve and keeps momentum high.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;How to pick the right hobby (and stick with it)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Two questions help cut through overwhelm:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Would I enjoy the process even if I never got “good”?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Does this invite other people in?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Then build a simple system:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Schedule it. Same day, same hour, treat it like a class.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Keep gear visible and ready. Barriers kill habits.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Track streaks, not perfection. Miss a day? Start a new streak.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Pair it with an anchor you already do (walk after coffee, practice guitar during the 3 p.m. slump).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Share progress publicly enough to feel accountable (a monthly photo roundup, a club calendar), but not so public it becomes performative.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;What these hobbies have in common&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They feed competence, connection, and contribution—the three ingredients that &lt;a href="https://vegoutmag.com/lifestyle/s-if-you-want-to-look-and-feel-youthful-in-your-retirement-years-stop-doing-these-8-things-immediately/"&gt;make retired life feel rich&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br&gt;
Competence: you’re still learning, improving, and solving.&lt;br&gt;
Connection: you regularly see people who expect you and are glad you came.&lt;br&gt;
Contribution: someone else benefits from your time—your cooking club, a student, your own future self who gets to &lt;a href="https://vegoutmag.com/lifestyle/c-lc-7-quiet-behaviors-that-reveal-youre-aging-with-more-grace-than-most-people-your-age/"&gt;age with grace&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And they scale. You can walk farther or shorter, cook for two or twelve, shoot photos on your block or in Kyoto. No matter your budget or mobility, there’s a version that fits.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;A quick example week (steal it, tweak it)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mon&lt;/strong&gt;: 30-minute strength + garden check-in&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tue&lt;/strong&gt;: Literacy tutoring (1 hour) + camera walk home&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Wed&lt;/strong&gt;: Cooking club prep (make vinaigrette, chop veg)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Thu&lt;/strong&gt;: Group walk + coffee&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fri&lt;/strong&gt;: Music lesson or practice (10–20 minutes)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sat&lt;/strong&gt;: Micro-adventure day trip, journal five lines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sun&lt;/strong&gt;: Batch cook two easy plant-forward dishes for the week&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Swap in pottery, yoga, or volunteering as needed. The shape matters more than the specifics.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Final thought&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Retirement isn’t an empty calendar. It’s an invitation.&lt;br&gt;
Pick one hobby from this list and give it four weeks. If it doesn’t click, swap it out. If it does, double down.&lt;br&gt;
Either way, you’ll be living on purpose—and that’s what makes these years feel like the best ones.&lt;/p&gt;
						&lt;/div&gt;
					&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>VegOut</author><pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 00:02:43 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMirgFBVV95cUxNNVV2SzdiYXloX1ZKc0dzVjRFd2NjczMxS3ZYS0FNbXNBQUdNMFNlNDFUejVQTTZlZVJuUWJ4bW0tOEZsTlVUYmZZOExXdzBfdExFX21mSzE2QVRSdml0eXhNNEZ4eWZLd3A4MFpGbHRKb0djc3RwVE9jMVhoXzl5WTdqbnF1eHN1em1iQWdHeGgwakllUWdsWlEycnJ6ODUzU0daQnl0S0ZnNl9BaUE</guid></item><item><title>随着当局启动应急计划-无聊的熊猫，在南方州再次发现“僵尸鹿病”</title><link>https://www.boredpanda.com/zombie-deer-disease-hits-southern-state-as-second-case-recorded/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The&lt;/span&gt;&lt;b&gt; Florida&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span&gt; Fish and Wildlife Conservation Commission (FWC) has detected its second case of &lt;/span&gt;&lt;b&gt;Chronic Wasting Disease (CWD)&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span&gt;, a &lt;/span&gt;&lt;b&gt;malady&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span&gt; that has a &lt;/span&gt;&lt;b&gt;100 percent fatality&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span&gt; rate among &lt;/span&gt;&lt;b&gt;deer&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The first case (for 2025) of the illness was detected by the Sunshine State’s neighboring Georgia.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The University of Minnesota reported at the time that it was the 36th US state to report what the academic institution dubbed a “fatal prion disease.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div id="post-highlights"&gt;&lt;span class="h2"&gt;Highlights&lt;/span&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span class="bullet-wrapper"&gt;&lt;i class="bullet"&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;The Florida Fish and Wildlife Conservation Commission confirmed its second case of Chronic Wasting Disease.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span class="bullet-wrapper"&gt;&lt;i class="bullet"&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;The infected deer was found in Holmes County near the Georgia border.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span class="bullet-wrapper"&gt;&lt;i class="bullet"&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;CWD is 100 percent fatal in deer and has no known treatment or vaccine.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;b&gt;Florida has put in place a “disease response plan”&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Deer resting on grass in natural habitat, relevant to zombie deer disease and wildlife health concerns.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="attachment-link-container shareable-image-block" id="pedro-lastra-F0dmGPe2KG0-unsplash-68f4143d2858f__700" data-href="http://www.boredpanda.com/zombie-deer-disease-hits-southern-state-as-second-case-recorded/?image_id=pedro-lastra-F0dmGPe2KG0-unsplash-68f4143d2858f__700.jpg"&gt;&lt;a class="web-share-button list-item-share new-share-experiment" data-location="single-post-image" data-title="“Zombie Deer Disease” Detected Again In Southern State As Authorities Launch Emergency Response Plan" data-share-url="https://www.boredpanda.com/zombie-deer-disease-hits-southern-state-as-second-case-recorded/?media_id=pedro-lastra-F0dmGPe2KG0-unsplash-68f4143d2858f__700" data-image="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/pedro-lastra-F0dmGPe2KG0-unsplash-68f4143d2858f__700.jpg"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;svg class="svg-icon icon-share-icon" role="img" viewbox="0 0 16 16"&gt;&lt;title&gt;Share icon&lt;/title&gt;&lt;path d="M0 15C0 10.8824 5.22292 10.0588 8.79817 10.0588V14.1765L15.7006 8.23061C15.7941 8.15345 15.8695 8.05559 15.9213 7.94441C15.9731 7.83323 16 7.71155 16 7.58824C16 7.46492 15.9731 7.34314 15.9213 7.23196C15.8695 7.12078 15.7941 7.02302 15.7006 6.94586L8.79817 1V5.11765C2.3995 5.11765 0 9.76235 0 15Z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/pedro-lastra-F0dmGPe2KG0-unsplash-68f4143d2858f__700.jpg?utm_campaign=rebelboost_true" alt="Deer resting on grass in natural habitat, relevant to zombie deer disease and wildlife health concerns." title="Deer resting on grass in natural habitat, relevant to zombie deer disease and wildlife health concerns." loading="lazy" fetchpriority="low"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="post-tablet-ad-within-content post-ads"&gt;&lt;span class="dfp-ad" data-source="primis"&gt;&lt;span id="desktop-widget-loaded"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="post-content-media-source"&gt;Image credits: &lt;a href="https://unsplash.com/photos/selective-focus-of-brown-deer-lying-on-green-grass-during-daytime-F0dmGPe2KG0" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"&gt;Pedro Lastra/Unsplash&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The Florida conservation services noted that the most recent instance was detected in Holmes County near the state’s border with Georgia—close to where the latter discovered their first case.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“The recent case was a road-[fatality] 1.5 year old doe sampled less than a mile south of Florida’s 2023 detection,” the agency &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://myfwc.com/research/wildlife/health/white-tail-deer/cwd/" target="_blank" class=" staff-link" rel="noopener nofollow"&gt;&lt;span&gt;announced&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; on its website.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Said 2023 case involved a white-tailed deer that was hit by a vehicle on a highway. The discovery prompted a “disease response plan.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;b&gt;Florida’s conservation agency says it is taking the diagnosis seriously &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Deer showing severe symptoms of zombie deer disease in a wooded area as authorities respond to the outbreak in southern state.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="attachment-link-container shareable-image-block" id="7-68a6c946c822b__700-68f41447b20e1__700" data-href="http://www.boredpanda.com/zombie-deer-disease-hits-southern-state-as-second-case-recorded/?image_id=7-68a6c946c822b__700-68f41447b20e1__700.jpg"&gt;&lt;a class="web-share-button list-item-share new-share-experiment" data-location="single-post-image" data-title="“Zombie Deer Disease” Detected Again In Southern State As Authorities Launch Emergency Response Plan" data-share-url="https://www.boredpanda.com/zombie-deer-disease-hits-southern-state-as-second-case-recorded/?media_id=7-68a6c946c822b__700-68f41447b20e1__700" data-image="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/7-68a6c946c822b__700-68f41447b20e1__700.jpg"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;svg class="svg-icon icon-share-icon" role="img" viewbox="0 0 16 16"&gt;&lt;title&gt;Share icon&lt;/title&gt;&lt;path d="M0 15C0 10.8824 5.22292 10.0588 8.79817 10.0588V14.1765L15.7006 8.23061C15.7941 8.15345 15.8695 8.05559 15.9213 7.94441C15.9731 7.83323 16 7.71155 16 7.58824C16 7.46492 15.9731 7.34314 15.9213 7.23196C15.8695 7.12078 15.7941 7.02302 15.7006 6.94586L8.79817 1V5.11765C2.3995 5.11765 0 9.76235 0 15Z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/7-68a6c946c822b__700-68f41447b20e1__700.jpg?utm_campaign=rebelboost_true" alt="Deer showing severe symptoms of zombie deer disease in a wooded area as authorities respond to the outbreak in southern state." title="Deer showing severe symptoms of zombie deer disease in a wooded area as authorities respond to the outbreak in southern state." loading="lazy" fetchpriority="low"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="post-content-media-source"&gt;Image credits: &lt;a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/deer/comments/1ahgy2y/what_is_wrong_with_this_deer/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"&gt;Difficult_Cat1110&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Like the pledge accompanying its announcement two years ago, the recent confirmation stated: &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;“The FWC and its agency partners take CWD very seriously and are continuing with their comprehensive response plan with the goal of containing the disease within the area it was detected.” &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;“Because the second case is close to the original case, there will be no changes to the Management or Enhanced Surveillance Zones,” the website declared.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;b&gt;Florida has since tested 2500 deer for the illness&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Deer showing symptoms of zombie deer disease with visible growths on face and neck in a natural outdoor setting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="attachment-link-container shareable-image-block" id="6-68a6c944c115c__700-68f41449475a0__700" data-href="http://www.boredpanda.com/zombie-deer-disease-hits-southern-state-as-second-case-recorded/?image_id=6-68a6c944c115c__700-68f41449475a0__700.jpg"&gt;&lt;a class="web-share-button list-item-share new-share-experiment" data-location="single-post-image" data-title="“Zombie Deer Disease” Detected Again In Southern State As Authorities Launch Emergency Response Plan" data-share-url="https://www.boredpanda.com/zombie-deer-disease-hits-southern-state-as-second-case-recorded/?media_id=6-68a6c944c115c__700-68f41449475a0__700" data-image="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/6-68a6c944c115c__700-68f41449475a0__700.jpg"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;svg class="svg-icon icon-share-icon" role="img" viewbox="0 0 16 16"&gt;&lt;title&gt;Share icon&lt;/title&gt;&lt;path d="M0 15C0 10.8824 5.22292 10.0588 8.79817 10.0588V14.1765L15.7006 8.23061C15.7941 8.15345 15.8695 8.05559 15.9213 7.94441C15.9731 7.83323 16 7.71155 16 7.58824C16 7.46492 15.9731 7.34314 15.9213 7.23196C15.8695 7.12078 15.7941 7.02302 15.7006 6.94586L8.79817 1V5.11765C2.3995 5.11765 0 9.76235 0 15Z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/6-68a6c944c115c__700-68f41449475a0__700.jpg?utm_campaign=rebelboost_true" alt="Deer showing symptoms of zombie deer disease with visible growths on face and neck in a natural outdoor setting." title="Deer showing symptoms of zombie deer disease with visible growths on face and neck in a natural outdoor setting." loading="lazy" fetchpriority="low"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="post-content-media-source"&gt;Image credits: &lt;a href="https://x.com/PetnurseSue/status/1955790002052345865/photo/1" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"&gt;PetnurseSue&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The government website shows that the state has since checked a total of 2406 deer, and confirmed that 2 tested positive for CWD.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The FWC breakdown also shows that 90 evaluations are pending.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;b&gt;Experts advise against eating affected animals’ meat for fear of it leading to illnesses like mad cow disease&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Deer with large tumors on body, showing signs of zombie deer disease detected in southern state emergency response area.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="attachment-link-container shareable-image-block" id="2-68a6c93bc1dd2__700-68f4144a81412__700" data-href="http://www.boredpanda.com/zombie-deer-disease-hits-southern-state-as-second-case-recorded/?image_id=2-68a6c93bc1dd2__700-68f4144a81412__700.jpg"&gt;&lt;a class="web-share-button list-item-share new-share-experiment" data-location="single-post-image" data-title="“Zombie Deer Disease” Detected Again In Southern State As Authorities Launch Emergency Response Plan" data-share-url="https://www.boredpanda.com/zombie-deer-disease-hits-southern-state-as-second-case-recorded/?media_id=2-68a6c93bc1dd2__700-68f4144a81412__700" data-image="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/2-68a6c93bc1dd2__700-68f4144a81412__700.jpg"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;svg class="svg-icon icon-share-icon" role="img" viewbox="0 0 16 16"&gt;&lt;title&gt;Share icon&lt;/title&gt;&lt;path d="M0 15C0 10.8824 5.22292 10.0588 8.79817 10.0588V14.1765L15.7006 8.23061C15.7941 8.15345 15.8695 8.05559 15.9213 7.94441C15.9731 7.83323 16 7.71155 16 7.58824C16 7.46492 15.9731 7.34314 15.9213 7.23196C15.8695 7.12078 15.7941 7.02302 15.7006 6.94586L8.79817 1V5.11765C2.3995 5.11765 0 9.76235 0 15Z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/2-68a6c93bc1dd2__700-68f4144a81412__700.jpg?utm_campaign=rebelboost_true" alt="Deer with large tumors on body, showing signs of zombie deer disease detected in southern state emergency response area." title="Deer with large tumors on body, showing signs of zombie deer disease detected in southern state emergency response area." loading="lazy" fetchpriority="low"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="post-content-media-source"&gt;Image credits: &lt;a href="https://x.com/povertybayhunt" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"&gt;povertybayhunt&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="post-desktop-ad-within-content post-ads margin-left"&gt;&lt;span class="dfp-ad"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="pg-ad-label"&gt;ADVERTISEMENT&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p id="boredpandacom_desktop_post_2" align="center" data-freestar-ad="__728x90"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;blockquote class="tiktok-embed" cite="https://www.tiktok.com/@ericaachristinee/video/7520785539415526670" data-video-id="7520785539415526670"&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The University of Minnesota &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cidrap.umn.edu/chronic-wasting-disease/georgia-confirms-cwd-case-becoming-36th-us-state-report-fatal-prion-disease#:~:text=.-,Georgia%20confirms%20CWD%20case%2C%20becoming%2036th%20US%20state%20to%20report,'%20in%20the%20immediate%20area.%22" target="_blank" class=" staff-link" rel="noopener nofollow"&gt;&lt;span&gt;describes&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; the illness as a “fatal neurodegenerative disease,” caused by “infectious misfolded proteins” or prions.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The academic institution’s online platform notes that it can be contracted by other members of the Cervidae family, like elk and moose, through “environmental contamination.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;While not known to affect humans, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.boredpanda.com/body-language-expert-breaks-down-king-charles-subtle-signs-of-impatience-towards-trump/" target="_blank" class=" staff-link" rel="noopener "&gt;&lt;span&gt;experts&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; advise against eating affected animals for the fear that it could trigger bovine spongiform encephalopathy, better known as mad cow disease.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;It must be noted that aside from the loss of weight and bodily functions in the late stages of the &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.boredpanda.com/cancer-stricken-ex-victorias-secret-model-rejected-after-offering-to-walk-this-years/" target="_blank" class=" staff-link" rel="noopener "&gt;&lt;span&gt;illness&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;, there are &lt;/span&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span&gt;no&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;span&gt; visual symptoms in affected animals.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;b&gt;CWD is not to be confused with the wart-like cutaneous fibromas found on deer, wild rabbits, and squirrels&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Deer standing near a residential area, highlighting concerns about Zombie Deer Disease detected in a southern state.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="attachment-link-container shareable-image-block" id="4-68a6c94008a71__700-68f4144bb27f4__700" data-href="http://www.boredpanda.com/zombie-deer-disease-hits-southern-state-as-second-case-recorded/?image_id=4-68a6c94008a71__700-68f4144bb27f4__700.jpg"&gt;&lt;a class="web-share-button list-item-share new-share-experiment" data-location="single-post-image" data-title="“Zombie Deer Disease” Detected Again In Southern State As Authorities Launch Emergency Response Plan" data-share-url="https://www.boredpanda.com/zombie-deer-disease-hits-southern-state-as-second-case-recorded/?media_id=4-68a6c94008a71__700-68f4144bb27f4__700" data-image="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/4-68a6c94008a71__700-68f4144bb27f4__700.jpg"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;svg class="svg-icon icon-share-icon" role="img" viewbox="0 0 16 16"&gt;&lt;title&gt;Share icon&lt;/title&gt;&lt;path d="M0 15C0 10.8824 5.22292 10.0588 8.79817 10.0588V14.1765L15.7006 8.23061C15.7941 8.15345 15.8695 8.05559 15.9213 7.94441C15.9731 7.83323 16 7.71155 16 7.58824C16 7.46492 15.9731 7.34314 15.9213 7.23196C15.8695 7.12078 15.7941 7.02302 15.7006 6.94586L8.79817 1V5.11765C2.3995 5.11765 0 9.76235 0 15Z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/4-68a6c94008a71__700-68f4144bb27f4__700.jpg?utm_campaign=rebelboost_true" alt="Deer standing near a residential area, highlighting concerns about Zombie Deer Disease detected in a southern state." title="Deer standing near a residential area, highlighting concerns about Zombie Deer Disease detected in a southern state." loading="lazy" fetchpriority="low"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="post-content-media-source"&gt;Image credits: &lt;a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/Jakeymakeme/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"&gt;Jakeymakeme&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Social media has since caught wind of the outbreak, and one netizen observed, “Eating a zombie deer is 100% safer than anything you buy in your local grocery stores.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Said “zombie deer” is the moniker given to cervids that have been seen with large warts on their skin.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;These unsightly growths are known as cutaneous fibromas, which can be passed from deer, rabbits, and squirrels but are relatively harmless to their hosts.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Unlike the fatal CWD, the only time cutaneous fibromas can lead to their hosts passing away is when they affect their ability to forage and eat or evade predators.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;b&gt;The term “zombie deer” has been pinned on animals with cutaneous fibromas and, more recently, those with CWD&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Young deer standing on grass with signs of zombie deer disease, highlighting wildlife health concerns in a southern state.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="attachment-link-container shareable-image-block" id="3-68a6c93d77c55__700-68f4144d4323c__700" data-href="http://www.boredpanda.com/zombie-deer-disease-hits-southern-state-as-second-case-recorded/?image_id=3-68a6c93d77c55__700-68f4144d4323c__700.jpg"&gt;&lt;a class="web-share-button list-item-share new-share-experiment" data-location="single-post-image" data-title="“Zombie Deer Disease” Detected Again In Southern State As Authorities Launch Emergency Response Plan" data-share-url="https://www.boredpanda.com/zombie-deer-disease-hits-southern-state-as-second-case-recorded/?media_id=3-68a6c93d77c55__700-68f4144d4323c__700" data-image="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/3-68a6c93d77c55__700-68f4144d4323c__700.jpg"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;svg class="svg-icon icon-share-icon" role="img" viewbox="0 0 16 16"&gt;&lt;title&gt;Share icon&lt;/title&gt;&lt;path d="M0 15C0 10.8824 5.22292 10.0588 8.79817 10.0588V14.1765L15.7006 8.23061C15.7941 8.15345 15.8695 8.05559 15.9213 7.94441C15.9731 7.83323 16 7.71155 16 7.58824C16 7.46492 15.9731 7.34314 15.9213 7.23196C15.8695 7.12078 15.7941 7.02302 15.7006 6.94586L8.79817 1V5.11765C2.3995 5.11765 0 9.76235 0 15Z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/3-68a6c93d77c55__700-68f4144d4323c__700.jpg?utm_campaign=rebelboost_true" alt="Young deer standing on grass with signs of zombie deer disease, highlighting wildlife health concerns in a southern state." title="Young deer standing on grass with signs of zombie deer disease, highlighting wildlife health concerns in a southern state." loading="lazy" fetchpriority="low"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="post-content-media-source"&gt;Image credits: &lt;a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/Jakeymakeme/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"&gt;Jakeymakeme&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“What in the world is a zombie deer?” asked another &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.boredpanda.com/doctor-suggests-taylor-swift-pregnant-visible-changes-viral-video/" target="_blank" class=" staff-link" rel="noopener "&gt;&lt;span&gt;netizen&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;, unfamiliar with the term connected to the warty animals&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="post-desktop-ad-within-content post-ads margin-left"&gt;&lt;span class="dfp-ad"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="pg-ad-label"&gt;ADVERTISEMENT&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p id="boredpandacom_desktop_post_3" align="center" data-freestar-ad="__728x90"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“It’s CWD (Chronic Wasting Disease),” responded another mistakenly, “similar to mad cow but only transmitted through deer and moose and like animals.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;b&gt;CWD has since been addressed at a federal level, with Congress shelling out $35 million on it every year&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="video-container"&gt;&lt;iframe title="YouTube video player" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/V-CPTdyP90o?si=50w4qr32i_5_u4lJ" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" loading="lazy" fetchpriority="low"&gt;VIDEO&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Young deer standing in a grassy field, highlighting concerns about zombie deer disease in southern state emergency response efforts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="attachment-link-container shareable-image-block" id="divide-by-zero-FGkNt8tO04I-unsplash-68f4144124ce2__700" data-href="http://www.boredpanda.com/zombie-deer-disease-hits-southern-state-as-second-case-recorded/?image_id=divide-by-zero-FGkNt8tO04I-unsplash-68f4144124ce2__700.jpg"&gt;&lt;a class="web-share-button list-item-share new-share-experiment" data-location="single-post-image" data-title="“Zombie Deer Disease” Detected Again In Southern State As Authorities Launch Emergency Response Plan" data-share-url="https://www.boredpanda.com/zombie-deer-disease-hits-southern-state-as-second-case-recorded/?media_id=divide-by-zero-FGkNt8tO04I-unsplash-68f4144124ce2__700" data-image="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/divide-by-zero-FGkNt8tO04I-unsplash-68f4144124ce2__700.jpg"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;svg class="svg-icon icon-share-icon" role="img" viewbox="0 0 16 16"&gt;&lt;title&gt;Share icon&lt;/title&gt;&lt;path d="M0 15C0 10.8824 5.22292 10.0588 8.79817 10.0588V14.1765L15.7006 8.23061C15.7941 8.15345 15.8695 8.05559 15.9213 7.94441C15.9731 7.83323 16 7.71155 16 7.58824C16 7.46492 15.9731 7.34314 15.9213 7.23196C15.8695 7.12078 15.7941 7.02302 15.7006 6.94586L8.79817 1V5.11765C2.3995 5.11765 0 9.76235 0 15Z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/divide-by-zero-FGkNt8tO04I-unsplash-68f4144124ce2__700.jpg?utm_campaign=rebelboost_true" alt="Young deer standing in a grassy field, highlighting concerns about zombie deer disease in southern state emergency response efforts." title="Young deer standing in a grassy field, highlighting concerns about zombie deer disease in southern state emergency response efforts." loading="lazy" fetchpriority="low"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="post-content-media-source"&gt;Image credits: &lt;a href="https://unsplash.com/photos/brown-deer-standing-on-green-grass-field-FGkNt8tO04I" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"&gt; Divide By Zero/Unsplash&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“It’s coined the term zombie deer because of what happens.. ‘weight loss, poor coordination, drooling, and a vacant stare, as their brains deteriorate into a spongy consistency’,” attempted another.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“It doesn’t mean it’s walking around [deceased], it’s in the process of [expiring].”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;CWD has since been addressed at a federal level, with the Chronic Wasting Disease Research and Management Act being &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.trcp.org/2022/12/23/house-senate-send-important-chronic-wasting-disease-legislation-presidents-desk/" target="_blank" class=" staff-link" rel="noopener nofollow"&gt;&lt;span&gt;approved&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; by Congress in December 2022.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The bill earmarked $35 million per year for research on the animal illness, which was slated to focus on detection in live animals, prevention, and understanding what caused the spread of the &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.boredpanda.com/facepalm-worthy-cringe-silly-posts/" target="_blank" class=" staff-link" rel="noopener "&gt;&lt;span&gt;disease&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;One netizen, in the wake of COVID, wonders which lab CWD was generated in&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Comment mentioning zombie deer disease in Florida, highlighting concerns and local reactions to the outbreak.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="post-desktop-ad-within-content post-ads margin-left"&gt;&lt;span class="dfp-ad"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="pg-ad-label"&gt;ADVERTISEMENT&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p id="boredpandacom_desktop_post_4" align="center" data-freestar-ad="__728x90"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Comment about zombie deer disease safety compared to grocery store food, emphasizing the topic of zombie deer disease detection.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Comment on social media post with text about zombie deer disease, highlighting concerns about its detection and emergency response plans.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Facebook comment by Sharon Moyer asking about any connection to GMO mosquitoes, relevant to zombie deer disease concerns.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Comment from Rita Vicky Berger DuBois asking what a zombie deer is, referencing zombie deer disease concerns.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="post-desktop-ad-within-content post-ads margin-left"&gt;&lt;span class="dfp-ad"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="pg-ad-label"&gt;ADVERTISEMENT&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p id="boredpandacom_desktop_post_infinite_0" align="center" data-freestar-ad="__728x90"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Comment asking which lab the zombie deer disease sample came from in an online discussion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Comment by user Anthony Saviano expressing a view on deer consumption amid concerns about zombie deer disease detection.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Comment text on light blue background about deer, referencing the Simpsons, related to zombie deer disease detected in southern state.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Comment by Timothy Brown reading wait until the frozen gators show up on a social media platform.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="post-desktop-ad-within-content post-ads margin-left"&gt;&lt;span class="dfp-ad"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="pg-ad-label"&gt;ADVERTISEMENT&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p id="boredpandacom_desktop_post_infinite_1" align="center" data-freestar-ad="__728x90"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Comment warning about eating affected meat related to zombie deer disease concerns.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Social media comment mentioning walking dead zombies, related to concerns about zombie deer disease detected again.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Comment from Peter Winberg stating not transmitted to humans yet about zombie deer disease concerns.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Screenshot of a comment saying Good thing I don’t eat deer referencing zombie deer disease detection.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="post-desktop-ad-within-content post-ads margin-left"&gt;&lt;span class="dfp-ad"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="pg-ad-label"&gt;ADVERTISEMENT&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p id="boredpandacom_desktop_post_infinite_2" align="center" data-freestar-ad="__728x90"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;div id="postPoll-9524016" class="post-poll poll-wrapper single-post" data-poll-viewed="false" data-post-id="9524016" data-main-post-id="" data-poll-id="17888"&gt; &lt;input class="post-9524016-poll-value" type="hidden" value="eyJwb2xsSWQiOjE3ODg4LCJwb3N0SWQiOjk1MjQwMTYsImhpZGVDb21tZW50cyI6ZmFsc2UsInF1ZXN0aW9ucyI6W3siaWQiOjE3ODg4LCJwb2xsSWQiOjE3ODg4LCJ0ZXh0IjoiRG9lcyB0aGUgdGVybSBcdTIwMWN6b21iaWUgZGVlclx1MjAxZCBtYWtlIHlvdSBtb3JlIGNvbmNlcm5lZCBhYm91dCBDV0Q/Iiwib3JkZXIiOm51bGwsImFuc3dlcnMiOlt7ImlkIjo2ODIwMiwicXVlc3Rpb25JZCI6MTc4ODgsInRleHQiOiJZZXMsIGl0IHNvdW5kcyBzZXJpb3VzLiIsInZvdGVzIjoyMX0seyJpZCI6NjgyMDMsInF1ZXN0aW9uSWQiOjE3ODg4LCJ0ZXh0IjoiTm8sIGl0XHUyMDE5cyBtZWRpYSBoeXBlLiIsInZvdGVzIjoxMn0seyJpZCI6NjgyMDQsInF1ZXN0aW9uSWQiOjE3ODg4LCJ0ZXh0IjoiQSBsaXR0bGUsIEkgd2FudCBtb3JlIGluZm8uIiwidm90ZXMiOjh9LHsiaWQiOjY4MjA1LCJxdWVzdGlvbklkIjoxNzg4OCwidGV4dCI6Ik5vdCBjb25jZXJuZWQgYXQgYWxsLiIsInZvdGVzIjoyfV19XSwicG9zdFRpdGxlIjpudWxsLCJwb3N0VXJsIjoiaHR0cHM6XC9cL3d3dy5ib3JlZHBhbmRhLmNvbVwvem9tYmllLWRlZXItZGlzZWFzZS1oaXRzLXNvdXRoZXJuLXN0YXRlLWFzLXNlY29uZC1jYXNlLXJlY29yZGVkXC8ifQ=="&gt; &lt;div data-bind="if: isInitialised()"&gt;    &lt;div data-bind="if: !isLoading() &amp;amp;&amp;amp; isShowingResults"&gt; &lt;div class="poll-content"&gt; &lt;h3 class="answered-content-title"&gt;Thanks! Check out the results:&lt;/h3&gt; &lt;h3 class="answered-content-question" data-bind="text: currentQuestionText()"&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;  &lt;p class="total-votes" data-bind="visible: totalVotes() &amp;gt; 10 &amp;amp;&amp;amp; isShowingResults &amp;amp;&amp;amp; totalVotesDisplayMode !== 0"&gt; &lt;span class="text"&gt;Total votes · &lt;/span&gt; &lt;span data-bind="text: totalVotesFormatted"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;  &lt;div class="subscribe-to-newsletter-block-wrapper"&gt; &lt;p class="badge"&gt;Newsletter&lt;/p&gt; &lt;div class="subscribe-to-newsletter-block"&gt; &lt;p class="left"&gt; &lt;h3 class="title"&gt;Subscribe to Access &lt;br&gt; Exclusive Polls&lt;/h3&gt; &lt;/p&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;  &lt;div class="disclaimer"&gt; &lt;p&gt;By entering your email and clicking Subscribe, you're agreeing to let us send you customized marketing messages about us and our advertising partners. You are also agreeing to our &lt;a href="https://www.boredpanda.com/privacy-policy/"&gt;Privacy Policy&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div data-bind="if: newsletterSubscribed" class="thank-you"&gt; &lt;div class="wrapper"&gt;  &lt;p class="right"&gt;Thank you! You've successfully subscribed to newsletters!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;     &lt;p class="clearfix"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Bored Panda</author><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 23:04:50 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilgFBVV95cUxOV2tHT0hOaUhSVEp1aDM4dGNhOHV3U1BhZTRZaTQ4SFFFVUxKMldaYlN4THhvcWNxUlphRkdZNEpqaVJtS3JLQng2WEZCRmRIVzNFNE1vTVpHZFVzYjA1cXpmRXl2Y3NVYTQxSVBDbjZUZUpoaEtuRGh0aThuWEc5eDRzU2YyU3lod1dhSUtkSzlaR2E0YUE</guid></item><item><title>老年男性的精子携带更多突变，它们可能会变得有害- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/older-mens-sperm-carry-more-mutations-and-they-may-turn-harmful</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Potentially harmful &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mutation"&gt;DNA mutations&lt;/a&gt; can amass in men's sperm as they age, new research has found, which may in turn impact the number of mutations passed on to children – and the risks of disease in the next generation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mutations occur in DNA when cells replicate, and arise either by random chance or because of &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/air-pollution-strongly-associated-with-dna-mutations-tied-to-lung-cancer"&gt;environmental stresses&lt;/a&gt;. They can impact how well the body works, or have no observable effect at all. Mutations accumulate as time goes by, just like wear and tear on a car – but it hasn't been clear how much these genetic mishaps affect sperm in older men.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Researchers from the Wellcome Sanger Institute and King's College London in the UK used a new high-resolution analysis technique called NanoSeq to look in detail at mutations in the sperm of men aged 24-75 years, and the genes those mutations affected.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/it-s-not-just-women-faulty-sperm-can-contribute-to-repeated-miscarriages"&gt;Sperm Could Be a Bigger Factor in Miscarriages Than We've Been Led to Believe&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Not only do mutations occur at higher rates in older men, the data showed, but some are '&lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/nrurol.2016.37"&gt;selfish&lt;/a&gt;' – giving the cells that carry them a growth advantage, so they &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1111/j.2047-2927.2013.00175.x"&gt;replicate faster than or outlast&lt;/a&gt; other cells in the testes and gradually take over. Many of these mutations have previously &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.ajhg.2011.12.017"&gt;been linked&lt;/a&gt; to developmental disorders and cancers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We expected to find some evidence of selection shaping mutations in sperm," &lt;a href="https://www.sanger.ac.uk/news_item/hidden-evolution-in-sperm-raises-disease-risk-for-children-as-men-age/"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; geneticist Matthew Neville, from the Wellcome Sanger Institute.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"What surprised us was just how much it drives up the number of sperm carrying mutations linked to serious diseases."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers analyzed 81 sperm samples from 57 healthy men, some of whom &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/pair-of-twins-raised-in-different-countries-reveal-significantly-different-cognitive-abilities"&gt;were twins&lt;/a&gt; – a factor which helps separate the effects of age on sperm DNA mutations from inherited genetics.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Around 2 percent of sperm from men in their 30s were found to be carrying disease-causing mutations, which jumped up to 3-5 percent for middle-aged and older men (over the age of 43). By age 70, an average of 4.5 percent of sperm had potentially &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/reversible-molecular-changes-can-cause-cancer-study-shows"&gt;harmful mutations&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The team was also able to identify 40 genes affected by the 'selfish' mutant cells winning out in the positive selection competition in the testes. That will help in future research linking specific mutations to specific &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/your-risk-of-cancer-could-fluctuate-even-born-youre-born"&gt;disease risks&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_177234" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-177234" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/SpermChart.jpg" alt="Sperm chart" class="wp-image-177234 size-full" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/SpermChart.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/SpermChart-600x276.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-177234" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Sperm cells carrying potentially harmful mutations became more common as men aged. (Neville et al., &lt;em&gt;Nature&lt;/em&gt;, 2025)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Some changes in DNA not only survive but thrive within the testes, meaning that fathers who conceive later in life may unknowingly have a higher risk of passing on a harmful mutation to their children," &lt;a href="https://www.sanger.ac.uk/news_item/hidden-evolution-in-sperm-raises-disease-risk-for-children-as-men-age/"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; geneticist Matt Hurles, from the Wellcome Sanger Institute.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It's worth bearing in mind that not all of these mutations will necessarily be passed on to the next generation. Some of them may actually reduce the chances of reproduction in some way – by interfering with &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/world-first-scientists-film-the-exact-moment-a-human-embryo-implants"&gt;embryo development&lt;/a&gt;, for example.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;More work is required to figure out exactly how this steady increase in DNA mutations in men actually affects the &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/study-reveals-alarming-rise-of-superbugs-in-newborn-babies"&gt;health of their kids&lt;/a&gt;, but for now, we have a much better idea of the processes involved.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/spark-into-space-comp?utm_source=promo_astro"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro-642x272.jpg" alt="Mid Article Promo Astro" class="alignnone wp-image-177074 size-medium" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro-642x272.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro-768x326.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro-600x255.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro.jpg 844w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
These findings also give scientists a much closer look at the chain of cells that are known as the &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Germline"&gt;male germline&lt;/a&gt;, cells set aside for the job of passing on genetic material to the next generation – potentially with both positive and negative consequences.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The male germline is a dynamic environment where natural selection can favor harmful mutations, sometimes with consequences for the next generation," &lt;a href="https://www.sanger.ac.uk/news_item/hidden-evolution-in-sperm-raises-disease-risk-for-children-as-men-age/"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; geneticist Raheleh Rahbari, from the Wellcome Sanger Institute.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The research has been published in &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1038/s41586-025-09448-3"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Nature&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 21:01:27 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilwFBVV95cUxNSGhzSlpBeU1Sc0xuYnVLdlIySkFsT3F5dl9zWlM4RnU4b2NCSmRZeHVEb0J4UEZzMDNzTEZiUjZrTU5QRVd1TmozWktUZFNaYmYzRnVOZDAzMGxzekQxYVd1aFFVUUY2Vnp5ZkktUDRPVnZ3eFc5M2M3X01LSEJVY2pYZGJYNnhNdVJaemNLRHNjbENmakVF</guid></item><item><title>随着可怕的副作用飙升，医生揭露了褪黑激素的真相-每日邮报</title><link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-15044713/rise-melatonin-addiction-overdoses.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div itemprop="articleBody"&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Health experts have issued a warning about the 'terrifying' rise of melatonin use among children, which they say could lead to fatal overdoses. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Melatonin is a hormone naturally produced by the pineal gland in the brain. It helps regulate the body’s sleep-wake cycle (circadian rhythm). Melatonin levels rise in the evening, promoting drowsiness, and fall in the morning, promoting wakefulness. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The supplement is heavily regulated as a prescription-only medication in many parts of the world, including the UK, the EU and Australia. But in the US, the &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/fda/index.html" id="mol-e06c3c60-aace-11f0-889a-21cc4e50b213"&gt;FDA&lt;/a&gt; regulates it as an over-the-counter option.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;More than 67 million Americans take melatonin, and analysts predict sales of the supplement will top $588 million in 2025, up from $339 million in 2017.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But as adults turn to the hormone in droves to help kick insomnia, children are also being introduced to it, either intentionally by parents to aid fussy sleepers or by mistaking appetizing-looking melatonin gummies for a sweet treat. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;A 2023 study by the &lt;span&gt;American Academy of Sleep Medicine found that almost half (46 percent) of parents have given melatonin to a child under the age of 13 to help them fall asleep. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;And in 2022, the &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/centers-for-disease-control-and-prevention-cdc/index.html" id="mol-ca335fb0-9f06-11f0-a9b9-b94c99276d56"&gt;CDC&lt;/a&gt; revealed how, in the decade leading up to 2021, poison helplines dealt with 260,435 calls about children who had taken too much melatonin, a 530 percent increase from 2012.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In 2012, melatonin was responsible for one percent of pediatric poisonings. That rose to five percent in 2021.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Health experts are warning about the 'terrifying' rise of melatonin addiction and overdoses among children in the US, with little known about the long-term consequences of taking the sleep aid (Stock image)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    
    
    &lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Of the poison reports, two children died, five were put on a ventilator to help them breathe, nearly 300 ended up in intensive care and more than 4,000 were hospitalized.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Melatonin &lt;span&gt;is naturally produced in the brain's pineal gland, and its release into the body is controlled by light.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;During the day, melatonin levels in the body are low and we feel awake, but when the sun sets, more melatonin circulates in the body, preparing people for sleep.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Melatonin may be suggested to adults to help them fall or stay asleep, but the substance is generally not recommended for children without medical guidance because little is known about its long-term impacts. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Dr Keith Vossel, a neurologist at the University Of California Los Angeles, told the Daily Mail he would not recommend giving children melatonin as it is a hormone and 'could have effects on the timing of puberty, metabolism and immune system.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Studies have shown a link between melatonin intake and delayed puberty, as well as an &lt;span&gt;affect on related hormonal pathways. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;This is because melatonin interacts with the hypothalamic-pituitary-gonadal (HPG) axis - the hormonal system that controls puberty - so 'we need to be cautious and longer-term studies are needed,' Vossel said.&lt;/p&gt;
    
    
    
    
    
    &lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Like Vossel, Dr Rachel Toles, a clinical psychologist in California, told the Daily Mail she is concerned about the melatonin abuse among both adults and children. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Melatonin should never be the first solution for children’s sleep,' she said. 'It’s a hormone, not a harmless vitamin, and the long-term effects on developing brains are still unknown.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'The big issue is that the supplements look like candy and they are often left within children’s reach. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Some parents also give melatonin to their kids too freely, and it has become a cultural quick fix for sleep, which is concerning.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Along with having a possible impact on puberty, Toles said it can negatively affect the metabolism and immune systems. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Melatonin can negatively affect metabolism by disrupting glucose regulation and weight balance when misused, and may impair immune function by suppressing necessary inflammatory responses if overused. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Taking melatonin at the wrong time can disrupt insulin release and circadian control of glucose, leading to poor blood sugar control and weight gain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Meanwhile, excess melatonin can overly suppress pro-inflammatory signals, weakening necessary immune responses to infection.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Toles said that parents should also be aware that m&lt;span&gt;elatonin 'can cause grogginess, headaches and even more wakefulness at higher doses.' &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span&gt;'The real danger is using it to mask bigger issues like screen time, anxiety or inconsistent routines,' she added.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span&gt;There is also the possibility of children getting hooked on the supplement and their sleep getting worse in the long run. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;A typical dose for melatonin ranges from one to 3mg, taken about 30 minutes before bedtime, with most people rarely needing more than 5mg (Pictured: melatonin gummies on a store shelf)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span&gt;On Reddit, dozens of parents have revealed horror stories involving melatonin and their children. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span&gt;One mother revealed that she gives her son, who has autism and ADHD, one milligram of melatonin when on vacation. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span&gt;A typical adult dose for melatonin ranges from one milligram to 3mg, taken about 30 minutes before bedtime, with most people rarely needing more than 5mg.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span&gt;The recommended dose for young children is significantly lower (for three- to five-year-olds the dose is suggested not to exceed one milligram), and this amount can lead to a range of moderate to severe symptoms such as drowsiness, dizziness, headaches, nausea and agitation. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span&gt;The mother said she accidentally left the bottle of gummies in her two-year-old daughter's room, and the infant ended up taking in 26mg. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Ingesting 26mg of melatonin is a serious overdose for a toddler and requires immediate medical attention. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span&gt;The mother said she called poison control and they told her to monitor her daughter at home but to visit the ER if any symptoms worsened. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;A CDC report released in early 2022 revealed that in the decade leading up to 2021, poison helplines dealt with 260,435 calls about children who had taken too much melatonin (Stock image)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span&gt;On Facebook, Beth McCarty from Vancouver revealed her 11-year-old son, Ethan, took 18 melatonin gummies as he had watched his father take large doses of medication. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Sharing photos of Ethan looking drowsy in the back of an ambulance, she wrote: '&lt;/span&gt;So deeply thankful for the medics [and] poison control who responded after Ethan was literally laied [sic] out and plastered to the living room rug. They were all so calm with us and our boy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Parents, WATCH your kiddos with ANY med. Ethan sure knows never to try anything like this again.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In another post, Iowa-based mental health coach Marci Hanzelka McKinnon shared how she unknowingly got her son hooked on melatonin. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;As a warning to other parents, she wrote: 'Yep, we are guilty. We gave our son melatonin.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'No one knew (or no one told us) back then the dangers of using melatonin for our child.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'At that time the highest dose was 10mg; that was considered extremely high. We started him at 3mg and slowly kept moving it up because it stopped working.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Iowa-based mental health coach Marci Hanzelka McKinnon (pictured) shared how she unknowingly got her son hooked on melatonin&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Eventually we reached 10mg. Once that stopped working we stopped giving it to him and were no better off than we were before we started using it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Today, you can get 50mg of melatonin! That’s unbelievable! And so dangerous!'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span&gt;All of the doctors the Daily Mail spoke to agreed that sleep has become harder for children in the modern world with increased exposure to technology and busier schedules. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Still, they all advised against melatonin as a solution. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Los Angeles-based Dr Raj Dasgupta, the chief medical advisor for Sleepopolis, said the best thing to do before turning to sleep aids is to figure out why the child isn't sleeping first. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'S&lt;span&gt;ometimes it’s as simple as bedtime habits or anxiety,' he told the Daily Mail. 'I usually tell parents to exhaust all behavioral approaches before reaching for medication or supplements.'&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span&gt;And Dr David Sinclair, a professor at Harvard Medical School, said that '&lt;/span&gt;Natural alternatives are best' for addressing sleep issues. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'[Try] consistent bedtime routines, dimming lights in the evening and keeping screens out of the bedroom, and making sure kids get enough daylight and physical activity during the day,' he told the Daily Mail.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'I have seen cases where children were put on melatonin for sleep and it helped in the short term. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'But in most situations, once children get exercise, nighttime lights are dimmed and devices are taken away before bedtime, they didn’t need the supplement anymore.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Daily Mail</author><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 20:27:39 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilgFBVV95cUxObzI3dnQ4cUVfZ0tOUWhxSDdqYnNxV0loVzdIbnFUYjZxVHV3WWg1TUpEMmZSUGJFdm81amc2OFQyNGNXWmttVGozdlI5R2RfOTlsQmNrbnJYOE1QWWRQS0MtTzBkVnRkOWhhUmlpUzZqVTd1d1VheWdRRFlUVld4V2JxMjduNVNVRTNIWkR4RndDN1dKbVE</guid></item><item><title>世界更年期日：支持女性，加强系统-财富</title><link>https://fortune.com/2025/10/18/world-menopause-day-world-economic-forum-womens-health-support-women-october-18/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Menopause has long been treated as a quiet, private ordeal. That silence carries a cost. On World Menopause Day, bringing menopause out of the shadows is not a niche concern but a public priority with tangible dividends for health, equity, and economic growth. The conversation must move from scattered efforts to a coordinated plan that is practical to implement in clinics, workplaces, and national policies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="paywall"&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Perimenopause and menopause can span more than a decade. At any given moment, more than 450 million women worldwide are navigating this transition. According to research by the World Economic Forum’s Global Alliance for Women’s Health, closing the women’s health gap on menopause alone could yield an &lt;a href="https://www.weforum.org/publications/blueprint-to-close-the-women-s-health-gap-how-to-improve-lives-and-economies-for-all/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" aria-label="Go to https://www.weforum.org/publications/blueprint-to-close-the-women-s-health-gap-how-to-improve-lives-and-economies-for-all/" class="sc-5ad7098d-0 lcJVdL"&gt;estimated 2.4 million disability adjusted life years every year and roughly 120 billion dollars in annual GDP gains.&lt;/a&gt; These figures represent fewer missed workdays, steadier household income, and less strain on health systems. They also represent lives experienced with more comfort, clarity, and confidence. Numbers summarize the stakes, but lived experience explains them.



&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What stands in the way is not a lack of need but a lack of preparation across the systems that touch women’s lives. Diagnosis and care are often late, inconsistent, or inaccessible. And there is evidence to back this — a Yale University &lt;a href="https://journals.lww.com/menopausejournal/Abstract/2015/03000/Incremental_direct_and_indirect_costs_of_untreated.5.aspx" target="_blank" rel="noopener" aria-label="Go to https://journals.lww.com/menopausejournal/Abstract/2015/03000/Incremental_direct_and_indirect_costs_of_untreated.5.aspx" class="sc-5ad7098d-0 lcJVdL"&gt;review&lt;/a&gt; of insurance claims showed while 60% of women with significant symptoms of menopause seek treatment, almost 75% are left untreated. Training is part of the problem. &lt;a href="https://healthmatch.io/blog/why-are-there-so-many-menopause-knowledge-gaps" target="_blank" rel="noopener" aria-label="Go to https://healthmatch.io/blog/why-are-there-so-many-menopause-knowledge-gaps" class="sc-5ad7098d-0 lcJVdL"&gt;In one study&lt;/a&gt;, half of family medicine doctors reported only a single lecture on menopause during training, and one in five reported none at all. The workforce impact is visible. Research indicates that one in four women has considered leaving work during the transition, and one in ten who have worked through menopause left a job because of their symptoms. This is not only a productivity story, it is also one of opportunity cost. It is a story about experienced leaders stepping back, about teams losing anchors, and about families absorbing avoidable stress.



&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As an Expert Member of the one-of-its-kind multistakeholder platform, the World Economic Forum’s &lt;a href="https://initiatives.weforum.org/global-alliance-for-womens-health/home" target="_blank" rel="noopener" aria-label="Go to https://initiatives.weforum.org/global-alliance-for-womens-health/home" class="sc-5ad7098d-0 lcJVdL"&gt;Global Alliance for Women’s Health&lt;/a&gt;, as well as an expert medical advisor at acclaimed actress, director, producer, advocate, and entrepreneur, Halle Berry’s menopause care platform, &lt;a href="https://www.respin.health/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" aria-label="Go to https://www.respin.health/" class="sc-5ad7098d-0 lcJVdL"&gt;Respin Health&lt;/a&gt;, I see how quickly the conversation shifts when evidence meets execution. These organisations are helping translate science into clinical standards and employer policies, while informing policy frameworks that leaders can adopt and fund. Advocacy is meaningful when it results in actions that are easy to copy, measure, and sustain. Our work with Halle Berry, who &lt;a href="https://www.linkedin.com/feed/update/urn:li:activity:7381282254116921344" target="_blank" rel="noopener" aria-label="Go to https://www.linkedin.com/feed/update/urn:li:activity:7381282254116921344" class="sc-5ad7098d-0 lcJVdL"&gt;recently joined the Global Alliance for Women’s Health as Public Ambassador&lt;/a&gt;, showcases the sheer appetite and momentum that exists to redefine menopause and empower women to be the guardians of their own health. The path is known. What remains is follow-through.



&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“When we leave women to figure menopause out alone, we pay a grave price in health, productivity, and our very own dignity. We have to normalize this conversation about menopause. We have to make guidance useable. We have to improve access to quality care, and we need to invest in research and innovation,” said Halle Berry. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="content-sentinel" data-index="1"&gt;



&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Health care is the first place to start&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Menopause should be part of routine primary care, not a specialty service that only a few can reach. Screening can begin during routine visits for women in their forties and fifties, with clear pathways for counselling and treatment. Evidence based options include lifestyle approaches, non-hormonal treatments, and, when appropriate and safe, hormonal therapies guided by informed choice. Care should consider mental health and cardiometabolic risk, since &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC4377487/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" aria-label="Go to https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC4377487/" class="sc-5ad7098d-0 lcJVdL"&gt;sleep disruption, mood changes, and metabolic shifts&lt;/a&gt; often travel together. Referral pathways must connect primary care, gynaecology, mental health, and cardiometabolic services so women are not left to navigate a maze with contradictory advice. This is not about boutique clinics for the few. It is about equipping the front lines to meet a ubiquitous need.



&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Workplaces are the next lever. Simple adjustments can make a meaningful difference. Flexibility where feasible, paid time off for symptom flare days, and practical measures like temperature control and quiet rest areas reduce the friction that turns symptoms into lost days. Benefits should name menopause explicitly, so women know coverage exists. Manager training should normalize support without forcing disclosure. Employers who measure retention, error rates, and team performance before and after adopting these practices will find what many have already learned. Small investments stabilize teams and pay for themselves.



&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Research and product design must close the data gap and raise the bar for solutions. Studies should reflect the diversity of real women, including race, age, and co existing conditions. Endpoints should be comparable so clinicians and consumers can tell what works and for whom. Digital tools and consumer products that target sleep, cognition, thermoregulation, and pelvic health should be evaluated against evidence standards and priced for broad access. Innovation is welcome. So is rigor. Women deserve both.



&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Policy and financing can turn best practice into the baseline&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Essential menopause services belong in national primary health packages and in public and private insurance coverage. Governments can accelerate employer adoption with clear standards, public recognition, and targeted incentives that reward organizations for implementing menopause supportive policies. Public information campaigns can replace stigma with practical knowledge for women, partners, managers, and clinicians. Countries should publish a small set of indicators that matter in daily life. Time to diagnosis, treatment access, and workforce participation are simple to understand and powerful to track. Accountability is easier when the yardstick is clear.



&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why does this matter beyond the clinic and the workplace? Because when women’s health is prioritized, families and economies function better. Earlier diagnosis and appropriate treatment reduce absenteeism. Menopause supportive workplaces keep experienced talent on the job and reduce turnover. Good care prevents avoidable complications that are costly later. These mechanisms repeat across millions of women and thousands of organizations. The cumulative effect shows up in national productivity. The more important return, however, is human. Better sleep, clearer thinking, steadier mood, and restored confidence change how women experience midlife. That is growth measured in dignity and opportunity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="content-sentinel" data-index="3"&gt;



&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Effective advocacy pairs public leadership with technical depth and coordinated action. Public figures help make the issue relatable. Researchers and clinicians define what quality care looks like. Cross-sector forums align employers, health systems, and governments on practical standards and timelines. This combination turns awareness into accountable implementation. This is where platforms such as the Global Alliance for Women’s Health and the International Menopause Society bring real value to the conversation — by bringing together experts and leaders to make the shift from intention to implementation. 



&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;What should happen now? &lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Health systems can add a brief screening and counselling step to routine primary care visits and build simple referral pathways that do not collapse under real world pressure. Medical schools and continuing education providers can strengthen training, so the next generation of clinicians starts on firmer ground. Employers can publish a menopause policy, train managers, and update benefits language so support is easy to find. Researchers can design studies that reflect the diversity of women and use shared endpoints that allow transparent comparisons. Policymakers can put menopause care in the basic benefit package and require transparent reporting on access and outcomes. None of these actions is a moonshot. Each is a choice that aligns with what we already know.



&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Culture change travels alongside policy change. Partners can listen without judgment. Friends can share what has helped them. Community leaders can include menopause in health talks that already reach women where they live and work. The tone matters. Precision matters. A plan matters. Together they create an environment where a woman does not have to spend years searching for a name for her symptoms or for a path to relief.



&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;World&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;Menopause&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;Day should not be a once-a-year reminder. It should be a yearly accountability moment that asks a simple question: Did we make it easier this year for women to find accurate information, timely care, and practical support? If the answer is yes, the benefits will be visible in clinics, workplaces, homes, and countries.



&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The path is clear — what remains is resolve. Let us act today so more women can live, work, and thrive tomorrow.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="content-sentinel" data-index="5"&gt;



&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The opinions expressed in Fortune.com commentary pieces are solely the views of their authors and do not necessarily reflect the opinions and beliefs of &lt;/em&gt;Fortune&lt;em&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Fortune</author><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 20:16:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMisAFBVV95cUxOZ05OdGEtOHFjX3BWSkRKTV9LOXZOMS1EbGFCUkJwR2kyUlhNenVIYXllLV9RVHR5TzdFVFdUZE1zcXYwNTZCNG9CUFZJdnNNR1pud3B3d1pDazJsRUVTQ255QXhNb3pNcmtmNXVXU3B2QlFLRmlFSFJ1V0tQM2hNWkV0WGFsYVB5QnZCRmNvY0JkMUJoeDZxSkFPOVJ0RU5SejJnS3lFQ0FJV2dLQXkwSQ</guid></item><item><title>你怀孕的地方会影响你的大脑...地图显示最好的地方-每日邮报</title><link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-15199237/where-born-brain-development-map.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div itemprop="articleBody"&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The place where your parents conceived you could have permanently stunted your brain, a study suggests.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Researchers in &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/spain/index.html" id="mol-d12255e0-aabb-11f0-b109-4191f609bee1"&gt;Spain&lt;/a&gt; recruited women during their first trimester of pregnancy and, later, those babies that were born, and estimated how severely they were exposed to fine particulate matter (PM2.5).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;PM2.5 are a group of microscopic particles that are emitted directly into the air from fossils fuels burned from factories and gasoline-powered stoves and cars, as well as burning wood in fireplaces.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;These particles are so small, about &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/news/article-15170677/A-trendy-wood-burning-stove-killed-need-banned-anymore-damage.html?ico=comment-anchor"&gt;30 times thinner than a strand of human hair&lt;/a&gt;, that they undetectable by the naked eye and the nose and lungs can't filter them out, allowing them to travel to the bloodstream and induce widespread inflammation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Using MRI scans on the newborns, the researchers found that those whose mothers were exposed to higher levels of PM2.5 during pregnancy had slower myelination, the process by which myelin is formed. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Myelin is a protective sheath that coats pathways between neurons to help them better transmit information. It helps process electrical signals in the brain and allows the organ to mature. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Slow myelination can lead to developmental delays, low muscle tone and seizures. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The new study focused on children born in Spain, but PM2.5 is widely present in the US as well, particularly along the west coast and in the south. The US also has more air pollution than Spain, suggesting Americans could be facing a greater threat. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Researchers in Spain found exposure to fine particulate matter in the womb may slow the rate a baby's brain matures (stock image)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    
    
    
    
    
    &lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Gerard Martínez-Vilavella, study author and researcher at the MRI Unit of the Radiology Department at Hospital del Mar, said: 'Our study shows that the myelination process, a progressive indicator of brain maturation, occurs at a slower rate in newborns most exposed to PM2.5 during pregnancy.' &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;For the study, published last month in the journal &lt;a class="" rel="nofollow noreferrer noopener" target="_blank" href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0160412025005525?via%3Dihub#s0010"&gt;Environmental International&lt;/a&gt;, looked at 1,080 pregnant mothers who lived in Spain recruited between October 2018 and March 2021 during their first three months of pregnancy. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The women were between 18 and 45 years old and had an average age of 34. Two-thirds were of European descent. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;When the participants were 32 weeks pregnant, researchers invited them to volunteer their babies for the MRI portion of the study. A total of 93 infants received the scans after they were born. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;PM2.5 exposure levels were estimated in each participant's home, during their commute and at their workplace using data from monitoring sites and questionnaires. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The team found higher PM2.5 exposure early in pregnancy was associated with lower myelination in the cerebral cortex, the brain's center for thought, language, memory and sensory processing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Higher exposure later in pregnancy was associated with lower myelination throughout the brain overall. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Fetuses are more prone to lasting health effects early in gestation because their organs are rapidly developing at this time, including the brain, and early gestation is when genetic disorders tend to develop. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Pollution exposure early in pregnancy has been linked to congenital heart disease and birth defects like spina bifida, as well as low birth weight and permanent brain damage. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;And a 2024 review in the journal &lt;a class="" rel="nofollow noreferrer noopener" target="_blank" href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S2666765724001212#sec0011"&gt;Environmental Advances&lt;/a&gt; found that PM2.5 exposure in adults as well was linked damage in the lungs and respiratory system, heart, immune system and nervous system. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Pictured above are the Mono-Inyo craters in Mono County, California, where levels of fine particulate matter are more than five times higher than the national average (stock image)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Martínez-Vilavella said: 'Air pollution, specifically PM2.5, is associated with alterations in the myelination process, a fundamental mechanism of brain maturation. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Therefore, it is essential to continue controlling pollution levels and to study how this slowdown may affect the later brain development of children.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;However, the babies have not yet been followed to see if they have lasting health impacts.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;It's thought that PM2.5 triggers inflammation in the brain that damages nerve cells and the myelin sheath protecting them. PM2.5 is also so small that it can cross the blood-brain barrier and enter brain tissues directly.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The team noted more research is needed to see if older infants and children will suffer long-term harms from this decreased myelination.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Dr Jesús Pujol, head of the MRI Unit of the Radiology Department at Hospital del Mar, said: 'In the early stages of life, brain changes are large and complex. Both excessive slowdown and acceleration of brain maturation can be harmful to the child. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'However, it remains to be determined whether the observed effect is necessarily detrimental. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'This study opens an exciting new field of research aimed at determining the optimal speed of brain maturation during pregnancy and understanding how the mother and placenta may act as effective filters to protect and optimize this process.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In the US, the most recent data collected by the National Institute on Minority Health and Health Disparities, an arm of the NIH, shows the highest concentrations of PM2.5 are along the west coast. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Mono County, in northern California, reported the highest levels in 2020, the latest data available, at 39.1 micrograms per cubic meter, more than five times the national average of 7.3. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The US Environmental Protection Agency (EPA) recommends being exposed to no more than nine micrograms per cubic meter of PM2.5 in a year. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;With just 13,000 residents, Mono County is the least populated county in California and is home to dense rock formations and volcanic fields and craters, which spread fine ash particles and convert chemicals like sulfur dioxide into fine particulate matter like PM2.5. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Clackamas County, Oregon, and Marion County, Oregon, followed closely behind with 30.4 and 25 micrograms per cubic meter. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Just outside of Portland, Oregon, Clackamas County, home to 421,000 people, has long suffered poor air quality due to wildfire smoke and seasonal wood burning. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Experts from the American Lung Association believe Marion County, which is just below Clackamas County and has 300,000 residents, suffers high PM2.5 levels because pollution from nearby highways and farm fields gets trapped in the mountain ranges.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;On the opposite end of the spectrum, Carlton County, Minnesota, reports just 1.3 micrograms per cubic meter of PM2.5, according to the latest data. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Just beneath Lake Superior, 36,000-resident Carlton County is heavily forested, reducing pollution exposure from highways and cities.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Daily Mail</author><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 18:11:19 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikwFBVV95cUxQNE9fQmtsRlJGLVNJZFRmeUtBWUU4bFJDTjdLWVU1Zkk3N2duU3FXVzV5azU4NEpQWWR2R1V1bjJwcTM0RFlZTnZVZ0VaaXFCZDBBR0FNU2FtSzFtNUNQdUhJSXFnSEpPdlhCOGNkcWgtR1p6SkNhQTNNaU5lQ3pUaV84c2FEUDNzNWM4VWxibFFPYk0</guid></item><item><title>罕见的新型糖尿病是婴儿独有的，科学家报告- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/rare-new-form-of-diabetes-is-unique-to-babies-scientists-report</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Scientists have identified a single gene that gives rise to a rare form of  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/diabetes" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73018" data-postid="177022" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;diabetes&lt;/a&gt;, unique to newborn babies. Mutations of this gene can disable and ultimately kill off insulin-producing cells.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The new discovery reveals that the pancreas's beta cells – which create the insulin hormone our bodies need to manage blood glucose – are entirely dependent on the &lt;em&gt;TMEM167A&lt;/em&gt; gene. This gene also affects neuron function.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The ability to generate insulin-producing cells from  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/stem-cells" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73034" data-postid="177022" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;stem cells&lt;/a&gt; has enabled us to study what is dysfunctional in the beta cells of patients with rare forms as well as other types of diabetes," &lt;a href="https://news.exeter.ac.uk/faculty-of-health-and-life-sciences/researchers-discover-of-a-new-type-of-diabetes-in-babies/"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; diabetologist Miriam Cnop, from Free University of Brussels in Belgium. "This is an extraordinary model for studying disease mechanisms and testing treatments."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/a-distinct-new-form-of-diabetes-is-officially-recognized"&gt;A Distinct New Form of Diabetes Is Officially Recognized&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The international team mapped the genes of six babies who had been diagnosed with neonatal diabetes and &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Microcephaly"&gt;microcephaly&lt;/a&gt; before 6 months of age. Five of these babies also had epilepsy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This combination of diagnoses in infants is known as MEDS (microcephaly, epilepsy, and diabetes syndrome), and it's extremely rare, with only 11 individuals recorded so far.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Before this study, two genes had been linked to the syndrome: &lt;em&gt;IER3IP1 &lt;/em&gt;and YIPF5. For a baby to be born with MEDS, they must have inherited two mutated copies of the gene, one from each parent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gene sequencing revealed that the same inheritance pattern applies to MEDS babies with the insulin-blocking variant of the &lt;em&gt;TMEM167A&lt;/em&gt; gene, making this the third genetic cause of MEDS.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;TMEM167A &lt;/em&gt;is active across the pancreas and the brain in both adults and infants, humans and mice, which may explain why these babies experience problems with the function of both organs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To better understand how the &lt;em&gt;TMEM167A&lt;/em&gt; gene variant causes diabetes, the researchers removed the gene from human pluripotent stem cells, replacing it with the variant taken from one MEDS patient's DNA. These stem cells were then encouraged to develop into beta cells.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_177048" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-177048" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/fgene-08-00021-g001.jpg" alt="diagram of b cell issues" class="size-full wp-image-177048" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/fgene-08-00021-g001.jpg 1000w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/fgene-08-00021-g001-642x437.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/fgene-08-00021-g001-609x415.jpg 609w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/fgene-08-00021-g001-768x523.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/fgene-08-00021-g001-600x409.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-177048" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Similar beta cell failures occur in type 2 diabetes, as shown here. (Swisa et al., &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.3389/fgene.2017.00021"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Fronti. Genet.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, 2017)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;The gene variant didn't interfere with this development, but the beta cells produced were far from functional. Exposed to glucose, they did not release the insulin they're supposed to.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These cells also didn't cope well with the resulting disruptions to their endoplasmic reticulum (the maze-like structure inside a cell that shuttles material around): it tended to kill the beta cell.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/spark-into-space-comp?utm_source=promo_launch"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Launch-642x272.jpg" alt="Mid Article Promo Launch" class="alignnone wp-image-177073 size-medium" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Launch-642x272.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Launch-768x326.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Launch-600x255.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Launch.jpg 844w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
"Finding the DNA changes that cause diabetes in babies gives us a unique way to find the genes that play key roles in making and secreting insulin," &lt;a href="https://news.exeter.ac.uk/faculty-of-health-and-life-sciences/researchers-discover-of-a-new-type-of-diabetes-in-babies/"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; University of Exeter molecular geneticist Elisa de Franco.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The finding of specific DNA changes causing this rare type of diabetes in six children led us to clarifying the function of a little-known gene, &lt;em&gt;TMEM167A&lt;/em&gt;, showing how it plays a key role in insulin secretion."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This research was published in &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1172/JCI195756"&gt;The Journal of Clinical Investigation&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 18:01:58 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilwFBVV95cUxNSmpKSE1vR05iNUJmWGFQeXR6cDZIQnZCek1vTVl3VDFyZ01ReHBZTGNIYks1cVY3ZTZoLW1YdEpsVmNKaFBGbU9GZFhFM3JQMFhNWk16NnJpRWNsZTMxSHkySV8tM19yeHc4ejNaazdIeE9zNG9uSmN1UmFLb0pLRFNRVVRXelU1UlhqWElwZGN2RlU0Mm5B</guid></item><item><title>奥斯卡获奖女演员黛安·基顿死于细菌性肺炎。以下是关于感染的须知事项-福布斯</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/omerawan/2025/10/18/oscar-award-winning-actress-diane-keaton-died-of-bacterial-pneumonia-heres-what-to-know-about-the-infection/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="fs-article fs-responsive-text current-article article-body"&gt;&lt;figure class="embed-base image-embed embed-0" role="presentation"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="bMqrj"&gt;&lt;p class="Jp--BF7-"&gt;&lt;span class="Ccg9Ib-7 _8XF2kHYM"&gt;LOS ANGELES, CALIFORNIA - MAY 01: Actress Diane Keaton attends the premiere of STX's "Poms" at Regal LA Live on May 01, 2019 in Los Angeles, California. (Photo by Rodin Eckenroth/WireImage)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;small class="pGGCM2aD"&gt;WireImage&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Beloved Oscar winning actress Diane Keaton died of bacterial pneumonia at the age of 79, according to a &lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2025/10/16/movies/diane-keaton-cause-of-death.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer" data-ga-track="ExternalLink:https://www.nytimes.com/2025/10/16/movies/diane-keaton-cause-of-death.html" aria-label="death certificate"&gt;&lt;u data-ga-track="ExternalLink:https://www.nytimes.com/2025/10/16/movies/diane-keaton-cause-of-death.html"&gt;death certificate&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; from Saint John’s Health Center in Santa Monica, CA. Every year, pneumonia leads to about 1.2 million hospitalizations in the United States and over 41,000 deaths, according to the &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/nchs/fastats/pneumonia.htm" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer" data-ga-track="ExternalLink:https://www.cdc.gov/nchs/fastats/pneumonia.htm" aria-label="CDC"&gt;&lt;u data-ga-track="ExternalLink:https://www.cdc.gov/nchs/fastats/pneumonia.htm"&gt;CDC&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. Here is everything you need to know about pneumonia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="subhead-embed"&gt;Pneumonia- Causes And Symptoms&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pneumonia is an infection of the lung that results in the air sacs within the lungs to fill with fluid and pus. This can impact the body’s ability to take in oxygen, which then results in difficulty breathing for many patients. The disease can range from mild to life-threatening, depending on a person’s age, overall health, and type of organism that is causing the illness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The infection can be caused by a variety of different pathogens, including bacteria, viruses, and fungi. The most common type would be bacterial pneumonia, as was the cause in Keaton’s case. This type of pneumonia can produce more severe symptoms and is most commonly caused by the bacteria &lt;em&gt;Streptococcus Pneumoniae&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="vestpocket nsO6K"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Viral pneumonia is often caused by respiratory viruses such as influenza viruses, respiratory syncytial virus (RSV) and of course coronaviruses (COVID-19). Vaccines for all three of these viruses are available and can largely prevent the disease or mitigate symptoms. Fungal pneumonia is less common and typically affects people with weakened immune systems such as those with HIV or patients on chemotherapy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Signs and symptoms of pneumonia can appear similar to the common flu, but usually last longer, according to the &lt;a href="https://www.mayoclinic.org/diseases-conditions/pneumonia/symptoms-causes/syc-20354204" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer" data-ga-track="ExternalLink:https://www.mayoclinic.org/diseases-conditions/pneumonia/symptoms-causes/syc-20354204" aria-label="Mayo Clinic"&gt;&lt;u data-ga-track="ExternalLink:https://www.mayoclinic.org/diseases-conditions/pneumonia/symptoms-causes/syc-20354204"&gt;Mayo Clinic&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. The most common symptoms for pneumonia include fever, cough, difficulty breathing, shortness of breath, chest pain and fatigue.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="subhead-embed"&gt;Conditions Associated With Pneumonia&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Several health conditions can increase the risk of developing pneumonia or worsen its severity. Some of these underlying medical conditions include asthma, diabetes, heart failure, chronic kidney disease and chronic obstructive pulmonary disease. Those individuals with weakened immune systems are also at risk because they are less able to fight infections effectively. These would include patients that have cancer, HIV or are on long-term steroid use.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="subhead-embed"&gt;Why Pneumonia Can Be Devastating For Seniors&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Older adults account for the majority of pneumonia-related deaths each year in the U.S., particularly those aged 75 and above, according to the &lt;a href="https://blogs.cdc.gov/nchs/2020/03/11/4831/#:~:text=Over%20the%20past%2020%20years,Vital%20Statistics%20System%2C%20CDC%20WONDER." target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer" data-ga-track="ExternalLink:https://blogs.cdc.gov/nchs/2020/03/11/4831/#:~:text=Over%20the%20past%2020%20years,Vital%20Statistics%20System%2C%20CDC%20WONDER." aria-label="CDC"&gt;&lt;u data-ga-track="ExternalLink:https://blogs.cdc.gov/nchs/2020/03/11/4831/#:~:text=Over%20the%20past%2020%20years,Vital%20Statistics%20System%2C%20CDC%20WONDER."&gt;CDC&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. In seniors, physical changes associated with aging such as decreased lung elasticity and a weaker cough reflex can make it more challenging to clear bacteria and different organisms from the lungs. In addition, the elderly are more likely to have underlying health conditions that can complicate a successful recovery. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article_paragraph_7"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;An important complication known as sepsis, which is life-threatening, is also more common among the elderly. This is when the infection spreads to the bloodstream and can affect different organs in the body. In this scenario, the body’s immune system overreacts to the infection, causing damage and inflammation to multiple organs. This can ultimately lead to respiratory failure and death if left untreated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="MWrh7"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="subhead-embed"&gt;Preventing Pneumonia&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many of the various causes of pneumonia can be prevented from vaccines. The most common viral pneumonias such as flu, RSV, and COVID-19 can largely be prevented through vaccination. The pneumococcal vaccine, which protects against the most common bacterial cause of pneumonia, is now recommended for children younger than the age of 5 and adults 50 years of age and older, according to the &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/pneumococcal/hcp/vaccine-recommendations/index.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer" data-ga-track="ExternalLink:https://www.cdc.gov/pneumococcal/hcp/vaccine-recommendations/index.html" aria-label="CDC"&gt;&lt;u data-ga-track="ExternalLink:https://www.cdc.gov/pneumococcal/hcp/vaccine-recommendations/index.html"&gt;CDC&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. Vaccines remain the best protection against severe illness, hospitalization and death.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In addition, regular handwashing, covering coughs and sneezes and avoiding close contact with sick individuals can reduce transmission of respiratory illnesses. Finally, strengthening the immune system through regular exercise, sleep and avoiding smoking can add an extra layer of protection against acquiring debilitating infections.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pneumonia, as exemplified through the death of beloved actress Diane Keaton, remains a serious concern for public health. Although pneumonia can affect anyone at any age, early recognition and preventive strategies can help mitigate poor outcomes from an infection that affects millions of Americans every year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Forbes</author><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 16:50:17 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi7gFBVV95cUxQUGp2eGN1ak1QQmpIOTR5M1Bib0REM0otQkNBUzI0S2ZlVHAwWmR2YUlaY3Frc3NuTFlpTUhVZHFXWWV5cWdPRnVZYVNzb0lvVGVwSWF2WnZLcENkSU8ydGRmdHVOUzE1cUswMldtWS1fT2Q4enZReVZJdVNjOUtldlkwU19BOF9EWC1udUd3UEgyaFBNVWR3bWNXd1M1Rzd6RHplRUkxWllzMkk2dmJXa2FDVG1VLThQcXNxc2RlV0JROVlCQUYxVm9STWVJVEwtOFlqRWloMURFZXRCQ054Ny04RExaUTBXOG13MVVB</guid></item><item><title>新冠肺炎病例可能有所减少，但医生发现这一1种呼吸道疾病有所增加-雅虎</title><link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/articles/covid-cases-might-down-doctors-161602605.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="" data-article-body="true"&gt;&lt;h2 class="mb-4 text-xl font-bold md:text-2xl"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Toward the end of the summer and the start of the school year, COVID-19 cases were high across the country, with lots of people dealing with fatigue, congestion, headache, sore throat, and other bothersome symptoms.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;figure class="relative mb-4"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="relative text-sm mt-1 pr-2.5"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; Morsa Images / Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;This is all part of the predictable COVID pattern, but what about cases now?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“COVID has a summer peak, and then it wanes a little bit, and then ... what it has been doing is picking up again around Thanksgiving and Christmas, as people start gathering,” said &lt;a href="https://med.umn.edu/bio/jill-foster" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Dr. Jill Foster;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Dr. Jill Foster&lt;/a&gt;, a professor at the University of Minnesota Medical School.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;At the moment, we’re in a lull from COVID-19, Foster said. This may feel like a breath of fresh air for those afraid of catching the virus, but this doesn’t mean COVID cases aren’t around at all.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;According to &lt;a href="https://publichealth.jhu.edu/faculty/1821/suruchi-sood" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Suruchi Sood;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Suruchi Sood&lt;/a&gt;, an assistant professor at Johns Hopkins University in Baltimore, there are some Centers for Disease Control COVID tracking delays partly because of the government shutdown. But from the data that is available and anecdotally in her own practice, “We don’t seem to be seeing, thankfully, yet, an uptick of COVID.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;COVID tracking data isn’t as detailed or accurate as it was earlier in the pandemic because of a variety of factors, including less testing and funding changes. However, between what doctors who spoke to HuffPost are observing in their clinics ― along with the data available ― it does appear that we are beyond the late-summer, early fall peak.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;We may not have another peak this year, but “my guess is that it’ll pick back up again when people start gathering, staying indoors more, being in close proximity to each other,” Foster said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mb-4 text-xl font-bold md:text-2xl"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;While COVID-19 may be low, there appears to be one illness that’s increasing right now.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.buzzfeed.com/lizmrichardson/doctors-health-lies-misconceptions?utm_source=yahoo-recirc-links" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Medical Professionals Are Calling Out The Biggest &amp;quot;Health Misconceptions&amp;quot; People Still Believe (But Really Shouldn't);elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Medical Professionals Are Calling Out The Biggest "Health Misconceptions" People Still Believe (But Really Shouldn't)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="relative mb-4"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="relative text-sm mt-1 pr-2.5"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; Simpleimages / Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.buzzfeed.com/fabianabuontempo/small-habits-that-can-change-your-body?utm_source=yahoo-recirc-links" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk='slk:People Are Sharing The "Harmless" Habits That Changed Their Bodies Forever;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas' class="link "&gt;People Are Sharing The "Harmless" Habits That Changed Their Bodies Forever&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;You may be surprised to hear that COVID-19 cases are dipping, especially if you’re one of the many people fighting congestion and a sore throat this week.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“If we look at our own data from Northeast Ohio ... if we looked at this most recent week from our data, and this is specimens that are collected in our lab, the SARS-CoV-2 activity continued to decline from its ‘summer peak,’” said &lt;a href="https://providers.clevelandclinic.org/provider/steven-gordon/4269710" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Dr. Steven Gordon;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Dr. Steven Gordon&lt;/a&gt;, the chairman of the Department of Infectious Disease at the Cleveland Clinic.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;At the Cleveland Clinic, COVID positivity rate was 5% last week, he noted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“What is higher up, and has been for the past few weeks, is the rhinovirus, which causes the traditional cold, as well as other enterovirus [which also cause cold symptoms] — and those are at 20% positivity,” Gordon said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;While Gordon is specifically referring to cases in Northeast Ohio, his findings align with the CDC data that’s available, which shows cases of rhinovirus and enterovirus were &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/nrevss/php/dashboard/index.html" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:increasing as of the end of September;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;increasing as of the end of September&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mb-4 text-xl font-bold md:text-2xl"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;There are steps you can take to stay healthy this fall.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;figure class="relative mb-4"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="relative text-sm mt-1 pr-2.5"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; Skynesher / Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.buzzfeed.com/kristinlouiseduncombe/vagina-atrophy-prolapse-menopause-beauty-standards?utm_source=yahoo-recirc-links" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:My Doctor Looked At My Vagina And Said 3 Shocking Words. It Started Me On A Life-Changing Journey.;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;My Doctor Looked At My Vagina And Said 3 Shocking Words. It Started Me On A Life-Changing Journey.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;As we head into virus season, now’s the time to think about the steps you can take to stay healthy this fall and winter, Gordon said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“We’d rather prevent, obviously, than treat,” said Gordon. The best protection against the flu is the flu shot, “and it’s still recommended for anyone greater than six months of age,” he added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The best way to prevent a severe COVID-19 infection and hospitalization is by getting the COVID shot, too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“Now that we have COVID vaccination available and influenza vaccination available, it takes several weeks for us to develop immunity, so now is a really great time to get vaccinated,” Sood said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;COVID vaccination is still a safe and effective way to reduce how sick you get. “There was &lt;a href="https://www.nejm.org/doi/full/10.1056/NEJMoa2510226" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:a study that just came out;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;a study that just came out&lt;/a&gt; ... showing that in the VA [Veterans] Health Systems, that even in this last season, COVID-19 vaccination reduced hospitalizations, deaths and ER visits in the VA population,” Sood explained.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;You can get your &lt;a href="https://www.uchealth.org/today/everything-you-need-to-know-about-the-2025-26-covid-19-vaccine-and-flu-shots/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:flu shot and COVID shot at the same time;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;flu shot and COVID shot at the same time&lt;/a&gt;, and they’re available at pharmacies throughout the country. It’s best to talk to your doctor or local pharmacy about COVID shot eligibility in your area.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;It’s also important to take care of your health overall by &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/life/topic/fitness" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:exercising;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;exercising&lt;/a&gt; and eating nutritious meals, Sood said. This can help protect you from respiratory viruses. Washing your hands is also a good way to stay well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“Another thing people can do is stay away from people that are sick,” said Foster.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;If you’re at the airport and notice someone is coughing and sneezing near you, get up and move. Or if you’re the one sneezing and coughing, stay home or wear a mask if you have to be around other people.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“That’s part of good citizenship, of trying to protect other people,” Foster said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mb-4 text-xl font-bold md:text-2xl"&gt;&lt;span&gt;At-home COVID-19 (or flu) tests are also important tools for respiratory virus season. If you test positive, stay away from other people and let your doctor know to see if you’re eligible for certain medications.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;figure class="relative mb-4"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="relative text-sm mt-1 pr-2.5"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; Olena Domanytska / Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.buzzfeed.com/hannahloewentheil/mundane-behaviors-impact-health?utm_source=yahoo-recirc-links" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk='slk:Medical Professionals Are Sharing "Mundane" Things That Actually Make So Many People Sick;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas' class="link "&gt;Medical Professionals Are Sharing "Mundane" Things That Actually Make So Many People Sick&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“I think we’ve sort of lost that sense of community a little bit ... what I do impacts others,” Foster said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;You never know if the person you’re sitting next to at a restaurant or passing by at the office has a problem with their immune system. “You might be giving them a death sentence when what you needed to do was either stay home or at least wear a mask when you went out in public. And that’s not that hard to do,” Foster said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;While COVID-19 cases aren’t high right now, that can change at any moment, which makes it important to take steps to stop the spread of the virus and to protect those around you.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;em&gt;This article originally appeared on&lt;/em&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/entry/covid-cases-lull-october-2025_l_68e7eb40e4b0a9f46d0c848d" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:HuffPost.;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;&lt;em&gt;HuffPost.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Also in Goodful: &lt;a href="https://www.buzzfeed.com/caradaniellebrown/friendship-breakup-best-friend-ghosted-reason?utm_source=yahoo-recirc-links" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:My Best Friend And I Stopped Talking For 5 Years. Then I Learned The Surprising Truth About Why She Cut Me Off.;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;My Best Friend And I Stopped Talking For 5 Years. Then I Learned The Surprising Truth About Why She Cut Me Off.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Also in Goodful: &lt;a href="https://www.buzzfeed.com/dannicaramirez/surprising-things-women-do-in-private?utm_source=yahoo-recirc-links" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk='slk:"My Husband Was Shocked": Women Are Sharing The Everyday Routines And Practices They Do In Private That Have Men Incredibly Baffled;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas' class="link "&gt;"My Husband Was Shocked": Women Are Sharing The Everyday Routines And Practices They Do In Private That Have Men Incredibly Baffled&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Also in Goodful: &lt;a href="https://www.buzzfeed.com/lizmrichardson/bad-health-advice-doctors-wont-follow?utm_source=yahoo-recirc-links" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk='slk:Medical Professionals Are Calling Out The Biggest "Mistakes" People Make All The Time While Trying To Improve Their Health;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas' class="link "&gt;Medical Professionals Are Calling Out The Biggest "Mistakes" People Make All The Time While Trying To Improve Their Health&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.buzzfeed.com/jillianwilson/covid-cases-lull-october-2025?utm_source=yahoo-recirc-links" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Read it on BuzzFeed.com;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Read it on BuzzFeed.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Yahoo</author><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 16:16:02 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiAFBVV95cUxNcmRkOWpya1JoNGJwb3hvaFB2ZGF0YkIwTndqQTMtQmRhRTBRN1NrS0tpMFkwbFpyWVdHUzRrTFZjUUgwZzhqOE51bmtCMnZHT1Q1V0c5Wm94NXhJUzlaSC1yTW5tVlF0dzZGQ2txYTVaQng4YnFmTEhuSlhYeERmLWJIQ09EV3Rl</guid></item><item><title>一种甜美的水果，还可以控制血糖水平。研究声称它降低了糖尿病患者的风险-《经济时报》</title><link>https://m.economictimes.com/magazines/panache/a-fruit-that-is-sweet-and-can-also-control-blood-sugar-levels-study-claims-it-lowers-diabetics-risk/articleshow/124570023.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div data-brcount="26" class="artText"&gt;&lt;p&gt;It may sound surprising, but research suggests that eating mangoes—a fruit known for its natural sweetness—can actually help manage &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a ref="dofollow" data-ga-onclick="Inarticle articleshow link click#Magazines#href" href="/topic/blood-sugar-levels" target="_blank"&gt;blood sugar levels&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;. A study conducted by researchers at &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a ref="dofollow" data-ga-onclick="Inarticle articleshow link click#Magazines#href" href="/topic/george-mason-university" target="_blank"&gt;George Mason University&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; revealed that individuals who consumed mango daily had better blood sugar control and reduced body fat compared to those who opted for low-sugar snacks. The study’s findings, published in Foods in August 2025 under the title “Daily Mango Intake Improves Glycemic and Body Composition Outcomes in Adults with Prediabetes: A Randomized Controlled Study,” emphasize that the nutritional context of sugar within whole foods plays a more crucial role than the sugar content alone.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;The Science Behind Mango’s Benefits&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;In an interview with&lt;/p&gt;&lt;em&gt; Science Daily&lt;/em&gt;&lt;p&gt;, Raedeh Basiri, Assistant Professor in George Mason’s Department of Nutrition and Food Studies, explained that it’s not simply about how much sugar food contains, but about the overall nutritional makeup. Mangoes, for instance, offer a unique balance—while they contain natural sugars, these are accompanied by fiber, antioxidants, and essential vitamins. This combination helps slow sugar absorption, keeping blood glucose levels stable.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-mid-newpos-mgid="mgid_124570023" id="div-mgid-mid-newpos-124570023"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p id="E_3" class="etoro"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In contrast, foods that contain added sugars—such as processed cereals or packaged low-sugar snacks—lack this natural balance and can actually heighten the risk of developing diabetes. The fiber in mangoes supports digestion and promotes satiety, helping control appetite and preventing overeating, which further aids weight management.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Glycemic Index and Safe Consumption Tips&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mangoes fall within a moderate range on the glycemic index (GI), scoring between 51 and 56, a range comparable to orange juice. According to the &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a ref="dofollow" data-ga-onclick="Inarticle articleshow link click#Magazines#href" href="/topic/american-diabetes-association" target="_blank"&gt;American Diabetes Association&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; (ADA), this places mangoes in the low-to-medium GI category, making them suitable for moderate consumption. The ADA recommends choosing fruits that are fresh, frozen, or canned without added sugars.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-mid-vdoai="vdoai_124570023" id="div-vdoai-mid-124570023"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A typical serving of fruit should provide around 15 grams of carbohydrates, which roughly equals two-thirds of a cup of mango. The ADA also notes that fresh fruit tends to be more satisfying than dried varieties, as the portion size of dried fruit is smaller and can lead to excessive intake of sugars.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-size="[[300, 250], [600, 250], [600, 300]]" data-adsslot="/7176/Economictimes/ET_News/ET_News_ROS/ET_News_ROS_MID_INTL_300" data-loc="100" id="div-gpt-ad-858478126-1-124570023" class="country_specAD"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p data-size="[[300, 250], [600, 250], [600, 300]]" data-adsslot="/7176/Economictimes/ET_News/ET_News_ROS/ET_News_ROS_MID1_INTL_300" data-loc="2" id="div-gpt-ad-858478132-1-124570023" class="country_specAD2nd"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-size="[[300, 250], [600, 250], [600, 300]]" data-adsslot="/7176/Economictimes/ET_News/ET_News_ROS/ET_News_ROS_MID1_INTL_300" data-loc="5" id="div-gpt-ad-858478132-1-124570023" class="country_specAD2nd"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-size="[[300, 250], [600, 250], [600, 300]]" data-adsslot="/7176/Economictimes/ET_News/ET_News_ROS/ET_News_ROS_MID1_INTL_300" data-loc="3" id="div-gpt-ad-858478132-1-124570023" class="country_specAD2nd"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Additional Health Perks&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Beyond controlling blood sugar, mangoes may also improve cholesterol levels. A study published in the British Journal of Nutrition in 2011 observed that mice fed a high-fat diet supplemented with freeze-dried mango exhibited lower body fat, reduced cholesterol, and improved glucose levels compared to those treated with lipid- or sugar-lowering drugs like fenofibrate and rosiglitazone.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The research underscores that incorporating whole fruits like mangoes into one’s diet not only satisfies sweet cravings naturally but also supports metabolic health, making this tropical fruit a surprisingly smart choice for balanced living.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h3&gt;Signs Of High Blood Sugar&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;As per a Cleveland Clinic report, early signs of high blood sugar, also known as hyperglycemia, often appear gradually and may include excessive thirst or hunger, frequent urination, headaches, and blurred vision. These symptoms occur as the body struggles to manage rising glucose levels. If left unchecked for a longer period, chronic hyperglycemia can lead to more serious issues such as persistent fatigue, unexplained weight loss, recurring vaginal yeast or skin infections, and slow-healing cuts or sores. Recognizing these warning signals early is crucial, as timely lifestyle changes and medical intervention can help prevent severe complications like nerve damage or diabetes-related disorders.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;meta content="cms.article3" name="cmsei-article3"&gt;&lt;div class="inSideInd"&gt;&lt;div data-ga-action="Preference Banner InArticle Widget" data-ga-impression="Preference Banner InArticle Widget#Impressions | Preference Banner | Articleshow#url" class="Pbanner"&gt;&lt;div class="Pbannertext"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Add &lt;/p&gt;&lt;img alt="ET Logo" src="https://img.etimg.com/photo/123467569.cms"&gt;&lt;p&gt; as a Reliable and Trusted News Source&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Economic Times</author><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 16:15:29 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigAJBVV95cUxQNkQzYUE3YktFWHNVSHpSYzZrVWtrY083WWthSEhacWprS20wR01OUjc2ZlpVSFRnWUdVbVRhZEpPNER1LWFlWEtRNFVZU3RPR2g2dkJWRi1QNlNDNHpTY3o0MGItYTF6N2pZOEl6UWlDMV8tOWNTaHdjSS1qTF9ZX2cwUXhoaklrQ1NlSkZzQkpwSWVVT1lLNS1adjlrUnpGSTZndzNoM1RqOEdmUndQSU84VkJKQ0JYaTlZVkhpT3dVdnBVd2NUYkwtZmJNbGJFU2F2V1VCdmw5TGxaTHlvNVA3TU01NERjdGpzbm50eVB3VEREM1pnN3pTc2xDMkVm0gGGAkFVX3lxTE1odjBmSW9fMUk2YlJXLWdHM3ZSb2lZY2tMeXh3N01VMk9IMHBJVFYtQUtmWm9xOHpSN2czQUxtTDI0eUh4aVB4Qm5yVVd6bkhCcFJLb0NHWG93Q25LUmdSd3NnQ1k3cUp5MFZTaFZseWlDVGk4YXYyT3VuUmZwcVFmV2ktUEM4aHBtS2pQZmxjTTFuZXhoNE5wRnk2OGRvSVNjTnZ0VUgwMlFIOGxWRjVPYmNieU9HTTBGaTJsOFE5QnhLbm9IZktpSFZkUV9UVWFMR0NaSUw1RnFqOXVEaUU2alJPZlVRVkVPTUc1c2YtNjZmSDRCUG5CemdVTEh2QVBRUnJRWlE</guid></item><item><title>当助听器还不够时--《纽约时报》</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/10/18/health/cochlear-implants-older-people.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The New York Times</author><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 14:29:08 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigwFBVV95cUxNMDZ0U2dXYTN0MXdWanVzT2RGek8wOXYzaDk0TmlqYldvWkZ2NUhmdERxZmNHXzVXSUpOR05WLWhINjEyeU9lN0xWWVVZLVd1N2JIUHZVRUdIQXNYRldrQzdTRkU0YUt2eU9ISFdsYkNNRmNWeW9VazBLRmFMVzhtVFVBMA</guid></item><item><title>音乐可以帮助缓解手术或疾病带来的疼痛。科学家正在倾听- KSL.com</title><link>https://www.ksl.com/article/51392022/music-could-help-ease-pain-from-surgery-or-illness-scientists-are-listening</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="articleContainer"&gt;&lt;p&gt;SAN DIEGO — Nurse Rod Salaysay works with all kinds of instruments in the hospital: a thermometer, a stethoscope and sometimes his guitar and ukulele.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the recovery unit of UC San Diego Health, Salaysay helps patients manage pain after surgery. Along with medications, he offers tunes on request and sometimes sings. His repertoire ranges from folk songs in English and Spanish to Minuet in G Major and movie favorites like "Somewhere Over the Rainbow."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Patients often smile or nod along. Salaysay even sees changes in their vital signs like lower heart rate and blood pressure, and some may request fewer painkillers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"There's often a cycle of worry, pain, anxiety in a hospital," he said, "but you can help break that cycle with music."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Salaysay is a one-man band, but he's not alone. Over the past two decades, live performances and recorded music have flowed into hospitals and doctors' offices as research grows on how songs can help ease pain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The healing power of song may sound intuitive given music's deep roots in human culture. But the science of whether and how music dulls acute and chronic pain — technically called music-induced analgesia — is just catching up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;No one suggests that a catchy song can fully eliminate serious pain. But several recent studies, including in the journals &lt;a href="https://journals.lww.com/pain/abstract/2025/08000/individualizing_musical_tempo_to_spontaneous_rates.11.aspx" rel="nofollow" target="_blank"&gt;Pain&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41598-024-72882-2" rel="nofollow" target="_blank"&gt;Scientific Reports&lt;/a&gt;, have suggested that listening to music can either reduce the perception of pain or enhance a person's ability to tolerate it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What seems to matter most is that patients — or their families — choose the music selections themselves and listen intently, not just as background noise.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Pain is a really complex experience," said Adam Hanley, a psychologist at Florida State University. "It's created by a physical sensation, and by our thoughts about that sensation and emotional reaction to it."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Two people with the same condition or injury may feel vastly different levels of acute or chronic pain. Or the same person might experience pain differently from one day to the next.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Acute pain is felt when pain receptors in a specific part of the body — like a hand touching a hot stove — send signals to the brain, which processes the short-term pain. Chronic pain usually involves long-term structural or other changes to the brain, which heighten overall sensitivity to pain signals. Researchers are still investigating how this occurs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Pain is interpreted and translated by the brain," which may ratchet the signal up or down, said Dr. Gilbert Chandler, a specialist in chronic spinal pain at the Tallahassee Orthopedic Clinic.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Researchers know music can draw attention away from pain, lessening the sensation. But studies also suggest that listening to preferred music helps dull pain more than listening to podcasts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Music is a distractor. It draws your focus away from the pain. But it's doing more than that," said Caroline Palmer, a psychologist at McGill University who studies music and pain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Scientists are still tracing the various neural pathways at work, said Palmer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We know that almost all of the brain becomes active when we engage in music," said Kate Richards Geller, a registered music therapist in Los Angeles. "That changes the perception and experience of pain — and the isolation and anxiety of pain."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The idea of using recorded music to lessen pain associated with dental surgery began in the late 19th century before local anesthetics were available. Today researchers are studying what conditions make music most effective.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Researchers at Erasmus University Rotterdam in the Netherlands conducted a study on 548 participants to see how listening to five &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41598-024-72882-2" rel="nofollow" target="_blank"&gt;genres of music&lt;/a&gt; — classical, rock, pop, urban and electronic — extended their ability to withstand acute pain, as measured by exposure to very cold temperatures.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All music helped, but there was no single winning genre.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The more people listened to a favorite genre, the more they could endure pain," said co-author Dr. Emy van der Valk Bouman. "A lot of people thought that classical music would help them more. Actually, we are finding more evidence that what's best is just the music you like."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The exact reasons are still unclear, but it may be because familiar songs activate more memories and emotions, she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The simple act of choosing is itself powerful, said Claire Howlin, director of the Music and Health Psychology Lab at Trinity College Dublin, who co-authored a study that suggested &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41598-024-72882-2" rel="nofollow" target="_blank"&gt;allowing patients to select songs&lt;/a&gt; improved their pain tolerance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It's one thing that people can have control over if they have a chronic condition — it gives them agency," she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Active, focused listening also seems to matter.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hanley, the Florida State psychologist, co-authored a preliminary study suggesting &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40225443/" rel="nofollow" target="_blank"&gt;daily attentive listening&lt;/a&gt; might reduce chronic pain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Music has a way of lighting up different parts of the brain," he said, "so you're giving people this positive emotional bump that takes their mind away from the pain."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It's a simple prescription with no side effects, some doctors now say.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cecily Gardner, a jazz singer in Culver City, California, said she used music to help get through a serious illness and has sung to friends battling pain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Music reduces stress, fosters community," she said, "and just transports you to a better place."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>KSL.com</author><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 14:09:47 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMisgFBVV95cUxNb3JoTHZnQkNxVXNYUVRjcUh2QXd4enRsVHZIRVBKbS14TXVZQ3JHZWg1RXFwN1ZISnJNQnJidXJMR01SNDBCeTZqTGxENUhFcDkzNkN5dWx1ZTFhYkxOSDhSNjJoam9GdE1SNzZUVnZZV3hZWmdBMGJoRzc3cEM1MnpYRzc4aGFabUhsbEZjMXNrU1lyQzdseDZjTFRBYWh4QWFOdmdCcmJvWkwtd19wWVVn</guid></item><item><title>意见：世界更年期日将犹他州更年期护理差距置于聚光灯下-雅虎</title><link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/articles/opinion-world-menopause-day-puts-140000477.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="" data-article-body="true"&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Oct. 18 is designated as World Menopause Day by the &lt;a href="https://www.imsociety.org/education/world-menopause-day-2025/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:International Menopause Society;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;International Menopause Society&lt;/a&gt;. The purpose of the day is to raise awareness of menopause and the support options available for improving health and well-being. So it’s the right moment to examine how the U.S. and Utah perform on menopause care.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Fewer than 5% of American women use hormone replacement therapy (HRT), according to &lt;a href="https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jama-health-forum/fullarticle/2823976" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:JAMA;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;JAMA&lt;/a&gt;, to help manage symptoms they experience during the menopause transition. Compare that with an HRT usage rate closer to 15% in the U.K. and Australia, where prescribing is steadily rising.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;American health care practitioners are not well prepared: only &lt;a href="https://www.mayoclinicproceedings.org/article/S0025-6196(18)30701-8/abstract" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:6.8%;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;6.8%&lt;/a&gt; of family medicine, internal medicine and obstetrics and gynecology residents reported feeling adequately prepared to manage women experiencing menopause transition symptoms, according to a 2019 Mayo Clinic survey. Six years later, that has undoubtedly risen with the increasing general awareness of menopause, but it’s still shockingly low.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Utahns face some additional challenges. The state does fairly well on the ratio of obstetricians and gynecologists (OB-GYNs) to women, ranking &lt;a href="https://www.beckersphysicianleadership.com/physician-workforce/womens-health-providers-by-state-2023/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:18th;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;18th&lt;/a&gt; in the country. However, as a state with one of the highest birth rates, Utah OB-GYNs are busy with maternal care rather than menopause care. While women often think to turn first to their OB-GYNs for help with menopause, they might not be the best equipped. Primary care physicians (PCPs) can provide menopause care, but Utah has one of the &lt;a href="https://www.beckershospitalreview.com/rankings-and-ratings/states-ranked-by-total-primary-care-physicians-in-2024/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:worst ratios of PCPs to residents;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;worst ratios of PCPs to residents&lt;/a&gt; in the entire United States.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Medication options are also more limited in the U.S. There are no approved testosterone treatments for menopausal women despite the fact that in appropriate dosages, testosterone can increase energy, improve sexual function, and preserve muscle mass and bone health. American doctors only prescribe testosterone to women “off label,” whereas Australia offers a cream approved specifically for postmenopausal women.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="mb-4 text-lg font-bold"&gt;The shadow of old data&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;So why is the U.S. so different in our approach to menopause care?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Much of the hesitation originates with a Women’s Health Initiative study published in 2002. The data from that study was &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC10758198/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:presented in black-and-white terms that overstated risks;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;presented in black-and-white terms that overstated risks&lt;/a&gt;. But those headlines stuck, and two decades later, many women are still paying the price. It takes &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC3241518/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:17 years;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;17 years&lt;/a&gt; on average for medical research updates to translate into day-to-day medical practice. This is far too long for women to wait for effective and appropriate menopause care.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Despite the need to close the gap between current medical practice and new research, the U.S. still lacks adequate medical training around menopause. Only &lt;a href="https://medicalxpress.com/news/2023-08-survey-menopause-residency.html" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:31.3%;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;31.3%&lt;/a&gt; of obstetrics and gynecology residency program directors report they have any type of menopause curriculum as part of their residents’ training. For most, this curriculum consists of one to two lectures per year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="mb-4 text-lg font-bold"&gt;The human cost of delay&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;When menopause symptoms go untreated, the costs are high. Sleep suffers. Cognitive function declines. Emotional well-being takes a hit. Productivity at work drops. And over time, without hormone replacement intervention, health risks can mount — most specifically, increases in osteoporosis, cardiovascular disease and the likelihood of Alzheimer’s.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;So better menopause care isn’t just a women’s health issue. It’s a public health issue.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="mb-4 text-lg font-bold"&gt;Moving forward&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;While we don’t know everything about hormones, in large part because of a significant gap in research on women’s health specifically, the overwhelming consensus today is that &lt;a href="https://www.bcrf.org/about-breast-cancer/hrt-breast-cancer-risk/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:HRT is both safe for most women;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;HRT is both safe for most women&lt;/a&gt; and the most effective solution to treat menopause-related symptoms. And it should be readily available. This requires better education for health care providers, more specialized and holistic care, and less stigma. It also means giving women space to track their own symptoms, understand what’s changing and decide what “forward” looks like for them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;That’s why I founded &lt;a href="http://inflexxionhealth.com/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Inflexxion Health;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Inflexxion Health&lt;/a&gt; — so that together, we can ensure that women in Utah no longer have to wait for the care they deserve.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;This &lt;a href="https://www.imsociety.org/education/world-menopause-day-2025/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:World Menopause Day;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;World Menopause Day&lt;/a&gt;, awareness must translate into action.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Yahoo</author><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiwFBVV95cUxOM2NtUWVXUjlobnRmamxSQ1lkZE5LNXZhMExkVmdJa3NUQ3U5LWlpTjVwRzgtSjZOdlJFRFl5NjZNS09GY3h3cVpFUUttN1dVR3dwZV8wcTBsZXk4M3gzNGh0bHhqTElGWjRIUDRiMHJHUnhnbFJoY3FnTEctVXpxQXA4MF9oNHZSUU5j</guid></item><item><title>随着危险的病毒在美国地区传播，卫生官员发出警告： “已经超过去年的总数” -雅虎</title><link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/articles/health-officials-issue-warning-dangerous-140000417.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="" data-article-body="true"&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The Whiteside County Health Department has brought awareness to West Nile virus cases in Illinois that have already surpassed last year's total, &lt;a href="https://www.kwqc.com/2025/09/17/west-nile-cases-illinois-already-higher-than-last-years-total/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:as reported by KWQC;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;as reported by KWQC&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;"Illinois … has confirmed 79 cases so far this year, already exceeding last year's total by 10," said Whiteside County Health Department representative Cory Law.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;There has been one death due to the virus.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="mb-4 text-lg font-bold"&gt;What's happening?&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;As the planet warms, environmental factors like an increase in the frequency and severity of extreme weather conditions, such as increased rainfall, are creating ideal breeding grounds for mosquitoes and other insects that spread disease. As global temperatures rise, the habitats for these insects — called vectors — expand and breeding increases, so there is a higher risk of vector-borne illness in humans.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="mb-4 text-lg font-bold"&gt;Why are vector-borne illnesses important to control?&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;When vectors have ideal conditions, they are free to reproduce and expand their habitats, so humans are at greater risk of contracting viruses.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;In Illinois, the West Nile virus, specifically, is mainly spread through the bite of an infected mosquito that has fed on an infected bird.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;While most people who contract the virus only experience mild flu-like symptoms, vulnerable populations such as people with chronic health conditions or weakened immune systems, or older adults, are at higher risk for severe illness. They may experience tremors, convulsions, coma, or even death. The Illinois resident who died of West Nile was in their 60s.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="mb-4 text-lg font-bold"&gt;What's being done about the increased risk of vector-borne illnesses?&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Illinois officials are advising locals to use EPA-registered insect repellent, wear long-sleeve shirts and pants when outside to minimize skin exposure, avoid being outside at dawn and dusk when mosquitoes are most active, and remove any standing water around their property.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;In the long term, around the world, it is important that we continue to &lt;a href="https://guide.thecooldown.com/explore/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:support sustainable practices;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;support sustainable practices&lt;/a&gt; to reduce pollution in order to reduce rising temperatures, so that vector-borne illness is minimized.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Join our &lt;a href="https://www.thecooldown.com/future-newsletter/?recyXgyr69tDbvL2f" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:free newsletter;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;free newsletter&lt;/a&gt; for &lt;strong&gt;good news&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;useful tips&lt;/strong&gt;, and don't miss &lt;a href="https://rb.gy/ivhzmj" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:this cool list;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;this cool list&lt;/a&gt; of easy ways to help yourself while helping the planet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Yahoo</author><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilgFBVV95cUxOZ2tsdzhDZ1UtZ1V6ZVNrZ0dJQXExbFBjVUs4ZU1ZNmRDeVk5U0llZVBsa3YyLV9SYzl4NXk4RF81NjRRQ1AyVW5sNmdkTmRkeGJTZy1rQzl3SHJjcjJqM3RqMnhmMjFhOTg2N3J0R2p4OTQ3ZUFVMDVDaXBJTC1fcmFzTzJJcWswMmZucWl1aXdWYWhPY3c</guid></item><item><title>我们是否生活在一个愚蠢的黄金时代？ -卫报</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2025/oct/18/are-we-living-in-a-golden-age-of-stupidity-technology</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body-commercial-selector article-body-viewer-selector dcr-11jq3zt"&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-15rw6c2"&gt;S&lt;/span&gt;tep into the Massachusetts Institute of Technology (MIT) Media Lab in Cambridge, US, and the future feels a little closer. Glass cabinets display prototypes of weird and wonderful creations, from tiny desktop robots to a surrealist sculpture created by an AI model prompted to design a tea set made from body parts. In the lobby, an AI waste-sorting assistant named Oscar can tell you where to put your used coffee cup. Five floors up, research scientist Nataliya Kosmyna has been working on wearable brain-computer interfaces she hopes will one day enable people who cannot speak, due to neurodegenerative diseases such as amyotrophic lateral sclerosis, to communicate using their minds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Kosmyna spends a lot of her time reading and analysing people’s brain states. Another project she is working on is a wearable device – one prototype looks like a pair of glasses – that can tell when someone is getting confused or losing focus. Around two years ago, she began receiving out-of-the blue emails from strangers who reported that they had started using large language models such as ChatGPT and felt their brain had changed as a result. Their memories didn’t seem as good – was that even possible, they asked her? Kosmyna herself had been struck by how quickly people had already begun to rely on generative AI. She noticed colleagues using ChatGPT at work, and the applications she received from researchers hoping to join her team started to look different. Their emails were longer and more formal and, sometimes, when she interviewed candidates on Zoom, she noticed they kept pausing before responding and looking off to the side – were they getting AI to help them, she wondered, shocked. And if they were using AI, how much did they even understand of the answers they were giving?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="sign-in-gate"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;With some MIT colleagues, Kosmyna set up an experiment that used an electroencephalogram to monitor people’s brain activity while they wrote essays, either with no digital assistance, or with the help of an internet search engine, or ChatGPT. She found that the more external help participants had, the lower their level of brain connectivity, so those who used ChatGPT to write showed significantly less activity in the brain networks associated with cognitive processing, attention and creativity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;In other words, whatever the people using ChatGPT felt was going on inside their brains, the scans showed there wasn’t much happening up there.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The study’s participants, who were all enrolled at MIT or nearby universities, were asked, right after they had handed in their work, if they could recall what they had written. “Barely anyone in the ChatGPT group could give a quote,” Kosmyna says. “That was concerning, because you just wrote it and you do not remember anything.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Kosmyna is 35, trendily dressed in a blue shirt dress and a big, multicoloured necklace, and she speaks faster than most people can think. As she observes, writing an essay requires skills that are important in our wider lives: the ability to synthesise information, consider competing perspectives and construct an argument. You use these skills in everyday conversations. “How are you going to deal with that? Are you going to be, like, ‘Err … can I just check my phone?’” she says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The experiment was small (54 participants) and has not yet been peer reviewed. In June, however, Kosmyna posted it online, thinking other researchers might find it interesting, and then she went about her day, unaware that she had just created an international media frenzy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Alongside the journalist requests, she received more than 4,000 emails from around the world, many from stressed-out teachers who feel their students aren’t learning properly because they are using ChatGPT to do their homework. They worry AI is creating a generation who can produce passable work but don’t have any usable knowledge or understanding of the material.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The fundamental issue, Kosmyna says, is that as soon as a technology becomes available that makes our lives easier, we’re evolutionarily primed to use it. “Our brains love shortcuts, it’s in our nature. But your brain needs friction to learn. It needs to have a challenge.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;If brains need friction but also instinctively avoid it, it’s interesting that the promise of technology has been to create a “frictionless” user experience, to ensure that, provided we slide from app to app or screen to screen, we will meet no resistance. The frictionless user experience is why we unthinkingly offload ever more information and work to our digital devices; it’s why internet rabbit holes are so easy to fall down and so hard to climb out of; it’s why generative AI has already integrated itself so completely into most people’s lives.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;We know, from our collective experience, that once you become accustomed to the hyperefficient cybersphere, the friction-filled real world feels harder to deal with. So you avoid phone calls, use self-checkouts, order everything from an app; you reach for your phone to do the maths sum you could do in your head, to check a fact before you have to dredge it up from memory, to input your destination on Google maps and travel from A to B on autopilot. Maybe you &lt;a href="https://www.arts.gov/stories/blog/2024/federal-data-reading-pleasure-all-signs-show-slump#:~:text=Last%20fall,%20the%20NEA%20reported,54.6%20percent%20ten%20years%20earlier." data-link-name="in body link"&gt;stop reading books&lt;/a&gt; because maintaining that kind of focus feels like friction; maybe you dream of owning a self-driving car. Is this the dawn of what the writer and education expert Daisy Christodoulou calls a “&lt;a href="https://substack.nomoremarking.com/p/are-we-living-in-a-stupidogenic-society" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;stupidogenic society&lt;/a&gt;”, a parallel to an &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/society/2025/may/20/young-people-obesity-2030-report" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;obesogenic society&lt;/a&gt;, in which it is easy to become stupid because machines can think for you?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;aside data-spacefinder-role="inline" data-gu-name="pullquote" class="dcr-nyoej5"&gt;&lt;svg viewbox="0 0 22 14" class="dcr-scql1j"&gt;&lt;path d="M5.255 0h4.75c-.572 4.53-1.077 8.972-1.297 13.941H0C.792 9.104 2.44 4.53 5.255 0Zm11.061 0H21c-.506 4.53-1.077 8.972-1.297 13.941h-8.686c.902-4.837 2.485-9.411 5.3-13.941Z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;blockquote class="dcr-zzndwp"&gt;AI companies are determined to push their products on to the public before we fully understand the psychological and cognitive costs&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Human intelligence is too broad and varied to be reduced to words such as “stupid”, but there are worrying signs that all this digital convenience is costing us dearly. Across the economically developed countries of the Organisation for Economic Co-operation and Development (OECD), Pisa scores, which measure 15-year-olds’ reading, maths and science, &lt;a href="https://archive.ph/0S5wK#selection-3313.60-3313.87" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;tended to peak around 2012&lt;/a&gt;. While over the 20th century IQ scores increased globally, perhaps due to improved access to education and better nutrition, in many developed countries they appear to have been declining.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Falling test and IQ scores are the subject of hot debate. What is harder to dispute is that, with every technological advance, we deepen our dependence on digital devices and find it harder to work or remember or think or, frankly, function without them. “It’s only software developers and drug dealers who call people users,” Kosmyna mutters at one point, frustrated at AI companies’ determination to push their products on to the public before we fully understand the psychological and cognitive costs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;In the ever-expanding, frictionless online world, you are first and foremost a user: passive, dependent. In the dawning era of AI-generated misinformation and deepfakes, how will we maintain the scepticism and intellectual independence we’ll need? By the time we agree that our minds are no longer our own, that we simply cannot think clearly without tech assistance, how much of us will be left to resist?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr class="dcr-z9ge1j"&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-15rw6c2"&gt;S&lt;/span&gt;tart telling people that you’re worried about what intelligent machines are doing to our brains and there’s a risk that, in the not-too-distant future, everyone will laugh at what a fuddy-duddy you were. Socrates worried that writing would weaken people’s memories and encourage only superficial understanding: not wisdom but “the conceit of wisdom” – an argument that is strikingly similar to many critiques of AI. What happened instead was that writing and the technological advances that followed – the printing press, mass media, the internet era – meant that ever more people had access to ever more information. More people could develop great ideas, and they could share those ideas more easily, and this made us cleverer and more innovative, as individuals and as communities.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;After all, writing didn’t only change how we access and retain information; it changed how we think. A person can achieve more complex tasks with a notebook and paper to hand than without: most people can’t work out 53,683 divided by 7 in their head but could have a stab at doing long division on paper. I couldn’t have dictated this piece, but writing helped me organise and clarify my thoughts. As humans, we’re very good at what experts call “cognitive offloading”, namely using our physical environment to reduce our mental load, and this in turn helps us achieve more complex cognitive tasks. Imagine how much harder it would be to function each day without a calendar or phone reminders, or without Google to remember everything for you. In the best case scenario, intelligent people working in partnership with intelligent machines will achieve new intellectual feats and solve tricky problems: we’re already seeing, for instance, how AI can help scientists discover &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41591-024-03434-4" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;new drugs faster&lt;/a&gt; and doctors detect &lt;a href="https://www.cancer.gov/research/infrastructure/artificial-intelligence" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;cancer earlier and more efficiently&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The complication is, if technology is truly making us cleverer – turning us into efficient, information-processing machines – why do we spend so much time feeling dumb?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Last year, “brain rot” was named Oxford University Press’s word of the year, a term that captures both the specific feeling of mindlessness that descends when we spend too much time scrolling through rubbish online and the corrosive, aggressively dumb content itself, the nonsense memes and AI garble. When we hold our phones we have, in theory, most of the world’s accumulated knowledge at our fingertips, so why do we spend so much time dragging our eyeballs over dreck?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;One issue is that our digital devices have not been designed to help us think more efficiently and clearly; almost everything we encounter online has been designed to capture and monetise our attention. Each time you reach for your phone with the intention of completing a simple, discrete, potentially self-improving task, such as checking the news, your primitive hunter-gatherer brain confronts a multibillion-pound tech industry devoted to throwing you off course and holding your attention, no matter what. To extend Christodoulou ’s metaphor, in the same way that one feature of an obesogenic society are food deserts – whole neighbourhoods in which you cannot buy a healthy meal – large parts of the internet are information deserts, in which the only available brain food is junk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;aside data-spacefinder-role="inline" data-gu-name="pullquote" class="dcr-nyoej5"&gt;&lt;svg viewbox="0 0 22 14" class="dcr-scql1j"&gt;&lt;path d="M5.255 0h4.75c-.572 4.53-1.077 8.972-1.297 13.941H0C.792 9.104 2.44 4.53 5.255 0Zm11.061 0H21c-.506 4.53-1.077 8.972-1.297 13.941h-8.686c.902-4.837 2.485-9.411 5.3-13.941Z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;blockquote class="dcr-zzndwp"&gt;Digital multitasking gives you a false sense of being on top of things without ever getting to the bottom of anything&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;In the late 90s the tech consultant Linda Stone, who was working as a professor at New York University, noticed that her students were using technology very differently from her colleagues at Microsoft, where she also worked. While her Microsoft colleagues were disciplined about working on two screens – one for emails, perhaps, and another for Word, or a spreadsheet – her students seemed to be trying to do 20 things at once. She coined the term “continuous partial attention” to describe the stressful, involuntarily state we often find ourselves in when we’re trying to toggle between several cognitively demanding activities, such as responding to emails while on a Zoom call. When I first heard the term I realised that I, like most people I know, live most of my life in a state of continuous partial attention, whether I’m guiltily checking my phone when I’m supposed to be playing with my kids, or incessantly sidetracked by texts and emails when I’m trying to write, or trying to relax while watching Netflix and simultaneously doing an online food shop, still wondering why I feel as chilled-out as an over-microwaved dinner. Digital multitasking makes us feel productive, but this is often illusory. “You have a false sense of being on top of things without ever getting to the bottom of anything,” Stone tells me. It also makes you feel permanently on edge: one study she conducted found that 80% of people experience “screen apnea” when checking their emails: they become so caught up in the endless notifications that they forget to breathe properly. “Your fight or flight system becomes up-regulated, because you’re constantly trying to stay on top of things,” she says, and this hypervigilance has cognitive costs: it makes us more forgetful, worse at making decisions and less attentive.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure data-spacefinder-role="inline" data-spacefinder-type="model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.NewsletterSignupBlockElement" class="dcr-173mewl"&gt;&lt;a data-ignore="global-link-styling" href="#EmailSignup-skip-link-23" class="dcr-jzxpee"&gt;skip past newsletter promotion&lt;/a&gt;&lt;aside aria-label="newsletter promotion" class="dcr-av5vqf"&gt;&lt;div class="dcr-10et71f"&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-1sbse14"&gt;Sign up to &lt;span&gt;Inside Saturday&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-1xjndtj"&gt;The only way to get a look behind the scenes of the Saturday magazine. Sign up to get the inside story from our top writers as well as all the must-read articles and columns, delivered to your inbox every weekend.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;gu-island name="SecureSignup" priority="feature" deferuntil="visible" props='{"newsletterId":"inside-saturday","successDescription":"The only way to get a look behind the scenes of the Saturday magazine. Sign up to get the inside story from our top writers as well as all the must-read articles and columns, delivered to your inbox every weekend."}'&gt;&lt;/gu-island&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-1eusqlu"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Privacy Notice: &lt;/strong&gt;Newsletters may contain information about charities, online ads, and content funded by outside parties. If you do not have an account, we will create a guest account for you on &lt;a data-ignore="global-link-styling" href="https://www.theguardian.com" rel="noreferrer" class="dcr-1rjy2q9"&gt;theguardian.com&lt;/a&gt; to send you this newsletter. You can complete full registration at any time. For more information about how we use your data see our &lt;a data-ignore="global-link-styling" href="https://www.theguardian.com/help/privacy-policy" rel="noreferrer" class="dcr-1rjy2q9"&gt;Privacy Policy&lt;/a&gt;. We use Google reCaptcha to protect our website and the Google &lt;a data-ignore="global-link-styling" href="https://policies.google.com/privacy" rel="noreferrer" class="dcr-1rjy2q9"&gt;Privacy Policy&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a data-ignore="global-link-styling" href="https://policies.google.com/terms" rel="noreferrer" class="dcr-1rjy2q9"&gt;Terms of Service&lt;/a&gt; apply.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;p id="EmailSignup-skip-link-23" tabindex="0" aria-label="after newsletter promotion" role="note" class="dcr-jzxpee"&gt;after newsletter promotion&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figure id="5997b8a7-9bff-443f-9fc0-3a2b91779d13" data-spacefinder-role="inline" data-spacefinder-type="model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.ImageBlockElement" class="dcr-173mewl"&gt;&lt;figcaption data-spacefinder-role="inline" class="dcr-fd61eq"&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-1inf02i"&gt;&lt;svg viewbox="0 0 18 13"&gt;&lt;path d="M18 3.5v8l-1.5 1.5h-15l-1.5-1.5v-8l1.5-1.5h3.5l2-2h4l2 2h3.5l1.5 1.5zm-9 7.5c1.9 0 3.5-1.6 3.5-3.5s-1.6-3.5-3.5-3.5-3.5 1.6-3.5 3.5 1.6 3.5 3.5 3.5z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Illustration: Justin Metz/The Guardian&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Continuous partial attention helps explain both brain rot as a mental state – because what is it if not cognitive overwhelm, the point at which you stop resisting the onslaught of digital distraction and allow your brain to rest in the internet’s warm, murky shallows? – and the existence of the online slop itself. After all, what matters to tech companies financially is not that you want to be reading what you’re reading, or that you love what you listen to or what you’re looking at, only that you are unwilling or unable to pull yourself away. This is why streaming services such as Netflix crank out bland, formulaic films that are euphemistically labelled “casual viewing” and are literally designed for viewers &lt;a href="https://www.nplusonemag.com/issue-49/essays/casual-viewing/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;who aren’t really watching&lt;/a&gt;, and Spotify playlists are filled with &lt;a href="https://harpers.org/archive/2025/01/the-ghosts-in-the-machine-liz-pelly-spotify-musicians/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;generic stock music&lt;/a&gt; by fake artists, to provide background music, “Chill Out” or “Party” vibes, for listeners who aren’t really listening. In short, the modern internet doesn’t necessarily make you an idiot, but it definitely primes you to act like one.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr class="dcr-z9ge1j"&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-15rw6c2"&gt;I&lt;/span&gt;t is into this climate that generative AI arrived, with an entirely novel offer. Until recently you could only outsource remembering and some data processing to technology; now you can outsource thinking itself. Given that we spend most of our lives feeling overstimulated and frazzled, it’s little wonder that so many have jumped at the chance to let a computer do more things we would have once done for ourselves– such as write work reports or emails, or plan a holiday. As we transition from the internet era to the AI era, what we’re consuming is not only ever more low-value, ultra-processed information, but more information that is essentially predigested, delivered in a way that is designed to bypass important human functions, such as assessing, filtering and summarising information, or actually considering a problem rather than finessing the first solution presented to us.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Michael Gerlich, head of the Centre for Strategic Corporate Foresight and Sustainability at SBS Swiss Business School, began studying the impact of generative AI on critical thinking because he noticed the quality of classroom discussions decline. Sometimes he’d set his students a group exercise, and rather than talk to one another they continued to sit in silence, consulting their laptops. He spoke to other lecturers, who had noticed something similar. Gerlich recently conducted a study, involving 666 people of various ages, and found those who used AI more frequently &lt;a href="https://download.ssrn.com/2025/1/4/5082524.pdf?response-content-disposition=inline&amp;amp;amp;X-Amz-Security-Token=IQoJb3JpZ2luX2VjEKT%2F%2F%2F%2F%2F%2F%2F%2F%2F%2FwEaCXVzLWVhc3QtMSJIMEYCIQCmRbALQalkGRB3jehFvi8nWZYpU%2BYsnAEPxO%2BoBB3wfQIhANrBGQfOPSK1dN8whuYILYNDsxhGw%2Bwlhc2H60tAdzgIKr0FCB0QBBoMMzA4NDc1MzAxMjU3IgzIZwV6noZaCGBCVVgqmgX8DsiB0tO6Adb6CtCDPG%2BnQuA6DxEy0Z2ot1NJ2g2bvGSRRq45nuWOo55d55Pz5bq%2F2M5wU2wtGpw5wlb6CD9YvJ5RgiQGq3YyIkesQhcbzGWlfVuSdjgcbsDcWtTaLR1%2FCalN8Qv2qhaW%2FrHHuHpjQyYMVXjtb2IPyLmswLY2CPhkWGTiqPlpkCubG2OmeQkyPABjnsk4wPNsu1YQF8bRjglekBXqg3n6osewqzYFUTnkMjtzN%2Ff4LnScCLPqmUZujjlUMxR3lwy8TfqsgVGYJ7hnrrOJ4TSmwp%2FlUXMADWyKGsTl6M1m%2Fjjk725o2M7FQF1QVC%2BWdr4cbvYt07ZydSFlMsGOAD8BoK98ngz7AZx92KjzmEqXkNewaMMlLeKCxUj63VkBBBBbCqPm3HnjU9IX1DQccbCyyT1oBWJXx6fE%2FZHR87Ch3W37DlLrvpoATKzuFIcj6uVsw1y4SS3C9sbdadKKuIQmJq5UpJI%2FL8n%2Fhl2wEPI8INq%2BIF0AMJzea5sajvfxqKEwTpcCI%2BB1eBLhq7%2FcCcTOFTgKG2xCHSgQw0yyYvUYKiOg4WLpSLzTP%2B%2B2QYaSAo3DQ69YfTW4E%2Fyfub5uv%2BimLRlJY3GtSJI4%2F%2B202Poiky3aW8nRQcLqoCWs7dtmnQeAr6vGsV2LEd2uwdRQYXve7A7%2B1WtkcCrskewpY30QvFeJzVH4OXJXtdxDPWUzblSI8g4FeWb8fgWqyEwLwh6miJ1jWclzK2rsA8a5jr5i4noPlcyqDEMFy49K709tHkYqUxT8SQt1ksox35sTMMqGs8ANPHU8WvnLZ2tsPGwR15V98q9XG6X7U6f9zki0jOUys0%2BGUQ4TPKCBlMC%2BeQ0n6VmMvvPHUQRj5dJJLfeo4M4w3dOMxgY6sAEBzWuQ5bMH%2FMBg3a1NXRNmFhsyMCvI%2FoOPTxuCMwut7ECx2YbOwEm1S4gm2wJnBcCP8Qd31iHo5fUdO4dC%2BbB8jPxyh%2Fb5fpLJgHhiWmgZurM4ql8KNWP2jH9NLdxv%2BZi9x8MfXGMnTTYL43ceUvMzKQY8J%2FvxFvIAi2kT0CLsJUl%2FkPk723vqh%2FWIZrVfOn0A%2FBLIta2wTijg3itrnZYER8X%2BBSrcMHw8cAtHblhuxA%3D%3D&amp;amp;amp;X-Amz-Algorithm=AWS4-HMAC-SHA256&amp;amp;amp;X-Amz-Date=20250911T204332Z&amp;amp;amp;X-Amz-SignedHeaders=host&amp;amp;amp;X-Amz-Expires=300&amp;amp;amp;X-Amz-Credential=ASIAUPUUPRWEWUPPMNLX%2F20250911%2Fus-east-1%2Fs3%2Faws4_request&amp;amp;amp;X-Amz-Signature=dda7f43bea1f7f00507c51a611aa025ba9386abe173968804683fc1892469502&amp;amp;amp;abstractId=5082524" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;scored lower on critical thinking&lt;/a&gt;. (As he notes, to date his work only provides evidence for a correlation between the two: it’s possible that people with lower critical thinking abilities are more likely to trust AI, for example.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;aside data-spacefinder-role="inline" data-gu-name="pullquote" class="dcr-nyoej5"&gt;&lt;svg viewbox="0 0 22 14" class="dcr-scql1j"&gt;&lt;path d="M5.255 0h4.75c-.572 4.53-1.077 8.972-1.297 13.941H0C.792 9.104 2.44 4.53 5.255 0Zm11.061 0H21c-.506 4.53-1.077 8.972-1.297 13.941h-8.686c.902-4.837 2.485-9.411 5.3-13.941Z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;blockquote class="dcr-zzndwp"&gt;Are schools equipped to produce creative thinkers – or is the education system going to churn out mindless, AI-essay writing drones?&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Like many researchers, Gerlich believes that, used in the right way, AI can make us cleverer and more creative – but the way most people use it produces bland, unimaginative, factually questionable work. One concern is the so-called “anchoring effect”. If you post a question to generative AI, the answer it gives you sets your brain on a certain mental path and makes you less likely to consider alternative approaches. “I always use the example: imagine a candle. Now, AI can help you improve the candle. It will be the brightest ever, burn the longest, be very cheap and amazing looking, but it will never develop to the lightbulb,” he says. To get from the candle to a lightbulb you need a human who is good at critical thinking, someone who might take a chaotic, unstructured, unpredictable approach to problem solving. When, as has happened in many workplaces, companies roll out tools such as the chatbot Copilot without offering decent AI training, they risk producing teams of passable candle-makers in a world that demands high-efficiency lightbulbs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;There is also the bigger issue that adults who use AI as a shortcut have at least benefited from going through the education system in the years before it was possible to get a computer to write your homework for you. One &lt;a href="https://www.hepi.ac.uk/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/HEPI-Kortext-Student-Generative-AI-Survey-2025.pdf" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;recent British survey&lt;/a&gt; found that &lt;a href="https://www.hepi.ac.uk/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/HEPI-Kortext-Student-Generative-AI-Survey-2025.pdf" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;92% of university students&lt;/a&gt; use AI, and about 20% have used AI to write all or part of an assignment for them. Under these circumstances, how much are they learning? Are schools and universities still equipped to produce creative, original thinkers who will build better, more intelligent societies – or is the education system going to churn out mindless, gullible, AI essay-writing drones?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr class="dcr-z9ge1j"&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-15rw6c2"&gt;S&lt;/span&gt;ome years ago, Matt Miles, a psychology teacher at a high school in Virginia in the US, was sent on a training programme on tech in schools. The teachers were shown a video in which a schoolgirl is caught checking her phone during lessons. In the video, she looks up and says, “You think I’m just on TikTok or playing games. I’m actually in a research room talking to a water researcher from Botswana for a project.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“It’s laughable. You show it to the kids and they all laugh, right?” Miles says. Alarmed at the disconnect between how policymakers view tech in education and what teachers were seeing in the classroom, in 2017 Miles and his colleague Joe Clement, who teaches economics and government at the same school, published &lt;a href="https://screenschooled.com/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;Screen Schooled&lt;/a&gt;, a book that argued that technology overuse is making kids dumber. In the years since, smartphones have been banned from their classrooms, but students still work from their laptops. “We had one kid tell us, and I think it was pretty insightful, ‘If you see me on my phone, there’s a 0% chance I’m doing something productive. If you see me on my laptop, there’s a 50% chance,’” Miles says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;aside data-spacefinder-role="inline" data-gu-name="pullquote" class="dcr-nyoej5"&gt;&lt;svg viewbox="0 0 22 14" class="dcr-scql1j"&gt;&lt;path d="M5.255 0h4.75c-.572 4.53-1.077 8.972-1.297 13.941H0C.792 9.104 2.44 4.53 5.255 0Zm11.061 0H21c-.506 4.53-1.077 8.972-1.297 13.941h-8.686c.902-4.837 2.485-9.411 5.3-13.941Z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;blockquote class="dcr-zzndwp"&gt;In essence what is happening with these technologies is we’re experimenting on children&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Until the pandemic, many teachers were “rightly sceptical” about the benefits of introducing more technology into the classroom, Faith Boninger, a researcher at the University of Colorado, observes, but when lockdowns forced schools to go online, a new normal was created, and ed tech platforms such as Google Workspace for Education, Kahoot! and Zearn became ubiquitous. With the spread of generative AI came new promises that it could revolutionise education and usher in an era of personalised student learning, while also reducing the workload for teachers. But almost all the research that has found benefits to introducing tech in classrooms is funded by the ed-tech industry, and most large-scale independent research has found that screen time gets in the way of achievement. A global OECD study found, for instance, that the more students use tech in schools, &lt;a href="https://www.bbc.com/news/business-34174796" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;the worse their results&lt;/a&gt;. “There is simply no independent evidence at scale for the effectiveness of these tools … in essence what is happening with these technologies is we’re experimenting on children,” says Wayne Holmes, a professor of critical studies of artificial intelligence and education at University College London. “Most sensible people would not go into a bar and meet somebody who says, ‘Hey, I’ve got this new drug. It’s really good for you’ – and just use it. Generally, we expect our medicines to be rigorously tested, we expect them to be prescribed to us by professionals. But suddenly when we’re talking about ed tech, which apparently is very beneficial for children’s developing brains, we don’t need to do that.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;What worries Miles and Clement is not only that their students are permanently distracted by their devices, but that they will not develop critical thinking skills and deep knowledge when quick answers are only a click away. Where once Clement would ask his class a question such as, “Where do you think the US ranks in terms of GDP per capita?” and guide his students as they puzzled over the solution, now someone will have Googled the answer before he’s even finished his question. They know students use ChatGPT constantly and get annoyed if they aren’t provided with a digital copy of their assignment, because then they must type rather than copy and paste the relevant questions into an AI assistant or the Google search bar. “Being able to Google something and providing the right answer isn’t knowledge,” Clement says. “And having knowledge is incredibly important so that when you hear something that’s questionable or maybe fake, you think, ‘Wait a minute, that contradicts all the knowledge I have that says otherwise, right?’ It’s no wonder there’s a bunch of idiots walking about who think that the Earth is flat. Like, if you read a flat Earth blog, you think, ‘Ah, that makes a lot of sense’ because you don’t have any understanding or knowledge.” The internet is already awash with conspiracy and misinformation, something that will only become worse as AI hallucinates and produces plausible fakes, and he worries that young people are poorly equipped to navigate it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;During the pandemic, Miles says, he found his young son weeping over his school-issued tablet. His son was doing an online maths program and he had been tasked with making six using the fewest number of one, three and five tokens. He kept suggesting using two threes, and the computer kept telling him he was wrong. Miles tried one and five, which the computer accepted. “That’s kind of the nightmare you get with a non-human AI, right?” Miles observes: students often approach topics in unanticipated and interesting ways, but machines struggle to cope with idiosyncrasy. Listening to his story, however, I was struck by a different kind of nightmare. Maybe the dawn of the new golden era of stupidity doesn’t begin when we submit to super-intelligent machines; it starts when we hand over power to dumb ones.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Guardian</author><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 13:21:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipwFBVV95cUxOaTlPNEh0NjJmNGVtcDUyWEJhbVZSazk1MGpMbXpFc25PTl9vZ1VBdk11a09yRnlyZXMxTEYyMmtWM1hhNEpseDRvcFNHbk5Za2lFdWh3emZyLVl4dm1rNTg5cjBJcElRMEZCaU12ZUJOQWdtcFdKWXlsakthNkJRa3E5cWpKbENXaTI0R2hpNUpTcXROTHZIb09UWlBtb1plUUtJaVVFYw</guid></item><item><title>音乐可以帮助缓解手术或疾病带来的疼痛。科学家正在倾听-美联社新闻</title><link>https://apnews.com/article/music-pain-research-healing-surgery-medicine-495a90c22ca196da0e95ffe515fb4cbd</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="LeaderBoardAd-Mobile "&gt;
                                    
                                        
                                            
                                        
                                    
                                &lt;/p&gt;
                            
                            
                                
                                
                                    &lt;div class="RichTextStoryBody RichTextBody"&gt;
                                        &lt;p&gt;Nurse Rod Salaysay works with all kinds of instruments in the hospital: a thermometer, a stethoscope and sometimes his guitar and ukulele.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the recovery unit of UC San Diego Health, Salaysay helps patients manage &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://apnews.com/article/nonopioid-painkiller-fda-vertex-pharmaceuticals-b1dd4276fce3d88ff32e3062e95f408f"&gt;pain after surgery.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Along with medications, he offers &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://apnews.com/article/895c5b00f554466894d1d50a851ef5ec"&gt;tunes on request&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; and sometimes sings. His repertoire ranges from folk songs in English and Spanish to Minuet in G Major and movie favorites like “Somewhere Over the Rainbow.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Patients often smile or nod along. Salaysay even sees changes in their vital signs like lower heart rate and blood pressure, and some may request fewer painkillers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“There’s often a cycle of worry, pain, anxiety in a hospital,” he said, “but you can help break that cycle with music.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Salaysay is a one-man band, but he’s not alone. Over the past two decades, live performances and recorded music have flowed into hospitals and doctors’ offices as research grows on how songs can help ease pain. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h2&gt;Scientists explore how music affects pain perception&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://apnews.com/article/c75e6a1185024a7c8892dacf56e6e308#"&gt;healing power&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; of song may sound intuitive given music’s deep roots in human culture. But the science of whether and how music dulls acute and chronic pain — technically called music-induced analgesia — is just catching up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;No one suggests that a catchy song can fully eliminate serious pain. But several recent studies, including in the journals &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://journals.lww.com/pain/abstract/2025/08000/individualizing_musical_tempo_to_spontaneous_rates.11.aspx" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Pain&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; and &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41598-024-72882-2" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Scientific Reports&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;, have suggested that listening to music can either reduce the perception of pain or enhance a person’s ability to tolerate it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What seems to matter most is that patients — or their families — choose the music selections themselves and listen intently, not just as background noise.&lt;/p&gt;
    
&lt;h2&gt;How music can affect pain levels&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Pain is a really complex experience,” said Adam Hanley, a psychologist at Florida State University. “It’s created by a physical sensation, and by our thoughts about that sensation and emotional reaction to it.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Two people with the same condition or injury may feel vastly different levels of acute or chronic pain. Or the same person might experience pain differently from one day to the next.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Acute pain is felt when pain receptors in a specific part of the body — like a hand touching a hot stove — send signals to the brain, which processes the short-term pain. Chronic pain usually involves long-term structural or other changes to the brain, which heighten overall sensitivity to pain signals. Researchers are still investigating how this occurs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Pain is interpreted and translated by the brain,” which may ratchet the signal up or down, said Dr. Gilbert Chandler, a specialist in chronic spinal pain at the Tallahassee Orthopedic Clinic. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Researchers know music can draw attention away from pain, lessening the sensation. But studies also suggest that listening to preferred music helps dull pain more than listening to podcasts. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Music is a distractor. It draws your focus away from the pain. But it’s doing more than that,” said Caroline Palmer, a psychologist at McGill University who studies music and pain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Scientists are still tracing the various neural pathways at work, said Palmer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“We know that almost all of the brain becomes active when we engage in music,” said Kate Richards Geller, a registered music therapist in Los Angeles. “That changes the perception and experience of pain — and the isolation and anxiety of pain.”&lt;/p&gt;
    
&lt;h2&gt;Music genres and active listening &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The idea of using recorded music to lessen pain associated with dental surgery began in the late 19th century before local anesthetics were available. Today researchers are studying what conditions make music most effective.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Researchers at Erasmus University Rotterdam in the Netherlands conducted a study on 548 participants to see how listening to five &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41598-024-72882-2" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;genres of music&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; — classical, rock, pop, urban and electronic — extended their ability to withstand acute pain, as measured by exposure to very cold temperatures.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All music helped, but there was no single winning genre. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The more people listened to a favorite genre, the more they could endure pain,” said co-author Dr. Emy van der Valk Bouman. “A lot of people thought that classical music would help them more. Actually, we are finding more evidence that what’s best is just the music you like.”&lt;/p&gt;
    
&lt;p&gt;The exact reasons are still unclear, but it may be because familiar songs activate more memories and emotions, she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The simple act of choosing is itself powerful, said Claire Howlin, director of the Music and Health Psychology Lab at Trinity College Dublin, who co-authored a study that suggested &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41598-024-72882-2" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;allowing patients to select songs&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; improved their pain tolerance. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“It’s one thing that people can have control over if they have a chronic condition — it gives them agency,” she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Active, focused listening also seems to matter.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hanley, the Florida State psychologist, co-authored a preliminary study suggesting &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40225443/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;daily attentive listening&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; might reduce chronic pain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Music has a way of lighting up different parts of the brain,” he said, “so you’re giving people this positive emotional bump that takes their mind away from the pain.” &lt;/p&gt;
    
&lt;p&gt;It’s a simple prescription with no side effects, some doctors now say.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cecily Gardner, a jazz singer in Culver City, California, said she used music to help get through a serious illness and has sung to friends battling pain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Music reduces stress, fosters community,” she said, “and just transports you to a better place.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;___&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="optimizelyHubpeekId" class="optimizelyHubpeekClass"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Associated Press Health and Science Department receives support from the Howard Hughes Medical Institute’s Department of Science Education and the Robert Wood Johnson Foundation. The AP is solely responsible for all content.&lt;/p&gt;
                                    &lt;/div&gt;
                                
                            

                            
                    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>AP News</author><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 13:04:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipwFBVV95cUxQQlRkci1teTBkaEJqRXZMTUVkVEh1aTBlY0dDR00zekxiUTJCNTV3cWFQbTNRSHhVMkRnX3pFZDlRTXdxMnVHMGZnWHdqQU5hZ193WFd1Yjd2WVlkdkNTN0xYSDJpcVFYX0RLcG1HeFl6aFZNT2t4RExPRHFCbWV2TkY2dzBPNnBWdm5wT2w1NElYNnZuSDhuSUl6Zk1NS0tkTEpCWkJTSQ</guid></item><item><title>一只渴求鲜血的侵入性虫子正在犹他州南部蔓延--《盐湖论坛报》</title><link>https://www.sltrib.com/news/2025/10/18/invasive-mosquitoes-found-southern/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body-container" itemprop="articleBody"&gt;&lt;p class="body-raw"&gt;&lt;b&gt;St. George • &lt;/b&gt;A potentially deadly invasive species is making a home in southern Utah’s most populous county, and they are out for blood.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-raw"&gt;Meet the Aedes aegypti mosquito, which infests urban and residential areas, feeds primarily on humans and is a known spreader of dengue, chikungunya, West Nile virus, yellow fever, Zika and other deadly diseases.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-raw"&gt;That said, exterminators are not exactly rolling out the welcome wagon for the mosquitoes plaguing many Washington County neighborhoods. And the chemical greeting they are extending to the bloodsuckers is more lethal than convivial.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-raw"&gt;David Heaton, spokesperson for the Southwest Utah Public Health Department, said the inhospitable welcome is necessary because mosquitoes are known to carry a legion of tropical diseases. Fortunately, he added, there are no known human cases of such ailments in Washington County this year, though one pool of Aedes aegypti tested positive for West Nile.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-raw"&gt;“We don’t have any of those diseases for these mosquitoes to spread, and hopefully none will be imported into [the area],” Heaton said. “But there is always that potential.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-raw"&gt;Aedes aegypti mosquitoes have cropped up in Santa Clara, St. George, Washington City, Hurricane and Springdale neighborhoods over the past few weeks after several storms dumped monsoonal moisture on the drought-prone area. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-raw"&gt;While the water has been welcomed, the mosquitoes are not. Neither are the large red welts that residents who have been bitten by the bugs sport on their wrists, ankles and other thin-skinned areas.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-raw"&gt;“I’ve heard some people with the bites have gone to the hospital to find out what is going on,” said Sean Amodt, manager of the Southwest Mosquito Abatement District. “They didn’t know what was causing it or how to deal with it.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Stealth flyers&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="body-raw"&gt;Frequently mislabeled as “no-see-ums,” the pests tend to fly low and evade human detection, according to Amodt. He said people often don’t know they have been bitten until the welts and bruises emerge. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-raw"&gt;In recent weeks, district abatement teams have responded to 40 requests from people pleading with them to exterminate the mosquitoes infesting their yards. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-raw"&gt;“The statement we constantly hear from them is, ‘Help, we are getting eaten alive,’” Amodt said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-raw"&gt;Killing the mosquitoes is easier than finding them. Often, abatement workers who respond to a complaint will have to comb an entire neighborhood to find the source of the infestation. To alert residents in an infested area about the problem, Amodt’s workers pass out public health pamphlets, directing them to remove clutter and standing water in their yards. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-raw"&gt;Aedes aegypti mosquitoes were first detected and summarily dispatched in Washington County in 2013, in the Harrisburg area near Leeds, according to the district manager. Seven years later, they resurfaced in a St. George yard, and they have been showing up in more neighborhoods and in greater numbers over the past few years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-raw"&gt;Amodt said the mosquitoes, which are identifiable by the lyre-like mark on their upper thorax and black and white bandings on their legs, are believed to have infiltrated the area from the larvae in the potting soils and mulch from infected areas that are sold at local hardware and other stores.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-raw"&gt;Often labeled urban mosquitoes, he explained, their larvae are typically found in birdbaths, plant pots, tires, under rocks in decorative ponds, even bottle caps — all places where water can accumulate. Adult females typically lay eggs on the side of containers, where they hatch once the water level rises. The life cycle for the mosquitoes ranges from two to four weeks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-raw"&gt;In that time, though, the adult females — the ones that do the biting — can wreak havoc. For starters, they bite during the day rather than just in the morning or evenings. And they are voracious.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-raw"&gt;“Adult females can bite someone up to twelve times for one blood meal, which is used to secure the protein needed to develop their eggs,” Amodt said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-raw"&gt;Abatement crews use spray or foggers to rid areas of adult mosquitoes. They also dump out water pooled in containers and treat water where larva is found. Despite their best efforts, abatement officials concede, Aedes aegypti mosquitoes’ range has expanded to Washington County–at least from May through November.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-raw"&gt;County residents who need relief from the pests can call 435-627-0076 or fill out a service request on the &lt;a href="https://www.swmosquito.org/" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;district’s website&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Salt Lake Tribune</author><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 12:02:34 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMif0FVX3lxTE90cThkWUx0NVJIdmlPUEJZUi1LRGlEMF9HbFM2LVQ5dzRYbGRqUkVrTFR5RE4tZHQyRFVUOHFuMzZXNnd5bHY5eHFaN0c3YS1BWFdwSkRsRWF5OThKWTNVeEhyLWNZOWNzOUtUWTJmZXlEeHpUb2dRMVRpZ3dDcm8</guid></item><item><title>医生分享“清晰明了”的痴呆症早期症状-都柏林直播</title><link>https://www.dublinlive.ie/news/health/doctor-shares-clear-telling-earliest-32703242</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article id="article-body" class="ArticleBody_article__AwrJE" data-testid="body"&gt;&lt;h1 class="HeadingOne_heading-one__mmNWJ  __className_77fa0c" publication="dublinlive"&gt;Doctor shares 'clear and telling' earliest sign of dementia&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;h2 class="LeadText_lead-text__wd_PA __className_20a898" data-testid="leadtext" publication="dublinlive"&gt;Dementia is a syndrome characterised by an ongoing decline in brain function, with numerous causes and types&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;div class="Byline_byline-container__K_Owl" data-testid="byline"&gt;&lt;span data-testid="byline-content" class="Byline_byline-content-wrapper__Imque"&gt;&lt;div class="Byline_author-badge-date-wrapper__Q7jj1"&gt;&lt;div class="Byline_author-and-badge-wrapper__2dsv1"&gt;&lt;p class="Authors_authors-container__wVWas" data-tmdatatrack="author" data-testid="byline-author"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong class="Strong_strong__e2x35 __className_20a898"&gt;Elle May Rice&lt;/strong&gt; Content Editor Under 35s Lifestyle&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="Byline_dates-container__Rqzf2"&gt;&lt;span class="" data-testid="byline-publishedDate"&gt;12:59, 18 Oct 2025&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;button class="LightboxBtn_lightbox-btn__eoxYS" aria-label="Open image viewer" aria-haspopup="dialog" aria-controls="image-lightbox"&gt;&lt;div class="ImageEmbed_image-embed__0T8WX ImageEmbed_image-lead__Ti3qQ" data-testid="leadimage" data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-articleid="32703240"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="ImageEmbed_fig-caption__qotOK"&gt;&lt;span class="ImageEmbed_camera-style__Qjeby"&gt;&lt;svg viewbox="0 0 16 16" fill="none" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"&gt;&lt;g clip-path="url(#clip0_209_94274)"&gt;&lt;path opacity="0.16" fill-rule="evenodd" clip-rule="evenodd" d="M14 4H2V10.6667C2 11.403 2.59695 12 3.33333 12H12.6667C13.403 12 14 11.403 14 10.6667V4ZM8 10C9.10457 10 10 9.10457 10 8C10 6.89543 9.10457 6 8 6C6.89543 6 6 6.89543 6 8C6 9.10457 6.89543 10 8 10Z" fill="var(--color-sem-icon-primary-default)"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="M2 3.33331H14V11.3333C14 12.0697 13.403 12.6666 12.6667 12.6666H3.33333C2.59695 12.6666 2 12.0697 2 11.3333V3.33331Z" stroke="var(--color-sem-icon-primary-default)" stroke-width="1.33333" stroke-linejoin="round"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;circle cx="8" cy="8" r="2" stroke="var(--color-sem-icon-primary-default)" stroke-width="1.33333" stroke-linecap="round" stroke-linejoin="round"&gt;&lt;/circle&gt;&lt;path d="M11.3332 1.33331L12.6665 1.33331" stroke="var(--color-sem-icon-primary-default)" stroke-width="1.33333" stroke-linecap="round" stroke-linejoin="round"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/g&gt;&lt;defs&gt;&lt;clippath id="clip0_209_94274"&gt;&lt;rect fill="white"&gt;&lt;/rect&gt;&lt;/clippath&gt;&lt;/defs&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="ImageEmbed_caption-title__FSINC"&gt;Dementia and Alzheimer's are both cognitive diseases&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="ImageEmbed_caption-credit__uNiU6"&gt;(Image: Westend61/Getty Images)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/button&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh " data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-type="paragraph" publication="dublinlive"&gt;A medical professional has shed light on the "earliest" symptom of dementia and Alzheimer's disease, describing it as a "clear and telling" sign of these cognitive conditions. &lt;a class="TextLink_text-link__dBSS0 TextLink_enabled__dJF3l" href="https://www.dublinlive.ie/all-about/dementia" target="_self" aria-label="" tabindex="0"&gt;Dementia&lt;/a&gt; is a syndrome characterised by a continuous decline in brain function, with various causes and types.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh " data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-type="paragraph" publication="dublinlive"&gt;People often confuse Alzheimer's disease and dementia. Alzheimer's disease is actually a type of dementia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh " data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-type="paragraph" publication="dublinlive"&gt;Dr Stephen Cabral, a Neuropathy expert and host of The Cabral Concept podcast, shared one specific sign that could indicate dementia. He also pointed out another symptom to be mindful of, reports &lt;a class="TextLink_text-link__dBSS0 TextLink_enabled__dJF3l" href="https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/health/doctor-shares-earliest-sign-dementia-36078697" target="_self" aria-label="" tabindex="0"&gt;the Mirror&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh " data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-type="paragraph" publication="dublinlive"&gt;The video was titled: "The earliest sign of Alzheimer's and Dementia is getting lost more easily... This is the most clear and telling sign that somebody later in life is developing one of these cognitive diseases."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="BoxStyles_box-container__Qk3WH BoxStyles_non-commercial__aiWwo undefined" data-testid="recommended-1" publication="dublinlive"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh " data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-type="paragraph" publication="dublinlive"&gt;In the short video, Dr Cabral explained: "The earliest sign of dementia and Alzheimer's that truly is an indicator, not the mis-recalling of memories or words or names, but it's actually the number one is getting lost more easily. If you're younger and stressed, you forget where you put your keys, you forget someone's name, you forget the next thing that you were supposed to do? Not uncommon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh " data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-type="paragraph" publication="dublinlive"&gt;"What would be uncommon even when you're younger is to say, 'I don't know where I am right now. I'm lost.' That's a different story than not being able to recall something."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="BoxStyles_box-container__Qk3WH BoxStyles_non-commercial__aiWwo undefined" data-testid="non-commercial-1" publication="dublinlive"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh " data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-type="paragraph" publication="dublinlive"&gt;The doctor also highlighted a secondary warning sign that could indicate dementia. He referred to it as '1B', implying it's just secondary to the first symptom. He further explained: "And a 1B that they gave, let's say that's the 1A, a 1B would say that they're no longer able to park straight.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh " data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-type="paragraph" publication="dublinlive"&gt;"So if you're with a parent or grandparent, with a loved one, and they're not able to. Maybe they couldn't parallel park before, but they're not able to pull into a spot and straight, that can be an early sign of dementia and Alzheimer's."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="HeadingThree_heading-three__PBHLs  __className_77fa0c" publication="dublinlive"&gt;Signs of dementia&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh " data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-type="paragraph" publication="dublinlive"&gt;Symptoms of dementia may include difficulties with:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class="UnorderedList_unordered-list__gzblI" data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-type="unordered-list" publication="dublinlive"&gt;&lt;li class="sc-700e1ff3-0 VljCu"&gt;memory loss&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="sc-700e1ff3-0 VljCu"&gt;thinking speed&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="sc-700e1ff3-0 VljCu"&gt;mental sharpness and quickness&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="sc-700e1ff3-0 VljCu"&gt;language, such as using words incorrectly, or trouble speaking&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="sc-700e1ff3-0 VljCu"&gt;understanding&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="sc-700e1ff3-0 VljCu"&gt;judgement&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="sc-700e1ff3-0 VljCu"&gt;mood&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="sc-700e1ff3-0 VljCu"&gt;movement&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="sc-700e1ff3-0 VljCu"&gt;difficulties doing daily activities&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh " data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-type="paragraph" publication="dublinlive"&gt;Those living with dementia can show less interest in their usual activities, and might struggle to control their behaviour or emotions. They may also find social interactions challenging and show reduced interest in maintaining relationships and socialising. Their personality might change, and they may demonstrate less empathy (understanding and compassion).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="HeadingThree_heading-three__PBHLs  __className_77fa0c" publication="dublinlive"&gt;Early signs of Alzheimer's&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh " data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-type="paragraph" publication="dublinlive"&gt;During the initial stages, the primary symptom of Alzheimer's disease is memory lapses. Someone in the early stages of Alzheimer's disease may:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class="UnorderedList_unordered-list__gzblI" data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-type="unordered-list" publication="dublinlive"&gt;&lt;li class="sc-700e1ff3-0 VljCu"&gt;forget about recent conversations or events&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="sc-700e1ff3-0 VljCu"&gt;misplace items&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="sc-700e1ff3-0 VljCu"&gt;forget the names of places and objects&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="sc-700e1ff3-0 VljCu"&gt;have trouble thinking of the right word&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="sc-700e1ff3-0 VljCu"&gt;ask questions repetitively&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="sc-700e1ff3-0 VljCu"&gt;show poor judgement or find it harder to make decisions&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="sc-700e1ff3-0 VljCu"&gt;become less flexible and more hesitant to try new things&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh " data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-type="paragraph" publication="dublinlive"&gt;There are often signs of mood changes, such as increasing anxiety or agitation, or periods of confusion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh " data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-type="paragraph" publication="dublinlive"&gt;&lt;strong class="Strong_strong__e2x35"&gt;Join our Dublin Live breaking news service on WhatsApp. Click&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a class="TextLink_text-link__dBSS0 TextLink_enabled__dJF3l" href="https://chat.whatsapp.com/DJTiyHweTeJHu5aLKRIiPc" target="_blank" aria-label="[object Object] Link opens in a new tab." tabindex="0"&gt;&lt;strong class="Strong_strong__e2x35"&gt;this link&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong class="Strong_strong__e2x35"&gt;to receive your daily dose of Dublin Live content. We also treat our community members to special offers, promotions, and adverts from us and our partners. If you don’t like our community, you can check out any time you like. If you’re curious, you can read our&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a class="TextLink_text-link__dBSS0 TextLink_enabled__dJF3l" href="https://www.reachplc.com/site-services/privacy-policy" target="_blank" aria-label="[object Object][object Object] Link opens in a new tab." tabindex="0"&gt;&lt;strong class="Strong_strong__e2x35"&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong class="Strong_strong__e2x35"&gt;Privacy Notice&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong class="Strong_strong__e2x35"&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh " data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-type="paragraph" publication="dublinlive"&gt;&lt;strong class="Strong_strong__e2x35"&gt;For all the latest news from Dublin and surrounding areas&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong class="Strong_strong__e2x35"&gt;&lt;a class="TextLink_text-link__dBSS0 TextLink_enabled__dJF3l" href="https://www.dublinlive.ie/" target="_blank" aria-label="visit our homepageLink opens in a new tab." tabindex="0"&gt;visit our homepage&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong class="Strong_strong__e2x35"&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Dublin Live</author><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 12:02:33 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiwFBVV95cUxOdUpRdkVUY3lvT2VfWlVLeEdUbHMwOUJ2eFVwd3lMaTMtZ3plVXplZTA5SXRxMjZHZzY4cjEzNFFBSzBSZXVTamZ0TDdDV0VyZ0JuLXhYR0taUjdRZDdCYXVaQ2dMemF6WDlNOWFVSE1qRTBzbmU4SEpJVDIzRDNJMDFOblFNUjN3SGZ30gGQAUFVX3lxTFBYWXV5RjNBZU56WU9aZUQyby1md3h3aElTYzdkV3haMUNnOWRNdlo2Qzc1Rkgwa1RHSUoweS0ta1lEN1VSYzVpWlhELU9NNERCTlU2Y3ozRmNUNzdGN0FpN05FRTNHTGRHSk5lUml4MTlRT0YwZk5QVUxJMmw3ckhnMUFSV29VUWtVUXMzdkh0Mg</guid></item><item><title>男性大脑比女性大脑收缩得更快，研究结果- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/male-brains-shrink-faster-than-female-brains-study-finds</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;New evidence has found that male brains really may shrink faster than female brains with age.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Among 4,726 participants with healthy cognition, brain scans have revealed "modest yet systematic sex differences" in how neurological tissue wastes away.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The human brain &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1001/archneur.60.7.989"&gt;naturally shrinks&lt;/a&gt; as we get older, and those who die with  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/go/IaO" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73015" data-postid="177626" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;Alzheimer's&lt;/a&gt; disease have brains that &lt;a href="https://www.nia.nih.gov/health/alzheimers-causes-and-risk-factors/what-happens-brain-alzheimers-disease"&gt;show drastic volume losses&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Women are diagnosed with Alzheimer's at &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1038/s41591-025-03564-3"&gt;twice the rate of men&lt;/a&gt;, but surprisingly little is known about how a person's sex impacts their brain volume as they age.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As it turns out, the female brain may actually lose &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Grey_matter"&gt;gray&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/White_matter"&gt;white matter&lt;/a&gt; at a slower rate than the male brain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Related: &lt;/b&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/men-and-women-may-respond-differently-to-latest-alzheimers-drugs"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Men And Women May Respond Differently to Latest Alzheimer's Drugs&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"If women's brains declined more, that could have helped explain their higher Alzheimer's prevalence," co-author Anne Ravndal, a neuroscientist at the University of Oslo in Norway, &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-025-03353-5"&gt;told &lt;em&gt;Nature&lt;/em&gt; journalist Rachel Fieldhous&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Ravndal and an international team of researchers pulled together more than 12,000 brain scans, collected over the years from participants aged 17 to 95. Each individual had at least two brain MRIs, with an average interval of about 3 years between them.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;After controlling for sex-based differences in brain size, the team found that men showed a decline in a greater number of brain regions, including many parts of the cortex, in older age.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Meanwhile, women showed a decline in fewer regions, and the thickness of their cortex was less altered with age.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The findings suggest that there are real sex differences in the biology of aging, but the results should be interpreted with caution, &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1073/pnas.2510486122"&gt;the authors note&lt;/a&gt;, as far more research is needed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_177643" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-177643" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/SexDifferencesAging-642x495.png" alt="Age Differences Between Sexes" class="size-medium wp-image-177643" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/SexDifferencesAging-642x495.png 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/SexDifferencesAging-875x675.png 875w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/SexDifferencesAging-768x593.png 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/SexDifferencesAging-1536x1185.png 1536w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/SexDifferencesAging-600x463.png 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/SexDifferencesAging.png 1542w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-177643" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Differences between male and female participants in the study. (Ravndal et al., &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1073/pnas.2510486122"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span&gt;PNAS&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, 2025)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Despite extensive investigation into the &lt;a href="https://academic.oup.com/biomedgerontology/article/77/11/2177/6529714"&gt;biology of the aging brain&lt;/a&gt;, there remains an &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/grave-consequences-scientists-warn-of-extreme-bias-in-brain-aging-research"&gt;&lt;span&gt;extreme sex bias&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; in the field. &lt;span&gt;In 2019, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41467-022-29903-3"&gt;only 5 percent&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; of published studies in neuroscience or psychiatry considered the influence of sex.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.neurobiolaging.2021.06.002"&gt;Inconsistent findings abound&lt;/a&gt;. Today, it remains unclear whether men and women differ in the extent or speed of brain decline.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some studies show steeper declines in gray and white matter &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.neurobiolaging.2019.05.020"&gt;among men&lt;/a&gt;, while others show steeper declines &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1371/journal.pone.0114478"&gt;among women&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The new research, led by researchers at the University of Oslo in Norway, sought to clear up the picture. Between the sexes, researchers found sex-based differences in total brain volume, subcortical brain volume, cortical thickness, and surface area, among dozens of other measurements.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What these losses mean for cognitive function requires further research. Scientists are only just starting to understand how brain shape is &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/a-signal-of-future-dementia-may-be-hidden-in-the-shape-of-your-brain"&gt;linked to disease&lt;/a&gt;, and some studies &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/a-new-alzheimers-drug-shrinks-the-brain-scientists-say-thats-the-point"&gt;suggest that shrinkage&lt;/a&gt; can sometimes be helpful.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The location of volume loss can certainly give important clues. &lt;span&gt;Surprisingly, Ravndal and colleagues found no difference in volume changes to the &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Hippocampus"&gt;hippocampus &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;– a neural hub for memory and learning closely involved in dementia.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Only in older age did women in the study begin to show a faster decline in the hippocampus, once their relative life expectancy was taken into account. But this may simply be a delay in aging: a product of &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/it-s-not-just-humans-females-outlive-males-in-other-mammals-too"&gt;women living longer&lt;/a&gt; than men and not necessarily a sign that explains their dementia risk. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When the authors compared men and women who were predicted to live the same amount, some of the brain decline between the sexes balanced out.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/spark-into-space-comp?utm_source=promo_launch"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Launch-642x272.jpg" alt="Mid Article Promo Launch" class="alignnone wp-image-177073 size-medium" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Launch-642x272.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Launch-768x326.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Launch-600x255.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Launch.jpg 844w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Teasing apart the impact of sex on the brain from other genetic and environmental forces is tricky business, made all the more challenging by a lack of longitudinal research.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A 2023 review argued that the &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/grave-consequences-scientists-warn-of-extreme-bias-in-brain-aging-research"&gt;continued scientific bias&lt;/a&gt; in brain aging studies has "grave consequences" for wellbeing and places a "disproportionate burden" on female health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Research on the aging female brain is long overdue.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The study was published in &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1073/pnas.2510486122"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span&gt;PNAS&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 12:01:51 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijgFBVV95cUxQcGZVMThQbDJ3MndZbC1OOGF1a3pjTjlNdjItc0pabjRoUzE3RFN6OHRMbkFjWGJQSFVnVmJSQ3hPUlNBYlVYTEFMQnpHMVdPT3J5LXJBOFJ0VFBRNl85UlExZllKRW9hZHR6enZKMVNGWkpnQkE2V1YzNm1ZcTNwUldORm9fVllYVFBOdXBR</guid></item><item><title>27岁的女性在几乎无视警告标志后被诊断出患有乳腺癌： “难以置信” - CBS新闻</title><link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/breast-cancer-young-diagnosis-awareness-mammogram-cleveland-clinic-nyu-langone/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;section class="content__body"&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Marissa Coreno was embracing a new life in 2021. She had just moved out of her parents' house and was spending more time in the gym. She liked her job at a hospital in Ohio. Everything seemed to be going great — until she found a lump in her armpit. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Coreno wasn't particularly concerned at first. She was 27 and had no family history of cancer. But her colleagues thought she shouldn't ignore it. An ultrasound found "questionable characteristics." That was followed by a &lt;span class="link"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/news/mammograms-breast-cancer-screening-questions-experts/" target="_blank" data-invalid-url-rewritten-http=""&gt;mammogram&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;, then a biopsy. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Three days later, Coreno was diagnosed with Stage II breast cancer that had spread to her lymph nodes. She said she felt like her world had been turned upside down. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It was devastating. It took a while to process. I knew it was positive, and I knew I had breast cancer but in my head, it was like 'No way,'" Coreno said. "You hear about these cases and you see them on TV but it was hard to believe that this was now my life." &lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="embed embed--type-image is-image embed--float-none embed--size-medium"&gt;
    
                                    
      &lt;span class="img embed__content"&gt;&lt;img src="https://assets1.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/10/15/e80eb04b-f0bb-470d-8914-830308f6c4d0/thumbnail/620x1083/1e10ef47ea5bd67855064539af41fbb5/img-3258-1.jpg#" alt="img-3258-1.jpg " srcset="https://assets1.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/10/15/e80eb04b-f0bb-470d-8914-830308f6c4d0/thumbnail/620x1083/1e10ef47ea5bd67855064539af41fbb5/img-3258-1.jpg 1x, https://assets3.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/10/15/e80eb04b-f0bb-470d-8914-830308f6c4d0/thumbnail/1240x2166/fc8e571500e321be0ca889608d7cb97b/img-3258-1.jpg 2x" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;

      
          &lt;figcaption class="embed__caption-container"&gt;
        
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__caption"&gt;Marissa Coreno.&lt;/span&gt;
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__credit"&gt;
            
                Marissa Coreno

                          &lt;/span&gt;
              &lt;/figcaption&gt;
      &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;An increase in young diagnoses &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Breast cancer is the leading cause of cancer death in U.S. women aged 20 to 49, and the incidence rate of &lt;span class="link"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/news/elissa-kalver-her2-positive-metastatic-breast-cancer-memorial-sloan-kettering-ucla/" target="_blank" data-invalid-url-rewritten-http=""&gt;breast cancer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; in women under 50 has risen faster than in women over 50, &lt;a href="https://www.bcrf.org/about-breast-cancer/breast-cancer-young-women/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"&gt;according to the Breast Cancer Research Foundation&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;

    
&lt;p id="mpu-plus-outstream-middle" data-ad="mpu-plus-outstream-middle" class="ad-mpu-plus-outstream-middle ad-wrapper " data-ad-unit='"mpu-plus-outstream-middle"'&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"I've been a physician for over 25 years. When I first started practicing, we saw women in their 40s and now we're seeing the late 20s and early 30s more commonly," said Dr. Mary Gemignani, the director of the Women's Early Onset Cancer Program and chief of the Division of Breast Surgery at NYU Langone, who was not involved in Coreno's care. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Still, breast cancer diagnoses in women as young as Coreno are rare. The &lt;a href="https://www.cancer.org/content/dam/cancer-org/research/cancer-facts-and-statistics/breast-cancer-facts-and-figures/2024/breast-cancer-facts-and-figures-2024.pdf" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"&gt;American Cancer Society&lt;/a&gt; estimates that only about 1 in 1,344 women will develop breast cancer in their 20s. Younger patients are unlikely to have &lt;span class="link"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/news/doctor-explains-why-mammograms-should-start-at-age-40/" target="_blank" data-invalid-url-rewritten-http=""&gt;regular screenings&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;, Gemignani said, since most women &lt;span class="link"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/news/breast-cancer-awareness-month-early-screening-diagnosis-northwestern-university/" target="_blank" data-invalid-url-rewritten-http=""&gt;do not receive mammograms&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; until they are 40. Younger women also tend to have "more aggressive" tumors or be diagnosed with rarer disease subtypes, Gemignani said. There is no &lt;span class="link"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/news/breast-cancer-increase-reasons/" target="_blank" data-invalid-url-rewritten-http=""&gt;proven reason&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; for the increase, she said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gemignani said younger women tend to have unique needs, including fertility concerns, which make it important for them and their doctors to develop a personalized &lt;span class="link"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/news/olivia-munn-breast-cancer-story-test-inside-edition-correspondent-alison-hall/" target="_blank" data-invalid-url-rewritten-http=""&gt;treatment plan&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;. Coreno said she found few research studies that looked at outcomes for her age group but spoke candidly with Dr. Baidehi Maiti, a medical oncologist at the Cleveland Clinic, about her best options. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Being so young and not having a lot of research or studies or proof out there, every option I had along the way, I chose the most," Coreno said. "I was very protective." &lt;/p&gt;

    
    
&lt;p id="mpu-flex-inc3" data-ad="mpu-flex-inc" class="ad-mpu-flex-inc ad-wrapper " data-ad-unit='["mpu-flex-inc",3]'&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Connection amid "exhausting" chemotherapy &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Coreno's treatment started with four months of "exhausting" chemotherapy to stop her cancer from spreading any further. Her mom moved in to help take care of her, while her dad drove her to every appointment. Coreno said she lost her hair and could barely leave the house. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Going from such an active life — I was in my prime, I was working out on the regular, I was so proud of what I had accomplished — to not even having enough energy to get off the couch was hard," Coreno said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="embed embed--type-image is-image embed--float-none embed--size-medium"&gt;
    
                                    
      &lt;span class="img embed__content"&gt;&lt;img src="https://assets3.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/10/15/6c02dcc8-578c-419d-a183-10ae09cd5fce/thumbnail/620x827/ef2da15e6d32eca1dcda715bc6ae4bd0/img-7118-original-1.jpg#" alt="img-7118-original-1.jpg " srcset="https://assets3.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/10/15/6c02dcc8-578c-419d-a183-10ae09cd5fce/thumbnail/620x827/ef2da15e6d32eca1dcda715bc6ae4bd0/img-7118-original-1.jpg 1x, https://assets2.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/10/15/6c02dcc8-578c-419d-a183-10ae09cd5fce/thumbnail/1240x1654/31fe0a9641c11cfb7ff0c9fea8e1bf18/img-7118-original-1.jpg 2x" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;

      
          &lt;figcaption class="embed__caption-container"&gt;
        
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__caption"&gt;Marissa Coreno in the hospital.&lt;/span&gt;
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__credit"&gt;
            
                Marissa Coreno

                          &lt;/span&gt;
              &lt;/figcaption&gt;
      &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There was one bright spot: One night, Coreno decided to "eat (her) feelings" and ordered Crumbl cookies. She posted a picture of the delivery on Instagram. She received a message about the sweet treat from Anthony, a former classmate. The two struck up a conversation and "just never stopped talking." &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It was so nice to talk to somebody, have somebody listen to me, have a new friend that I could confide in," Coreno said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Eventually, the two went on a date. Coreno dreaded leaving the house and was self-conscious about wearing a wig but enjoyed herself. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"He didn't even mention the wig. We just had a great time," Coreno said. "It just felt so natural." &lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="embed embed--type-image is-image embed--float-none embed--size-medium"&gt;
    
                                    
      &lt;span class="img embed__content"&gt;&lt;img src="https://assets2.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/10/15/81029970-bc2d-47dd-979d-8ff56533ca82/thumbnail/620x1091/17885e8123520e4ed4a66eee032b2fcf/img-7993-original-1.jpg#" alt="img-7993-original-1.jpg " srcset="https://assets2.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/10/15/81029970-bc2d-47dd-979d-8ff56533ca82/thumbnail/620x1091/17885e8123520e4ed4a66eee032b2fcf/img-7993-original-1.jpg 1x, https://assets1.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/10/15/81029970-bc2d-47dd-979d-8ff56533ca82/thumbnail/1240x2182/d20a17e220b7e223a015b54190b6d0d7/img-7993-original-1.jpg 2x" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;

      
          &lt;figcaption class="embed__caption-container"&gt;
        
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__caption"&gt;Marissa Coreno in the hospital.&lt;/span&gt;
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__credit"&gt;
            
                Marissa Coreno

                          &lt;/span&gt;
              &lt;/figcaption&gt;
      &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After chemotherapy, Coreno underwent a &lt;span class="link"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/news/olivia-munn-breast-cancer-diagnosed/" target="_blank" data-invalid-url-rewritten-http=""&gt;double mastectomy&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;, followed by a reconstruction surgery and 25 days of radiation therapy, Maiti said. Coreno started hormone therapy in March 2022 and will continue it until 2032. She also has regular scans. The treatment stops her body from creating estrogen to limit the chance of the cancer returning. Coreno is currently cancer-free, Maiti said. &lt;/p&gt;

    
    
&lt;p id="mpu-flex-inc4" data-ad="mpu-flex-inc" class="ad-mpu-flex-inc ad-wrapper " data-ad-unit='["mpu-flex-inc",4]'&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"She has not let cancer define her life," Maiti said. "She's thriving as a breast cancer survivor and living her life to the fullest." &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;"Life is beautiful" &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The hormone therapy sent Coreno into menopause at 28. Working out is harder now, she said, and she grapples with hot flashes and has trouble sleeping. It has taken years for her to get used to the new normal. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I thought this would be the easy part," Coreno, now 31, said. "After treatment was over is when what I went through hit me the most." &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Amid the difficult adjustment, her relationship with Anthony turned more serious. They were married in August 2024 and spent their honeymoon in Italy. Over the summer, they celebrated their anniversary in Cancún, Mexico. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="embed embed--type-image is-image embed--float-none embed--size-medium"&gt;
    
                                    
      &lt;span class="img embed__content"&gt;&lt;img src="https://assets1.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/10/15/9f2509a7-36d8-43fa-8400-40bc443f912c/thumbnail/620x930/1f9d7fe7bb145ef1422456b8630af7bb/coreno1517-original-1.jpg#" alt="coreno1517-original-1.jpg " srcset="https://assets1.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/10/15/9f2509a7-36d8-43fa-8400-40bc443f912c/thumbnail/620x930/1f9d7fe7bb145ef1422456b8630af7bb/coreno1517-original-1.jpg 1x, https://assets2.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/10/15/9f2509a7-36d8-43fa-8400-40bc443f912c/thumbnail/1240x1860/0b4c7ac0649ac996d953bda3a74cbb91/coreno1517-original-1.jpg 2x" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;

      
          &lt;figcaption class="embed__caption-container"&gt;
        
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__caption"&gt;Marissa and Anthony Coreno on their wedding day. &lt;/span&gt;
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__credit"&gt;
            
                Arlee Reust/Azkalynn Photography

                          &lt;/span&gt;
              &lt;/figcaption&gt;
      &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Coreno also hopes that sharing her story encourages others to investigate any warning signs they experience. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I just want everyone to realize that it seems like it will never be you, it seems like it's always going to be someone else, it seems like it's going to be a person on the TV, but it can happen to you," Coreno said. "If you feel uncertain about anything, you need to speak up and get checked out. If, for some reason, you don't get the best news, there is light at the end of the tunnel. It might not seem like it. It might seem like it's a very long tunnel. But life is beautiful afterwards." &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/section&gt;

  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>CBS News</author><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMirAFBVV95cUxNMEtPM1lxU2Y4bHE0VmtLc2RtMXlkZ3JNVjlKVXJiRlRscjB6eTNxNW9JZm5fdFBwZUJGZmFlaE16aVFpUDI5MjdJU2o4UVhLbERhVmp6ampzNkNjbkJ3RVFBcU5vbE9sRE5WVktKQWtBUTJHRmdyQ2VRVXZKUXIyVDdsdkdRWk9EcFp3R1NLa3I1MGJtTHNQQ00tdktLWllDRzBtWUFjUkxNU1Nn0gGyAUFVX3lxTFBhaVlLMDFpLVQtbGJpaHM2bHVocmFnQkhxcHBlWXBYUGVSdjlfSG9Sbi03UE1FNDNGRlpnSV95R1hpaU5CbjJjN21oVXhmSzdxeHRDeW16ck5MREhTZ2J2UXRCUTM4S2xsNzd4clNGWFVFTnNnV2FqWFhIdWc1emRoZDZCRDc2d2VhWXJSdDhfb21kZTA1ZE1SQU1mMGIwZWZTYkFRQzFsS19CVGg0dnBPRGc</guid></item><item><title>只有前列腺癌专家才能回答的13个问题- The Telegraph</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/health-fitness/conditions/cancer/questions-prostate-cancer-specialist/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="component article-body-text    " data-test="article-body-text"&gt;
  
  

	

	
	

	
	



  
  
    &lt;p&gt;Testosterone is to prostate cancer what fuel is to fire, so sometimes we administer these hormones. This can cause mood changes, fatigue, breast enlargement, breast tenderness, anger issues, brain fog, and potential long-term bone loss, similar to women in menopause. There’s also an associated risk of cardiac issues in the long term with hormone treatment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="u-heading-size-medium u-heading-style-normal"&gt;9. What can be done to alleviate the side effects?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;We have very large teams that help with these and there is a strong multidisciplinary approach. If someone has erectile issues, we can offer tablets, injections or vacuum pumps, or we can insert an inflatable cylinder into the penis – it’s rare but it’s done.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If there is &lt;a class="ck-custom-link" href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/health-fitness/conditions/ageing/causes-of-incontinence-how-manage-symptoms-support/"&gt;incontinence&lt;/a&gt;, most of the time normal function returns. We work on pelvic muscle training, and have pads, penile clamps, emotional support and counselling. We can implant an artificial sphincter, but robot surgery and aftercare is sufficiently advanced, meaning enough of the anatomy and nerve structure is preserved and very few people need the sphincter. Most of the time post-surgery, the first week is stormy, but within about three months, 70 per cent will regain control, and within 12 months most people are dry. Only 5 per cent have lasting issues.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Faecal incontinence is more associated with radiotherapy and may require surgery – but this affects only 0.1 per cent. It’s extremely rare and it all improves over time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;With hormone treatments, we can give drugs to prevent breast enlargement. If they are experiencing hot flushes, we can offer acupuncture. Exercise is very helpful in dealing with weight gain or diabetes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="u-heading-size-medium u-heading-style-normal"&gt;10. Can people decide against treatment?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Suppose a 93-year-old man is diagnosed with prostate cancer – we put him on a watchful waiting pathway, where we do some tests and keep an eye on them. The PSA is a good marker once there is a diagnosis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We use doubling time. If someone has a PSA test in January and they have a PSA of four, and by March it’s eight, that is definitely something we need to investigate. We know overdiagnosis and overtreatment can be a problem and we do a lot of work to prevent that happening. If a patient doesn’t want any treatment, we will watch them and test them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="u-heading-size-medium u-heading-style-normal"&gt;11. How do I know whether the treatment is working?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;We monitor patients based on PSA levels, scans, and symptoms. We bring patients back to clinic, involve their GPs, and engage community nurses. Success rates are very high: 90-95 per cent for locally confined prostate cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This depends on initial pathology, but if the cancer is confined to the prostate, we’re talking about a significant chance of complete cure. We’re seeing major improvements in survival data with modern treatments.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="u-heading-size-medium u-heading-style-normal"&gt;12. What is the effect on my fertility?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Treatment will render you infertile. We routinely bank patients’ sperm – if they haven’t &lt;a class="ck-custom-link" href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/health-fitness/parenting/fertility/"&gt;completed their family&lt;/a&gt;, we organise that the next day [after diagnosis], usually.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="u-heading-size-medium u-heading-style-normal"&gt;13. What are the chances of cancer coming back?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;It all depends on the treatment. Success rates are very high.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;With surveillance alone, about 20-30 per cent of patients will need treatment in five years. With focal therapy, the recurrence rate is 20-40 per cent at five years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;With radiotherapy or surgery, it depends on the grade of cancer:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Low-risk: Surgery – 5 per cent recurrence; radiotherapy – 5-20 per cent.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Medium-risk: Surgery – 20 per cent; radiotherapy – 20-40 per cent.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;High-risk: Surgery – 50 per cent; radiotherapy – 50-70 per cent.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
  
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Telegraph</author><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMinwFBVV95cUxPak56Sm41VFdkT1p1V3gyRkw4UlBqbFhwX3RaeWt1TzBJUW5DaEdIUFVGcW5iWjFCX3NtNEY3Z3pmYy1jZUFPOEFhNEQzZUJEU1V4aDEwZVFQaU5KN3J6eGpaNkgtUlVic3ZHZmFLdE5NWktXXzRzM0MtaVdUU204SjBLODlDSFI5UU1fM2ozd1Nlb0ExazNLY2ZCSEdFNjg</guid></item><item><title>27岁的女性在几乎无视警告标志后被诊断出患有乳腺癌： “难以置信” - CBS新闻</title><link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/breast-cancer-young-diagnosis-awareness-mammogram-cleveland-clinic-nyu-langone/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;section class="content__body"&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Marissa Coreno was embracing a new life in 2021. She had just moved out of her parents' house and was spending more time in the gym. She liked her job at a hospital in Ohio. Everything seemed to be going great — until she found a lump in her armpit. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Coreno wasn't particularly concerned at first. She was 27 and had no family history of cancer. But her colleagues thought she shouldn't ignore it. An ultrasound found "questionable characteristics." That was followed by a &lt;span class="link"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/news/mammograms-breast-cancer-screening-questions-experts/" target="_blank" data-invalid-url-rewritten-http=""&gt;mammogram&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;, then a biopsy. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Three days later, Coreno was diagnosed with Stage II breast cancer that had spread to her lymph nodes. She said she felt like her world had been turned upside down. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It was devastating. It took a while to process. I knew it was positive, and I knew I had breast cancer but in my head, it was like 'No way,'" Coreno said. "You hear about these cases and you see them on TV but it was hard to believe that this was now my life." &lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="embed embed--type-image is-image embed--float-none embed--size-medium"&gt;
    
                                    
      &lt;span class="img embed__content"&gt;&lt;img src="https://assets1.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/10/15/e80eb04b-f0bb-470d-8914-830308f6c4d0/thumbnail/620x1083/1e10ef47ea5bd67855064539af41fbb5/img-3258-1.jpg#" alt="img-3258-1.jpg " srcset="https://assets1.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/10/15/e80eb04b-f0bb-470d-8914-830308f6c4d0/thumbnail/620x1083/1e10ef47ea5bd67855064539af41fbb5/img-3258-1.jpg 1x, https://assets3.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/10/15/e80eb04b-f0bb-470d-8914-830308f6c4d0/thumbnail/1240x2166/fc8e571500e321be0ca889608d7cb97b/img-3258-1.jpg 2x" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;

      
          &lt;figcaption class="embed__caption-container"&gt;
        
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__caption"&gt;Marissa Coreno.&lt;/span&gt;
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__credit"&gt;
            
                Marissa Coreno

                          &lt;/span&gt;
              &lt;/figcaption&gt;
      &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;An increase in young diagnoses &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Breast cancer is the leading cause of cancer death in U.S. women aged 20 to 49, and the incidence rate of &lt;span class="link"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/news/elissa-kalver-her2-positive-metastatic-breast-cancer-memorial-sloan-kettering-ucla/" target="_blank" data-invalid-url-rewritten-http=""&gt;breast cancer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; in women under 50 has risen faster than in women over 50, &lt;a href="https://www.bcrf.org/about-breast-cancer/breast-cancer-young-women/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"&gt;according to the Breast Cancer Research Foundation&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;

    
&lt;p id="mpu-plus-outstream-middle" data-ad="mpu-plus-outstream-middle" class="ad-mpu-plus-outstream-middle ad-wrapper " data-ad-unit='"mpu-plus-outstream-middle"'&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"I've been a physician for over 25 years. When I first started practicing, we saw women in their 40s and now we're seeing the late 20s and early 30s more commonly," said Dr. Mary Gemignani, the director of the Women's Early Onset Cancer Program and chief of the Division of Breast Surgery at NYU Langone, who was not involved in Coreno's care. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Still, breast cancer diagnoses in women as young as Coreno are rare. The &lt;a href="https://www.cancer.org/content/dam/cancer-org/research/cancer-facts-and-statistics/breast-cancer-facts-and-figures/2024/breast-cancer-facts-and-figures-2024.pdf" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"&gt;American Cancer Society&lt;/a&gt; estimates that only about 1 in 1,344 women will develop breast cancer in their 20s. Younger patients are unlikely to have &lt;span class="link"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/news/doctor-explains-why-mammograms-should-start-at-age-40/" target="_blank" data-invalid-url-rewritten-http=""&gt;regular screenings&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;, Gemignani said, since most women &lt;span class="link"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/news/breast-cancer-awareness-month-early-screening-diagnosis-northwestern-university/" target="_blank" data-invalid-url-rewritten-http=""&gt;do not receive mammograms&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; until they are 40. Younger women also tend to have "more aggressive" tumors or be diagnosed with rarer disease subtypes, Gemignani said. There is no &lt;span class="link"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/news/breast-cancer-increase-reasons/" target="_blank" data-invalid-url-rewritten-http=""&gt;proven reason&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; for the increase, she said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gemignani said younger women tend to have unique needs, including fertility concerns, which make it important for them and their doctors to develop a personalized &lt;span class="link"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/news/olivia-munn-breast-cancer-story-test-inside-edition-correspondent-alison-hall/" target="_blank" data-invalid-url-rewritten-http=""&gt;treatment plan&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;. Coreno said she found few research studies that looked at outcomes for her age group but spoke candidly with Dr. Baidehi Maiti, a medical oncologist at the Cleveland Clinic, about her best options. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Being so young and not having a lot of research or studies or proof out there, every option I had along the way, I chose the most," Coreno said. "I was very protective." &lt;/p&gt;

    
    
&lt;p id="mpu-flex-inc3" data-ad="mpu-flex-inc" class="ad-mpu-flex-inc ad-wrapper " data-ad-unit='["mpu-flex-inc",3]'&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Connection amid "exhausting" chemotherapy &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Coreno's treatment started with four months of "exhausting" chemotherapy to stop her cancer from spreading any further. Her mom moved in to help take care of her, while her dad drove her to every appointment. Coreno said she lost her hair and could barely leave the house. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Going from such an active life — I was in my prime, I was working out on the regular, I was so proud of what I had accomplished — to not even having enough energy to get off the couch was hard," Coreno said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="embed embed--type-image is-image embed--float-none embed--size-medium"&gt;
    
                                    
      &lt;span class="img embed__content"&gt;&lt;img src="https://assets3.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/10/15/6c02dcc8-578c-419d-a183-10ae09cd5fce/thumbnail/620x827/ef2da15e6d32eca1dcda715bc6ae4bd0/img-7118-original-1.jpg#" alt="img-7118-original-1.jpg " srcset="https://assets3.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/10/15/6c02dcc8-578c-419d-a183-10ae09cd5fce/thumbnail/620x827/ef2da15e6d32eca1dcda715bc6ae4bd0/img-7118-original-1.jpg 1x, https://assets2.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/10/15/6c02dcc8-578c-419d-a183-10ae09cd5fce/thumbnail/1240x1654/31fe0a9641c11cfb7ff0c9fea8e1bf18/img-7118-original-1.jpg 2x" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;

      
          &lt;figcaption class="embed__caption-container"&gt;
        
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__caption"&gt;Marissa Coreno in the hospital.&lt;/span&gt;
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__credit"&gt;
            
                Marissa Coreno

                          &lt;/span&gt;
              &lt;/figcaption&gt;
      &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There was one bright spot: One night, Coreno decided to "eat (her) feelings" and ordered Crumbl cookies. She posted a picture of the delivery on Instagram. She received a message about the sweet treat from Anthony, a former classmate. The two struck up a conversation and "just never stopped talking." &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It was so nice to talk to somebody, have somebody listen to me, have a new friend that I could confide in," Coreno said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Eventually, the two went on a date. Coreno dreaded leaving the house and was self-conscious about wearing a wig but enjoyed herself. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"He didn't even mention the wig. We just had a great time," Coreno said. "It just felt so natural." &lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="embed embed--type-image is-image embed--float-none embed--size-medium"&gt;
    
                                    
      &lt;span class="img embed__content"&gt;&lt;img src="https://assets2.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/10/15/81029970-bc2d-47dd-979d-8ff56533ca82/thumbnail/620x1091/17885e8123520e4ed4a66eee032b2fcf/img-7993-original-1.jpg#" alt="img-7993-original-1.jpg " srcset="https://assets2.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/10/15/81029970-bc2d-47dd-979d-8ff56533ca82/thumbnail/620x1091/17885e8123520e4ed4a66eee032b2fcf/img-7993-original-1.jpg 1x, https://assets1.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/10/15/81029970-bc2d-47dd-979d-8ff56533ca82/thumbnail/1240x2182/d20a17e220b7e223a015b54190b6d0d7/img-7993-original-1.jpg 2x" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;

      
          &lt;figcaption class="embed__caption-container"&gt;
        
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__caption"&gt;Marissa Coreno in the hospital.&lt;/span&gt;
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__credit"&gt;
            
                Marissa Coreno

                          &lt;/span&gt;
              &lt;/figcaption&gt;
      &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After chemotherapy, Coreno underwent a &lt;span class="link"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/news/olivia-munn-breast-cancer-diagnosed/" target="_blank" data-invalid-url-rewritten-http=""&gt;double mastectomy&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;, followed by a reconstruction surgery and 25 days of radiation therapy, Maiti said. Coreno started hormone therapy in March 2022 and will continue it until 2032. She also has regular scans. The treatment stops her body from creating estrogen to limit the chance of the cancer returning. Coreno is currently cancer-free, Maiti said. &lt;/p&gt;

    
    
&lt;p id="mpu-flex-inc4" data-ad="mpu-flex-inc" class="ad-mpu-flex-inc ad-wrapper " data-ad-unit='["mpu-flex-inc",4]'&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"She has not let cancer define her life," Maiti said. "She's thriving as a breast cancer survivor and living her life to the fullest." &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;"Life is beautiful" &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The hormone therapy sent Coreno into menopause at 28. Working out is harder now, she said, and she grapples with hot flashes and has trouble sleeping. It has taken years for her to get used to the new normal. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I thought this would be the easy part," Coreno, now 31, said. "After treatment was over is when what I went through hit me the most." &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Amid the difficult adjustment, her relationship with Anthony turned more serious. They were married in August 2024 and spent their honeymoon in Italy. Over the summer, they celebrated their anniversary in Cancún, Mexico. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="embed embed--type-image is-image embed--float-none embed--size-medium"&gt;
    
                                    
      &lt;span class="img embed__content"&gt;&lt;img src="https://assets1.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/10/15/9f2509a7-36d8-43fa-8400-40bc443f912c/thumbnail/620x930/1f9d7fe7bb145ef1422456b8630af7bb/coreno1517-original-1.jpg#" alt="coreno1517-original-1.jpg " srcset="https://assets1.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/10/15/9f2509a7-36d8-43fa-8400-40bc443f912c/thumbnail/620x930/1f9d7fe7bb145ef1422456b8630af7bb/coreno1517-original-1.jpg 1x, https://assets2.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/10/15/9f2509a7-36d8-43fa-8400-40bc443f912c/thumbnail/1240x1860/0b4c7ac0649ac996d953bda3a74cbb91/coreno1517-original-1.jpg 2x" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;

      
          &lt;figcaption class="embed__caption-container"&gt;
        
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__caption"&gt;Marissa and Anthony Coreno on their wedding day. &lt;/span&gt;
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__credit"&gt;
            
                Arlee Reust/Azkalynn Photography

                          &lt;/span&gt;
              &lt;/figcaption&gt;
      &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Coreno also hopes that sharing her story encourages others to investigate any warning signs they experience. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I just want everyone to realize that it seems like it will never be you, it seems like it's always going to be someone else, it seems like it's going to be a person on the TV, but it can happen to you," Coreno said. "If you feel uncertain about anything, you need to speak up and get checked out. If, for some reason, you don't get the best news, there is light at the end of the tunnel. It might not seem like it. It might seem like it's a very long tunnel. But life is beautiful afterwards." &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/section&gt;

  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>CBS News</author><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMirAFBVV95cUxNMEtPM1lxU2Y4bHE0VmtLc2RtMXlkZ3JNVjlKVXJiRlRscjB6eTNxNW9JZm5fdFBwZUJGZmFlaE16aVFpUDI5MjdJU2o4UVhLbERhVmp6ampzNkNjbkJ3RVFBcU5vbE9sRE5WVktKQWtBUTJHRmdyQ2VRVXZKUXIyVDdsdkdRWk9EcFp3R1NLa3I1MGJtTHNQQ00tdktLWllDRzBtWUFjUkxNU1Nn</guid></item></channel></rss>