<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>GNews Health</title><link>https://news.google.com/</link><description></description><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>Rare virus that killed Hackman’s wife linked to 3 deaths in Calif. town - The Washington Post</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMilAFBVV95cUxOOFQ2LTNkQVlfOHlpRUFIWF9NankxMldnN2xNMGo4LThmVkd1LWNGY3NRQ1M0cHpJTFlzbzZDOUw3NDlSb3VzLTNwSUxrUmsyRGJiRkZTQjAzYWREeXMwVzlUOG83V2l3U1hoanhMaVNXLTZBMkNyUkRBYVI1WDdqTWpDNkFEY2txZDRuRmZIQnd0Ukxa?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="meteredContent grid-center"&gt;&lt;div class="teaser-content"&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="E7ZNMQFMGNBXDNHGMQ6DNUG3JM" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Three people in a rural California town have died in recent weeks after contracting hantavirus, local health officials said, the same rare infection spread by rodents &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/health/2025/03/08/hantavirus-gene-hackman-wife-death-arakawa/" target="_blank"&gt;that killed Betsy Arakawa&lt;/a&gt;, the pianist and wife of actor &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/obituaries/2025/02/27/gene-hackman-actor-dead-obituary/" target="_blank"&gt;Gene Hackman&lt;/a&gt;, in February.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-subscribe-cta" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="WQPHTAWXHRDKBDEIWJ7SDZRGPA" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;The three victims were all residents of Mammoth Lakes, a popular ski town in the Sierra Nevada mountain range, Mono County public health officials &lt;a href="https://monocounty.ca.gov/cao/page/third-hantavirus-related-death-confirmed-mono-county" target="_blank"&gt;said in a statement last week&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="SJUPDRMTJVB7BKIM64QNDTRNBA" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;The statement said it was “strikingly unusual” to have recorded three cases of the virus this early in the year, as the infection is typically detected later in the spring or summer. All three of the deceased began experiencing illnesses in February.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="CKEDSAHMPNBNRFKP3EUSIZLNWE" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;“We believe that deer mouse numbers are high this year in Mammoth (and probably elsewhere in the Eastern Sierra). An increase in indoor mice elevates the risk of Hantavirus exposure,” said Tom Boo, Mono County’s public health officer, who described the deaths as tragic and alarming.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="UGW4KC2CTVG4BCZ3XSEITDHDCY" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;While no further cases have been detected locally in the past month, Boo said he remained concerned by the uptick.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-topic-follow-interstitial" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="SD6FY4HZQRC3ZEKWOGVIRGMTDA" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Hantavirus was first detected in humans in the United States about three decades ago. In February, the infection &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/health/2025/03/08/hantavirus-gene-hackman-wife-death-arakawa/" target="_blank"&gt;gained widespread attention&lt;/a&gt; after it was linked to the death of Arakawa, whose body was found alongside Hackman’s in their Santa Fe home that month. &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/style/2025/03/07/gene-hackman-betsy-arakawa-death-investigation-new-mexico/" target="_blank"&gt;According to officials&lt;/a&gt;, Hackman probably died of a combination of high blood pressure and extensive heart disease days after the death of his wife. He had advanced Alzheimer’s disease and may not have realized his wife had died.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="OPUD2GJW6ZAEVIMIA75NPXMFQ4" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;According to the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention, &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/health/2025/03/08/hantavirus-gene-hackman-wife-death-arakawa/" target="_blank"&gt;hantaviruses are usually spread&lt;/a&gt; through contact with rodents, including through mouse and rat urine, droppings, saliva or — in rare cases — a bite or scratch.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="GUAAY6BMDBD6NK7J74DJC3QV5Q" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;People can contract the disease by breathing in dust from dried rodent urine, saliva or droppings, which can happen when cleaning. It can develop into hantavirus pulmonary syndrome, a lung disease that may kill about 38 percent of people who develop respiratory symptoms, &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/hantavirus/about/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;according to the CDC&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="4MXKSFBXMRHPFPHBVIX4QOTCVE" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Symptoms of the infection, which is generally not transmitted person to person, typically start to show one to eight weeks after the first contact with the virus.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="AWTPQIESSJCDXBTSCNHB7GAIJY" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Hantavirus is rare but not unusual, and deer mice — the only source of the virus in the area — are widespread in the Eastern Sierra region, according to county health officials. Mono County has recorded 27 cases of hantavirus since 1993, the statement said — more than any other county in California.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="4BOXROXY6BAMBEGR6XA6QP4ZLY" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;The vast majority of cases detected in the United States — 96 percent — occur west of the Mississippi River, &lt;a href="https://www.lung.org/lung-health-diseases/lung-disease-lookup/hantavirus-pulmonary-syndrome/learn-about-hantavirus-pulmonary-syndrome-hps" target="_blank"&gt;according&lt;/a&gt; to the American Lung Association.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="JLSZ7XGO6RFS3NX5JZEY4MKWTI" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Boo said there was no evidence that any of the three latest victims had engaged in behaviors associated with exposure, such as cleaning poorly ventilated indoor areas or outbuildings with a lot of mouse waste.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="HOFOGFRO6BEKTHWEM6TZX4XFAE" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Investigations by local and state public health officials found some evidence of mice in the workplaces of all three of the deceased, which is not unusual for this time of year in the area, as well as mice in one of their homes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="FYE6HSNOBJBXPBTX672HVCUQFE" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Health officials urged county residents and visitors to be vigilant for signs of indoor rodent activity and be careful around their waste.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2025 11:50:21 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilAFBVV95cUxOOFQ2LTNkQVlfOHlpRUFIWF9NankxMldnN2xNMGo4LThmVkd1LWNGY3NRQ1M0cHpJTFlzbzZDOUw3NDlSb3VzLTNwSUxrUmsyRGJiRkZTQjAzYWREeXMwVzlUOG83V2l3U1hoanhMaVNXLTZBMkNyUkRBYVI1WDdqTWpDNkFEY2txZDRuRmZIQnd0Ukxa</guid></item><item><title>A Second Child Dies of Measles in Texas - The New York Times</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMidEFVX3lxTFA4UVh2TWlBNHYxVXdaYTg3ZURfX3lfdlJzeGJ6YVZoR1lXRlV3bVRFSUZtR0piODZvWlVzZGpJbVFFd3JqNm12ZXd6WGUyU0I3VGxWM2owRGZ4cms4MVlSQlR1N1VMN0xlakZBUldmN3Jxc2Y5?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="css-s99gbd StoryBodyCompanionColumn" data-testid="companionColumn-0"&gt;&lt;div class="css-53u6y8"&gt;&lt;p class="css-at9mc1 evys1bk0"&gt;The measles crisis in West Texas has claimed the life of another child, the second death in an outbreak that has burned through the region and infected dozens of residents in bordering states.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="css-at9mc1 evys1bk0"&gt;The 8-year-old girl died early Thursday morning of “measles pulmonary failure” at a hospital in Lubbock, Texas, according to records obtained by The New York Times. It is the second confirmed measles death in a decade in the United States.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="css-at9mc1 evys1bk0"&gt;The first was an &lt;a class="css-yywogo" href="https://www.nytimes.com/2025/02/26/us/texas-measles-outbreak-death.html" title=""&gt;unvaccinated child who died in West Texas&lt;/a&gt; in February. Another unvaccinated person &lt;a class="css-yywogo" href="https://www.nytimes.com/2025/03/06/health/measles-death-new-mexico.html" title=""&gt;died in New Mexico&lt;/a&gt; after testing positive for measles, though officials have not yet confirmed that measles was the cause of death.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="css-at9mc1 evys1bk0"&gt;A Trump administration official said on Saturday night that the girl’s cause of death is “still being looked at.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="css-s99gbd StoryBodyCompanionColumn" data-testid="companionColumn-1"&gt;&lt;div class="css-53u6y8"&gt;&lt;p class="css-at9mc1 evys1bk0"&gt;Since late January, when the outbreak began, West Texas has reported 480 cases of measles and 56 hospitalizations. The outbreak has also spread to bordering states, sickening 54 people in New Mexico and 10 in Oklahoma.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="css-s99gbd StoryBodyCompanionColumn" data-testid="companionColumn-2"&gt;&lt;div class="css-53u6y8"&gt;&lt;p class="css-at9mc1 evys1bk0"&gt;If the virus continues to spread at this pace, the country risks losing its measles elimination status, a hard-fought victory earned in 2000. Public health officials in West Texas have predicted the outbreak will &lt;a class="css-yywogo" href="https://www.nytimes.com/2025/03/21/health/measles-outbreak-texas.html" title=""&gt;continue for a year&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="css-at9mc1 evys1bk0"&gt;Robert F. Kennedy, the nation’s health secretary, has faced intense criticism for his handling of the outbreak. A prominent vaccine skeptic, he has offered &lt;a class="css-yywogo" href="https://www.nytimes.com/2025/03/02/health/measles-vaccination-texas-kennedy.html" title=""&gt;muted support for vaccination&lt;/a&gt; and has &lt;a class="css-yywogo" href="https://www.nytimes.com/2025/03/04/health/texas-measles-outbreak-kennedy.html" title=""&gt;emphasized untested treatments&lt;/a&gt; for measles, like cod liver oil.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="css-at9mc1 evys1bk0"&gt;According to doctors in Texas, Mr. Kennedy’s endorsement of alternative treatments has contributed to patients delaying critical care and ingesting &lt;a class="css-yywogo" href="https://www.nytimes.com/2025/03/25/health/measles-kennedy-vitamin-a.html" title=""&gt;toxic levels&lt;/a&gt; of vitamin A.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="css-s99gbd StoryBodyCompanionColumn" data-testid="companionColumn-3"&gt;&lt;div class="css-53u6y8"&gt;&lt;p class="css-at9mc1 evys1bk0"&gt;Experts also fear that the Trump administration’s recent decisions to dismantle international public health safeguards and pull funding from local health departments have made &lt;a class="css-yywogo" href="https://www.nytimes.com/2025/04/05/health/measles-outbreaks-texas-kennedy.html" title=""&gt;large, multistate outbreaks more likely&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="css-s99gbd StoryBodyCompanionColumn" data-testid="companionColumn-4"&gt;&lt;div class="css-53u6y8"&gt;&lt;p class="css-at9mc1 evys1bk0"&gt;Measles is one of the most contagious pathogens. The virus can linger in the air for up to two hours after an infected person has left the room and spreads when a sick person breathes, coughs or sneezes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="css-at9mc1 evys1bk0"&gt;Within a week or two of being exposed, those who are infected may develop a high fever, cough, runny nose and red, watery eyes. Within a few days, a telltale rash breaks out as flat, red spots on the face and then spreads down the neck and torso to the rest of the body.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="css-at9mc1 evys1bk0"&gt;In most cases, these symptoms resolve in a few weeks. But in rare cases, the virus causes pneumonia, making it difficult for patients, but especially children, to get oxygen into their lungs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="css-s99gbd StoryBodyCompanionColumn" data-testid="companionColumn-5"&gt;&lt;div class="css-53u6y8"&gt;&lt;p class="css-at9mc1 evys1bk0"&gt;It may also cause brain swelling, which can leave lasting problems, like blindness, deafness and intellectual disabilities.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="css-at9mc1 evys1bk0"&gt;For every 1,000 children who get measles, one or two will die, according to the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention. The virus also harms the body’s immune defenses, leaving it vulnerable to other pathogens.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="css-798hid etfikam0"&gt;Christina Jewett contributed reporting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The New York Times</author><pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2025 11:36:04 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMidEFVX3lxTFA4UVh2TWlBNHYxVXdaYTg3ZURfX3lfdlJzeGJ6YVZoR1lXRlV3bVRFSUZtR0piODZvWlVzZGpJbVFFd3JqNm12ZXd6WGUyU0I3VGxWM2owRGZ4cms4MVlSQlR1N1VMN0xlakZBUldmN3Jxc2Y5</guid></item><item><title>Scientists Discover a “Second Heart” That Powers Our Blood Circulation - The Daily Galaxy</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiowFBVV95cUxQOEtPVmhKYzRtTUYwcWNEYndMcGZHTEhLNHJIWHE3eWdpcS1sN1JLTEZOMFRWOVNVamVSRk1HNVZkcFRZdnlBam5zamVYakg3bkNjTTZPajJxazdYSTNTSUtZSzJNZHViRTM3eE9QeWtiYmgxUWU0S3dwR1pwNGpSWmxLY2FPU25yRndNOUU4SjZZVF9oOWlUTkdsbG43czdET0Ew?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="dynamic-entry-content"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;aorta&lt;/strong&gt;, a large &lt;strong&gt;blood vessel&lt;/strong&gt; responsible for transporting &lt;strong&gt;oxygenated blood&lt;/strong&gt; from the heart to the rest of the body, plays a crucial role in our &lt;strong&gt;circulatory system&lt;/strong&gt;. While it has long been known that the aorta has &lt;strong&gt;elastic properties&lt;/strong&gt; that help absorb &lt;strong&gt;pressure variations&lt;/strong&gt;, recent research reveals that the aorta’s role extends beyond this passive function. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="code-block code-block-2"&gt;

    
    &lt;ins class="adsbygoogle" data-ad-client="ca-pub-6966113680805338" data-ad-slot="1096651400" data-ad-format="auto" data-full-width-responsive="true"&gt;&lt;/ins&gt;
    
    
&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;p&gt;New findings suggest that the aorta actively assists the heart by generating a &lt;strong&gt;wave-pumping effect&lt;/strong&gt;, providing crucial support for &lt;strong&gt;blood circulation&lt;/strong&gt;, particularly in individuals with heart failure.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Discovering the Aortic Wave-Pumping Effect&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The study, published in the&lt;a href="https://royalsocietypublishing.org/doi/10.1098/rsif.2024.0887" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt; &lt;em&gt;Journal of The Royal Society Interface&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, delves into a remarkable discovery that the aorta can function much like a &lt;strong&gt;secondary heart&lt;/strong&gt;, assisting the primary heart in pumping &lt;strong&gt;blood&lt;/strong&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="code-block code-block-3"&gt;


&lt;ins class="adsbygoogle" data-ad-client="ca-pub-6966113680805338" data-ad-slot="4349301016" data-ad-format="auto" data-full-width-responsive="true"&gt;&lt;/ins&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;p&gt;The phenomenon, known as “&lt;strong&gt;wave-pumping&lt;/strong&gt;,” occurs when the aorta stretches and recoils in response to the heart’s contraction and relaxation cycles. Researchers suggest that this process, which was initially observed in the &lt;strong&gt;embryonic stages&lt;/strong&gt; of &lt;strong&gt;blood circulation&lt;/strong&gt;, may persist into adulthood, playing a vital role in &lt;strong&gt;blood flow&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;In the study, researchers used magnetic resonance imaging &lt;strong&gt;(MRI) &lt;/strong&gt;to monitor the movement of the aorta in 159 participants, including those with heart &lt;strong&gt;failure&lt;/strong&gt;. Their results highlighted a significant difference in the &lt;strong&gt;aortic displacement profiles&lt;/strong&gt; between healthy individuals and heart failure patients. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The healthy group exhibited greater aortic stretching, which was less pronounced in those with heart &lt;strong&gt;failure&lt;/strong&gt;. This provides further evidence that the aorta’s stretch and recoil could help enhance circulation when the &lt;strong&gt;heart’s&lt;/strong&gt; pumping capacity is compromised.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="code-block code-block-3"&gt;


&lt;ins class="adsbygoogle" data-ad-client="ca-pub-6966113680805338" data-ad-slot="4349301016" data-ad-format="auto" data-full-width-responsive="true"&gt;&lt;/ins&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;The Mechanics of Aortic Stretch and Recoil&lt;/h2&gt;


&lt;div class="gb-container gb-container-c6586980"&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Aortic wave-pumping, or “i&lt;strong&gt;mpedance pumping&lt;/strong&gt;,” relies on the aorta’s ability to store and release &lt;strong&gt;energy&lt;/strong&gt; during the &lt;strong&gt;cardiac cycle&lt;/strong&gt;. During the heart’s contraction &lt;strong&gt;(systole)&lt;/strong&gt;, the aorta stretches as blood is pushed into it. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Then, during relaxation &lt;strong&gt;(diastole),&lt;/strong&gt; the aorta recoils, releasing the&lt;a href="https://dailygalaxy.com/2025/03/atomic-collisions-unleash-energy-bursts/" target="_blank" data-type="post" data-id="81309" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt; stored energy &lt;/a&gt;and helping maintain &lt;strong&gt;blood flow&lt;/strong&gt;. This wave-pumping effect works in tandem with the heart’s pumping mechanism, assisting the overall circulation without the need for additional heartbeats.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;This discovery is significant as it unveils a previously underappreciated aspect of aortic function. The study suggests that this wave-pumping effect could become an essential mechanism, especially in those suffering from heart failure, where the heart’s ability to pump blood is reduced. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="code-block code-block-3"&gt;


&lt;ins class="adsbygoogle" data-ad-client="ca-pub-6966113680805338" data-ad-slot="4349301016" data-ad-format="auto" data-full-width-responsive="true"&gt;&lt;/ins&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;p&gt;The aorta’s contribution to circulation could alleviate some of the burden placed on the heart, supporting the flow of &lt;strong&gt;oxygenated blood&lt;/strong&gt; through the body.&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;div class="wp-block-image"&gt;
&lt;figure class="aligncenter size-large"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="" alt="(a) The In Vitro Hydraulic Circuit To Conduct The Experiments" class="wp-image-85239" data-lazy-srcset="https://dailygalaxy.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/A-The-in-vitro-hydraulic-circuit-to-conduct-the-experiments-1200x560.jpeg 1200w, https://dailygalaxy.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/A-The-in-vitro-hydraulic-circuit-to-conduct-the-experiments-380x177.jpeg 380w, https://dailygalaxy.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/A-The-in-vitro-hydraulic-circuit-to-conduct-the-experiments-520x243.jpeg 520w, https://dailygalaxy.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/A-The-in-vitro-hydraulic-circuit-to-conduct-the-experiments-1536x717.jpeg 1536w, https://dailygalaxy.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/A-The-in-vitro-hydraulic-circuit-to-conduct-the-experiments-2048x956.jpeg 2048w" data-lazy-sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" data-lazy-src="https://dailygalaxy.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/A-The-in-vitro-hydraulic-circuit-to-conduct-the-experiments-1200x560.jpeg"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://dailygalaxy.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/A-The-in-vitro-hydraulic-circuit-to-conduct-the-experiments-1200x560.jpeg" alt="(a) The In Vitro Hydraulic Circuit To Conduct The Experiments" class="wp-image-85239" srcset="https://dailygalaxy.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/A-The-in-vitro-hydraulic-circuit-to-conduct-the-experiments-1200x560.jpeg 1200w, https://dailygalaxy.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/A-The-in-vitro-hydraulic-circuit-to-conduct-the-experiments-380x177.jpeg 380w, https://dailygalaxy.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/A-The-in-vitro-hydraulic-circuit-to-conduct-the-experiments-520x243.jpeg 520w, https://dailygalaxy.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/A-The-in-vitro-hydraulic-circuit-to-conduct-the-experiments-1536x717.jpeg 1536w, https://dailygalaxy.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/A-The-in-vitro-hydraulic-circuit-to-conduct-the-experiments-2048x956.jpeg 2048w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px"&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;figcaption class="wp-element-caption"&gt;&lt;em&gt;(A) The in vitro hydraulic circuit to conduct the experiments. The pressure and flow measurements are collected at the location of the sensors. (B) Time profile of the aortic root displacement for three cases: healthy individual of 41 years old, healthy individual of 65 years old and heart failure patient who was 43 years old. Design of the cam in the cam-follower mechanism for modelling the longitudinal stretch of the aorta is also shown in this figure.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;


&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Implications for Heart Failure Treatment&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The implications of these findings could be profound for &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://dailygalaxy.com/2024/12/doctors-say-the-heart-might-be-able-to-heal-itself-but-what-does-that-mean-for-heart-failure/" target="_blank" data-type="post" data-id="74582" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;heart failure treatment&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;. As the aorta plays a supplementary role in &lt;strong&gt;blood circulation&lt;/strong&gt;, its function could be targeted in therapies aimed at reducing the strain on the heart. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Researchers are exploring potential treatments to enhance the &lt;strong&gt;elasticity&lt;/strong&gt; of the aorta, which could help support circulation in patients with &lt;strong&gt;heart failure&lt;/strong&gt;. Some existing antihypertensive medications already work to modify &lt;strong&gt;arterial stiffness&lt;/strong&gt;, but their effect on the aorta’s wave-pumping mechanism remains an area for further research.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="code-block code-block-3"&gt;


&lt;ins class="adsbygoogle" data-ad-client="ca-pub-6966113680805338" data-ad-slot="4349301016" data-ad-format="auto" data-full-width-responsive="true"&gt;&lt;/ins&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;p&gt;The findings from this study could also explain why some individuals with weakened hearts can still maintain adequate blood circulation. The aorta may compensate for the heart’s decreased ability to pump &lt;strong&gt;blood&lt;/strong&gt;, ensuring that the body continues to receive the necessary &lt;strong&gt;oxygen&lt;/strong&gt; and nutrients. U&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;nderstanding the wave-pumping effect of the aorta offers new hope for improving heart &lt;strong&gt;failure management&lt;/strong&gt; and could lead to the development of more effective treatments.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Daily Galaxy</author><pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiowFBVV95cUxQOEtPVmhKYzRtTUYwcWNEYndMcGZHTEhLNHJIWHE3eWdpcS1sN1JLTEZOMFRWOVNVamVSRk1HNVZkcFRZdnlBam5zamVYakg3bkNjTTZPajJxazdYSTNTSUtZSzJNZHViRTM3eE9QeWtiYmgxUWU0S3dwR1pwNGpSWmxLY2FPU25yRndNOUU4SjZZVF9oOWlUTkdsbG43czdET0Ew</guid></item><item><title>Switching Western diets for this region's food could improve health - Euronews.com</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMizgFBVV95cUxORldWX2ZoTEdLaG4wOW9ROGZVSWlLN3BncFYxbkFlekFaaGFfWk5HS1ZfZzNUNklRUTZhYmtwSHYzWFNvWTcyWVRIMTNhRENEbGxJVTRoeGdMVXF5QlJ2TVRNcVhmSERyRHJTeXlBT0lSWU9KUGxQNFRvenJ4X0dIU3lvOGNsdlBPSjNWZmNmQ0VMSnVhLWZHQmlWZDRIRE85ejJjU0FJSFpFcXZ3bGhQZzRHRXUzTmdiRVA4V0xzTlNGUFo2NHo4dHJJUXRhdw?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p&gt;S$�E�q  ��7
I[���
"'�?h�,����� L�v\n����_����v�ۮ��Z6�??��̙�Hc��CJ�gT���b��n��S� w��K_�n��4���t��~��b���*��A6�0�fW#���8��~]Ճ�:a��	�'�w��z�����j�ݵ��c��*$��=tQ��^� X �X�C ��t_�_�r�I'Q�B�AQņ*כs�\t����$�=۩�P�T�|����[����VѢ��h6#����� N~��ׯ�$+(IJ����sVj�{���ޯ_%�Zv#�Xö�(�; JR�l��W�gW��Y���!�|��,����3v^d��j9�:��rlI��0� 1	��)0�FLi�~�&amp;gt;����&amp;amp;����DM��圊�Q���Xo��]b�q�řk"��WAkN�.}}���󦚆��D4���P�����_��ö/:�ҒT�=S���V�2�I&amp;gt;=c&amp;gt;��pg�(�^�5�|m�H���u,	��b�J�^��h�$�@�ɷ���A~�ο������n�`�|Y��7�lwO��v�0��Ӈ���Ʒj��1m�QC�Y&amp;gt;��ҳ��
���sv��a~�W�ߙ#�9����-��1�ͩ#�8�7����uee��$�g&lt;zap s x9&gt;&lt;/zap&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Euronews.com</author><pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2025 09:33:33 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMizgFBVV95cUxORldWX2ZoTEdLaG4wOW9ROGZVSWlLN3BncFYxbkFlekFaaGFfWk5HS1ZfZzNUNklRUTZhYmtwSHYzWFNvWTcyWVRIMTNhRENEbGxJVTRoeGdMVXF5QlJ2TVRNcVhmSERyRHJTeXlBT0lSWU9KUGxQNFRvenJ4X0dIU3lvOGNsdlBPSjNWZmNmQ0VMSnVhLWZHQmlWZDRIRE85ejJjU0FJSFpFcXZ3bGhQZzRHRXUzTmdiRVA4V0xzTlNGUFo2NHo4dHJJUXRhdw</guid></item><item><title>After “The White Lotus,” Lorazepam Lives On in Memes and Merch - The New York Times</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMigwFBVV95cUxNY1FRSFNiSkdUMlQxR1ZYQUxfR2NHeHRvampENHNlRGlqQ0U2MjlEeEpQUjBOQjJmME5zMUYxV3A0ZkVISEZ3eEg3clBNN0dXcGxmTzhxakxETEk5UWUzNkQ1cU50OE8xanhkeFVCb0V5dzVDVE9KVnNIYmYxaHJFNi1zaw?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="css-s99gbd StoryBodyCompanionColumn" data-testid="companionColumn-0"&gt;&lt;div class="css-53u6y8"&gt;&lt;p class="css-at9mc1 evys1bk0"&gt;Etsy has been flooded with hats and candles asking the question: “Has Anyone Seen My Lorazepam?” Social media is rife with videos of people enunciating “lorazepam” in a faux Southern drawl. Lorazepam even made a cameo on a recent episode of “Saturday Night Live,” when the actress Chloe Fineman raucously shouted the word during a sketch.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="css-at9mc1 evys1bk0"&gt;As anyone even loosely familiar with Season 3 of “The White Lotus” may know, this sudden tsunami of references to a prescription medication used to treat anxiety is not a sign of mass desperation. Rather, it’s a manifestation of an unceasing fan obsession with Victoria Ratliff, a character on the HBO TV show, the current season of which ends on Sunday.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="css-at9mc1 evys1bk0"&gt;Played by Parker Posey, Victoria is a wealthy North Carolina woman on vacation at a wellness resort in Thailand, who, despite the idyllic setting, regularly expresses a need for her lorazepam, a drug known for being &lt;a class="css-yywogo" href="https://www.nytimes.com/2025/03/12/well/mind/lorazepam-white-lotus-risk-benzodiazepines.html" title=""&gt;tough to quit&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="css-at9mc1 evys1bk0"&gt;A massage? It could make her “very stressed out” and “claustrophobic,” Victoria says. The lorazepam helps her “to really relax,” she tells a masseuse.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="css-s99gbd StoryBodyCompanionColumn" data-testid="companionColumn-1"&gt;&lt;div class="css-53u6y8"&gt;&lt;p class="css-at9mc1 evys1bk0"&gt;A party on a yacht? “Certain social situations make me anxious,” Victoria drawls at her eldest son, Saxon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="css-at9mc1 evys1bk0"&gt;Her daughter Piper’s decision to make a major life change? “I don’t even have my lorazepam,” a distraught Victoria declares after her bottle goes missing. “I’m going to have to drink myself to sleep.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="css-1336jj"&gt;&lt;div class="css-121kum4"&gt;&lt;p class="css-171quhb"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="css-asuuk5"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;div class="css-7axq9l" data-testid="optimistic-truncator-noscript"&gt;&lt;svg viewbox="0 0 24 24" aria-hidden="true" class="css-1b5b8u1"&gt;&lt;path fill="currentColor" fill-rule="evenodd" d="M2.5 12a9.5 9.5 0 1 1 19 0 9.5 9.5 0 0 1-19 0Zm8.5 1.75v-7.5h2v7.5h-2Zm0 2v2h2v-2h-2Z" clip-rule="evenodd"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;div data-testid="optimistic-truncator-noscript-message" class="css-6yo1no"&gt;&lt;p class="css-3kpklk"&gt;We are having trouble retrieving the article content.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="css-3kpklk"&gt;Please enable JavaScript in your browser settings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;div class="css-1dv1kvn" id="optimistic-truncator-a11y" tabindex="-1"&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thank you for your patience while we verify access. If you are in Reader mode please exit and &lt;a href="https://myaccount.nytimes.com/auth/login?response_type=cookie&amp;amp;client_id=vi&amp;amp;redirect_uri=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.nytimes.com%2F2025%2F04%2F06%2Fstyle%2Fthe-white-lotus-lorazepam-memes.html&amp;amp;asset=opttrunc"&gt;log into&lt;/a&gt; your Times account, or &lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/subscription?campaignId=89WYR&amp;amp;redirect_uri=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.nytimes.com%2F2025%2F04%2F06%2Fstyle%2Fthe-white-lotus-lorazepam-memes.html"&gt;subscribe&lt;/a&gt; for all of The Times.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="css-1g71tqy"&gt;&lt;svg viewbox="0 0 24 24" aria-hidden="true" class="css-63woee" data-testid="optimistic-truncator-spinner"&gt;&lt;g fill="currentColor"&gt;&lt;path d="M11.28 22.8a.72.72 0 1 0 1.44 0v-6.72a.72.72 0 1 0-1.44 0v6.72Z" opacity=".37"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="M17.766 21.16a.72.72 0 1 0 1.165-.846l-3.95-5.436a.72.72 0 1 0-1.165.846l3.95 5.437Z" opacity=".26"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="M1.506 14.653a.72.72 0 0 0 .445 1.37l6.391-2.078a.72.72 0 1 0-.445-1.369l-6.39 2.077Z" opacity=".61"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="M5.07 20.314a.72.72 0 0 0 1.164.847l3.95-5.437a.72.72 0 1 0-1.165-.846l-3.95 5.436Z" opacity=".48"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="M22.049 16.022a.72.72 0 0 0 .445-1.37l-6.391-2.076a.72.72 0 1 0-.445 1.37l6.39 2.076Z" opacity=".17"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="M22.494 9.347a.72.72 0 1 0-.445-1.37l-6.391 2.078a.72.72 0 1 0 .445 1.369l6.39-2.077Z" opacity=".09"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="M6.234 2.84a.72.72 0 0 0-1.165.846l3.95 5.436a.72.72 0 0 0 1.165-.846l-3.95-5.437Z" opacity=".87"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="M1.951 7.978a.72.72 0 1 0-.445 1.37l6.391 2.076a.72.72 0 1 0 .445-1.37l-6.39-2.076Z" opacity=".74"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="M18.93 3.686a.72.72 0 0 0-1.164-.847l-3.95 5.437a.72.72 0 0 0 1.165.846l3.95-5.436Z" opacity=".02"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="M12.72 1.2a.72.72 0 1 0-1.44 0v6.72a.72.72 0 0 0 1.44 0V1.2Z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/g&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;div data-testid="optimistic-truncator-message" class="css-6yo1no"&gt;&lt;p class="css-3kpklk"&gt;Thank you for your patience while we verify access.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="css-3kpklk"&gt;Already a subscriber? &lt;a data-testid="log-in-link" class="css-z5ryv4" href="https://myaccount.nytimes.com/auth/login?response_type=cookie&amp;amp;client_id=vi&amp;amp;redirect_uri=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.nytimes.com%2F2025%2F04%2F06%2Fstyle%2Fthe-white-lotus-lorazepam-memes.html&amp;amp;asset=opttrunc"&gt;Log in&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="css-3kpklk"&gt;Want all of The Times? &lt;a data-testid="subscribe-link" class="css-z5ryv4" href="https://www.nytimes.com/subscription?campaignId=89WYR&amp;amp;redirect_uri=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.nytimes.com%2F2025%2F04%2F06%2Fstyle%2Fthe-white-lotus-lorazepam-memes.html"&gt;Subscribe&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The New York Times</author><pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2025 09:00:47 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigwFBVV95cUxNY1FRSFNiSkdUMlQxR1ZYQUxfR2NHeHRvampENHNlRGlqQ0U2MjlEeEpQUjBOQjJmME5zMUYxV3A0ZkVISEZ3eEg3clBNN0dXcGxmTzhxakxETEk5UWUzNkQ1cU50OE8xanhkeFVCb0V5dzVDVE9KVnNIYmYxaHJFNi1zaw</guid></item><item><title>Scoop: RFK Jr. plans Texas trip after possible second measles-related death there - Axios</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiakFVX3lxTE42Z0NHYVJYVjFRbmRJOFM4aEVLWjFScjdUNTdidlI1VlBnTGlOZnpUMDVwVmhhWGYxaDNjbnFoVU1OMkZBZ3cwamM4cmNqS2w0SWhtVEx4N2owNVlUWG01MVRYc3REU1B1a1E?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Axios</author><pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2025 04:36:41 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiakFVX3lxTE42Z0NHYVJYVjFRbmRJOFM4aEVLWjFScjdUNTdidlI1VlBnTGlOZnpUMDVwVmhhWGYxaDNjbnFoVU1OMkZBZ3cwamM4cmNqS2w0SWhtVEx4N2owNVlUWG01MVRYc3REU1B1a1E</guid></item><item><title>10 magnesium-rich vegetarian foods to try - Times of India</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMi0AFBVV95cUxNMFdfZ2NqZ2twS2E4dTBsV2hGV01kRkJpLXVIYzZfQ0hSZmJmSTB0dHFnMXBEOUVldVhtOExEWFlJTHJVcWdNbFhDUnQ1TEV2ZXhxTFdVRlBKX21ySzJBSU04U2JOcXE1SVFQM2lkNnBFaGZBM2RoTEhySEpYSlNhNWlweGhFV2R5aVpkRklBbldJZDJSU2JmVVF1RlJXQjdXU0ZsQzV4RXlmNWJRWndYMHdURTJYczBvd3hjZllGczRFeE9Nc0trdmRuakM4Mzlw0gHQAUFVX3lxTE0wV19nY2pna3BLYTh1MGxXaEZXTWRGQmktdUhjNl9DSFJmYmZJMHR0cWcxcEQ5RWV1WG04TERYWUlMclVxZ01sWENSdDVMRXZleHFMV1VGUEpfbXJLMkFJTThTYk5xcTVJUVAzaWQ2cEVoZkEzZGhMSHJISlhKU2E1aXB4aEVXZHlpWmRGSUFuV0lkMlJTYmZVUXVGUldCN1dTRmxDNXhFeWY1YlFad1gwd1RFMlhzMG93eGNmWUZzNEV4T01zS2t2ZG5qQzgzOXA?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;amp-story-grid-layer class="recircular" id="rcontent" template="vertical"&gt;&lt;div class="letterbox"&gt;&lt;p class="mid-heading"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;You may also like&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="rc3 pa"&gt;How to make South-Indian style soft and ...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="rc5 pa"&gt;How to make delicious high-protein Chick...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/amp-story-grid-layer&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2025 03:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi0AFBVV95cUxNMFdfZ2NqZ2twS2E4dTBsV2hGV01kRkJpLXVIYzZfQ0hSZmJmSTB0dHFnMXBEOUVldVhtOExEWFlJTHJVcWdNbFhDUnQ1TEV2ZXhxTFdVRlBKX21ySzJBSU04U2JOcXE1SVFQM2lkNnBFaGZBM2RoTEhySEpYSlNhNWlweGhFV2R5aVpkRklBbldJZDJSU2JmVVF1RlJXQjdXU0ZsQzV4RXlmNWJRWndYMHdURTJYczBvd3hjZllGczRFeE9Nc0trdmRuakM4Mzlw0gHQAUFVX3lxTE0wV19nY2pna3BLYTh1MGxXaEZXTWRGQmktdUhjNl9DSFJmYmZJMHR0cWcxcEQ5RWV1WG04TERYWUlMclVxZ01sWENSdDVMRXZleHFMV1VGUEpfbXJLMkFJTThTYk5xcTVJUVAzaWQ2cEVoZkEzZGhMSHJISlhKU2E1aXB4aEVXZHlpWmRGSUFuV0lkMlJTYmZVUXVGUldCN1dTRmxDNXhFeWY1YlFad1gwd1RFMlhzMG93eGNmWUZzNEV4T01zS2t2ZG5qQzgzOXA</guid></item><item><title>NHS cancer screening reporting errors led to mother's death - BBC</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiWkFVX3lxTE9yX2dGVzNueVhXODF3SFFEanZBTEpVWmNvcU1JeE1hTWJscHlrZlJDMkhNNUlNRi15akNHU1l4TzM0YVk3TEFaNWtNUGpQNlZ6amtwOGh3cDRRd9IBX0FVX3lxTFBVQ3VsVGZjZ2RxRnRpT0NKdFFadXhWN3d3NDJKRlU1MXpmU0dDQnNEcThsZGUybTlpb0FWaFFRYThQMXFKWDdsN19VS2stcWtGNnlCSlVJbnRKRGZtSms0?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article&gt;&lt;p data-component="headline-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 eeiVGB"&gt;&lt;h1 class="sc-518485e5-0 itISwu"&gt;Cancer screening reporting errors led to mum's death&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 ejjhCR"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="hero-image" class="sc-a34861b-1 jxzoZC"&gt;&lt;img src="/bbcx/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-a34861b-0 cOpVbP hide-when-no-script"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/66bb/live/f660a1f0-097f-11f0-97e4-bd334276dd19.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/66bb/live/f660a1f0-097f-11f0-97e4-bd334276dd19.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/66bb/live/f660a1f0-097f-11f0-97e4-bd334276dd19.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/66bb/live/f660a1f0-097f-11f0-97e4-bd334276dd19.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/66bb/live/f660a1f0-097f-11f0-97e4-bd334276dd19.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/66bb/live/f660a1f0-097f-11f0-97e4-bd334276dd19.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/66bb/live/f660a1f0-097f-11f0-97e4-bd334276dd19.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/66bb/live/f660a1f0-097f-11f0-97e4-bd334276dd19.jpg.webp" loading="eager" alt="Family handout Louise Gleadell pictured before the severity of her cancer illness took hold. " class="sc-a34861b-0 efFcac"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-a34861b-2 hesJxn"&gt;Family handout&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 bdPeAJ"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-8353772e-0 iUqqeb"&gt;Louise Gleadell died aged 38 from cervical cancer after being wrongly told her tests were negative in both 2008 and 2012&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 dlWCEZ"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;The family of a mother who died from cervical cancer after twice being wrongly told she had negative results have been awarded undisclosed damages.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;The misreporting of Louise Gleadell's cervical screening results was admitted by University Hospitals of Leicester NHS Trust following her death aged 38 in March 2018.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;An internal review in 2017 found the samples, taken four years apart, were not good enough to produce reliable results but neither Ms Gleadell - a mum to three boys - nor her relatives were told about the "inadequate" samples while she was still alive.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;Her family have now been given an undisclosed payout, with the trust apologising for its mistakes that had "devastating consequences".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 dlWCEZ"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;Ms Gleadell, from Cossington in Leicestershire, was diagnosed with cervical cancer two years prior to her death. It was, by that stage, too late to have surgery.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;Two cervical screening tests, carried out in 2008 and 2012, were misreported to her as negative. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;It meant that over a four-year period, she had been given false reassurance about her health when she was developing cervical cancer, and the opportunity to treat pre-cancerous cells passed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;In fact, following the trust's 2017 internal review, both samples were found to have been "inadequate", and it found Ms Gleadell should have been invited back to have the tests repeated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 bdPeAJ"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-8353772e-0 iUqqeb"&gt;Clare and Laura Gleadell say the loss of their sister has been devastating, especially for her three sons&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 dlWCEZ"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;Ms Gleadell's sisters, Laura and Clare Gleadell, say their grief has been compounded by knowing that their sister's death was avoidable.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;Laura, 43, said: "Her death was preventable and that for us is ultimately really hard.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;"It would not have developed into cancer had she been recalled in either 2008 or 2012.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;"If she had had treatment for cell abnormalities before it even developed into cancer, she would not have died."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;Clare stressed knowing the test results were misreported and led to her death is "incredibly hard to live with".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;The 40-year-old added: "It is something we probably think about most days, if not every day." &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;The sisters described Louise as devoted to her three boys, who were aged two, 11 and 13 when they lost their mum.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;"Family to her was everything," they said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 jFCfG"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-a34861b-1 jxzoZC"&gt;&lt;img src="/bbcx/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-a34861b-0 cOpVbP hide-when-no-script"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/1141/live/66aa3db0-0997-11f0-b6a3-51bb8c2f0bab.png.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/1141/live/66aa3db0-0997-11f0-b6a3-51bb8c2f0bab.png.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/1141/live/66aa3db0-0997-11f0-b6a3-51bb8c2f0bab.png.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/1141/live/66aa3db0-0997-11f0-b6a3-51bb8c2f0bab.png.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/1141/live/66aa3db0-0997-11f0-b6a3-51bb8c2f0bab.png.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/1141/live/66aa3db0-0997-11f0-b6a3-51bb8c2f0bab.png.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/1141/live/66aa3db0-0997-11f0-b6a3-51bb8c2f0bab.png.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/1141/live/66aa3db0-0997-11f0-b6a3-51bb8c2f0bab.png.webp" loading="lazy" alt='Family handout A family day trip. Louise Gleadell smiling alongside her three boys described as her "pride and joy" by her sisters' class="sc-a34861b-0 efFcac"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-a34861b-2 hesJxn"&gt;Family handout&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 bdPeAJ"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-8353772e-0 iUqqeb"&gt;Louise, pictured with her three boys&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 dlWCEZ"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;Louise began feeling unwell in late 2015, experiencing pain, abnormal bleeding and unexpected weight loss.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;By February of the following year, she was so concerned about her health that she paid privately for an ultrasound scan. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;The findings led to further investigations, and a biopsy provided by the NHS led to a diagnosis of cervical cancer in March.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;Louise underwent chemotherapy, radiotherapy, and brachytherapy - which is internal radiation treatment. Initially, she recovered well but a few months later developed new symptoms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;Towards the end of 2016, doctors told her the disease was terminal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;With donations, Louise travelled abroad for immunotherapy in Germany but ultimately it did not stop the fatal spread of the cancer. She died at the Loros Hospice in Leicester.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 jFCfG"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-a34861b-1 jxzoZC"&gt;&lt;img src="/bbcx/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-a34861b-0 cOpVbP hide-when-no-script"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/34b1/live/8bdef890-0998-11f0-94d4-6f954f5dcfa3.png.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/34b1/live/8bdef890-0998-11f0-94d4-6f954f5dcfa3.png.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/34b1/live/8bdef890-0998-11f0-94d4-6f954f5dcfa3.png.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/34b1/live/8bdef890-0998-11f0-94d4-6f954f5dcfa3.png.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/34b1/live/8bdef890-0998-11f0-94d4-6f954f5dcfa3.png.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/34b1/live/8bdef890-0998-11f0-94d4-6f954f5dcfa3.png.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/34b1/live/8bdef890-0998-11f0-94d4-6f954f5dcfa3.png.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/34b1/live/8bdef890-0998-11f0-94d4-6f954f5dcfa3.png.webp" loading="lazy" alt='Family handout Younger sisters Clare and Laura  remember Louise as "mischievous" growing up and " vivacious" in adulthood and someone for whom "family was everything"' class="sc-a34861b-0 efFcac"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-a34861b-2 hesJxn"&gt;Family handout&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 bdPeAJ"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-8353772e-0 iUqqeb"&gt;The family appointed solicitors to look at Louise's case&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 dlWCEZ"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;The NHS routinely looks back and re-examines test findings after someone is diagnosed with cervical cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;After appointing solicitors to examine the case, the family found out that the NHS trust knew of the misreporting of the results in the summer of 2017 - before Louise died.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;It is not clear why Louise was not told about this.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;Specialist clinical negligence lawyer, Gemma Lewis, of Moosa-Duke Solicitors, uncovered the situation and said the trust should have told Louise.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;"I don't think the family should have had to find out from me," she added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;"Someone with a medical background should have explained things, who could answer any follow-up questions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;"It should not take a legal investigation - that they might not have decided to undertake - to uncover the truth."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 bdPeAJ"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-8353772e-0 iUqqeb"&gt;Solicitor Gemma Lewis has been working with the family to find answers&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 dlWCEZ"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;Richard Mitchell, chief executive at the trust, said: "I am deeply sorry that mistakes were made in how we cared for and communicated with Louise and for the devastating consequences.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;"Errors like those in Louise's care are rare, and there have been significant improvements in cervical screening since 2019 when human papillomavirus (HPV)  testing was introduced nationally. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;"Locally, following an investigation into Louise's care, we have strengthened our processes for sharing the findings of cervical screening quality audits to ensure timely and open communication.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;"We understand Louise's family may still have questions and we have reached out to offer a meeting."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 bdPeAJ"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-8353772e-0 iUqqeb"&gt;Laura and Clare regularly visit their sister's grave, where there is a memorial bench &lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 dlWCEZ"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;Following the trust's apology, Louise's sisters stressed that they would encourage all women to go for a &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.nhs.uk/conditions/cervical-screening/" class="sc-c9299ecf-0 beIoQm"&gt;cervical screening&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;The NHS says cervical screening checks a sample of cells from your cervix for certain types of human papillomavirus (HPV).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;These types of HPV can cause abnormal changes to the cells in your cervix and are called "high risk" types of HPV.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;If high risk types of HPV are found during screening, the sample of cells is also checked for abnormal cell changes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;If abnormal cells are found, they can be treated so they do not get a chance to turn into cervical cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;Louise's sisters added that they intended to take up the trust's offer of a meeting. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;Clare said: "We have unanswered questions - exactly how and why was Louise given false information after her smears and why, after her diagnosis, when the mistakes were highlighted were the family not told?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;"The hardest part is seeing Louise's three boys without their mother. It's heartbreaking - the impact of went wrong has been awful."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="embed-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 jVHuOl"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BBC</author><pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2025 00:29:09 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiWkFVX3lxTE9yX2dGVzNueVhXODF3SFFEanZBTEpVWmNvcU1JeE1hTWJscHlrZlJDMkhNNUlNRi15akNHU1l4TzM0YVk3TEFaNWtNUGpQNlZ6amtwOGh3cDRRd9IBX0FVX3lxTFBVQ3VsVGZjZ2RxRnRpT0NKdFFadXhWN3d3NDJKRlU1MXpmU0dDQnNEcThsZGUybTlpb0FWaFFRYThQMXFKWDdsN19VS2stcWtGNnlCSlVJbnRKRGZtSms0</guid></item><item><title>‘Til dementia do us part: Study finds greater cognitive decline among married - Straight Arrow News</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMimwFBVV95cUxPLVZpY0ZfZGI0dERzRjhLZ2luY2ctNm9Cc3RSV0pBYTBabFU0Q1p5YXpTQV9MdTlhSms2M0NjRVNDdGZ0aXJJZjZ3VF9aR2lsQUUxVS1abGdrbVEyTWE0UmxGaFFicTAtYWJpNnpERnI3bnB3SzFkTXpXa0pfMkRCV2VuSXptajEybmVYZlgyU1dNSU1zdmVucV9kRQ?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="san-syndication-wrapper wp-block-san-syndication-wrapper"&gt;
	
	

&lt;ul class="wp-block-list"&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A new study suggests that married and widowed individuals bear a significantly higher risk of developing dementia than their unmarried and divorced counterparts. The findings contradict long-held beliefs that marriage produces better health outcomes. &lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;More than 24,000 people between the ages of 50 and 104 participated in the study, which lasted upwards of 18 years depending on the participant. &lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;While the study failed to yield definitive reasons why single people have a lower risk of developing dementia, potential reasons include a more robust social life, greater self-reliance, or psychologically richer lives. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;



&lt;hr class="wp-block-separator has-alpha-channel-opacity"&gt;



&lt;h4 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-full-story"&gt;Full Story&lt;/h4&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Prevailing wisdom has long held that married people enjoy better health outcomes throughout life. However, &lt;a href="https://alz-journals.onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/alz.70072" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;a new study&lt;/a&gt; published in the journal Alzheimer’s &amp;amp; Dementia suggests that married individuals are significantly more likely to develop dementia than their unmarried and divorced counterparts.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="wp-block-san-media-landscape-mobile"&gt;
	&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Researchers from the Florida State University College of Medicine and the University of Montpellier tracked more than 24,000 participants between the ages of 50 and 104 for up to 18 years. Each participant –– who identified as married, widowed, divorced or never married –– began the study without dementia, though some had mild cognitive impairment.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;div class="wp-block-san-app-download"&gt;
    &lt;div class="wp-block-san-app-download__desktop"&gt;
        &lt;img decoding="async" class="mobile-hidden" src="https://san.com/wp-content/themes/straightarrow-2023/assets/images/app-download-block-qr-code.png" alt="QR code for SAN app download"&gt;

        &lt;div class="wp-block-san-app-download__author"&gt;
			
            &lt;p class="wp-block-san-app-download__title"&gt;
				Download the SAN app today to stay up-to-date with Unbiased. Straight Facts™.            &lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
        &lt;p class="wp-block-san-app-download__subtitle"&gt;
        Point phone camera here&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;


&lt;p&gt;The participants enrolled in the study from 42 different Alzheimer’s Disease Research Centers nationwide and yielded a combined 122,000 “person-years of data,” &lt;a href="https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-04-marriage-linked-higher-dementia-older.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;according to Medical Xpress&lt;/a&gt;. They received annual neuropsychological evaluations and clinical exams.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h4 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-digging-into-the-data"&gt;Digging into the data&lt;/h4&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Key to the team’s findings was that  21.9% of both married and widowed participants developed dementia, Alzheimer’s or Lewy body dementia over the course of the study, while only 12.8% and 12.4% of divorced and never-married participants did, respectively. The researchers also noted that their findings largely held regardless of a person’s age, sex, race, education level, lifestyle choices and other variables tied to physical and mental health.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Of the participants who became widowed during the study’s period, the researchers found that they were less likely to develop dementia than those who were married throughout.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Likewise, while some participants began the study with mild cognitive impairment, the unmarried group was again less likely to progress into clinical dementia over the course of their participation in the study.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Additionally, unmarried men showed the least risk of developing dementia.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h4 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-the-not-so-secret-life-of-single-people"&gt;The not-so-secret life of single people&lt;/h4&gt;



&lt;p&gt;While the study failed to yield definitive answers as to why unmarried and divorced people are less susceptible to dementia, its authors posit several theories, including that single people maintain more robust social ties with their friends and community, and that they are required to be more self-reliant.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“Never married individuals are also more likely to socialize with friends and neighbors and are more likely to engage in healthier behaviors than their married counterparts,” &lt;a href="https://www.psychologytoday.com/us/blog/living-single/202504/dementia-is-more-common-among-the-married-than-the-unmarried" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;the study’s authors write&lt;/a&gt;. “Married individuals tend to have less social integration and are engaged in less frequent and lower-quality interactions in their networks compared to their unmarried counterparts. These positive aspects of well-being and social ties may potentially serve as protective factors against dementia over time.”  &lt;/p&gt;






&lt;p&gt;Similarly, &lt;a href="https://www.psychologytoday.com/us/blog/living-single/202504/dementia-is-more-common-among-the-married-than-the-unmarried" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;writing in Psychology Today&lt;/a&gt;, Dr. Bella DePaulo, an expert on single people and author of “Single at Heart” notes that unmarried individuals “may have more psychologically rich lives characterized by a variety of interesting and unique experiences.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;DePaulo adds, “Leading that kind of life may well keep people cognitively sharp.”&lt;/p&gt;





	
&lt;/div&gt;


&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Straight Arrow News</author><pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 23:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimwFBVV95cUxPLVZpY0ZfZGI0dERzRjhLZ2luY2ctNm9Cc3RSV0pBYTBabFU0Q1p5YXpTQV9MdTlhSms2M0NjRVNDdGZ0aXJJZjZ3VF9aR2lsQUUxVS1abGdrbVEyTWE0UmxGaFFicTAtYWJpNnpERnI3bnB3SzFkTXpXa0pfMkRCV2VuSXptajEybmVYZlgyU1dNSU1zdmVucV9kRQ</guid></item><item><title>Rare virus that killed Gene Hackman's wife linked to 3 deaths in California town - NBC News</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiwgFBVV95cUxPSDg5b1pzU0ZOc29ROEVEcDNLY1VpVkZsZ1VqSkc2WjF6cXhycGgxWEc2U0F1elJzalQ4bHhLeUVSbHJxWkJtcy1ldEl4emNBbHhXQlUzcXVIX1kta2MxS3dXR09SWjVocktJNkctY3ctZDg2cEpSV1NEVF9VSUl5SVNOaVlvWUpGbk5mWGNEalQzaUdnSGZYNG1OZVI4bzhITGlkZ09RWmR6UGVERUZKdm9pWGVONTk1eFZGSXJsNU9MUQ?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body__content"&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;Public health officials in California confirmed that three people in the town of Mammoth Lakes have &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/hantavirus-caused-death-betsy-arakawa-wife-gene-hackman-rcna195418" target="_blank"&gt;died from hantavirus&lt;/a&gt;, the same virus that killed actor Gene Hackman’s wife in February.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;In a statement released Thursday, health officials in Mono County reported a third death from hantavirus pulmonary syndrome in the rural town in the state's Eastern Sierra region, calling the situation “tragic” and “alarming.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="taboolaReadMoreBelow"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;Hantavirus is a relatively rare virus spread by rodents — typically mice — to humans from the animals’ urine, droppings and saliva.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;“The occurrence of three cases in a short period has me worried, especially this early in the year,” Dr. Tom Boo, a county public health officer, &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/monohealthdepartment/posts/pfbid034Xem45nWHe6KEBbZsgdsAa6MZCYZo2vncbLJgH8gwLrr6vDCE8hyfhSWbUUK88Pal" target="_blank"&gt;said in a statement&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;Boo said hantavirus cases are usually seen later in the spring and summer. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;The latest death was the third from hantavirus in Mammoth Lakes since early February, the county health and human services division said. The deceased was a young adult, but Boo said health officials do not yet know how the person was infected.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;“The home had no evidence of mouse activity,” he said. “We observed some mice in the workplace, which is not unusual for indoor spaces this time of year in Mammoth Lakes. We haven’t identified any other activities in the weeks before illness that would have increased this person’s exposure to mice or their droppings.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;Deer mice are widespread in California's Eastern Sierra region, but Boo said their numbers are thought to be higher than normal this year, which could &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/hantavirus-arizona-warn-spread-potentially-fatal-rcna162593" target="_blank"&gt;increase the risk of exposure to hantavirus&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="recommended-intersection-ref" data-activity-map="recommended-article-body-recommended" data-testid="recommended-wrapper"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="recommended-intersection-ref" data-activity-map="recommended-article-body-recommended" data-testid="recommended-wrapper"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;The latest death comes weeks after investigators revealed that &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/officials-share-update-mystery-deaths-gene-hackman-wife-rcna195281" target="_blank"&gt;Betsy Arakawa, the wife of Gene Hackman&lt;/a&gt;, died from hantavirus pulmonary syndrome. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;Arakawa and Hackman were found dead in their home in Santa Fe, New Mexico, on Feb. 26. Hackman tested negative for hantavirus, and an autopsy determined that the &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/officials-share-update-mystery-deaths-gene-hackman-wife-rcna195281" target="_blank"&gt;actor’s cause of death&lt;/a&gt; was “hypertensive and atherosclerotic cardiovascular disease with Alzheimer’s disease as a significant contributory factor.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;Cases of hantavirus are relatively rare but can be devastating. Symptoms include fatigue, fever, muscle aches, coughing and shortness of breath, according to the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention. Severe cases can progress to the lungs and become fatal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;Boo said there have been no indications so far that the three people who died engaged in activities typically linked to hantavirus exposure, such as cleaning out areas with mouse droppings or with poor indoor ventilation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;He said people should be vigilant and careful about the presence of mice, and should exercise particular caution around the animals’ droppings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="endmark body-graf"&gt;“We’ve now gone about a month without any additional suspect cases, but remain concerned about the increase in activity,” Boo said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>NBC News</author><pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 22:50:53 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiwgFBVV95cUxPSDg5b1pzU0ZOc29ROEVEcDNLY1VpVkZsZ1VqSkc2WjF6cXhycGgxWEc2U0F1elJzalQ4bHhLeUVSbHJxWkJtcy1ldEl4emNBbHhXQlUzcXVIX1kta2MxS3dXR09SWjVocktJNkctY3ctZDg2cEpSV1NEVF9VSUl5SVNOaVlvWUpGbk5mWGNEalQzaUdnSGZYNG1OZVI4bzhITGlkZ09RWmR6UGVERUZKdm9pWGVONTk1eFZGSXJsNU9MUQ</guid></item><item><title>Rare virus that killed Gene Hackman's wife linked to 3 deaths in California town - NBC News</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiwgFBVV95cUxPSDg5b1pzU0ZOc29ROEVEcDNLY1VpVkZsZ1VqSkc2WjF6cXhycGgxWEc2U0F1elJzalQ4bHhLeUVSbHJxWkJtcy1ldEl4emNBbHhXQlUzcXVIX1kta2MxS3dXR09SWjVocktJNkctY3ctZDg2cEpSV1NEVF9VSUl5SVNOaVlvWUpGbk5mWGNEalQzaUdnSGZYNG1OZVI4bzhITGlkZ09RWmR6UGVERUZKdm9pWGVONTk1eFZGSXJsNU9MUdIBVkFVX3lxTFBkNHRDTVBMRVlTLWJwbWhpbzVFNzlETDZINWpRaEtQNDQ3WGhlRUVIM1lfd2RHTVotTEJRcFVCeUdwRjJZbU4zQ3NISTZnVUF2QnRnVkZR?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body__content"&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;Public health officials in California confirmed that three people in the town of Mammoth Lakes have &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/hantavirus-caused-death-betsy-arakawa-wife-gene-hackman-rcna195418" target="_blank"&gt;died from hantavirus&lt;/a&gt;, the same virus that killed actor Gene Hackman’s wife in February.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;In a statement released Thursday, health officials in Mono County reported a third death from hantavirus pulmonary syndrome in the rural town in the state's Eastern Sierra region, calling the situation “tragic” and “alarming.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="taboolaReadMoreBelow"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;Hantavirus is a relatively rare virus spread by rodents — typically mice — to humans from the animals’ urine, droppings and saliva.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;“The occurrence of three cases in a short period has me worried, especially this early in the year,” Dr. Tom Boo, a county public health officer, &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/monohealthdepartment/posts/pfbid034Xem45nWHe6KEBbZsgdsAa6MZCYZo2vncbLJgH8gwLrr6vDCE8hyfhSWbUUK88Pal" target="_blank"&gt;said in a statement&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;Boo said hantavirus cases are usually seen later in the spring and summer. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;The latest death was the third from hantavirus in Mammoth Lakes since early February, the county health and human services division said. The deceased was a young adult, but Boo said health officials do not yet know how the person was infected.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;“The home had no evidence of mouse activity,” he said. “We observed some mice in the workplace, which is not unusual for indoor spaces this time of year in Mammoth Lakes. We haven’t identified any other activities in the weeks before illness that would have increased this person’s exposure to mice or their droppings.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;Deer mice are widespread in California's Eastern Sierra region, but Boo said their numbers are thought to be higher than normal this year, which could &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/hantavirus-arizona-warn-spread-potentially-fatal-rcna162593" target="_blank"&gt;increase the risk of exposure to hantavirus&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="recommended-intersection-ref" data-activity-map="recommended-article-body-recommended" data-testid="recommended-wrapper"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="recommended-intersection-ref" data-activity-map="recommended-article-body-recommended" data-testid="recommended-wrapper"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;The latest death comes weeks after investigators revealed that &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/officials-share-update-mystery-deaths-gene-hackman-wife-rcna195281" target="_blank"&gt;Betsy Arakawa, the wife of Gene Hackman&lt;/a&gt;, died from hantavirus pulmonary syndrome. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;Arakawa and Hackman were found dead in their home in Santa Fe, New Mexico, on Feb. 26. Hackman tested negative for hantavirus, and an autopsy determined that the &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/officials-share-update-mystery-deaths-gene-hackman-wife-rcna195281" target="_blank"&gt;actor’s cause of death&lt;/a&gt; was “hypertensive and atherosclerotic cardiovascular disease with Alzheimer’s disease as a significant contributory factor.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;Cases of hantavirus are relatively rare but can be devastating. Symptoms include fatigue, fever, muscle aches, coughing and shortness of breath, according to the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention. Severe cases can progress to the lungs and become fatal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;Boo said there have been no indications so far that the three people who died engaged in activities typically linked to hantavirus exposure, such as cleaning out areas with mouse droppings or with poor indoor ventilation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;He said people should be vigilant and careful about the presence of mice, and should exercise particular caution around the animals’ droppings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="endmark body-graf"&gt;“We’ve now gone about a month without any additional suspect cases, but remain concerned about the increase in activity,” Boo said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>NBC News</author><pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 22:50:53 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiwgFBVV95cUxPSDg5b1pzU0ZOc29ROEVEcDNLY1VpVkZsZ1VqSkc2WjF6cXhycGgxWEc2U0F1elJzalQ4bHhLeUVSbHJxWkJtcy1ldEl4emNBbHhXQlUzcXVIX1kta2MxS3dXR09SWjVocktJNkctY3ctZDg2cEpSV1NEVF9VSUl5SVNOaVlvWUpGbk5mWGNEalQzaUdnSGZYNG1OZVI4bzhITGlkZ09RWmR6UGVERUZKdm9pWGVONTk1eFZGSXJsNU9MUdIBVkFVX3lxTFBkNHRDTVBMRVlTLWJwbWhpbzVFNzlETDZINWpRaEtQNDQ3WGhlRUVIM1lfd2RHTVotTEJRcFVCeUdwRjJZbU4zQ3NISTZnVUF2QnRnVkZR</guid></item><item><title>Breakthrough Prize Announces 2025 Laureates in Life Sciences, Fundamental Physics, and Mathematics - Breakthrough Prize</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiTkFVX3lxTE1xN21vWXRnd3pONFFZZHM5ekFPemZPYjJQclVUU3piWEJwbnkxd0VsZm5wY3BSVGNVOHduRU1VcWNGWW1rc2p3UndRNFEtdw?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="main"&gt;

	&lt;h1&gt;Breakthrough Prize Announces 2025 Laureates in Life Sciences, Fundamental Physics, and Mathematics&lt;/h1&gt;
    &lt;div class="b"&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;“Oscars® of Science” Awards Six $3 Million Prizes&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GLP-1 Diabetes and Obesity Discovery | Multiple Sclerosis Causes and Treatments | DNA Editing&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Exploration of Nature at Shortest Distances&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Proof of Geometric Langlands Conjecture&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Special Prize Awarded to Giant of Theoretical Physics&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Breakthrough Prize in Life Sciences Awarded to Daniel J. Drucker, Joel Habener, Jens Juul Holst, Lotte Bjerre Knudsen and Svetlana Mojsov; Alberto Ascherio and Stephen L. Hauser; and David R. Liu&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Breakthrough Prize in Fundamental Physics Awarded to More than 13,000 Researchers from ATLAS, CMS, ALICE and LHCb Experiments at CERN&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Breakthrough Prize in Mathematics Awarded to Dennis Gaitsgory&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Special Breakthrough Prize in Fundamental Physics Awarded to Gerardus 't Hooft&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Six New Horizons Prizes Awarded for Early-Career Achievements in Physics and Mathematics&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Three Maryam Mirzakhani New Frontiers Prizes Awarded to Women Mathematicians for Early-Career Work&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Laureates Announced and Honored at Annual Breakthrough Prize Ceremony in Los Angeles&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;April 5, 2025 – Los Angeles&lt;/strong&gt; – The Breakthrough Prize Foundation today announced the winners of the 2025 Breakthrough Prizes, honoring scientists driving remarkable discoveries in gene editing, human diseases, the fundamental particles of the Universe and its underlying mathematical principles.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Breakthrough Prize – popularly known as the “Oscars® of Science” – was created to celebrate the wonders of our scientific age by founding sponsors &lt;strong&gt;Sergey Brin&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;Priscilla Chan&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;Mark Zuckerberg&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;Julia&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;Yuri Milner&lt;/strong&gt;, and &lt;strong&gt;Anne Wojcicki&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Six Breakthrough Prizes of $3 million each were awarded in Life Sciences, Fundamental Physics, and Mathematics. In addition, the foundation announced eight early-career physicists and mathematicians are sharing six $100,000 New Horizons Prizes. Three women mathematicians recently completing PhDs are each receiving a $50,000 Maryam Mirzakhani New Frontiers Prize. This year’s prize money totals $18.75 million, bringing the amount conferred over the 14 years of the Breakthrough Prize to more than $326 million.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“This year’s Breakthrough Prize laureates have made amazing strides – including treatments for major diseases affecting millions of people worldwide – showing once again the transformative power of curiosity-driven basic science.&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;– Priscilla Chan and Mark Zuckerberg&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“The questions these laureates are asking are among the deepest questions there are – about the workings of life, the nature of the Universe and the abstract landscapes of mathematics. It’s inspiring to see scientists seeking and finding answers to these questions.”&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;– Yuri Milner&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“The breakthroughs being recognized this year are extraordinary – including, in my own field, amazing gene-editing technologies that are already having a big impact. I’m excited to learn more about the scientists’ ideas across all the fields.” &lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;– Anne Wojcicki&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Life Sciences&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Daniel J. Drucker&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;Joel Habener&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;Jens Juul Holst&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;Lotte Bjerre Knudsen&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;Svetlana Mojsov&lt;/strong&gt; share the Breakthrough Prize in Life Sciences. These five scientists' complementary contributions – from basic hormone discovery through physiological understanding to pharmaceutical development – have led to highly effective drugs for diabetes and obesity, ushering in a new era of &lt;strong&gt;GLP-1&lt;/strong&gt; medicines for cardiometabolic disorders. Between them their breakthroughs include: the discovery of the gene encoding the GLP-1 hormone; the synthesis, isolation and characterization of the hormone’s biologically active forms; the demonstration that it is produced in the gut and stimulates insulin production; elucidation of its broader physiological roles, including control of appetite and energy homeostasis; the development of a more stable version of the hormone that continues to act in the body for days rather than hours; and its translation into a new class of drugs that is transforming the treatment of metabolic diseases affecting hundreds of millions of people worldwide.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Stephen L. Hauser&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;Alberto Ascherio&lt;/strong&gt; share the Breakthrough Prize in Life Sciences. The two researchers have transformed the understanding and treatment of &lt;strong&gt;multiple sclerosis&lt;/strong&gt; (MS), a debilitating neurodegenerative disease in which the immune system attacks the insulating protein around nerve fibers. Among other contributions, Hauser overturned the scientific consensus on the mechanism of MS, identifying the immune system’s B cells as the primary driver of damage to nerve cells. He was also instrumental in the development and testing of B cell-depleting therapies, which have revolutionized modern treatment of the disease. Meanwhile, through painstaking long-term epidemiological analysis, Ascherio discovered the necessary condition for getting MS: infection with the Epstein-Barr virus (EBV). The majority of the population carries this pathogen, normally without severe effects, but Ascherio showed that contracting it raises the risk of developing MS by a factor of 32. This work opens the possibility of treating MS with antiviral drugs, and for the development of a vaccine for EBV that could effectively prevent MS altogether.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;David R. Liu&lt;/strong&gt; is awarded the Breakthrough Prize in Life Sciences for developing two powerful, widely used &lt;strong&gt;gene-editing&lt;/strong&gt; technologies. These technologies are engineered molecular machines that correct mutations in our DNA that cause genetic diseases in patients. Importantly, they do not require cutting the DNA double-helix, and thus lead to fewer unwanted outcomes. In 2016 Liu’s lab developed base editing, which corrects the single-letter “misspellings” that constitute about 30 percent of mutations known to cause genetic diseases. Then in 2019 his lab invented prime editing, which replaces whole stretches of defective DNA with a corrected version, and in principle could be used to repair nearly all disease-causing mutations. These technologies have already been distributed more than 20,000 times to labs around the world, resulting in thousands of published advances in research, agriculture, and biomedicine. In animals, base editing and prime editing have successfully corrected mutations to rescue blood diseases such as sickle-cell disease and beta-thalassemia, neurological disorders such as ALS and spinal muscular atrophy (SMA), muscle diseases such as muscular dystrophy and cardiomyopathies, genetic forms of blindness, genetic forms of hearing loss, several metabolic disorders, and progeria, a premature aging disease. At least 15 base editing and prime editing clinical trials have begun in five countries, with beneficial and, in some cases, life-saving results already confirmed in patients for the treatment of T-cell leukemia, sickle-cell disease, beta-thalassemia, and high cholesterol.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Fundamental Physics&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Breakthrough Prize in Fundamental Physics is awarded to thousands of researchers from more than 70 countries representing four experimental collaborations at &lt;strong&gt;CERN&lt;/strong&gt;’s &lt;strong&gt;Large Hadron Collider&lt;/strong&gt; (LHC) – &lt;strong&gt;ATLAS&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;CMS&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;ALICE&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;LHCb&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The $3 million prize is allocated to ATLAS ($1 million); CMS ($1 million), ALICE ($500,000) and LHCb ($500,000), in recognition of &lt;strong&gt;13,508&lt;/strong&gt; co-authors of publications based on LHC Run-2 data released between 2015 and July 15, 2024. [ATLAS – 5,345 researchers; CMS – 4,550; ALICE – 1,869; LHCb – 1,744].&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In consultation with the leaders of the experiments, the Breakthrough Prize Foundation will donate 100 percent of the prize funds to the &lt;strong&gt;CERN &amp;amp; Society Foundation&lt;/strong&gt;. The prize money will be used by the collaborations to offer grants for doctoral students from member institutes to spend research time at CERN, giving the students experience working at the forefront of science and new expertise to bring back to their home countries and regions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The four experiments are recognized for testing the modern theory of particle physics – the Standard Model – and other theories describing physics that might lie beyond it to high precision. This includes precisely measuring properties of the Higgs boson and elucidating the mechanism by which the Higgs field gives mass to elementary particles; probing extremely rare particle interactions, and exotic states of matter that existed in the first moments of the Universe; discovering more than 72 new hadrons and measuring subtle differences between matter and antimatter particles; and setting strong bounds on possibilities for new physics beyond the Standard Model, including dark matter, supersymmetry and hidden extra dimensions. ATLAS and CMS are general-purpose experiments, which pursue the full program of exploration offered by the LHC’s high-energy and high-intensity proton and ion beams. They synchronously announced the discovery of the Higgs boson in 2012 and continue to investigate its properties. ALICE studies the quark-gluon plasma, a state of extremely hot and dense matter that existed in the first microseconds after the Big Bang. And LHCb explores minute differences between matter and antimatter, violation of fundamental symmetries, and the complex spectra of composite particles (“hadrons”) made of heavy and light quarks. By performing these extraordinarily precise and delicate tests, the LHC experiments have pushed the boundaries of fundamental physics to unprecedented limits.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Mathematics&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dennis Gaitsgory&lt;/strong&gt; wins the Breakthrough Prize in Mathematics for his central role in the proof of the geometric Langlands conjecture. The &lt;strong&gt;Langlands program&lt;/strong&gt; is a broad research program spanning several fields of mathematics. It grew out of a series of conjectures proposing precise connections between seemingly disparate mathematical concepts. Such connections are powerful tools; for example, the proof of Fermat’s Last Theorem reduces to a particular instance of the Langlands conjecture. These Langlands program equivalences can be thought of as generalizations of the Fourier transform, a tool that relates waves to frequency spectrums and has widespread uses from seismology to sound engineering. In the case of the geometric Langlands conjecture, the proposed one-to-one correspondence is between two very different sets of objects, analogous to these spectrums and waves: on the spectrum side are abstract algebraic objects called representations of the fundamental group, which capture information about the kinds of loop that can wrap around certain complex surfaces; on the “wave” side are sheaves, which, loosely speaking, are rules assigning vector spaces to points on a surface. Gaitsgory has dedicated much of the last 30 years to the geometric Langlands conjecture. In 2013 he wrote an outline of the steps required for a proof, and after more than a decade of intensive research in 2024 he and his colleagues published the full proof, comprising over 800 pages spread over 5 papers. This is a monumental advance, expected to have deep implications in other areas of mathematics too, including number theory, algebraic geometry and mathematical physics.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Special Breakthrough Prize in Fundamental Physics&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Gerard 't Hooft&lt;/strong&gt;, winner of the Special Breakthrough Prize in Fundamental Physics, is one of the world’s most pre-eminent theoretical physicists. In the early 1970s he made crucial contributions to the foundations of what would later become known as the Standard Model of the subatomic particles. He proved that Yang-Mills theories (the mathematical framework underlying theories of both the weak and strong nuclear forces) make sense when treated quantum mechanically – that they can give finite, calculable results rather than meaningless infinities – thus validating theories which became central to the Standard Model. He made several crucial contributions to understanding the theory of the strong force, including resolving a major problem involving the masses of particles through special field configurations called instantons; he developed new mathematical tools for studying strongly interacting quarks; and he introduced the fruitful approach of studying the strong force by imagining it is mediated by many more varieties of quarks and gluons than it actually is. These and other contributions helped establish the Standard Model as a workable theory and provided powerful tools for calculating its predictions. 't Hooft has studied the quantum effects that can explain how information is processed in black holes, which led to the development of the holographic principle in cosmology, and possibly to new alternative ways to interpret quantum mechanics.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;New Horizons in Physics Prize&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This year’s New Horizons in Physics Prizes honor early-career researchers across a wide range of fields. In atomic physics, &lt;strong&gt;Waseem Bakr&lt;/strong&gt; has created quantum gas microscopes that can image individual atoms confined in an optical lattice, advancing the study of strongly interacting quantum systems. In quantum information, a field at the fertile intersection of physics, mathematics and computer science, &lt;strong&gt;Jeongwan Haah&lt;/strong&gt; has developed models of emergent quantum systems –macroscopic systems exhibiting quantum behavior, whose potential applications include quantum computing; these models include ‘Haah's code’, which has opened the field of a class of quasi-particles called fractons. And in astronomy, &lt;strong&gt;Sebastiaan Haffert&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;Rebecca Jensen-Clem&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;Maaike van Kooten&lt;/strong&gt; have designed and enabled novel techniques for extreme adaptive optics, which are systems that compensate for the effects of Earth’s atmosphere on light reaching terrestrial telescopes. Their work promises to enable the direct detection of the smallest exoplanets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;New Horizons in Mathematics Prize&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Modern physics and higher mathematics share intimate connections, and it is notable that the research areas of all three of this year’s New Horizons in Mathematics Prize winners have links to quantum physics. &lt;strong&gt;Ewain Gwynne&lt;/strong&gt; is recognized for his work in conformal probability, which studies probabilistic objects such as random curves and surfaces. &lt;strong&gt;John Pardon&lt;/strong&gt; has produced a number of important results in geometry and topology, particularly in the field of symplectic geometry and pseudo-holomorphic curves, which are certain types of smooth surfaces in manifolds. &lt;strong&gt;Sam Raskin&lt;/strong&gt; has played a significant role in the major recent progress on the geometric Langlands program (see Mathematics section above), including the final proof of the geometric Langlands conjecture in characteristic 0.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Maryam Mirzakhani New Frontiers Prize&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Maryam Mirzakhani New Frontiers Prize is awarded to outstanding women mathematicians who have recently completed their PhDs. &lt;strong&gt;Si Ying Lee&lt;/strong&gt; has found a new approach to an important problem in the Langlands program (see Mathematics section above), succeeding in reducing it to a local problem. &lt;strong&gt;Rajula Srivastava&lt;/strong&gt; has made progress in a challenging area at the intersection of harmonic analysis and number theory. Her work focuses on bounding the number of lattice points one can find near a given smooth surface, with important applications to Diophantine approximation in higher dimensions. &lt;strong&gt;Ewin Tang&lt;/strong&gt; has invented quantum computing algorithms for machine learning. She also proved that certain calculations, which quantum algorithms were widely considered to be exponentially faster at solving, can actually be solved in comparable time by a normal (non-quantum) computer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Citations for 2025 Laureates&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;2025 Breakthrough Prize in Life Sciences&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;
		&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Daniel J. Drucker&lt;/strong&gt;, Lunenfeld-Tanenbaum Research Institute, Sinai Health, and University of Toronto&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Joel Habener&lt;/strong&gt;, Massachusetts General Hospital and Harvard University&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jens Juul Holst&lt;/strong&gt;, Novo Nordisk Foundation Center for Basic Metabolic Research and the Department of Biomedical Sciences, University of Copenhagen&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lotte Bjerre Knudsen&lt;/strong&gt;, Novo Nordisk&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Svetlana Mojsov&lt;/strong&gt;, Rockefeller University&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;p&gt;For the discovery and characterization of GLP-1 and revealing its physiology and potential in treating diabetes and obesity.&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;
		&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Alberto Ascherio&lt;/strong&gt;, Harvard University&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Stephen L. Hauser&lt;/strong&gt;, University of California, San Francisco&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;p&gt;For establishing the role of B cells in multiple sclerosis and developing B-cell based treatments, and for revealing that Epstein-Barr virus infection is the leading risk for multiple sclerosis.&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;
		&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;David R. Liu&lt;/strong&gt;, Merkin Institute for Transformative Technologies in Healthcare at the Broad Institute of MIT and Harvard, Harvard University, and Howard Hughes Medical Institute&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;p&gt;For developing base editing and prime editing, technologies that edit the DNA of living systems without cutting the DNA double helix, and rewrite segments of genes at their native locations, enabling the correction or replacement of virtually any mutation.&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;2025 Breakthrough Prize in Fundamental Physics&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;ATLAS&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;CMS&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;ALICE&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;LHCb&lt;/strong&gt; Collaborations at &lt;strong&gt;CERN&lt;/strong&gt;’s &lt;strong&gt;Large Hadron Collider&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For detailed measurements of Higgs boson properties confirming the symmetry-breaking mechanism of mass generation, the discovery of new strongly interacting particles, the study of rare processes and matter-antimatter asymmetry, and the exploration of nature at the shortest distances and most extreme conditions at CERN’s Large Hadron Collider.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The $3 million prize is allocated to ATLAS ($1 million); CMS ($1 million), ALICE ($500,000) and LHCb ($500,000), in recognition of 13,508 co-authors of publications based on LHC Run-2 data released between 2015 and July 15, 2024. [ATLAS – 5,345 researchers; CMS – 4,550; ALICE – 1,869; LHCb – 1,744].&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In consultation with the leaders of the experiments, the Breakthrough Prize Foundation will donate 100 percent of the prize funds to the &lt;strong&gt;CERN &amp;amp; Society Foundation&lt;/strong&gt;. The prize money will be used by the collaborations to offer grants for doctoral students from member institutes to spend research time at CERN, giving the students experience working at the forefront of science and new expertise to bring back to their home countries and regions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The names of each prizewinner can be found at &lt;a href="https://breakthroughprize.org/Laureates/1"&gt;breakthroughprize.org/Laureates/1&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;2025 Special Breakthrough Prize in Fundamental Physics&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;
		&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Gerardus 't Hooft&lt;/strong&gt;, Utrecht University&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;p&gt;For fundamental insights into gauge theory and the standard model.&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;2025 Breakthrough Prize in Mathematics&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;
		&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dennis Gaitsgory&lt;/strong&gt;, Max Planck Institute for Mathematics&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;p&gt;For foundational works and numerous breakthrough contributions to the geometric Langlands program and its quantum version; in particular, the development of the derived algebraic geometry approach and the proof of the geometric Langlands conjecture in characteristic 0.&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;


&lt;h3&gt;2025 New Horizons in Mathematics Prize&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;
		&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ewain Gwynne&lt;/strong&gt;, University of Chicago&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;p&gt;For contributions to conformal probability, in particular to the understanding of the LQG metric.&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;
		&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;John Pardon&lt;/strong&gt;, Stony Brook University&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;p&gt;For contributions to symplectic topology and other areas of geometry and topology.&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;
		&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sam Raskin&lt;/strong&gt;, Yale University&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;p&gt;For contributions to the geometric Langlands program, including the theory of the Whittaker model and the proof of the geometric Langlands conjecture in characteristic 0.&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;2025 Maryam Mirzakhani New Frontiers Prize&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;
		&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Si Ying Lee&lt;/strong&gt;, Stanford University (PhD Harvard University 2022)&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;p&gt;For contributions to the theory of Shimura varieties.&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;
		&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Rajula Srivastava&lt;/strong&gt;, University of Bonn and Max Planck Institute for Mathematics (PhD University of Wisconsin 2022)&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;p&gt;For contributions in harmonic analysis and analytic number theory, including contributions to the problem of counting rational points near smooth manifolds.&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;
		&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ewin Tang&lt;/strong&gt;, University of California, Berkeley (PhD University of Washington 2023)&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;p&gt;For developing classical analogs of quantum algorithms for machine learning and linear algebra, and for advances in quantum machine learning on quantum data.&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;2025 New Horizons in Physics Prize&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;
		&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Waseem Bakr&lt;/strong&gt;, Princeton University&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;p&gt;For the realization of quantum gas microscopes for atoms and molecules, providing a microscopic view on correlations and transport in strongly interacting quantum systems.&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;
		&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jeongwan Haah&lt;/strong&gt;, Stanford University&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;p&gt;For the discovery of Haah's code, in which fractal conservation laws emerge, and other models bringing discrete mathematical structures to physics.&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;
		&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sebastiaan Haffert&lt;/strong&gt;, Leiden University, Leiden Observatory and University of Arizona, Steward Observatory&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Rebecca Jensen-Clem&lt;/strong&gt;, University of California, Santa Cruz&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Maaike van Kooten&lt;/strong&gt;, National Research Council Canada&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;p&gt;For demonstrating new extreme adaptive optics techniques that will allow the direct detection of the smallest exoplanets.&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;




&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Videos and Photos Can Be Downloaded Here&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://files.rubenstein.com" target="_blank"&gt;files.rubenstein.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;User: BPMedia25&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Pass: press&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;About The Breakthrough Prize&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For the 13&lt;sup&gt;th&lt;/sup&gt; year, the Breakthrough Prize, renowned as the “Oscars® of Science,” recognizes the world’s top scientists. Each prize is $3 million and presented in the fields of Life Sciences, Fundamental Physics and Mathematics. In addition, up to three New Horizons in Physics Prizes, up to three New Horizons in Mathematics Prizes and up to three Maryam Mirzakhani New Frontiers Prizes are given out to early-career researchers each year. Laureates attend a gala award ceremony designed to celebrate their achievements and inspire the next generation of scientists.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Breakthrough Prizes were founded by Sergey Brin, Priscilla Chan and Mark Zuckerberg, Julia and Yuri Milner, and Anne Wojcicki and have been sponsored by foundations established by them. Selection Committees composed of previous Breakthrough Prize laureates in each field choose the winners. Information on the Breakthrough Prize is available at &lt;a href="https://breakthroughprize.org"&gt;breakthroughprize.org&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Contact&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For media inquiries:&lt;br&gt;
&lt;a href="mailto:media@breakthroughprize.org"&gt;media@breakthroughprize.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;OR&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Rubenstein Communications, Inc.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
New York, New York
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	Kristen Bothwell&lt;br&gt;
	&lt;a href="mailto:kbothwell@rubenstein.com"&gt;kbothwell@rubenstein.com&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	Alice McGillion&lt;br&gt;
	&lt;a href="mailto:amcgillion@rubenstein.com"&gt;amcgillion@rubenstein.com&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Breakthrough Prize</author><pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 22:34:49 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiTkFVX3lxTE1xN21vWXRnd3pONFFZZHM5ekFPemZPYjJQclVUU3piWEJwbnkxd0VsZm5wY3BSVGNVOHduRU1VcWNGWW1rc2p3UndRNFEtdw</guid></item><item><title>Three Boston-area researchers win Breakthrough Prizes, the ‘Oscars of Science’ - The Boston Globe</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMigAFBVV95cUxOTFUyZEVhNXJPSV83cS1kRVF3blVCNkJxSXlseWQ3a0pmd1dSaThhUVRGOGN0b3RtZ1hQbXVEVXBWT0JUS3pPdFBPaTdNNjF3VF9BdDJGLTZ1U084MFVJdmp3VVdlR2ZfakFfcHVYLXQxc2NRVTYzdFNQOWNES2t6OQ?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="body | gutter_16--desktop gutter_16--tablet paywalled_content
              "&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;One of the prizes, awarded to Liu, who conducts his research at The Broad Institute in Cambridge, recognizes his lab’s discovery of base and prime gene editing to fight genetic diseases. The technology corrects DNA mutations without the need for cutting DNA’s double-helix structure like previous technologies have. Base editing, developed by Liu’s lab in 2016, corrects single-letter “misspellings” in DNA, and his lab’s 2019 invention of prime editing replaces full stretches of faulty DNA with corrected versions.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Liu’s technology has been distributed to more than 20,000 non-profit labs worldwide that are working on treatments for a wide range of genetic diseases, many of which are rare diseases that often do not get attention from large pharmaceuticals. The technology makes it “economically feasible to create therapeutics for small markets,” according to a news release.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Fifteen clinical trials of the technology are ongoing in five different countries, and life-saving results have been seen in patients with T-cell leukemia, sickle-cell disease, beta-thalassemia, and high cholesterol have already been seen.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;“It was really a huge team effort,” said Liu. “It’s a wonderful testament to the the hard work of many of the the people who I’ve had the honor of working with over the past 26 years.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Liu intends to donate his prize winnings to fund research in other labs that might be struggling from &lt;a href="https://www.bostonglobe.com/2025/03/06/metro/trump-kills-science-funding-dei/" target="_blank"&gt;federal funding cuts&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Habener along with four fellow researchers will share in another of the prizes for the discovery of GLP-1 medications in treating diabetes and obesity. The drugs mimic the GLP-1 hormone in the body, which regulates blood sugar and appetite.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;“I never thought my dream would come true to discover something that impacts millions, even billions, of lives,” said Habener, who researched at Harvard University and Massachusetts General Hospital.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;The award is being shared by Daniel J. Drucker, Jens Juul Holst, Lotte Bjerre Knudsen, and Svetlana Mojsov. Drucker, who is now at the University of Toronto, and Mojsov, at Rockefeller University, both contributed to the discovery while they were at Harvard and MGH.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;The team’s invention, which &lt;a href="https://www.statnews.com/2023/09/27/weight-loss-obesity-glp1-svetlana-mojsov/" target="_blank"&gt;spanned over decades of research&lt;/a&gt;, established a &lt;a href="https://www.bostonglobe.com/2025/01/21/business/weight-loss-drugs-wegovy-zepbound-obesity-insurance/" target="_blank"&gt;robust market&lt;/a&gt; for the medications.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;A third prize will go to Harvard researcher Ascherio and the University of California’s Stephen L. Hauser, for their work finding the virus connected to risk for multiple sclerosis. Those findings may lead to the possibility to treat the disease earlier with antiviral drugs, making it more manageable, or the development of a vaccine to stop the disease at its root.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Ascherio is now looking to how the discovery could be built upon to start fighting other diseases before they take hold.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;“We are desperately trying to get funding, to expand our research to apply the same blueprint of study design to investigate the role of infection in other diseases, which is a major question that is unanswered at this point,” said Ascherio.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Ascherio found all people who develop multiple sclerosis must have had Epstein Barr Virus previously, which is one of the most common human viruses and the cause of infectious mononucleosis, also known as “mono.” Many people contract the disease, especially in childhood, without ever knowing they had&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;it, and contracting the disease multiplies the risk for developing MS by 32 times.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr class="tagline_hr | border_foreground border_half gutter_20_28--mobile
               margin_none text_align_left width_100px"&gt;&lt;p class="tagline | font_primary inline_block  margin_top_32"&gt;Maren Halpin can be reached at &lt;a href="mailto:maren.halpin@globe.com" class="" target="_blank"&gt;maren.halpin@globe.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Boston Globe</author><pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 22:30:57 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigAFBVV95cUxOTFUyZEVhNXJPSV83cS1kRVF3blVCNkJxSXlseWQ3a0pmd1dSaThhUVRGOGN0b3RtZ1hQbXVEVXBWT0JUS3pPdFBPaTdNNjF3VF9BdDJGLTZ1U084MFVJdmp3VVdlR2ZfakFfcHVYLXQxc2NRVTYzdFNQOWNES2t6OQ</guid></item><item><title>Traveler with measles was at Houston airport, say officials - Chron</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMingFBVV95cUxPbjVCdlh4S24xWWtPeEF1N1dVOWlrbmZfa1lWU3NPYndrN3k1dlVjazUybjBoRDZfUWpITjJPQ0xpYzBFUXpWYVUyV2tqdk5uam00TzNjZE9NSDZKQU1nYVAzOGZqcjhmTGNDT3c3UlVDdU5JYmZ4U2tvM1BjME1VMVhyZDBucDhvSlg2VkFaS09uV1dXaS1kUE1DMEU4Zw?oc=5</link><description>&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;
    
        
&lt;/body&gt;
</description><author>Chron</author><pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 21:40:16 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMingFBVV95cUxPbjVCdlh4S24xWWtPeEF1N1dVOWlrbmZfa1lWU3NPYndrN3k1dlVjazUybjBoRDZfUWpITjJPQ0xpYzBFUXpWYVUyV2tqdk5uam00TzNjZE9NSDZKQU1nYVAzOGZqcjhmTGNDT3c3UlVDdU5JYmZ4U2tvM1BjME1VMVhyZDBucDhvSlg2VkFaS09uV1dXaS1kUE1DMEU4Zw</guid></item><item><title>Measles case confirmed in traveler passing through Hobby Airport - KHOU</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMizgFBVV95cUxORTJBUXhBR1pOcktDVFgtcHo2QkdnUmVLbXo0WGZINS1kUHgzZl90cUQxN0tmYWtSam5QNDVoYkR2bFdhWVl3QnNydnpyUGV1R3BVV01NaDR2NGxVY3hvazlGYjZsTkQ5eWdlc0hwS3Fqa3hVdU9sNURIanJzc29TZlcwYTBRdGpxb21lXy1oSy1LQkVVak9ieldtRWpwRkhWMGtheHBMQ21fZWU0QkJIRkEwcHFxQ1NmQmxwVVlzb0QzTHBoTnNSWnZWOUoyUQ?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="article__summary"&gt;The Houston Health Department confirmed a measles case in an unvaccinated traveler at Hobby Airport on March 30.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;div class="article__body"&gt;
                    &lt;div class="article__section article__section_type_text utility__text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;HOUSTON — The Houston Health Department has confirmed a &lt;a href="/article/news/health/harris-county-texas-measles-case/285-17e0abcd-8829-42e7-a16b-1bd7ca1b3ca0" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;case of measles&lt;/a&gt; in an unvaccinated person who passed through Hobby Airport while infectious on Sunday, March 30. The traveler, who arrived from Mexico, was at multiple locations within the airport between 4 p.m. and 8 p.m.&lt;/p&gt;                    &lt;/div&gt;
                    &lt;div class="article__section article__section_type_text utility__text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The infectious person moved through several areas of the airport, including the Western Concourse, Customs, baggage claim, and the Central Concourse before boarding a connecting flight to their final destination.&lt;/p&gt;                    &lt;/div&gt;
                        
                    &lt;div class="article__section article__section_type_text utility__text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Editor's note: Video above is from earlier this week when a person in Harris County under 18 without a history of travel was diagnosed with measles. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;                    &lt;/div&gt;
                    &lt;div class="article__section article__section_type_text utility__text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Health officials said there are no additional confirmed cases in Houston at this time and emphasize that this case has no connection to any local measles cases in the Greater Houston area.&lt;/p&gt;                    &lt;/div&gt;
                    &lt;div class="article__section article__section_type_text utility__text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"If you were at Hobby Airport on March 30, 2025, between 4–8 p.m. and are concerned about possible exposure, please call your primary care provider before seeking in-person healthcare," said Dr. David Persse, Chief Medical Officer for the City of Houston. "Do not visit an emergency room unless you are experiencing symptoms such as fever, cough, runny nose, red eyes, or a rash and have called ahead to allow them to prepare for your arrival."&lt;/p&gt;                    &lt;/div&gt;
                    
                    &lt;div class="article__section article__section_type_text utility__text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On Thursday, Harris County Public Health said a &lt;a href="/article/news/health/harris-county-texas-measles-case/285-17e0abcd-8829-42e7-a16b-1bd7ca1b3ca0" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;child in unincorporated Harris County&lt;/a&gt; had a confirmed case of measles. There were nearly &lt;a href="/article/news/health/measles/texas-measles-outbreak-cases-reported-april-4-update/285-7a6e9fc0-43be-48b1-9f61-4c87969acc34" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;500 cases of measles&lt;/a&gt; in an outbreak in west Texas.&lt;/p&gt;                    &lt;/div&gt;
                    &lt;div class="article__section article__section_type_text utility__text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Measles is a highly contagious virus that spreads through the air via coughing and sneezing. Anyone who was in the airport during the specified timeframe may have been exposed and should monitor their health for the next 21 days, through April 20.&lt;/p&gt;                    &lt;/div&gt;
                    &lt;div class="article__section article__section_type_text utility__text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dr. Persse emphasized vaccination as the best protection against measles, noting that the disease "can lead to serious complications, especially in young children and those with weakened immune systems." He urged everyone to verify their immunization status and ensure they are up to date.&lt;/p&gt;                    &lt;/div&gt;
                    &lt;div class="article__section article__section_type_text utility__text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For more information on measles symptoms, the MMR vaccine, vaccination protocols, and steps to take following possible exposure, residents can visit HoustonHealth.Org or call 832-393-4220.&lt;/p&gt;                    &lt;/div&gt;
                                &lt;p class="article__section article__section_type_embed"&gt;
                                    
                                &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>KHOU</author><pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 21:31:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMizgFBVV95cUxORTJBUXhBR1pOcktDVFgtcHo2QkdnUmVLbXo0WGZINS1kUHgzZl90cUQxN0tmYWtSam5QNDVoYkR2bFdhWVl3QnNydnpyUGV1R3BVV01NaDR2NGxVY3hvazlGYjZsTkQ5eWdlc0hwS3Fqa3hVdU9sNURIanJzc29TZlcwYTBRdGpxb21lXy1oSy1LQkVVak9ieldtRWpwRkhWMGtheHBMQ21fZWU0QkJIRkEwcHFxQ1NmQmxwVVlzb0QzTHBoTnNSWnZWOUoyUQ</guid></item><item><title>5 nurses on same floor of Boston-area hospital develop brain tumors - New York Daily News</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMigwFBVV95cUxOekxVRFlZWi1fNWZwM1J5cTVFSzZtb2trWmlVa0lPZTFQR0hJUE0zMWlGLWhCTWhJc0pmdDEzZl82NDlfM0VhYlZ4aWhQeFFXcWJ0X3JZT0hMcGZvSUZxWE1kRF9ra21rMDVCOGFIVnJEVWZNUmJmX2s5dUtadGdhRXZpTQ?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="body-copy"&gt;&lt;p class="wp-remixd-voice-wrapper"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Five nurses who worked on the same floor of a Boston-area hospital &lt;a href="https://www.boston25news.com/news/local/25-investigates-newton-wellesley-hospital-investigating-brain-tumors-among-nurses/F2HUMVDIQZHLLO23DODCGCIVSQ/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;have all developed brain tumors.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In total, 11 members of the fifth-floor maternity unit at Mass General’s &lt;a href="https://www.massgeneralbrigham.org/en/patient-care/services-and-specialties/locations/newton-wellesley-hospital" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Newton-Wellesley Hospital&lt;/a&gt; have reported suffering from health issues, including the nurses diagnosed with the benign tumors. Two of those have the most common, benign type — &lt;a href="https://www.mayoclinic.org/diseases-conditions/meningioma/symptoms-causes/syc-20355643#:~:text=Most%20meningiomas%20grow%20very%20slowly,may%20be%20watched%20over%20time." target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;meningioma&lt;/a&gt; — according to the hospital, which is located about 10 miles west of Boston.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The hospital not provide specifics regarding the conditions of the other six staffers, saying only that &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/5-nurses-work-floor-massachusetts-hospital-brain-tumors-rcna199798" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;they suffered from unspecified health issues&lt;/a&gt;, NBC reported.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In response to the cluster, the Newton hospital launched an investigation “in collaboration with the Department of Occupational Health and Safety,” but did not uncover any “environmental risks which could be linked to the development of a brain tumor,” Jonathan Sonis, the hospital’s associate chief medical officer, and Sandy Muse, chief nursing officer, said in a statement to the network.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="s2nPlayer k-papQS7n5" data-type="float" data-s2n-api="dfm_stn_player_script_id_papQS7n5"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The probe ruled out the water supply, disposable masks, nearby X-rays and chemotherapy treatment on the floor below as potential triggers, the hospital added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Every staff member who came forward was given the opportunity to be interviewed by the Occupational Health and Safety team to evaluate each diagnosis in the context of their individual medical history and risk factors,” the statement continued. “As always, the health and wellbeing of our staff, clinicians, and patients is our absolute top priority.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But the &lt;a href="https://www.massnurses.org/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Massachusetts Nurses Association&lt;/a&gt; has taken issue with the conclusion, claiming the hospital’s review of the environmental factors was “not comprehensive,” NBC Boston reported. The union added that it has begun looking into the matter on its own.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The hospital&lt;a href="https://www.nbcboston.com/news/local/5-nurses-in-1-unit-at-newton-wellesley-hospital-diagnosed-with-brain-tumors/3676081/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt; cannot make this issue go away&lt;/a&gt; by attempting to provide a predetermined conclusion,” MNA said in a statement.&lt;/p&gt;

			&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>New York Daily News</author><pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 20:32:55 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigwFBVV95cUxOekxVRFlZWi1fNWZwM1J5cTVFSzZtb2trWmlVa0lPZTFQR0hJUE0zMWlGLWhCTWhJc0pmdDEzZl82NDlfM0VhYlZ4aWhQeFFXcWJ0X3JZT0hMcGZvSUZxWE1kRF9ra21rMDVCOGFIVnJEVWZNUmJmX2s5dUtadGdhRXZpTQ</guid></item><item><title>CDC’s top laboratory on sexually transmitted diseases is shut by Trump administration - statnews.com</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMisgFBVV95cUxNMFVyWERKOWRBZkJ3TnRjWmY3RFRYY3Bpd2phWkR3RVVrbkVTMGdMTXpoQl8yc0RJTlJGejl5V0FkdTJXeGxLWmtXMHNPVFBaV0hJV1p3cGFRLTNGZ2tITUFvcGtqTE1nbDFGbzVyTU5BM2NiM3BZZ2hteDBQMExIU2UyeU1VUG85dUNFa2M0Y01OZGlfWENkSGdPN000TDZhejl4SU9ZZXhydEh3SEZEV3p3?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content the-content wp-block-post-content is-layout-flow wp-block-post-content-is-layout-flow"&gt;&lt;p&gt;At a time when the world is down to a single drug that can reliably cure gonorrhea, the U.S. government has shuttered the country’s premier sexually transmitted diseases laboratory, leaving experts aghast and fearful about what lies ahead.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The STD lab at the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention — a leading player in global efforts to monitor for drug resistance in the bacteria that cause these diseases — was among the targets of major staff slashing at the CDC this past week. All 28 full-time employees of the lab were fired.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;STD clinicians and researchers were flummoxed, both because most of the other infectious diseases functions of the CDC were spared in this round of cuts, and because of the critical nature of the work the lab performed. Until the Trump administration announced the United States was withdrawing from the World Health Organization, the CDC lab was one of three international reference laboratories for STDs that worked with the WHO to conduct surveillance for infection rates and drug-resistance patterns and to recommend the best ways to treat these infections. The other two are in Australia and Sweden.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;A CDC white paper on antibiotic resistance released during the first Trump administration listed drug-resistant gonorrhea as &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/antimicrobial-resistance/media/pdfs/2019-ar-threats-report-508.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;one of five urgent threats&lt;/a&gt; facing the country. Antimicrobial resistance to that last drug that reliably works to cure gonorrhea, ceftriaxone, is rare but on the rise globally.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“The loss of this lab is a huge deal to the American people,” said David C. Harvey, executive director of the National Coalition of STD Directors, which represents state, city, and U.S. territorial STD prevention programs across the country. “Without that lab, we would have not been able to appropriately diagnose and monitor drug-resistant gonorrhea.”&lt;/p&gt;





&lt;p&gt;There has been no explanation from the Department of Health and Human Services, or its secretary, Robert F. Kennedy Jr., about why the STD lab was closed. When STAT asked the HHS press office about the closure, the response was swift — but wholly unrelated to the question posed.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“The critical work of the CDC will continue under Secretary Kennedy’s vision to streamline HHS to better serve the American people. The reorganization will strengthen the CDC with the transfer of the Administration for Strategic Preparedness and Response (ASPR), responsible for national disaster and public health emergency response, to the agency, reinforcing its core mission to protect Americans from health threats,” Emily Hilliard, deputy press secretary, said via email. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;A follow up from STAT noting that the information provided was not about the STD lab drew no response.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Though STDs don’t garner as many headlines as Ebola, influenza, or Covid-19, they are among the most common diseases in the world — not just infectious diseases, but diseases period, said Jeffrey Klausner, a professor of medicine in infectious diseases, population, and public health at the USC Keck School of Medicine. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Klausner was shocked by the CDC lab’s closure. “To me, this is like a blind man with a chainsaw has just gone through the system and arbitrarily cut things without any rationale,” he said in an interview. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;In terms of the decision’s implications for efforts to monitor for drug-resistant STDs, Klausner put it bluntly: “We are blind. As of [Tuesday], we are blind.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Ina Park, a professor at the UCSF School of Medicine, and a co-author of the CDC’s 2024 laboratory guidelines for the diagnosis of syphilis, was also appalled.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“It’s just horrific and it’s so foolish and shortsighted,” Park said. “This administration has sometimes brought people back when they’ve realized that a service is vital and this is one of the times where I’m hoping that they will step up and do this.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Klausner knows Kennedy personally, and reached out to tell him cutting the CDC’s STD lab was a mistake. As of Saturday, Klausner said he had not heard back from Kennedy on this issue.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The STD lab served multiple functions — updating treatment guidelines, monitoring resistance patterns, and working to develop better tests for syphilis, &lt;a href="https://www.statnews.com/2024/01/30/syphilis-rates-epidemic-united-states/"&gt;a resurgent infection&lt;/a&gt; for which existing tests are outdated.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;It was a resource for clinicians who are having trouble curing patients of STIs that are not responding to treatment. Park noted she recently consulted on a case involving a woman who had been suffering for nine months from trichomoniasis, a vaginal infection. It was not responding to the treatments the woman’s physician prescribed. Park urged the treating doctor to send a sample to the CDC for additional testing, and the resulting treatment recommendation cured the infection.&lt;/p&gt;





&lt;p&gt;The lab also leads the national surveillance for resistance patterns among STDs, generating genetic sequences of important isolates that it shares with the scientific community. That information is used in the development of tests and new therapeutics. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;One of the fired employees, who asked not to be named for fear of reprisals, noted the lab holds the world’s largest repository of gonorrhea isolates — over 50,000, dating back to 1988 when the CDC began to collect them. Many of those isolates are in a freezer farm contracted by the CDC. What will happen to this invaluable scientific resource? It’s not clear.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“They’re irreplaceable. Even if you have new mutations now, you always need to track where they came from. The evolution, the pressures on what genes and all that. You need those older ones to really study that,” the individual said.” Are they just going to autoclave the whole thing and destroy it?”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The fired lab employee noted that the work that was being done at the CDC STD lab is not done elsewhere. “There’s no duplication. There is no lab like us at NIH” — the National Institutes of Health — “or at any university. The university [researchers], they rely on our specimens to do work. But if no one collects them, it’s just a real blow.” &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Julie Dombrowski, a professor of medicine at the University of Washington and director of the Seattle and King County public health department’s HIV, STD and hepatitis C program, stressed that no one should expect the private sector to step in to fill the gap the closure has created.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“There is no commercial interest and little money to be made in this arena,” Dombrowski said in an email.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“It means we will lose ground in the fight against syphilis, we will be blind to national-level trends in antibiotic resistance among gonorrhea, and we will lose world-class expertise that will be very difficult to rebuild,” she said.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The loss of the CDC lab comes at a particularly fraught time. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Since the dawn of the antibiotic era, gonorrhea has systematically laid waste to every antibiotic used against it. The last reliably effective drug, ceftriaxone, is showing signs it too will soon be vanquished — reports of pan-resistant and extremely drug resistant gonorrhea have emerged in other parts of the world. What’s happening elsewhere will happen here, said Edward Hook, a professor emeritus at the University of Alabama at Birmingham, and an infectious diseases specialist who focuses on STIs.&lt;/p&gt;





&lt;p&gt;“We live in a global village and these are global processes,” Hook said. “You can go from one side of the world to another in less than a day, and as a result the antibiotic resistance and public health threats can spread very, very quickly.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;For the first time in years, two new drugs for gonorrhea are nearing the end of the developmental pipeline — a major accomplishment. But given gonorrhea’s relentless development of resistance, it’s only a matter of time before it will develop the mutations needed to get around the new drugs too, said Barbara Van Der Pol, a professor of medicine and public health in the Heersink School of Medicine at the University of Alabama at Birmingham. Without the CDC lab, national efforts to monitor for resistance to the new drugs won’t exist, she said.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“So we’re going to have new drugs hit the market, but we’re not going to have a mechanism that has been vetted at the national level and is standardized that we can deploy quickly,” Van Der Pol said.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;That lack of national standardization will create a situation where it’s hard to interpret what’s being seen, and when treatment guidelines ought to be changed, she said, likening the situation to the Wild West: “Everybody has a gun, but nobody knows when to use it.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The loss of the lab also comes as clinicians are starting to adopt a new approach to trying to prevent sexually transmitted infections in people at high risk of acquiring them. As of last year, the CDC recommended that men who have sex with other men along with transgender women take a dose of the antibiotic doxycycline within 72 hours of having sex. The approach, known as doxy PEP — for post-exposure prophylaxis — has been shown to reduce syphilis and chlamydia infections by about 70% and gonorrhea infections by about 50%.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Although there is a lot of hope associated with this approach, there are also concerns it could drive antibiotic resistance. Implementing it in the absence of a laboratory tasked with monitoring drug resistance nationally strikes STD experts as imprudent.  “We’ve lost one of our key tools to be able to monitor that resistance,” Klausner said.  “This is a terrible time to be cutting off the ability to conduct surveillance,” Park said.&lt;/p&gt;



                &lt;div class="gf_browser_unknown gform_wrapper gform-theme gform-theme--foundation gform-theme--framework gform-theme--orbital" data-form-theme="orbital" data-form-index="0" id="gform_wrapper_1396"&gt;
                        &lt;div class="gform_heading"&gt;
                            &lt;h2 class="gform_title"&gt;Have you been affected by cuts and restructuring at HHS?&lt;/h2&gt;
                            &lt;p class="gform_description"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
							&lt;p class="gform_required_legend"&gt;&lt;span class="gfield_required gfield_required_asterisk"&gt;*&lt;/span&gt;Required&lt;/p&gt;
                        &lt;/div&gt;
                        &lt;/div&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

		
		&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>statnews.com</author><pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 20:01:11 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMisgFBVV95cUxNMFVyWERKOWRBZkJ3TnRjWmY3RFRYY3Bpd2phWkR3RVVrbkVTMGdMTXpoQl8yc0RJTlJGejl5V0FkdTJXeGxLWmtXMHNPVFBaV0hJV1p3cGFRLTNGZ2tITUFvcGtqTE1nbDFGbzVyTU5BM2NiM3BZZ2hteDBQMExIU2UyeU1VUG85dUNFa2M0Y01OZGlfWENkSGdPN000TDZhejl4SU9ZZXhydEh3SEZEV3p3</guid></item><item><title>Two new malaria cases reported in south Trinidad - Trinidad and Tobago Newsday</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiigFBVV95cUxOVDNTZEhSMVhKR2w0QTViU1ptRy1EaDAwdWdMV2pXZmNnQmNiUGI3dnY4UVhUdTFTNkVqVmZwaXVQVTZqYVZLUkxYUXNXRUVzTzczU1AtelJBa2dLbS1aSXJIazVPa3Z4b1UtUUpNR0hDY0JFQ2ZrOUw2VGhTN0tyT2l1RWYxY184RlE?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article class="article-content"&gt;


	&lt;a class="article-category" href="https://newsday.co.tt/category/news"&gt;News&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;header&gt;
	&lt;h1&gt;Two new malaria cases reported in south Trinidad&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;/header&gt;



&lt;address class="article-author"&gt;
	&lt;a rel="author" href="https://newsday.co.tt/reporter/janelle-de-souza"&gt;
		Janelle De Souza								
	&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/address&gt;



&lt;time class="date-time" pubdate datetime="2025-04-05" title="Saturday 5 April 2025"&gt;14 Hrs Ago&lt;/time&gt;

&lt;figure id="article-featured-image" class="article-featured-image"&gt;&lt;img fetchpriority="high" src="https://newsday.co.tt/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/23242284-e1736982670559-1024x575.jpg" alt="Health Minister Terrence Deyalsingh. - File photo"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;Health Minister Terrence Deyalsingh. - File photo&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;p&gt;TWO more cases of malaria have been reported in south Trinidad.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;According to a Ministry of Health release on April 5, the new cases occurred in the same geographic location as the previous five cases, bringing the total number of malaria cases in 2025 to seven.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“The MoH takes this opportunity to remind the public that malaria is not endemic to Trinidad and Tobago at this time. Additionally, during the period 2015 to 2024 there have been 153 confirmed cases, which is an average of 15 cases per year. The majority of these cases are imported and/or introduced.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Malaria is a vector-borne infectious disease caused by parasites. The vector is predominantly the Anopheles species of mosquito which primarily bites at night.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It is noteworthy that unlike dengue, chikungunya and Zika, malaria is not spread by a virus. It is also important to note that the Aedes species of mosquito is not the primary vector for malaria.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="ad-manager-half-page-mobile-ad-300x600 ad-space-centered" id="div-gpt-ad-1550239531467-0"&gt;&amp;gt;

&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Early symptoms include fever, chills, headaches and fatigue, which may start within ten-15 days of being bitten by an infected female Anopheles mosquito.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It is suggested that high-risk groups such as people living in and around forested areas, farmers, hunters, hikers and environmentalists wear long-sleeved, loose-fitting and light-coloured clothes; use mosquito nets when sleeping; and use insect repellents, coils and vaporisers when possible.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;People experiencing any of these symptoms should visit their nearest health facility, the ministry advised.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/article&gt;



&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Trinidad and Tobago Newsday</author><pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 19:15:14 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiigFBVV95cUxOVDNTZEhSMVhKR2w0QTViU1ptRy1EaDAwdWdMV2pXZmNnQmNiUGI3dnY4UVhUdTFTNkVqVmZwaXVQVTZqYVZLUkxYUXNXRUVzTzczU1AtelJBa2dLbS1aSXJIazVPa3Z4b1UtUUpNR0hDY0JFQ2ZrOUw2VGhTN0tyT2l1RWYxY184RlE</guid></item><item><title>RFK Jr. Makes Jaw-Dropping Gaffe About Measles Outbreak - The Daily Beast</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMijgFBVV95cUxOYWY1aDRma043QnJBdnhqcnVVYkxYb1JwazJsM3dMX1hYRldRM2IzRHFNYURfNW1lSFY0R0RDSWtJeG1ER19jOE4tcm5sNzBpZjN3LTZjZ1N3VnI3LWNTVHBxeFBzTFBlX2Rzc2Q5anhvcHpKdG9Ta2tWZkVpRXVROGl1TU1PUkJsd1dpNkNR?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;&lt;b&gt;It’s a Beast of a time in Washington, D.C. &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Donald Trump’s reality show is full of new characters, plot twists, and cliffhangers, and the Daily Beast will navigate you through it. The 47th president won’t need to drain The Swamp. It’s all leaking here … &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.thedailybeast.com/newsletters/the-swamp/" rel="" title="https://www.thedailybeast.com/newsletters/the-swamp/"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;b&gt;Sign up here for the next unmissable installment of The Swamp&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;b&gt;.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;&lt;b&gt;And in an exclusive extract from this week’s edition, read about RFK Jr’s eye-popping measles flub.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;It had been a long working weekend at Mar-a-Lago and, to be fair, it’s hard to spend time with the president only to be abandoned to make your own way home.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;All &lt;a href="https://elink.thedailybeast.com/click/39261347.13424/aHR0cHM6Ly93d3cudGhlZGFpbHliZWFzdC5jb20va2V5d29yZC9yb2JlcnQtZi1rZW5uZWR5LWpyLz9zb3VyY2U9dGhlLXN3YW1wJnVzZXJfZW1haWxBPTk5NDcxMGQ1YzE0ZGI5ZDUwMGI5NTE5ZjY1NWJhM2M4JnVzZXJfZW1haWxCPTM2OWMyYjM3OTNkODlkOGU3MjNjM2Y5MGQ5NDBlZjk5YjE3NTg0ODlhYmE3MjdmOTIzYmNlMjJlMGI2ZDU5NWE/610014cd6b73c1236d5207aaB5b13a5d3" rel="" title="https://elink.thedailybeast.com/click/39261347.13424/aHR0cHM6Ly93d3cudGhlZGFpbHliZWFzdC5jb20va2V5d29yZC9yb2JlcnQtZi1rZW5uZWR5LWpyLz9zb3VyY2U9dGhlLXN3YW1wJnVzZXJfZW1haWxBPTk5NDcxMGQ1YzE0ZGI5ZDUwMGI5NTE5ZjY1NWJhM2M4JnVzZXJfZW1haWxCPTM2OWMyYjM3OTNkODlkOGU3MjNjM2Y5MGQ5NDBlZjk5YjE3NTg0ODlhYmE3MjdmOTIzYmNlMjJlMGI2ZDU5NWE/610014cd6b73c1236d5207aaB5b13a5d3"&gt;&lt;b&gt;RFK Jr.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt; could do was watch from the terminal window&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;at West Palm Beach Airport as Air Force One took flight at 5:40 p.m. on Sunday as storm clouds gathered overhead.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;It had been exactly 12 minutes between the time &lt;b&gt;Donald Trump&lt;/b&gt;’s motorcade arrived and wheels up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;The Health and Human Services secretary, wearing a pink flamingo tie, would have to wait a lot longer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;He had flown with the president from Washington on Friday afternoon along with &lt;b&gt;Howard Lutnick, Scott Bessent,&lt;/b&gt; and &lt;b&gt;John Arrigo&lt;/b&gt;, Trump’s&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;nominee to be ambassador to Portugal. Now he was left to fly commercial back to D.C.—on one of the airlines &lt;a href="https://elink.thedailybeast.com/click/39261347.13424/aHR0cHM6Ly93d3cudXNhdG9kYXkuY29tL3N0b3J5L3RyYXZlbC9haXJsaW5lLW5ld3MvMjAyNS8wMS8wMy9qZXRibHVlLWZpbmVkLWZsaWdodC1kZWxheXMvNzc0Mjg1NDgwMDcvP3NvdXJjZT10aGUtc3dhbXAmdXNlcl9lbWFpbEE9OTk0NzEwZDVjMTRkYjlkNTAwYjk1MTlmNjU1YmEzYzgmdXNlcl9lbWFpbEI9MzY5YzJiMzc5M2Q4OWQ4ZTcyM2MzZjkwZDk0MGVmOTliMTc1ODQ4OWFiYTcyN2Y5MjNiY2UyMmUwYjZkNTk1YQ/610014cd6b73c1236d5207aaB2bdcf3b0" rel="" title="https://elink.thedailybeast.com/click/39261347.13424/aHR0cHM6Ly93d3cudXNhdG9kYXkuY29tL3N0b3J5L3RyYXZlbC9haXJsaW5lLW5ld3MvMjAyNS8wMS8wMy9qZXRibHVlLWZpbmVkLWZsaWdodC1kZWxheXMvNzc0Mjg1NDgwMDcvP3NvdXJjZT10aGUtc3dhbXAmdXNlcl9lbWFpbEE9OTk0NzEwZDVjMTRkYjlkNTAwYjk1MTlmNjU1YmEzYzgmdXNlcl9lbWFpbEI9MzY5YzJiMzc5M2Q4OWQ4ZTcyM2MzZjkwZDk0MGVmOTliMTc1ODQ4OWFiYTcyN2Y5MjNiY2UyMmUwYjZkNTk1YQ/610014cd6b73c1236d5207aaB2bdcf3b0"&gt;notorious&lt;/a&gt; for flight delays (and dead &lt;a href="https://elink.thedailybeast.com/click/39261347.13424/aHR0cHM6Ly9hYmNuZXdzLmdvLmNvbS9VUy9kZWFkLWpldGJsdWUtbGFuZGluZy1nZWFyLWNvbXBhcnRtZW50LWZsb3JpZGEvc3Rvcnk_aWQ9MTE3NDEwNDA5JnNvdXJjZT10aGUtc3dhbXAmdXNlcl9lbWFpbEE9OTk0NzEwZDVjMTRkYjlkNTAwYjk1MTlmNjU1YmEzYzgmdXNlcl9lbWFpbEI9MzY5YzJiMzc5M2Q4OWQ4ZTcyM2MzZjkwZDk0MGVmOTliMTc1ODQ4OWFiYTcyN2Y5MjNiY2UyMmUwYjZkNTk1YQ/610014cd6b73c1236d5207aaB1a73ca20" rel="" title="https://elink.thedailybeast.com/click/39261347.13424/aHR0cHM6Ly9hYmNuZXdzLmdvLmNvbS9VUy9kZWFkLWpldGJsdWUtbGFuZGluZy1nZWFyLWNvbXBhcnRtZW50LWZsb3JpZGEvc3Rvcnk_aWQ9MTE3NDEwNDA5JnNvdXJjZT10aGUtc3dhbXAmdXNlcl9lbWFpbEE9OTk0NzEwZDVjMTRkYjlkNTAwYjk1MTlmNjU1YmEzYzgmdXNlcl9lbWFpbEI9MzY5YzJiMzc5M2Q4OWQ4ZTcyM2MzZjkwZDk0MGVmOTliMTc1ODQ4OWFiYTcyN2Y5MjNiY2UyMmUwYjZkNTk1YQ/610014cd6b73c1236d5207aaB1a73ca20"&gt;stowaways&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="c-media-item b-article-body__image"&gt;&lt;img data-chromatic="ignore" alt="Robert F. Kennedy Jr." class="c-image" loading="lazy" src="https://www.thedailybeast.com/resizer/v2/ZPP2LWD3KJEE5PSKOMVEA2LOXM.jpg?auth=ccdf57659f70cf801dda4711a82c97c47cc6b8bd026a26476e8e2471538da11f&amp;amp;width=800&amp;amp;height=1066" srcset="https://www.thedailybeast.com/resizer/v2/ZPP2LWD3KJEE5PSKOMVEA2LOXM.jpg?auth=ccdf57659f70cf801dda4711a82c97c47cc6b8bd026a26476e8e2471538da11f&amp;amp;width=274&amp;amp;height=365 274w, https://www.thedailybeast.com/resizer/v2/ZPP2LWD3KJEE5PSKOMVEA2LOXM.jpg?auth=ccdf57659f70cf801dda4711a82c97c47cc6b8bd026a26476e8e2471538da11f&amp;amp;width=400&amp;amp;height=533 400w, https://www.thedailybeast.com/resizer/v2/ZPP2LWD3KJEE5PSKOMVEA2LOXM.jpg?auth=ccdf57659f70cf801dda4711a82c97c47cc6b8bd026a26476e8e2471538da11f&amp;amp;width=768&amp;amp;height=1023 768w, https://www.thedailybeast.com/resizer/v2/ZPP2LWD3KJEE5PSKOMVEA2LOXM.jpg?auth=ccdf57659f70cf801dda4711a82c97c47cc6b8bd026a26476e8e2471538da11f&amp;amp;width=1024&amp;amp;height=1364 1024w, https://www.thedailybeast.com/resizer/v2/ZPP2LWD3KJEE5PSKOMVEA2LOXM.jpg?auth=ccdf57659f70cf801dda4711a82c97c47cc6b8bd026a26476e8e2471538da11f&amp;amp;width=1440&amp;amp;height=1918 1440w"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="c-media-item__fig-caption"&gt;&lt;span class="c-media-item__caption"&gt;The HHS secretary waited in the airport after being booted from Air Force One to find his own way home. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="c-media-item__credit"&gt;The Swamp. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;But the brief weather window was taken by Air Force One and Kennedy’s 6:34 p.m. JetBlue Flight 2534 was delayed over four hours. That left plenty of time to read “The Let Them Theory” while standing at the bookstore and gulp down some ultraprocessed airport snacks. Sure, RFK Jr. thinks that food is &lt;a href="https://elink.thedailybeast.com/click/39261347.13424/aHR0cHM6Ly93d3cudGhlZGFpbHliZWFzdC5jb20vcm9iZXJ0LWYta2VubmVkeS1qci10cmFzaGVzLWRvbmFsZC10cnVtcHMtZmFzdC1mb29kLWRpZXQtanVzdC1wb2lzb24vP3NvdXJjZT10aGUtc3dhbXAmdXNlcl9lbWFpbEE9OTk0NzEwZDVjMTRkYjlkNTAwYjk1MTlmNjU1YmEzYzgmdXNlcl9lbWFpbEI9MzY5YzJiMzc5M2Q4OWQ4ZTcyM2MzZjkwZDk0MGVmOTliMTc1ODQ4OWFiYTcyN2Y5MjNiY2UyMmUwYjZkNTk1YQ/610014cd6b73c1236d5207aaB41f28175" rel="" title="https://elink.thedailybeast.com/click/39261347.13424/aHR0cHM6Ly93d3cudGhlZGFpbHliZWFzdC5jb20vcm9iZXJ0LWYta2VubmVkeS1qci10cmFzaGVzLWRvbmFsZC10cnVtcHMtZmFzdC1mb29kLWRpZXQtanVzdC1wb2lzb24vP3NvdXJjZT10aGUtc3dhbXAmdXNlcl9lbWFpbEE9OTk0NzEwZDVjMTRkYjlkNTAwYjk1MTlmNjU1YmEzYzgmdXNlcl9lbWFpbEI9MzY5YzJiMzc5M2Q4OWQ4ZTcyM2MzZjkwZDk0MGVmOTliMTc1ODQ4OWFiYTcyN2Y5MjNiY2UyMmUwYjZkNTk1YQ/610014cd6b73c1236d5207aaB41f28175"&gt;“poison,”&lt;/a&gt; but eventually you break down and eat the french fries.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;By chance, a friendly face was waiting at the gate for the same plane. Theater producer &lt;b&gt;Victoria Leacock Hoffman&lt;/b&gt; had been at Miami and Palm Beach launch events for her husband &lt;b&gt;Cal&lt;/b&gt;’s (nephew of &lt;a href="https://elink.thedailybeast.com/click/39261347.13424/aHR0cHM6Ly93d3cudGhlZGFpbHliZWFzdC5jb20va2V5d29yZC9kdXN0aW4taG9mZm1hbi8_c291cmNlPXRoZS1zd2FtcCZ1c2VyX2VtYWlsQT05OTQ3MTBkNWMxNGRiOWQ1MDBiOTUxOWY2NTViYTNjOCZ1c2VyX2VtYWlsQj0zNjljMmIzNzkzZDg5ZDhlNzIzYzNmOTBkOTQwZWY5OWIxNzU4NDg5YWJhNzI3ZjkyM2JjZTIyZTBiNmQ1OTVh/610014cd6b73c1236d5207aaBebd2a3ba" rel="" title="https://elink.thedailybeast.com/click/39261347.13424/aHR0cHM6Ly93d3cudGhlZGFpbHliZWFzdC5jb20va2V5d29yZC9kdXN0aW4taG9mZm1hbi8_c291cmNlPXRoZS1zd2FtcCZ1c2VyX2VtYWlsQT05OTQ3MTBkNWMxNGRiOWQ1MDBiOTUxOWY2NTViYTNjOCZ1c2VyX2VtYWlsQj0zNjljMmIzNzkzZDg5ZDhlNzIzYzNmOTBkOTQwZWY5OWIxNzU4NDg5YWJhNzI3ZjkyM2JjZTIyZTBiNmQ1OTVh/610014cd6b73c1236d5207aaBebd2a3ba"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dustin Hoffman&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;) new book, &lt;i&gt;Easy to Slip&lt;/i&gt;. (The book is about a young man whose uncle is a famous actor which affects the entire family.) &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;Victoria and Bobby Jr. used to run in the same New York City circles. Back in the day, her filmmaker father, &lt;b&gt;Richard Leacock&lt;/b&gt;, made two movies with &lt;b&gt;RFK&lt;/b&gt;– &lt;i&gt;Primary in Crisis&lt;/i&gt; and &lt;i&gt;Hickory Hill.&lt;/i&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;A very large man running security on the Kennedy scion let her approach. After reconnecting with her old acquaintance, Victoria decided a word of warning might be useful for her fellow stranded passenger at Gate 8.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;“Be careful handling the measles outbreak,” she cautioned. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;Probably tired of batting away the chicken goujons at Mar-a-Lago, America’s health chief forgot all the glossy spin that got him through the confirmation process and shrugged. A Kennedy shrug.. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;“When I was a kid,” he told Victoria, “two million people got [measles] every year…and only 300 died.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;&lt;i&gt;Only!&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;And then he was off, finally, to his emergency exit row seat on the late, late flight to make his choice between Popchips, Classic Grahams or a Chewy Chocolate Granola Bar. No prizes for guessing his choice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.thedailybeast.com/newsletters/the-swamp/" target="_self" rel="" title="https://www.thedailybeast.com/newsletters/the-swamp/"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;b&gt;Sign up here for the next set of secrets from The Swamp&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;b&gt; direct to your inbox.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Daily Beast</author><pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 18:27:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijgFBVV95cUxOYWY1aDRma043QnJBdnhqcnVVYkxYb1JwazJsM3dMX1hYRldRM2IzRHFNYURfNW1lSFY0R0RDSWtJeG1ER19jOE4tcm5sNzBpZjN3LTZjZ1N3VnI3LWNTVHBxeFBzTFBlX2Rzc2Q5anhvcHpKdG9Ta2tWZkVpRXVROGl1TU1PUkJsd1dpNkNR</guid></item><item><title>I Was Taking More Than 20 Supplements a Day for My Health. It Was Actually Making Me Sicker - AOL.com</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMic0FVX3lxTE5HdXVDaGhFdTlwb1ZfaFVlN0VPZXlBTHhkZVZNc0VTVjhiSGt6Ri1OUjhVVHlNM2NhSXBSX1ZQMUxqdFEtakZEQmZNcGNNXzI3bEFJcTNSMGJfVWhpcG03a045TUZpUHBpM28zMm5GUFpoSjA?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="caas-body"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Reviewed by Dietitian Maria Laura Haddad-Garcia&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure"&gt;&lt;div class="caption-wrapper caption-aligned-with-image"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption-collapse"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Design elements: Abbey Littlejohn and Getty Images. EatingWell design.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"&lt;strong&gt;Key Takeaways&lt;/strong&gt;"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class="caas-list caas-list-bullet"&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;1 in 3 adults in the U.S. and Europe take at least one supplement a day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;While they can support better health, taking too many supplements can lead to life-threatening side effects.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Consult your primary health care provider before taking a new supplement.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;St. John’s wort. Iron. Calcium. At the peak of my illness with Lyme disease, my mother doled out more than 20 supplements a day, which I had to choke down with the meager meals I could force myself to eat. I wasn’t just suffering from typical Lyme disease symptoms—the bacteria that causes the infection had spread to my central nervous system, causing what is called neurological Lyme disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In addition to seeing a Lyme specialist and a neurologist, I regularly saw a naturopath who prescribed the boatload of supplements that he assured us would help me to walk again and recover my flagging cognitive function. But it turns out that megadosing me on vitamins I was already getting from food may have been making me sicker than I already was.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That was more than 20 years ago. Today, the science of supplements has been more carefully examined. With hindsight on my side, I wondered—was it my Lyme disease, the excessive supplementation or a combination thereof that kept me totally disabled for almost seven years?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fortunately, not everyone can relate to the extent of my experience. And while most people aren’t taking 20 supplements daily, I wouldn't be surprised if some come close.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We are inundated with talk of dietary supplements daily. Maybe it’s products being hawked by a peppy wellness influencer in your social feed, or on the ad break during your favorite podcast. Or perhaps family or friends bring up the supposed latest and greatest supplement during dinner. The idea that healthy eating isn’t enough is everywhere.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Can supplements be helpful when used appropriately, or should I toss the few that I still keep in my cupboard and instead stick to a balanced diet to get the nutrients my body needs? And what does science say are the real dangers of taking too many supplements? I talked to a medical toxicologist, a hepatologist (liver specialist) and a dietitian to understand more, and to avoid further pitfalls of the booming yet unchecked supplement industry.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Understanding Supplements and Their Role&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;What exactly qualifies as a dietary supplement? In essence, it’s anything you ingest that isn’t food or medication. According to the Food and Drug Administration, supplements can include vitamins, including elemental ones like A, B, C and D; botanicals or herbs, elderberry or ginger, botanical compounds (think &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/8036275/greens-powder-benefits/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:green powders;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;green powders&lt;/a&gt;); minerals, such as calcium and magnesium; and even live microbials, usually referred to as “probiotics.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“When we’re looking and thinking about supplementation, it’s to enhance the diet; so if there is a true deficiency, then supplementation would be warranted. It should not replace having a healthy diet,” explains &lt;a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/beth-czerwony-a879b629a/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Beth Czerwony, M.S., RD, CSOWM, LD;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Beth Czerwony, M.S., RD, CSOWM, LD&lt;/a&gt;, an outpatient dietitian for the Center for Human Nutrition at the Cleveland Clinic in Ohio.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In other words, nutritional supplements cannot and should not replace meals, or for that matter, medicines. Their name says it all. However, &lt;a href="https://www.houstonmethodist.org/doctor/david-victor/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:David W. Victor III, M.D.;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;David W. Victor III, M.D.&lt;/a&gt;, the interim chief of hepatology at Houston Methodist in Texas, says not to discount their power: “Every supplement can be considered in some way a drug because it is a substance taken for a therapeutic purpose.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Victor explains that, just like food or medicine, supplements are broken down in the digestive tract and absorbed into the bloodstream, which transports them to the appropriate tissues.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The reasons that people take supplements are as varied as our bodies themselves. I did it to potentially fill in dietary gaps, as well as to try to improve my ill health. It’s common to take vitamin C or &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/echinacea-benefits-8773248" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:echinacea;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;echinacea&lt;/a&gt; with the expectation of supporting immunity during cold and flu season. Others might turn to &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/vitamin-b12-benefits-8676211" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:vitamin B12;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;vitamin B12&lt;/a&gt; with the hope that it will boost energy levels or help improve workouts. The common factor is that consumers are seeking something they believe they can’t get from food or from the medications prescribed by their doctors. And the trend is only growing, with 1 in 3 adults in the United States and Europe taking at least one supplement per day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Under current laws, as laid out by the Dietary Supplement Health and Education Act in 1994, part of the Federal Food, Drug and Cosmetic Act, the FDA has no authority over dietary supplements, meaning it doesn’t regulate them. Instead, it’s up to supplement companies to provide oversight and ensure the safety of their products, which comes with some risks. For instance, a supplement may not contain what it says it does, or may contain an ingredient that isn’t listed. Even more so, anyone could sell a supplement without proving its effectiveness. However, if the FDA deems a supplement on the marketplace to be unsafe, it can request that the company recall the product.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;The Dangers of Too Many Supplements&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;While some supplements can be dangerous due to drug interactions or because of a person’s underlying health problems, usually, their toxicity lies in taking too many of them. As &lt;a href="https://www.vcuhealth.org/find-a-provider/john-downs" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:John W. Downs, M.D., M.P.H., FACP, FACOEM;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;John W. Downs, M.D., M.P.H., FACP, FACOEM&lt;/a&gt;, director of the Virginia Poison Center at VCU Health in Virginia, puts it, “Just like with all medications, it is important to recognize that more isn’t always better. Excessive intake of certain vitamins and nutritional supplements can be just as harmful as taking medications in excess of the prescribed doses.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And the &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/8053927/these-supplements-can-be-toxic-if-you-take-too-much/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:supplements that can be toxic;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;supplements that can be toxic&lt;/a&gt; when you take too much of them aren’t just obscure ingredients. Downs says that they include the basics. For example, a high dose of &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/what-is-vitamin-a-and-why-do-you-need-it-11702329" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:vitamin A;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;vitamin A&lt;/a&gt; could cause liver damage or increased pressure on the brain. Many of us don’t get enough vitamin D from food, and it’s estimated that around 40% of the U.S. population may have &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/7950001/signs-you-might-have-a-vitamin-d-deficiency/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:vitamin D insufficiency;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;vitamin D insufficiency&lt;/a&gt;. But taking too much can lead to elevated serum calcium concentrations, which can cause kidney dysfunction and mental status changes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Vitamin A and vitamin D are both fat-soluble. Czerwony says that means your body stores them in fat cells, rather than getting rid of them through urination, as with water-soluble ones (including most &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/8053927/these-supplements-can-be-toxic-if-you-take-too-much/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:B vitamins;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;B vitamins&lt;/a&gt; and vitamin C). Fat-soluble vitamins can accumulate in fat stores over time and result in “super-high levels and side effects,” she says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Since Victor deals with the liver every day, he’s especially well-positioned to have seen which supplements can wreak havoc. While &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/turmeric-benefits-8785974" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:turmeric supplements;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;turmeric supplements&lt;/a&gt; have been shown to be pretty safe in the short term for most people, he mentions this supplement and its active compound, curcumin, have caused liver damage in some people at doses as low as 500 milligrams daily (the lowest dose commonly found in turmeric supplements). It’s important to note that turmeric supplements contain much higher concentrations of curcumin compared to the spice per se. Plus, curcumin in food is much less bioavailable (how much is absorbed and used by your body) compared to the supplement.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another example is green tea. Green tea extract, reputed for &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/green-tea-and-antioxidant-absorption-8649839" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:its antioxidant properties;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;its antioxidant properties&lt;/a&gt;, may also cause injury to the liver when taken in excess, he notes. An excessive dose of green tea extract seems to be over 800 mg per day (or drinking 24 cups of green tea).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“It is also important to note that nutritional supplements sometimes contain unexpected ingredients which may also contribute to adverse health effects,” adds Downs. Reading labels carefully can help with this, but going back to the lack of FDA regulation, it’s also important to be judicious with which supplements you choose. Even more important? Working with your primary health care provider, who can not only tell you of any potential issues but also monitor how your supplements affect your body with blood work.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In my years of over-supplementing, I often couldn’t keep food down. Czerwony suggests that this might have been a symptom of my excessive consumption. “Most often, it’s going to be things like nausea or vomiting,” she explains. “Some people end up having diarrhea and headaches, and depending on whether they’re [taking] a fat-soluble vitamin, it could take some time to come on. It takes a little bit more time to accumulate in your system.” Gastrointestinal distress and headaches are the most common symptoms of chronic toxicity, but symptoms can vary from supplement to supplement.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And what if you take prescription medications? Our experts all agreed that there can be potentially catastrophic interactions. “St. John’s wort is known to interact with some of the enzymes in the liver, changing the concentration of many medicines in the body, so it should be used with great caution,” says Victor.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“St. John’s wort can also interact with other medications for depression, leading to a potentially life-threatening condition called serotonin toxicity,” adds Downs. Some symptoms of serotonin syndrome (or serotonin toxicity) include agitation, tachycardia and hallucinations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Czerwony points out that St. John’s wort can also decrease the efficacy of antibiotics, a trait it shares with many other supplements, including magnesium, calcium, iron and vitamins A, C and D. And antibiotics aren’t the only medications that can be weakened with supplements. She also mentions that she’s seen cancer patients who try to power up their immunity with supplements, only to counteract the effects of their chemotherapy drugs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;How to Safely Take Supplements&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Is there such a thing as safe supplement use? Yes, but it should take place under a doctor’s care. Here are some tips to do it safely:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class="caas-list caas-list-bullet"&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Choose supplements that have been independently verified: &lt;/strong&gt;Downs recommends making sure that your supplements come from reputable sources and that you check with your doctor or registered dietitian about the right dosage for you. As mentioned above, the FDA doesn’t regulate supplements nor verify that what they claim is true. That’s why it’s important to “Look for labels with the NSF or USP certification logos, which indicate that the supplement has undergone an independent review for quality control and consistency. And as always, if it sounds too good to be true, it probably is,” he cautions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Get bloodwork done when you start a new supplement: &lt;/strong&gt;“You can monitor the effect of a supplement on the liver by checking labs,” says Victor, who recommends doing blood work a month to 12 weeks after starting a new supplement. “Patients should be open with their doctor about what supplements they’re taking so that we can all make sure that we are aware of what could be causing liver inflammation,” he continues.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Be aware of available resources:&lt;/strong&gt; The National Institutes of Health maintains a website, &lt;a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/books/NBK547852/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:LiverTox;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;LiverTox&lt;/a&gt;, that allows patients to check the toxicity of their supplements. You can also reach your local certified poison control center at 1-800-222-1222 to discuss potential drug-and-supplement interactions, too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h2&gt;The Bottom Line&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Used correctly and under the oversight of a medical professional, nutritional supplements can be an integral enhancement to a balanced diet. For example, the depression that made my illness even more difficult to treat may have been improved with a safe, balanced vitamin D regimen. But taking more than 20 supplements a day was not the answer, especially when several of the ones I took likely lessened the efficacy of my antibiotic.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Supplementation should never replace a healthy diet; it’s just to enhance it,” says Czerwony. “You should not feel like you can just eat whatever you want and then just take a bunch of supplements and think that you’re going to be OK.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s all in the name—supplements are just that: something to supplement (or fill gaps) and build upon a healthy diet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Read the original article on &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/too-many-supplements-11708988" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:EATINGWELL;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;EATINGWELL&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>AOL.com</author><pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 17:10:41 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMic0FVX3lxTE5HdXVDaGhFdTlwb1ZfaFVlN0VPZXlBTHhkZVZNc0VTVjhiSGt6Ri1OUjhVVHlNM2NhSXBSX1ZQMUxqdFEtakZEQmZNcGNNXzI3bEFJcTNSMGJfVWhpcG03a045TUZpUHBpM28zMm5GUFpoSjA</guid></item><item><title>I Was Taking More Than 20 Supplements a Day for My Health. It Was Actually Making Me Sicker - EatingWell</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiZ0FVX3lxTE9lQjZpY0t5WEdQOVh5ZVNHcTQ4b3kzUGVLQnBRNXliRWZnazQ0bHBVT0FzRVFtSVZmdmNwUzRfc2luNXdJZFh1RjZWS2plMW9DeDZBYmYwZW9va0xFU2pjU0Y5ZUxSZ1E?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-page_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-page mntl-block structured-content" data-sc-sticky-offset="90" data-sc-ad-label-height="24" data-sc-ad-track-spacing="100" data-sc-min-track-height="250" data-sc-max-track-height="600" data-sc-breakpoint="50em" data-sc-load-immediate="4" data-sc-content-positions="[1, 1250, 1550, 1950, 2350, 2750, 3150, 3550, 3950]" data-bind-scroll-on-start="true"&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-block_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-callout mntl-sc-block-universal-callout theme-blockquote" data-tracking-id="mntl-sc-block-callout" data-tracking-container="true"&gt;
&lt;div class="mntl-sc-block-universal-callout__body"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Takeaways&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;1 in 3 adults in the U.S. and Europe take at least one supplement a day.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;While they can support better health, taking too many supplements can lead to life-threatening side effects. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Consult your primary health care provider before taking a new supplement.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="theme-blockquote__author_1-0" class="comp theme-blockquote__author mntl-text-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_2-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; St. John’s wort. Iron. Calcium. At the peak of my illness with Lyme disease, my mother doled out more than 20 supplements a day, which I had to choke down with the meager meals I could force myself to eat. I wasn’t just suffering from typical Lyme disease symptoms—the bacteria that causes the infection had spread to my central nervous system, causing what is called neurological Lyme disease.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_3-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_4-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; In addition to seeing a Lyme specialist and a neurologist, I regularly saw a naturopath who prescribed the boatload of supplements that he assured us would help me to walk again and recover my flagging cognitive function. But it turns out that megadosing me on vitamins I was already getting from food may have been making me sicker than I already was. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_5-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_6-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; That was more than 20 years ago. Today, the science of supplements has been more carefully examined. With hindsight on my side, I wondered—was it my Lyme disease, the excessive supplementation or a combination thereof that kept me totally disabled for almost seven years?
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_7-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_8-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Fortunately, not everyone can relate to the extent of my experience. And while most people aren’t taking 20 supplements daily, I wouldn't be surprised if some come close. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_9-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_10-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; We are inundated with talk of dietary supplements daily. Maybe it’s products being hawked by a peppy wellness influencer in your social feed, or on the ad break during your favorite podcast. Or perhaps family or friends bring up the supposed latest and greatest supplement during dinner. The idea that healthy eating isn’t enough is everywhere.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_11-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_12-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Can supplements be helpful when used appropriately, or should I toss the few that I still keep in my cupboard and instead stick to a balanced diet to get the nutrients my body needs? And what does science say are the real dangers of taking too many supplements? I talked to a medical toxicologist, a hepatologist (liver specialist) and a dietitian to understand more, and to avoid further pitfalls of the booming yet unchecked supplement industry.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_13-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-understanding-supplements-and-their-role"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_14-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; Understanding Supplements and Their Role &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_15-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; What exactly qualifies as a dietary supplement? In essence, it’s anything you ingest that isn’t food or medication. According to the Food and Drug Administration, supplements can include vitamins, including elemental ones like A, B, C and D; botanicals or herbs, elderberry or ginger, botanical compounds (think &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/8036275/greens-powder-benefits/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;green powders&lt;/a&gt;); minerals, such as calcium and magnesium; and even live microbials, usually referred to as “probiotics.”&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="2"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_16-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_17-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; “When we’re looking and thinking about supplementation, it’s to enhance the diet; so if there is a true deficiency, then supplementation would be warranted. It should not replace having a healthy diet,” explains &lt;a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/beth-czerwony-a879b629a/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Beth Czerwony, M.S., RD, CSOWM, LD&lt;/a&gt;, an outpatient dietitian for the Center for Human Nutrition at the Cleveland Clinic in Ohio.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="1"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_18-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_19-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; In other words, nutritional supplements cannot and should not replace meals, or for that matter, medicines. Their name says it all. However, &lt;a href="https://www.houstonmethodist.org/doctor/david-victor/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;David W. Victor III, M.D.&lt;/a&gt;, the interim chief of hepatology at Houston Methodist in Texas, says not to discount their power: “Every supplement can be considered in some way a drug because it is a substance taken for a therapeutic purpose.”
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_20-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_21-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Victor explains that, just like food or medicine, supplements are broken down in the digestive tract and absorbed into the bloodstream, which transports them to the appropriate tissues. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_22-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_23-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; The reasons that people take supplements are as varied as our bodies themselves. I did it to potentially fill in dietary gaps, as well as to try to improve my ill health. It’s common to take vitamin C or &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/echinacea-benefits-8773248" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;echinacea&lt;/a&gt; with the expectation of supporting immunity during cold and flu season. Others might turn to &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/vitamin-b12-benefits-8676211" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;vitamin B12&lt;/a&gt; with the hope that it will boost energy levels or help improve workouts. The common factor is that consumers are seeking something they believe they can’t get from food or from the medications prescribed by their doctors. And the trend is only growing, with 1 in 3 adults in the United States and Europe taking at least one supplement per day.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="3"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_24-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_25-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Under current laws, as laid out by the Dietary Supplement Health and Education Act in 1994, part of the Federal Food, Drug and Cosmetic Act, the FDA has no authority over dietary supplements, meaning it doesn’t regulate them.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="4"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Instead, it’s up to supplement companies to provide oversight and ensure the safety of their products, which comes with some risks. For instance, a supplement may not contain what it says it does, or may contain an ingredient that isn’t listed. Even more so, anyone could sell a supplement without proving its effectiveness. However, if the FDA deems a supplement on the marketplace to be unsafe, it can request that the company recall the product.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="5"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_26-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-the-dangers-of-too-many-supplements"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_27-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; The Dangers of Too Many Supplements &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_28-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; While some supplements can be dangerous due to drug interactions or because of a person’s underlying health problems, usually, their toxicity lies in taking too many of them. As &lt;a href="https://www.vcuhealth.org/find-a-provider/john-downs" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;John W. Downs, M.D., M.P.H., FACP, FACOEM&lt;/a&gt;, director of the Virginia Poison Center at VCU Health in Virginia, puts it, “Just like with all medications, it is important to recognize that more isn’t always better. Excessive intake of certain vitamins and nutritional supplements can be just as harmful as taking medications in excess of the prescribed doses.”
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_29-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_30-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; And the &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/8053927/these-supplements-can-be-toxic-if-you-take-too-much/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;supplements that can be toxic&lt;/a&gt; when you take too much of them aren’t just obscure ingredients. Downs says that they include the basics. For example, a high dose of &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/what-is-vitamin-a-and-why-do-you-need-it-11702329" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;vitamin A&lt;/a&gt; could cause liver damage or increased pressure on the brain. Many of us don’t get enough vitamin D from food, and it’s estimated that around 40% of the U.S. population may have &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/7950001/signs-you-might-have-a-vitamin-d-deficiency/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="3"&gt;vitamin D insufficiency&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="7"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; But taking too much can lead to elevated serum calcium concentrations, which can cause kidney dysfunction and mental status changes. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_31-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_32-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Vitamin A and vitamin D are both fat-soluble. Czerwony says that means your body stores them in fat cells, rather than getting rid of them through urination, as with water-soluble ones (including most &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/8053927/these-supplements-can-be-toxic-if-you-take-too-much/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;B vitamins&lt;/a&gt; and vitamin C).&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="6"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Fat-soluble vitamins can accumulate in fat stores over time and result in “super-high levels and side effects,” she says.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_33-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_34-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Since Victor deals with the liver every day, he’s especially well-positioned to have seen which supplements can wreak havoc. While &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/turmeric-benefits-8785974" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;turmeric supplements&lt;/a&gt; have been shown to be pretty safe in the short term for most people, he mentions this supplement and its active compound, curcumin, have caused liver damage in some people at doses as low as 500 milligrams daily (the lowest dose commonly found in turmeric supplements).&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="8"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; It’s important to note that turmeric supplements contain much higher concentrations of curcumin compared to the spice per se. Plus, curcumin in food is much less bioavailable (how much is absorbed and used by your body) compared to the supplement.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_35-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_36-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Another example is green tea. Green tea extract, reputed for &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/green-tea-and-antioxidant-absorption-8649839" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;its antioxidant properties&lt;/a&gt;, may also cause injury to the liver when taken in excess, he notes. An excessive dose of green tea extract seems to be over 800 mg per day (or drinking 24 cups of green tea).&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="9"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_37-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_38-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; “It is also important to note that nutritional supplements sometimes contain unexpected ingredients which may also contribute to adverse health effects,” adds Downs. Reading labels carefully can help with this, but going back to the lack of FDA regulation, it’s also important to be judicious with which supplements you choose. Even more important? Working with your primary health care provider, who can not only tell you of any potential issues but also monitor how your supplements affect your body with blood work. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_39-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_40-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; In my years of over-supplementing, I often couldn’t keep food down. Czerwony suggests that this might have been a symptom of my excessive consumption. “Most often, it’s going to be things like nausea or vomiting,” she explains. “Some people end up having diarrhea and headaches, and depending on whether they’re [taking] a fat-soluble vitamin, it could take some time to come on. It takes a little bit more time to accumulate in your system.” Gastrointestinal distress and headaches are the most common symptoms of chronic toxicity, but symptoms can vary from supplement to supplement. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_41-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_42-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; And what if you take prescription medications? Our experts all agreed that there can be potentially catastrophic interactions. “St. John’s wort is known to interact with some of the enzymes in the liver, changing the concentration of many medicines in the body, so it should be used with great caution,” says Victor.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="10"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_43-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_44-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; “St. John’s wort can also interact with other medications for depression, leading to a potentially life-threatening condition called serotonin toxicity,” adds Downs. Some symptoms of serotonin syndrome (or serotonin toxicity) include agitation, tachycardia and hallucinations.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="10"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_45-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_46-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Czerwony points out that St. John’s wort can also decrease the efficacy of antibiotics, a trait it shares with many other supplements, including magnesium, calcium, iron and vitamins A, C and D. And antibiotics aren’t the only medications that can be weakened with supplements. She also mentions that she’s seen cancer patients who try to power up their immunity with supplements, only to counteract the effects of their chemotherapy drugs.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="11"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_47-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-how-to-safely-take-supplements"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_48-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; How to Safely Take Supplements &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_49-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Is there such a thing as safe supplement use? Yes, but it should take place under a doctor’s care. Here are some tips to do it safely:
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_50-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_51-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Choose supplements that have been independently verified: &lt;/strong&gt;Downs recommends making sure that your supplements come from reputable sources and that you check with your doctor or registered dietitian about the right dosage for you. As mentioned above, the FDA doesn’t regulate supplements nor verify that what they claim is true. That’s why it’s important to “Look for labels with the NSF or USP certification logos, which indicate that the supplement has undergone an independent review for quality control and consistency. And as always, if it sounds too good to be true, it probably is,” he cautions. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Get bloodwork done when you start a new supplement: &lt;/strong&gt;“You can monitor the effect of a supplement on the liver by checking labs,” says Victor, who recommends doing blood work a month to 12 weeks after starting a new supplement. “Patients should be open with their doctor about what supplements they’re taking so that we can all make sure that we are aware of what could be causing liver inflammation,” he continues.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-sc-block-adslot-inline"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Be aware of available resources:&lt;/strong&gt; The National Institutes of Health maintains a website, &lt;a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/books/NBK547852/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;LiverTox&lt;/a&gt;, that allows patients to check the toxicity of their supplements. You can also reach your local certified poison control center at 1-800-222-1222 to discuss potential drug-and-supplement interactions, too.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_52-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_54-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-the-bottom-line"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_55-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; The Bottom Line &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_56-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Used correctly and under the oversight of a medical professional, nutritional supplements can be an integral enhancement to a balanced diet. For example, the depression that made my illness even more difficult to treat may have been improved with a safe, balanced vitamin D regimen.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="12"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; But taking more than 20 supplements a day was not the answer, especially when several of the ones I took likely lessened the efficacy of my antibiotic.  
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_57-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_58-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; “Supplementation should never replace a healthy diet; it’s just to enhance it,” says Czerwony. “You should not feel like you can just eat whatever you want and then just take a bunch of supplements and think that you’re going to be OK.” 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_59-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_60-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; It’s all in the name—supplements are just that: something to supplement (or fill gaps) and build upon a healthy diet.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>EatingWell</author><pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 16:11:40 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiZ0FVX3lxTE9lQjZpY0t5WEdQOVh5ZVNHcTQ4b3kzUGVLQnBRNXliRWZnazQ0bHBVT0FzRVFtSVZmdmNwUzRfc2luNXdJZFh1RjZWS2plMW9DeDZBYmYwZW9va0xFU2pjU0Y5ZUxSZ1E</guid></item><item><title>Does Added Protein Really Enhance The Nutrition of Your Food? - ScienceAlert</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMikwFBVV95cUxQa2ZIS1AwZ2tBWF9LYXpkbU1USl9sTHJQS0dLRVA5LUJNVm1BNldvVmNfTWEyNms3X2pzRFNKa1I4VGhuUzJvNlhNTmlXVjBQUjR2M0J1Z3BZelF0SjM2b2xLS2ZYYVV4R3E1elRZVjNKMlBjTzhjamYzQjh0aDVhQVJnVExpYUFVMDhpVy0zY2dsR3M?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Protein intake dominates fitness advice. Whether you want to build muscle, improve your fitness or watch your weight, the common advice handed out by everyone from fitness influencers to doctors is that we need more protein.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But while protein does play an essential role in maintaining our &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/38840697/"&gt;muscle mass and overall health&lt;/a&gt;, all this increased attention on the importance of protein &lt;a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/food-and-drink/high-protein-food-diet-recipes-dr-rupy-aujla-b2720439.html"&gt;in the media&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.menshealth.com/uk/nutrition/a754243/how-much-protein-should-i-eat-to-build-muscle/"&gt;fitness circles&lt;/a&gt; has sparked a surge in products marketed specifically for their protein content.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some chocolate bars, ice cream, pizza,  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/how-does-caffeine-wake-you-up" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73115" data-postid="157246" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;coffee&lt;/a&gt;, and even alcoholic beverages now &lt;a href="https://www.bevindustry.com/articles/97003-protein-flexes-its-muscles-as-consumers-look-to-add-more-protein-to-diet"&gt;market themselves as protein foods&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But our enthusiasm for protein might have gone too far. While protein is certainly important for our health, most of us don't need these protein-enhanced foods as a regular feature in our diet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Not to mention that this marketing may lead to a '&lt;a href="https://www.jneb.org/article/S1499-4046(19)30614-1/pdf"&gt;halo effect&lt;/a&gt;', where consumers mistakenly equate high protein content with &lt;a href="https://www.mdpi.com/2304-8158/13/8/1139"&gt;overall nutritional value&lt;/a&gt;. This effect can lead to the perception of protein-rich foods being inherently nutritious – even though many may not be.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Protein is essential for &lt;a href="https://www.clinicalnutritionespen.com/article/S2405-4577(24)00176-1/abstract"&gt;maintaining muscle mass&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC10259402/"&gt;immune function&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nutrition guidelines recommend people aim to eat &lt;a href="https://www.gov.uk/government/publications/coma-reports"&gt;around 0.75 g of protein&lt;/a&gt; per kilogram of body weight. But &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC11329409/"&gt;some evidence suggests&lt;/a&gt; this recommendation &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S1279770723001446?via%3Dihub"&gt;may be an underestimate&lt;/a&gt; – and that the recommendation should be around &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/26960445/"&gt;1.2 g-1.6 g per kg of body weight per day&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There's also a strong body of evidence that suggests the amount of protein we need changes depending on our health. For instance, people need to eat more protein when they're &lt;a href="https://ccforum.biomedcentral.com/articles/10.1186/s13054-021-03693-4"&gt;recovering from an illness&lt;/a&gt;. Research also shows that &lt;a href="https://www.jamda.com/article/S1525-8610(13)00326-5/fulltext"&gt;older adults&lt;/a&gt; should be aiming for at least 1.2 g per kg of body weight in order to combat &lt;a href="https://academic.oup.com/biomedgerontology/article/78/Supplement_1/67/7199271"&gt;age-related muscle loss&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Athletes also need to eat a greater amount of protein to &lt;a href="https://origin.health.gov/sites/default/files/2020-09/2014-june_elevate_health.pdf"&gt;support their training and recovery&lt;/a&gt;. Moreover, with the rising popularity of weight-loss drugs, strategies increasingly emphasise protein intake to &lt;a href="https://diabetesjournals.org/diabetes/article/73/Supplement_1/14-PUB/156089/14-PUB-The-Effect-of-Structured-Intensive"&gt;minimise muscle loss&lt;/a&gt; while losing weight.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But just because protein is good for maintaining muscle mass, that doesn't mean more is better. In fact, it seems that even when we &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC5828430/"&gt;consume large amounts of protein&lt;/a&gt;, only a some of this is actually used by the body.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Most of us probably need a little more protein than current guidelines suggest, but less than is often promoted by wellness influencers on social media (with some even suggesting we need up to &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/wolfcoach_/reel/DCUyAeJIH7K/"&gt;3 g of protein per kg of body weight&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ironically, the necessary amount of protein suggested by emerging evidence (&lt;a href="https://cdnsciencepub.com/doi/full/10.1139/apnm-2020-0760"&gt;1.2 g -1.6 g&lt;/a&gt; per kg of body weight per day) is close to what the &lt;a href="https://www.nutrition.org.uk/news/key-findings-from-ndns-report-for-years-9-to-11-combined/"&gt;average protein consumption already is&lt;/a&gt; in most western countries.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Most people can probably benefit from being more protein aware – not about how much protein they're consuming, but about the quality and frequency of their protein choices. Ideally, we should aim to consume small amounts of protein-rich foods more often during the day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Current evidence suggests around &lt;a href="https://www.nhs.uk/live-well/eat-well/food-guidelines-and-food-labels/the-eatwell-guide/"&gt;20 g-30 g of protein&lt;/a&gt; (around a handful of a protein source) at each meal supports muscle maintenance alongside physical activity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In an ideal world, this protein would come from whole foods (such as nuts, seeds, milk, eggs and legumes). But fortified protein products may have their space as a quick and easy snack – especially for those who may struggle to eat this much protein at each meal. It's important to eat these foods in moderation, however.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Ultra-processed products&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Supermarkets are full of "protein-enhanced" products. But while these products may contain additional protein, they may also contain additional sugars or carbohydrates.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For example, protein milk often contains &lt;a href="https://www.mcgill.ca/oss/article/student-contributors-health-and-nutrition/high-protein-milk-its-not-just-milk-added-protein-powder"&gt;double the protein&lt;/a&gt; of regular milk. It does this by removing water or adding dried milk.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Protein bars are another example. But depending on the brand you choose, alongside their additional protein content they may also be &lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2023/01/12/well/eat/protein-bars.html"&gt;high in sugar&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Many protein-fortified products share another common trait: they fall into the category of &lt;a href="https://www.yahoo.com/news/no-protein-powder-protein-shake-110306908.html?guccounter=1&amp;amp;guce_referrer=aHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuZ29vZ2xlLmNvbS8&amp;amp;guce_referrer_sig=AQAAAIBi1_2t4Yd7wU45o2XrHxyD3cJNSkbxNZ_oKTdMcEmMGC-MTxQOhxAsaKJSedLMG7HhWzJp44aL6nf0UFQwqoevTnMz3JF3uBDhvzwjK6-ACOpIQi4lAkxQFfVHeQ9uMRkmXRTr_O-RCsOAGHpUbIMBm8yZ940rt5vVk1w4_nuA"&gt;ultra-processed foods&lt;/a&gt;. Ultra-processed foods are &lt;a href="https://www.nutrition.org.uk/news/position-statement-on-the-concept-of-ultra-processed-foods-upf"&gt;commercially made products&lt;/a&gt; that include ingredients you wouldn't typically find in your own kitchen.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Research shows regularly consuming ultra-processed foods is consistently linked with &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/38363072/"&gt;poorer health outcomes&lt;/a&gt; – such as cardiovascular diseases and  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/diabetes" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73018" data-postid="157246" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;diabetes&lt;/a&gt;. Current discussions around ultra-processed foods suggests uncertainty regarding whether it's the processing itself, the poor nutritional quality of these foods or the combination of both of these factors that contribute to these negative health outcomes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Another issue with protein-enhanced products is that while they do indeed contain extra protein, some products &lt;a href="https://www.health.harvard.edu/blog/the-scoop-on-protein-powder-2020030918986"&gt;may lack fibre&lt;/a&gt;,  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/what-are-vitamins-and-do-we-really-need-to-take-them" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73116" data-postid="157246" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;vitamins&lt;/a&gt; and essential minerals. A &lt;a href="https://www.clinicalnutritionjournal.com/article/S0261-5614(23)00363-1/abstract"&gt;lack of fibre&lt;/a&gt; in modern diets is currently one of the biggest contributors to population-wide ill-health.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All foods have their place within a balanced diet. But protein is only one component of overall nutritional health. The rise in protein-fortified foods as health foods is concerning.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Protein-enhanced products are occasional foods that might support meeting protein intake, but they should not be mistaken for universally healthy foods. For people looking to reach their protein goals, choose a variety of protein sources, consider the role of convenience foods within the context of whole diet and think about other nutrients like fibre to really maximise health.&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://counter.theconversation.com/content/252236/count.gif?distributor=republish-lightbox-basic" alt="The Conversation" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" loading="lazy"&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/profiles/aisling-pigott-2310358"&gt;Aisling Pigott&lt;/a&gt;, Lecturer, Dietetics, &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/institutions/cardiff-metropolitan-university-1585"&gt;Cardiff Metropolitan University&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This article is republished from &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com"&gt;The Conversation&lt;/a&gt; under a Creative Commons license. Read the &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/protein-is-being-added-to-yoghurt-bread-and-even-coffee-but-is-it-really-good-for-our-health-252236"&gt;original article&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 16:01:15 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikwFBVV95cUxQa2ZIS1AwZ2tBWF9LYXpkbU1USl9sTHJQS0dLRVA5LUJNVm1BNldvVmNfTWEyNms3X2pzRFNKa1I4VGhuUzJvNlhNTmlXVjBQUjR2M0J1Z3BZelF0SjM2b2xLS2ZYYVV4R3E1elRZVjNKMlBjTzhjamYzQjh0aDVhQVJnVExpYUFVMDhpVy0zY2dsR3M</guid></item><item><title>My Husband Says There’s Only One Solution to His “Migraines.” I’m Not So Sure My Jaw Can Handle That. - Slate</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMikgFBVV95cUxOQk1oSGVpUDUzS2Q5Sk4tcUNHNVZKRVJCRkhVYWVYWVgxTnBYRHBORFl2SUszNkx2ZTZHUVhheUMzV003NWh6Yk80SHBCRmFsQmxLc2lqbVNfQUNPZ2VEenZCeUFXbTFBUkhUaDJzb1IwdGxsNnNINU16ajhONDVJaFVndUwwcjNhY2ZOTkRHUTByUQ?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article__content" itemprop="mainEntityOfPage"&gt;
          &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="18" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cm93172tx002lr7m7oecu8qv0@published"&gt;&lt;em&gt;How to Do It is Slate’s sex advice column. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Have a question? &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLSdx34-uOijrCIKqMdw5hnyYahSJBKa4AaSzDCu1nfcpmd3IjA/viewform"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Send it to Jessica and Rich here&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt; It’s anonymous!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="5" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cm931fgu9003e3b72tlo6ei7h@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dear How to Do It,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="79" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cm9318vgn001i3b72mxzxfl95@published"&gt;My husband suffers from serious migraines, but can’t take the medications available to treat them due to his sensitivity to the side effects. Recently he was incapacitated with one, and I asked him if there was anything I could do to help. He responded “How about a blow job?” I laughed about it, but when he said he was serious, I decided to give it a go and see if it made a difference. That’s when things started to get weird.&lt;/p&gt;



  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="82" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cm931aohy002q3b72fcjuabgb@published"&gt;Amazingly, he felt well enough after about 10 minutes to get back to work (he works from home due to his migraine issue). The thing is, now he wants a blow job every time a migraine strikes. Based on his reaction it actually does seem to alleviate his symptoms! The trouble is that he’s been having migraines and requiring my “help” at least three times a day lately. Is there any medical basis for this, or could he be taking advantage of the situation?&lt;br&gt;—An Unlikely Cure&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="4" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cm9318vk7001j3b72w4eyzqkw@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dear An Unlikely Cure,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="61" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cm9318vo6001k3b7215cf33yg@published"&gt;To truly test whether blow jobs are the panacea that he is claiming, you’ll want to have some kind of comparison between how orgasming through other means (like masturbation) does or doesn’t affect his migraines. To put it more bluntly: Why can’t this guy jerk off to relieve his pain? Has he given you an answer for this? Have you asked?&lt;/p&gt;


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="112" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cm9318vs0001l3b7203m1dcwi@published"&gt;To be clear, there is data suggesting that sexual activity may actually alleviate his migraines and/or the pain associated with them. A 2013 &lt;a href="https://journals.sagepub.com/doi/10.1177/0333102413476374"&gt;study&lt;/a&gt; in the journal &lt;em&gt;Cephalalgia&lt;/em&gt; found that 60 percent of survey responders who had experienced sexual activity during a migraine reported that their migraines improved in seeming response. Here “sexual activity” referred to “any sexual intercourse or masturbation with the aim of reaching an orgasm or an orgasm-like feeling.” The study is clear: “the kind of sexual activity did not seem to have any influence on the particular reaction” and “the primary headache associated with sexual activity appears to be independent of the specific sexual methods, e.g. while masturbating.”&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="108" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cm9318vvu001m3b72p2dosjub@published"&gt;This is why I wonder whether he has even tested whether masturbating would serve the same function as your blow jobs. Something tells me no, and that he’s effectively gilding the lily here. Perhaps he has been honest about the pain relief and less so about the necessary means. Incidentally, the study uncovered that men respond to this kind of relief particularly well (73.3 reported sexual activity marking improvement or stopping the migraine attack altogether versus 58 percent of women responders). The study authors postulated that the analgesic effect of sex on migraines may have something to do with the release of endorphins or mere distraction from pain.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="33" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cm9318vz6001n3b72xfp6hssu@published"&gt;If you don’t mind giving him three blow jobs a day, great, go for it. Otherwise, show him the study/this answer and tell him that he’ll do just as well on his own.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="1" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cm93197ha001u3b72cx3oo64n@published"&gt;&lt;span class="slate-paragraph--tombstone"&gt;—Rich&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;h3 class="subhead subhead--none" data-uri="slate.com/_components/subhead/instances/cm9319u7z002b3b723diibk1p@published"&gt;
&lt;p class="subhead__marker"&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
More Advice from Slate

&lt;/h3&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="74" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cm93172tx002or7m7o71wytk6@published"&gt;When I got back together with my now-wife after we broke up, I was surprised to discover that she’d picked up a lot of new skills in the bedroom. When we were together, the sex was good, but now, since she’s been with other people, it’s much, much better. I can’t help but be jealous about this—it drives me crazy to think about her being with other people. &lt;a href="https://slate.com/human-interest/2023/12/girlfriend-sexual-tricks-boyfriends-sex-advice.html"&gt;How can I handle these feelings?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;h3 class="subhead subhead--none" data-uri="slate.com/_components/subhead/instances/cm931fmlz003i3b725k5da9c1@published"&gt;
&lt;p class="subhead__marker"&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
Send Us Your Questions About the Workplace!

&lt;/h3&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="37" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cm931fu4q003n3b72ky7xbbm9@published"&gt;The columnists behind our new advice column, &lt;a href="https://slate.com/advice/good-job"&gt;Good Job&lt;/a&gt;, want to help you navigate your social dynamics at work. Does your colleague constantly bug you after hours? Has an ill-advised work romance gone awry? &lt;a href="https://forms.gle/DEVPsiDdnLHQVX7h7"&gt;Ask us your question here&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;

  

&lt;/div&gt;

      &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Slate</author><pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikgFBVV95cUxOQk1oSGVpUDUzS2Q5Sk4tcUNHNVZKRVJCRkhVYWVYWVgxTnBYRHBORFl2SUszNkx2ZTZHUVhheUMzV003NWh6Yk80SHBCRmFsQmxLc2lqbVNfQUNPZ2VEenZCeUFXbTFBUkhUaDJzb1IwdGxsNnNINU16ajhONDVJaFVndUwwcjNhY2ZOTkRHUTByUQ</guid></item><item><title>Serotonin Signals the Brain’s Best Guess About Future Rewards - Neuroscience News</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMilAFBVV95cUxQNFgxQmdLQkkxWkd0aFFPYVU1ZlRrUXpmQVgyTVNqRnFTQUYtWGc3a1pGUFVYVWoyQmY5UU9TdjF3dng0d21sWVljcnBiLW5oZUZXTkstdlF1SlBCVXlIS0xSekxCUmt1M3FqZG1UWnZnZVM5c2dnV2p0a1IxSzU5eWhzRmZlZnhEenN6MkZ6OUJOcDQy?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content body-color clearfix link-color-wrap"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary: &lt;/strong&gt;A new study reveals that serotonin neurons in the brain may play a crucial role in helping us estimate the value of future rewards. Rather than simply responding to pleasure or pain, serotonin appears to encode a “prospective value” signal—telling the brain how good the near future is likely to be.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Using reinforcement learning models and neural recordings from serotonin-rich regions, researchers found these neurons respond most to unexpected rewards. This insight sheds new light on the complex role of serotonin in decision-making, learning, and emotion, potentially changing how we understand mood disorders and mental health treatments.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Facts:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class="wp-block-list"&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Prospective Value Code:&lt;/strong&gt; Serotonin neurons encode expected future rewards, not just pleasure or pain.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Surprise Matters:&lt;/strong&gt; These neurons are especially activated by unexpected rewards.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Broad Implications:&lt;/strong&gt; Findings could reshape understanding of decision-making and mental health treatments.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Source: &lt;/strong&gt;University of Ottawa&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;In our day-to-day lives, we’re constantly making a slew of decisions from immediate matters to prospects on the far horizon. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But the evolutionary nuts-and-bolts of how our brains weigh these numerous daily decisions and what role is played by the neurotransmitter serotonin has been shrouded in mystery.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="wp-block-image size-full"&gt;&lt;picture fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" class="wp-image-108403"&gt; &lt;source type="image/webp" srcset="https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/04/serotonin-reward-prediction.jpg.webp 1200w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/04/serotonin-reward-prediction-300x200.jpg.webp 300w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/04/serotonin-reward-prediction-770x513.jpg.webp 770w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/04/serotonin-reward-prediction-1155x770.jpg.webp 1155w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/04/serotonin-reward-prediction-370x247.jpg.webp 370w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/04/serotonin-reward-prediction-293x195.jpg.webp 293w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/04/serotonin-reward-prediction-150x100.jpg.webp 150w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px"&gt;&lt;/source&gt; &lt;img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" src="https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/04/serotonin-reward-prediction.jpg" alt="This shows a brain." srcset="https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/04/serotonin-reward-prediction.jpg 1200w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/04/serotonin-reward-prediction-300x200.jpg 300w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/04/serotonin-reward-prediction-770x513.jpg 770w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/04/serotonin-reward-prediction-1155x770.jpg 1155w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/04/serotonin-reward-prediction-370x247.jpg 370w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/04/serotonin-reward-prediction-293x195.jpg 293w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/04/serotonin-reward-prediction-150x100.jpg 150w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px"&gt; &lt;/picture&gt;&lt;figcaption class="wp-element-caption"&gt;While the overall picture was extremely puzzling, he says it was then they realized they might be chasing something promising. Credit: Neuroscience News&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Now, a new study led by an interdisciplinary uOttawa Faculty of Medicine team delivers fascinating findings on this big topic and potentially unravels a hidden aspect of what our nervous system’s extraordinarily complex serotonin system is really doing inside the enigmatic organ in our skulls.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Published in the journal &lt;em&gt;Nature&lt;/em&gt;, this study from a highly impactful international collaboration was considered by one of the expert reviewers who evaluated the work to offer “broad implications across neuroscience, psychology, and psychiatry, enhancing our understanding of serotonin’s role in mood regulation, learning, and motivated behavior.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The team’s innovative work merges ideas from reinforcement learning (RL) theory – used in neuroscience to better understand learning, behavior, and decision-making – with recent hard-won insights into the filtering properties of the brain’s dorsal raphe nucleus. That’s a region of the mammalian brainstem rich in serotonin-producing neurons.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Serotonin is often painted as the brain’s “pleasure chemical.” Antidepressant drugs such as selective serotonin reuptake inhibitors (SSRIs) famously target the serotonin system as part of a multi-billion-dollar industry.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, serotonin’s precise role in the nervous system is ambiguous and perplexing: It’s implicated in everything from mood and movement regulation to appetite and sleep-wake cycles. The fact that it’s activated by pain, pleasure and surprise has long been a brain research puzzle.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;With this study, the uOttawa-led researchers put forth a unifying perspective on serotonin they dub a “prospective code for value” – a biological code for how the brain places a value for future rewards.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This code essentially explains why serotonin neurons are activated in the brain in response to both rewards and punishments, with a preference for surprising rewards.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Our work asks the question: What does serotonin tell the brain? In a nutshell, we find that its message closely matches the expectation of future rewards,” says senior author Dr. Richard Naud, associate professor at the Faculty of Medicine’s Department of Cellular and Molecular Medicineand the uOttawa Department of Physics.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Co-author Dr. Jean-Claude Béïque&lt;strong&gt;,&lt;/strong&gt; professor in the Department of Cellular and Molecular Medicine, puts the main findings like this: “Your brain needs to compute the expected value of the actions you contemplate and undertake as you interact with a changing world, asking ‘What’s the value of this decision versus that decision in that particular environment?’ That’s a hard problem.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“So what we think serotonin actually does in the brain is encode the expected value of a particular environment or course of actions in order to ultimately guide everyday decisions.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Drs. Béïque and Naud are both members of the uOttawa Brain and Mind Research Institute’s Centre for Neural Dynamics and Artificial Intelligence.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;About this neuroscience research news&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="has-background"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Author: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.uottawa.ca/en/gazette-news" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Richard Naud&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Source: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.uottawa.ca/en/gazette-news" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;University of Ottawa&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Contact: &lt;/strong&gt;Richard Naud – University of Ottawa&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Image: &lt;/strong&gt;The image is credited to Neuroscience News&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="has-background"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Original Research: &lt;/strong&gt;Closed access.&lt;br&gt;“&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1038/s41586-025-08731-7" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;A prospective code for value in the serotonin system&lt;/a&gt;” by Richard Naud et al. &lt;em&gt;Nature&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr class="wp-block-separator has-text-color has-pale-cyan-blue-color has-alpha-channel-opacity has-pale-cyan-blue-background-color has-background"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Abstract&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A prospective code for value in the serotonin system&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The in vivo responses of dorsal raphe nucleus serotonin neurons to emotionally salient stimuli are a puzzle. Existing theories centring on reward, surprise, salience and uncertainty individually account for some aspects of serotonergic activity but not others.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Merging ideas from reinforcement learning theory with recent insights into the filtering properties of the dorsal raphe nucleus, here we find a unifying perspective in a prospective code for value.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This biological code for near-future reward explains why serotonin neurons are activated by both rewards and punishments, and why these neurons are more strongly activated by surprising rewards but have no such surprise preference for punishments—observations that previous theories have failed to reconcile.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Finally, our model quantitatively predicts in vivo population activity better than previous theories.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;By reconciling previous theories and establishing a precise connection with reinforcement learning, our work represents an important step towards understanding the role of serotonin in learning and behaviour.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p class="clear"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Neuroscience News</author><pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 14:51:02 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilAFBVV95cUxQNFgxQmdLQkkxWkd0aFFPYVU1ZlRrUXpmQVgyTVNqRnFTQUYtWGc3a1pGUFVYVWoyQmY5UU9TdjF3dng0d21sWVljcnBiLW5oZUZXTkstdlF1SlBCVXlIS0xSekxCUmt1M3FqZG1UWnZnZVM5c2dnV2p0a1IxSzU5eWhzRmZlZnhEenN6MkZ6OUJOcDQy</guid></item><item><title>UK cosmetic surgery trends: body contouring and anti-wrinkles - BBC</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiWkFVX3lxTE10aTQ5bXdRX3ZFOXJhNlRQU21jLURBZjNwRXB1OUpYNzRNaDFlUG1tV2QwVldYMWpnVGcwV3NhSDJtclZ6X3RpZC1fZ3gtWGVsMktWaUFZbkUzQdIBX0FVX3lxTE0wVnYySEhyc01VeVdoZjZidHdObzBKSDNGUUdBTndoUWhmV0JuRmEwQ2hqRm5wRTY0S2t0aE1VTGZGN29PVk15MVpmeDNzempiRkNSbnI0TDZSdkhwS3g0?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article&gt;&lt;p data-component="headline-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 eeiVGB"&gt;&lt;h1 class="sc-518485e5-0 itISwu"&gt;The procedures driving UK's cosmetic surgery rise&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="byline-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 dlWCEZ"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="byline-new" class="sc-b42e7a8f-0 haItSe"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="byline-new-contributors" class="sc-b42e7a8f-12 fcCDwR"&gt;&lt;div class="sc-b42e7a8f-5 evAEAB"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;span class="sc-b42e7a8f-7 kItaYD"&gt;Michelle Roberts and Grace Dean&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="sc-b42e7a8f-8 bTSIhT"&gt;&lt;span&gt;BBC News&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 EXUng"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="hero-image" class="sc-a34861b-1 jxzoZC"&gt;&lt;img src="/bbcx/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-a34861b-0 cOpVbP hide-when-no-script"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/58a8/live/efba40f0-1167-11f0-a3a8-cd0c869b6aeb.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/58a8/live/efba40f0-1167-11f0-a3a8-cd0c869b6aeb.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/58a8/live/efba40f0-1167-11f0-a3a8-cd0c869b6aeb.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/58a8/live/efba40f0-1167-11f0-a3a8-cd0c869b6aeb.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/58a8/live/efba40f0-1167-11f0-a3a8-cd0c869b6aeb.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/58a8/live/efba40f0-1167-11f0-a3a8-cd0c869b6aeb.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/58a8/live/efba40f0-1167-11f0-a3a8-cd0c869b6aeb.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/58a8/live/efba40f0-1167-11f0-a3a8-cd0c869b6aeb.jpg.webp" loading="eager" alt="Getty Images Woman with pen markings on her upper arm to show where cosmetic surgeons might shape and remove tissue." class="sc-a34861b-0 efFcac"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-a34861b-2 hesJxn"&gt;Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 dlWCEZ"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;Treatments to remove wrinkles and tone arms, thighs and stomachs are driving a rise in cosmetic surgery, the &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://baaps.org.uk/media/press_releases/1891/cosmetic_surgery_trends_2024_facial_rejuvenation_surges_while_mens_procedures_decline" class="sc-c9299ecf-0 beIoQm"&gt;latest figures&lt;/a&gt; from UK private clinics suggest.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;There were 27,462 procedures performed in 2024 - a 5% rise on 2023 - of which more than nine in ten were on women.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;Boob jobs remained the most popular treatment, followed by breast reduction surgery in second place.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;But much of the rise was driven by increases in facial rejuvenation surgery, such as face and brow lifts and body contouring procedures like liposuction and tummy tucks, according to the British Association of Aesthetic Plastic Surgeons (BAAPS).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 dlWCEZ"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;The association's president said surgery has become cheaper and easier to access, while some patients say there is less stigma around cosmetic procedures.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;The most popular cosmetic surgeries, with their change from 2023 to 2024, are:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ol class="sc-5c9c90b0-0 jqAqjS"&gt;&lt;li class="sc-8d73edac-0 ezcCTE"&gt;Boob job (up 6%)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="sc-8d73edac-0 ezcCTE"&gt;Breast reduction (up 1%)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="sc-8d73edac-0 ezcCTE"&gt;Blepharoplasty, or eyelid surgery (up 13%)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="sc-8d73edac-0 ezcCTE"&gt;Abdominoplasty, or tummy tucks (up 6%)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="sc-8d73edac-0 ezcCTE"&gt;Liposuction, or fat removal (up 8%)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="sc-8d73edac-0 ezcCTE"&gt;Rhinoplasty, or nose jobs (down 1%)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="sc-8d73edac-0 ezcCTE"&gt;Face/neck lift (up 8%)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="sc-8d73edac-0 ezcCTE"&gt;Fat transfer (up 5%)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="sc-8d73edac-0 ezcCTE"&gt;Breast implant removal (down 5%)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="sc-8d73edac-0 ezcCTE"&gt;Otoplasty, or ear correction (up 2%)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 dlWCEZ"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;There was also a 24% rise in thigh lifts, and a 13% increase in brachioplasty, or "bingo wing" removal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;Non-surgical procedures like botox and fillers were also popular: nearly 10,000 were performed by BAAPS members in 2024.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;But "designer vagina" labiaplasty surgery, which changes the shape or size of the labia, appeared less popular, with the number carried out down by 7%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;Nugent said that cosmetic surgery had become "more accessible", and while she acknowledged that treatments still were expensive, she said that they had become a bit more affordable.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;This has coincided with a "shift in attitude" towards cosmetic procedures over the past decade because of a movement in society "towards wellness and looking after oneself", she said. Cosmetic surgery is "more normalised", she added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;Some of the growth in cosmetic surgery is also caused by people who previously had non-surgical procedures, like filler and Botox, now choosing to go under the knife because they were getting "fatigue" from repeatedly going to clinics to get the work done, Nugent said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;And the rise of weight-loss injections such as Ozempic, Wegovy and Mounjaro have played a role, too. Nugent said that some people taking these medications, also known as "skinny jabs", are getting surgery on their face.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;"As they lose weight they start to notice deflation and some sagging of their face," she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;The BAAPS statistics do not show how many people have surgery after taking weight-loss drugs, but Nugent said that of the patients she has treated, "more and more" are people taking the medications.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 eeiVGB"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-518485e5-0 DkKTF"&gt;'There's not as much stigma'&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 dlWCEZ"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;People have cosmetic surgery for a wide range of reasons.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;Kirsten White, 33, a talent acquisition specialist from Sheffield, had a breast reduction and uplift after losing weight with a gastric sleeve.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;She said her "breasts were basically down to my bellybutton" before surgery, leading to backache and the need for physiotherapy, she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;"I don't think people are surprised when I tell them I've had cosmetic surgery because I think it's pretty normal now," she said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;"There's not so much the stigma that there used to be that it's really taboo and people are a lot more supportive of doing what will make you feel happy."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 jFCfG"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-a34861b-1 jxzoZC"&gt;&lt;img src="/bbcx/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-a34861b-0 cOpVbP hide-when-no-script"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/14b6/live/f62f7090-1216-11f0-ba12-8d27eb561761.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/14b6/live/f62f7090-1216-11f0-ba12-8d27eb561761.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/14b6/live/f62f7090-1216-11f0-ba12-8d27eb561761.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/14b6/live/f62f7090-1216-11f0-ba12-8d27eb561761.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/14b6/live/f62f7090-1216-11f0-ba12-8d27eb561761.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/14b6/live/f62f7090-1216-11f0-ba12-8d27eb561761.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/14b6/live/f62f7090-1216-11f0-ba12-8d27eb561761.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/14b6/live/f62f7090-1216-11f0-ba12-8d27eb561761.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Kirsten White A selfie taken by a smiling woman with brunette hair" class="sc-a34861b-0 efFcac"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-a34861b-2 hesJxn"&gt;Kirsten White&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 bdPeAJ"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-8353772e-0 iUqqeb"&gt;Kirsten White says there's less stigma about people getting cosmetic procedures&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 dlWCEZ"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;Men underwent 1,799 surgical procedures in 2024, a slight drop from 2023 - making up just 6.6% of all surgeries in the BAAPS dataset.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;Nose jobs (rhinoplasty) remained the most popular among men, with 332 surgeries done in 2024, which is a 14% drop on 2023.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;Face and neck lifts increased by 26%, with 140 done in 2024, suggesting a growing interest in anti-aging procedures among men - though Nugent said it was harder to spot trends for men due to the smaller numbers treated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 eeiVGB"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-518485e5-0 DkKTF"&gt;Video calls 'heightened our awareness of our appearance'&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-18fde0d6-0 dlWCEZ"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;Beauty standards are shaped by social media and celebrity culture, said Dr Beth Daniels, director of the Centre for Appearance Research at UWE Bristol. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;The pandemic also caused a shift, when the move towards video calls "heightened our awareness of our appearance" because people saw their own faces on their computer screens.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;Dr Daniels said that society places value on youthful looks, which could push some women to get cosmetic procedures.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;"As women age, they're often discounted in a number of ways" and are "made to feel invisible in society", she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;BAAPS vice president Anthony Macquillan suggested the overall increase in facelifts could be linked to societal changes, such as the rising pension age.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;He said: "For many, this type of surgery is not just aesthetic but also functional, helping to maintain confidence, secure employment, and reduce anxiety associated with age-related bias."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;The BAAPS data is based on statistics from 233 of its members. Jim Frame, president of the UK Association of Aesthetic Plastic Surgeons and professor at Anglia Ruskin University, said that it does not cover all of the cosmetic surgery operations that happen in the UK because some is carried out by ENT and maxillofacial surgeons, or by non-BAAPS members, especially fillers and Botox.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;The data also does not include surgeries carried out overseas, where the lower cost of treatment in countries like Turkey attracts Brits. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;Cosmetic procedures and surgery carry risks and the NHS warns that they "can lead to serious complications if they're not done correctly". &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;It advises people to research thoroughly beforehand, including checking the credibility of the clinic and getting information about the most common complications of the procedure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-eb7bd5f6-0 fezwLZ"&gt;"There are a lot of susceptible people that are committing to surgeries that a fairly large proportion will regret," Prof Frame said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BBC</author><pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 14:43:13 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiWkFVX3lxTE10aTQ5bXdRX3ZFOXJhNlRQU21jLURBZjNwRXB1OUpYNzRNaDFlUG1tV2QwVldYMWpnVGcwV3NhSDJtclZ6X3RpZC1fZ3gtWGVsMktWaUFZbkUzQdIBX0FVX3lxTE0wVnYySEhyc01VeVdoZjZidHdObzBKSDNGUUdBTndoUWhmV0JuRmEwQ2hqRm5wRTY0S2t0aE1VTGZGN29PVk15MVpmeDNzempiRkNSbnI0TDZSdkhwS3g0</guid></item></channel></rss>