<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>GNews Health</title><link>https://news.google.com/</link><description></description><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>研究将大量饮酒与脑损伤、阿尔茨海默氏症联系起来-《华盛顿邮报》 | Study links heavy drinking to brain injuries, Alzheimer’s - The Washington Post</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMilAFBVV95cUxOdGg5bGVXc0I2QjFOd2kwWEdqaF85cGRSX2xaMlNzZHdtb1F3ajZSbmlSMERIRG5VNGI4aURWdGhOYV9sTmxZSWZzT0g5b2xzbUxmd2t1MDMwdFNiR18wZVZ3QzZ3ay1OTDB1MWZDaTg2LWppUVdQMHEzV2x6X3RJVktIWHI2eURXbDNNOTRMRGUtZHdU?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="meteredContent grid-center"&gt;&lt;div class="teaser-content"&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="Y5TGRGJK5RGA3EDTGAK3GRLAWE" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Consuming more than eight alcoholic drinks a week is associated with brain injuries linked to Alzheimer’s disease and cognitive decline, a recent study in the journal Neurology suggests.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="DIAXMQHKRZHKXHRBO6NY3Z5RBM" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;The &lt;a href="https://www.neurology.org/doi/10.1212/WNL.0000000000213555" target="_blank"&gt;analysis&lt;/a&gt; looked for links between heavy drinking and brain health. Researchers used autopsy data from the Biobank for Aging Studies at the University of São Paulo Medical School in Brazil collected between 2004 and 2024. The team analyzed data from 1,781 people ages 50 or older at death. The average age at death was 74.9.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-subscribe-cta" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="6W3SJABDLFHH7HHCMKKZOLVFLM" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;With the help of surveys of the deceased’s next of kin, researchers gathered information about the deceased’s cognitive function and alcohol consumption in the three months before their death.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="VVSLKMTC4ZCCXMDDVTIWMNJAAQ" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Among participants, 965 never drank, 319 drank up to seven drinks per week (moderate drinking), and 129 had eight or more drinks per week (heavy drinking). Another 368 were former heavy drinkers who had stopped drinking before their last three months of life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="N2L4ODBTRBGWLICDVXLZSN7VEM" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;The analysis showed that heavy drinkers and former heavy drinkers, respectively, had 41 percent and 31 percent higher odds of neurofibrillary tangles — clumps of the protein tau that accumulate inside brain neurons and have been associated with Alzheimer’s disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-topic-follow-interstitial" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="RML2WOPD2VEKJO5ZMB7JTFHH6U" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Moderate, heavy and former heavy drinkers also had a higher risk of hyaline arteriolosclerosis, which thickens the walls of small blood vessels in the brain, impeding blood flow and causing brain damage over time. Though 40 percent of those who never drank had vascular brain lesions, they were more common in moderate (44.6 percent), heavy (44.1 percent) and former heavy drinkers (50.2 percent), the study found.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="ONAMA2YZQFF57IEGR4ORKKLEI4" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;The association between heavy drinking and vascular brain lesions lingered even after adjusting for factors such as age, sex, heart disease and other health conditions. After adjusting for those factors, the researchers found that heavy drinkers had 133 percent higher odds of developing vascular brain lesions than those who never drank, while former heavy drinkers had 89 percent higher odds. Those categorized as moderate drinkers had 60 percent higher odds than their teetotaling counterparts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="NJGD5HEGR5ESLDRY6D6EPPNHDI" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Though moderate and heavy drinkers had similar cognitive scores to those who never drank, former heavy drinkers had lower cognitive scores.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="WMITFURIK5GGXIWMSU7ONL3HKE" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;The types of injuries associated with heavy drinking in the research are also linked to long-term issues with memory and thinking, Alberto Fernando Oliveira Justo, a researcher at the University of São Paulo Medical School who was the study’s lead author, said in a news &lt;a href="https://www.aan.com/PressRoom/Home/PressRelease/5251" target="_blank"&gt;release&lt;/a&gt;. “Understanding these effects is crucial for public health awareness and continuing to implement preventive measures to reduce heavy drinking.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-header" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;h5 class="wpds-c-vXjlY wpds-c-vXjlY-bALvEi-isCenteredLayout-false" data-qa="article-header" data-contentid="7DCTF67K35D3TMQMO42NSERH3U" data-apitype="header" level="6" id="7DCTF67K35D3TMQMO42NSERH3U"&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2025 12:01:35 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilAFBVV95cUxOdGg5bGVXc0I2QjFOd2kwWEdqaF85cGRSX2xaMlNzZHdtb1F3ajZSbmlSMERIRG5VNGI4aURWdGhOYV9sTmxZSWZzT0g5b2xzbUxmd2t1MDMwdFNiR18wZVZ3QzZ3ay1OTDB1MWZDaTg2LWppUVdQMHEzV2x6X3RJVktIWHI2eURXbDNNOTRMRGUtZHdU</guid></item><item><title>她的喉咙痛变成了ICU的长住。这个事业让医生们难堪了好几个月。-哥伦比亚广播公司新闻 | Her sore throat turned into a long ICU stay. The cause stumped doctors for months. - CBS News</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMijAFBVV95cUxPbVRHX0stdjRTYS1DVmJJT3o5LUVkZDZ1Nm9MVGE0RTQxN0s3MmtCY2dTbjlHTHZlWVBZLWtGLUh4SjVTcEhYd1d0d1A4dUhCRDFJNkZwc24wWjRCeUloTnZra2EweDZIYXppMjFXZXNFbS1tWk9CZGptVjR5cVVYWllUb1AyWnJfa0FoNtIBkgFBVV95cUxQcExOZGpwWjMyTklNQkZTX2I1Z0VmYmM1NzNqQWZpZjFTM3dFc3NjUTV3dUM1NmhMU0RrbmVfQ2JpenJKUXF3aEpWTGljOGtVQlVJQ296NVN2dVlZU0o3dWtPX1NFc0U0Mks0SWE0V3NNV0tQNWtCRUQzTGNENlRJUnljMTdZZjZUZHhGTkQ4TXdSdw?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;section class="content__body"&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;When speech pathologist Vanessa Abraham began to feel ill in 2019, she thought she had a bad case of the flu. She was exhausted and her body ached. Her voice was raspy. She was prescribed antibiotics, but they didn't help. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A week later, Abraham woke up in the middle of the night and tried to stand. She collapsed to the floor, struggling to breathe. Her husband took her to an area hospital, where Abraham was taken to the ICU and intubated. The ventilator helped her breathe but left her unable to speak. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Doctors didn't know what was causing her symptoms. Two days after being admitted, she was transferred to UC San Diego Health, a larger hospital. That's where she met Dr. Jared Rosen, then a medical student on an ICU rotation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While Abraham was in the ICU, doctors suggested multiple diagnoses, but none fit. Even scarier than the lack of answers was her continued intubation. She was unable to speak or eat. She was fighting paralysis that left her unable to move much of her body. Her neck was so weak that she couldn't raise her head without it flopping like a newborn baby's, Rosen said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="embed embed--type-image is-image embed--float-none embed--size-medium"&gt;
    
                                    
      &lt;span class="img embed__content"&gt;&lt;img src="https://assets3.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/04/18/3f271211-6bb2-45f1-a417-ced14380a29c/thumbnail/1240x1653/a438b57a6305f76f3acf6832e39f30c4/vanessa-hospital.jpg?v=04a4ba26f526ed8207f014fe1018c4aa#" alt="vanessa-hospital.jpg " loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;

      
          &lt;figcaption class="embed__caption-container"&gt;
        
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__caption"&gt;Vanessa Abraham in the ICU.&lt;/span&gt;
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__credit"&gt;
            
                Vanessa Abraham

                          &lt;/span&gt;
              &lt;/figcaption&gt;
      &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"I was very aware of what was going on," Abraham told CBS News. "It was beyond the worst experience I could have ever imagined myself being in."&lt;/p&gt;

    
&lt;p id="mpu-plus-outstream-middle" data-ad="mpu-plus-outstream-middle" class="ad-mpu-plus-outstream-middle ad-wrapper " data-ad-unit='"mpu-plus-outstream-middle"'&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Abraham said the only thing that helped relieve her anxiety during this time was the long hours Rosen would spend at her bedside, doing his best to keep her spirits up. As a medical student, he had fewer responsibilities than other members of her care team and was able to spend more time with Abraham. They also worked to develop communication methods Abraham could use. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;After several weeks, Abraham's symptoms began to improve. She was taken off the ventilator. After a month, she was released from the ICU. But doctors were still no closer to understanding what had caused her paralysis. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"There was no official label or term for what I was having. The fear of not knowing was terrifying," Abraham said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Diagnosing a rare form of an unusual condition &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;After being discharged from the ICU, Abraham still had weakness that left her unable to lift her right arm and made eating difficult, so she spent time in inpatient physical therapy. Even after that, she needed outpatient follow-up, as well as more specialized care like swallowing and voice therapy. She battled severe anxiety and depression. At times, she felt so overwhelmed that she considered taking her own life. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="embed embed--type-image is-image embed--float-none embed--size-medium"&gt;
    
                                    
      &lt;span class="img embed__content"&gt;&lt;img src="https://assets1.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/04/18/8df396ab-07d5-4bb3-a59f-bd82e7288719/thumbnail/1240x930/b7de61408d0c723b1095ddba34d777b4/vanessa-rehab-2.png?v=04a4ba26f526ed8207f014fe1018c4aa#" alt="vanessa-rehab-2.png " loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;

      
          &lt;figcaption class="embed__caption-container"&gt;
        
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__caption"&gt;Vanessa Abraham and her daughter as she recovers from her ICU stay. &lt;/span&gt;
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__credit"&gt;
            
                Vanessa Abraham

                          &lt;/span&gt;
              &lt;/figcaption&gt;
      &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One night, she searched for Rosen online and found his email address. Abraham wrote and asked if he remembered her. When he responded and said that he did, it "brought tears" to her eyes and "sparked some level of joy" that helped her have hope. &lt;/p&gt;

    
    
&lt;p id="leader-plus-inc3" data-ad="leader-plus-inc" class="ad-leader-plus-inc ad-wrapper " data-ad-unit='["leader-plus-inc",3]'&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That hope carried her through the next several months.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Finally, four months after her symptoms began, Abraham was diagnosed with a form of Guillain-Barré syndrome, a rare neurological disorder where the fibers around the nerves deteriorate and cause paralysis. In most cases, the paralysis starts in the legs and works its way upwards, according to Dr. Kiril Kiprovski, a neurologist and director of the Division of Neuromuscular Medicine at NYU Langone. Abraham had contracted the condition's even rarer pharyngeal-cervical-brachial variant, which attacks the muscles in the diaphragm and throat. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The variant is "very difficult to diagnose," Kiprovski said. There's no one test to determine if a person has Guillain-Barré syndrome or any of its variants, so doctors rely on clinical presentations. But they may not be familiar with the condition, Kiprovski said, because of its rarity. One person per 78,000 is diagnosed with Guillain-Barré syndrome annually, &lt;a href="https://my.clevelandclinic.org/health/diseases/15838-guillain-barre-syndrome" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"&gt;according to the Cleveland Clinic&lt;/a&gt;. Only about 3% of those patients are diagnosed with the pharyngeal-cervical-brachial variant, researchers &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC6472218/#ref2" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"&gt;have found&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;People diagnosed with Guillain-Barré syndrome or a variant of it tend to improve on their own, as Abraham did, Kiprovski said. Once Abraham was diagnosed, she was able to start receiving intravenous immunoglobulin treatment, where donor antibodies are given to a patient to strengthen their immune system. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;"It takes time"  &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Abraham continued her slow recovery. Having a name for what was happening to her helped her accept the laborious process. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I had to accept in my own head that this is going to be something that's just going to take time," Abraham said. "And that's how neuro diseases work. It takes time for your body to regenerate and heal." &lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="embed embed--type-image is-image embed--float-none embed--size-medium"&gt;
    
                                    
      &lt;span class="img embed__content"&gt;&lt;img src="https://assets1.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/04/18/357cf7aa-2c79-4253-8c15-64698ad1d03a/thumbnail/1240x1860/298334ca89e568c39b7e2b3925b7f242/vanessa.jpg?v=04a4ba26f526ed8207f014fe1018c4aa#" alt="vanessa.jpg " loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;

      
          &lt;figcaption class="embed__caption-container"&gt;
        
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__caption"&gt;Vanessa Abraham.&lt;/span&gt;
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__credit"&gt;
            
                Vanessa Abraham

                          &lt;/span&gt;
              &lt;/figcaption&gt;
      &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Six years later, Abraham still has neuromuscular weakness, but can go about much more of her daily routine. She is back at work, where her voiceless experience in the ICU informs her interactions with patients whose speech has been compromised. She spends as much time as possible in the gym, working to strengthen her body. She also stayed in touch with Rosen, who is now finishing a fellowship in critical care medicine at the University of California's Davis Medical Center. He told CBS News that Abraham's case inspired him to study that area of medicine. &lt;/p&gt;

    
    
&lt;p id="leader-plus-inc4" data-ad="leader-plus-inc" class="ad-leader-plus-inc ad-wrapper " data-ad-unit='["leader-plus-inc",4]'&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Abraham's recovery hasn't just been physical. She started attending a support group for people who have trauma after time in the ICU. The experience has helped her recover from the fear of those weeks on a ventilator. She has worked to raise awareness for the benefits of such groups. She also wrote a memoir detailing her experience. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"There's so much more to recovery than just getting strong again," Abraham said. &lt;/p&gt;

      

                  
        
      
                  
    

    


    
      
    
  

          
  
        
      &lt;div class="content-author"&gt;
      &lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/team/kerry-breen/" class="content-author__name" data-invalid-url-rewritten-http=""&gt;Kerry  Breen&lt;/a&gt;

      &lt;div class="content-author__bio"&gt;
                  &lt;div class="content-author__full-information"&gt;
            &lt;p class="content-author__text"&gt;Kerry Breen is a news editor at CBSNews.com. A graduate of New York University's Arthur L. Carter School of Journalism, she previously worked at NBC News' TODAY Digital. She covers current events, breaking news and issues including substance use.&lt;/p&gt;
                          
                &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
        &lt;/section&gt;

  
  

  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>CBS News</author><pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2025 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijAFBVV95cUxPbVRHX0stdjRTYS1DVmJJT3o5LUVkZDZ1Nm9MVGE0RTQxN0s3MmtCY2dTbjlHTHZlWVBZLWtGLUh4SjVTcEhYd1d0d1A4dUhCRDFJNkZwc24wWjRCeUloTnZra2EweDZIYXppMjFXZXNFbS1tWk9CZGptVjR5cVVYWllUb1AyWnJfa0FoNtIBkgFBVV95cUxQcExOZGpwWjMyTklNQkZTX2I1Z0VmYmM1NzNqQWZpZjFTM3dFc3NjUTV3dUM1NmhMU0RrbmVfQ2JpenJKUXF3aEpWTGljOGtVQlVJQ296NVN2dVlZU0o3dWtPX1NFc0U0Mks0SWE0V3NNV0tQNWtCRUQzTGNENlRJUnljMTdZZjZUZHhGTkQ4TXdSdw</guid></item><item><title>以下是正确使用鼻喷剂的方法，以及管理春季过敏的更多建议- NPR | Here's how to use nasal spray right and more tips for managing spring allergies - NPR</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMikAFBVV95cUxPbDFZRGtTcFYxRFdIU3hCVFRpdEtxUlRvamhQWllDMTJoM2lJTnFOSkhsUExhdm5ISTFMY3o4ckdhbzRCQUUzWmprSlIxcTNWNVVUckdfWjd1V2NjN0VIb0djVER1V18tNTV2bFRPNXNuM2RpS0lyeUhUS3JkTGIwWVg4d0cycDJ6OHVrcnAwemY?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="storytext" class="storytext storylocation linkLocation"&gt;
      &lt;div id="resg-s1-61390" class="bucketwrap image large"&gt;
            
&lt;div class="credit-caption"&gt;
    

    &lt;span class="credit" aria-label="Image credit"&gt;
        
        DDurrich/iStockphoto/Getty Images
        
    &lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;If you feel like your seasonal allergies are getting worse every year, it's not just you. Warming from climate change is making the pollen season longer, and more people are going to the doctor each year looking for relief, according to a recent &lt;a href="https://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/epdf/10.1002/lary.32124" target="_blank"&gt;research review&lt;/a&gt; published in the journal &lt;em&gt;The Laryngoscope. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;One study the reviewers looked at found the pollen season had already gotten 20 days longer in North America between 1990 and 2018, and several studies found an increase in average daily pollen concentrations. &lt;/p&gt;   
   
   

   &lt;p&gt;Luckily, there are ways to keep the pollen from taking over your life. NPR asked doctors for tips to help you manage your spring allergies before they manage you.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This story comes from NPR's &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.npr.org/newsletter/health" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Health newsletter&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;. Want more stories on the science of healthy living? &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.npr.org/newsletter/health" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Subscribe here.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;  &lt;/em&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;h3 class="edTag"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. Keep the outside outside &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Pollen can be carried in on just about any surface, warns Dr. Zachary Rubin a pediatric allergist and clinical immunologist who &lt;a href="https://drrubin.substack.com/" target="_blank"&gt;blogs about allergies&lt;/a&gt; and shares &lt;a href="https://linktr.ee/rubin_allergy?fbclid=PAZXh0bgNhZW0CMTEAAadZB16VfI48t4rNxPpq8LGfLlXSPCFs_gMO_ZloFK_Ods47Z08uMw6zELxkSw_aem_BhmrDvthdrUr_RrI6aDFBA" target="_blank"&gt;allergy-related tips on social media&lt;/a&gt;. Taking your shoes off and storing them in a closet or foyer is a good start, but there's more.  &lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;When you come home, "before you sit down on furniture or in your bed, you ideally should take off any clothes that would have been touching the outside world," Rubin says. Socks, pants, shirts all go directly in your laundry. Rubin also recommends taking a shower or a bath before bed to rinse pollen from your skin and hair.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;When indoors, Rubin recommends keeping your windows and doors closed as much as possible. That may be a bummer if you love a spring breeze, but you're inviting pollen and mold into your house whenever you open the windows, says Rubin.&lt;/p&gt;   
   

   &lt;p&gt;If you're allergic to pollen, the stuff is more likely to float through windows on a dry and windy day. Rubin says rainy days are good for flushing pollen out of the air. But if you're allergic to mold, it's better to keep windows shut on rainy days too.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;If you've just got to open those windows, Rubin says an indoor air purifier can provide some relief.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;h3 class="edTag"&gt;2. Wipe down or bathe your pets&lt;/h3&gt;   &lt;p&gt;If you have a dog, cat or any pet who spends time outside, wipe the animal off whenever they come inside, says Rubin. You can pick up allergy-friendly wipes at pet stores. It's also worth giving pets more frequent baths to remove pollen, says Dr. Neelima Tummala, an ENT physician and clinical assistant professor in otolaryngology at the New York University Grossman School of Medicine.&lt;/p&gt;   
   &lt;h3 class="edTag"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3. Keep your nose clean&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;   &lt;p&gt;First, look at when pollen counts are really high and try to avoid being outdoors during those times of day, advises Tummala. Right now we're in tree pollen season … and tree pollen tends to be highest in the mornings, she says.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt; Want to enjoy nature with fewer sneezes? It turns out the masks we got used to wearing to prevent COVID transmission "can be very helpful actually," says Rubin, when it comes to keeping out pollen and mold. He points to &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC7467086/" target="_blank"&gt;research&lt;/a&gt; where health care workers during the COVID-19 pandemic reported reduced allergy symptoms when they were wearing masks.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;It's also a good idea to rinse out your nose when you get home, says Rubin. You can do that with a neti pot or a saline spray. If you go the neti pot route, be sure to use distilled water, or tap water that's been boiled and cooled down, Rubin cautions. (Water straight from the tap comes with a small risk of &lt;a href="https://www.npr.org/2023/03/03/1160980794/neti-pot-safety-brain-eating-amoeba" target="_blank"&gt;sending an amoeba to eat your brain&lt;/a&gt; – eek!)&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;h3 class="edTag"&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;h3 class="edTag"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3. Know your meds and when to use what&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Different allergy medications treat different symptoms. Here are a few common ones, and what to know about how to use them.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;ul class="edTag"&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Oral and nasal antihistamines&lt;/strong&gt;. If you're experiencing itchy eyes, a runny nose, or sneezing, an oral antihistamine like Zyrtec, Claritin, or Allegra should help, Rubin says. Astepro is a nasal spray with antihistamine, which Rubin usually recommends pairing with a steroid spray. &lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Steroid nasal sprays. &lt;/strong&gt;If you've got congestion or postnasal drip, that's where nasal sprays come in. Examples of common steroid sprays are Flonase, Nasacort and Nasonex.  However, "We don't always tell people to take [steroid sprays] year-round," says Rubin. So check with your physician about how long you should be using it. Nasal steroid sprays take a few weeks to kick in, notes Tummala. With pollen season starting earlier, "you may need to start your intranasal steroid spray earlier than you used to," so they'll be optimally effective, she says.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Nasal decongestants&lt;/strong&gt;. If you're really stuffed up and need instant relief,  you may want to try  a nasal decongestant spray like Afrin or Vicks Sinex, Rubin says.  These sprays shrink the blood vessels in your nasal passages. But Rubin cautions against using them for more than 3 to 5 days at a time, because after you stop, you can develop a rebound nasal congestion that gets progressively worse. "You almost become dependent upon it and it's hard to get rid of," he warns.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h3 class="edTag"&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;h3 class="edTag"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;4. Nasal spray the right way &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;   
   &lt;p&gt;You're probably doing it wrong. I know I was. "A lot of people just naturally go&lt;em&gt;, snort, spray, snort&lt;/em&gt;. What that does is it just shoots the medicine to the back of your throat where you taste it. And if you taste it, you waste it," Rubin says.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;He &lt;a href="https://www.tiktok.com/@rubin_allergy/video/7219482513071148331" target="_blank"&gt;demonstrated how to use nasal spray properly&lt;/a&gt; in a TikTok that went viral. Here's his secret to getting it right:&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;"&lt;/em&gt;I tell people 'nose to toes.' So you look down and then you place the nozzle up, but then you tilt it slightly towards the ear on the same side as your nostril. And after you spray on each side, you look forward and breathe through your mouth. Breathe normally, maybe a slight inhalation through your nose, but you never snort it," Rubin advises.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Why aim towards the ear? The ear is connected to the back of the throat and nasal cavity through the eustachian tube, so decreasing inflammation in that area will lower the risk of getting fluid behind your ear. Pointing the spray bottle towards the ear also targets openings between your nasal passages and your sinuses, lowering your risk of developing a sinus infection, says Rubin.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;h3 class="edTag"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;5. Be aware of factors that can worsen your allergic reaction&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Rubin uses a concept called &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/p/DHjNoY8RLE0/" target="_blank"&gt;the allergy symptom threshold&lt;/a&gt; to explain how exposure to multiple allergens, along with other factors, can trigger symptoms.  "You could be exposed to one pollen grain and not sneeze, but if you're exposed to a thousand, you're going to sneeze because there's enough there that will activate the immune system," he explains.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;That goes for different kinds of allergens too. For instance, last week I was in Washington D.C., contending with pollen from the lovely cherry blossoms outside, and my sister's cat Felicia indoors. My sinuses were not pleased.&lt;/p&gt;   
   &lt;p&gt;"It's like you have a cup and you're filling it with different allergens and exposures, says Rubin." (He &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/p/DHjNoY8RLE0/" target="_blank"&gt;illustrates the concept&lt;/a&gt; in another video.)&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Other factors can also increase your likelihood of having an allergic reaction. For some people Rubin says, drinking alcohol lowers the threshold, and some are more vulnerable when they exercise, particularly outdoors.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;If you happen to be sick, "your immune system is aggravated and hyperactive," Rubin says, and more likely to respond to allergens. (It can also work the other way around – if mucus builds up in your sinuses because of allergies and you're less able to fend off a respiratory infection that comes your way, he says.)&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;It goes back to reducing exposure, says Rubin: The more you can cut back your exposures to all kinds of allergens and irritants, the more successful you'll be at preventing an allergic reaction.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;NPR's Maria Godoy contributed to this report.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>NPR</author><pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikAFBVV95cUxPbDFZRGtTcFYxRFdIU3hCVFRpdEtxUlRvamhQWllDMTJoM2lJTnFOSkhsUExhdm5ISTFMY3o4ckdhbzRCQUUzWmprSlIxcTNWNVVUckdfWjd1V2NjN0VIb0djVER1V18tNTV2bFRPNXNuM2RpS0lyeUhUS3JkTGIwWVg4d0cycDJ6OHVrcnAwemY</guid></item><item><title>肥胖症：孩子们应该在学校称体重吗？ - BBC | Obesity: Should children be weighed at school? - BBC</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiWkFVX3lxTFAyOWdOQldwZU1jSUIxTTRFYkFaMk1TZ2t4SlIzOFdwdmVCOC1SOVNkYjM4TUl4YXplMURCWWhoZnRGdlp5U2IyTTBrRkZlclpOTW9EWkljWFd4UdIBX0FVX3lxTE1wa0VaMG03VHdmb2tBZm9ncG9jck5rSjBwRVh1QU1jbXNYMjF5eDhHNkdyem93X1UtWEVkVjFiT2pBUTV3UG1pd1pXQ1F2Q3ZLQ1FNYzlxbEtqd0Uwdk9v?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article&gt;&lt;p data-component="headline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 fDtfvH"&gt;&lt;h1 class="sc-737179d2-0 dAzQyd"&gt;Mum upset by letter calling daughter, five, overweight&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 gyQxwn"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="hero-image" class="sc-4abb68ca-1 eOgpjw"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20250409-091508-0ef9b7676-web-2.19.1-12/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-4abb68ca-0 itgEAh hide-when-no-script"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/64d5/live/83adc4b0-0fc6-11f0-b234-07dc7691c360.png.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/64d5/live/83adc4b0-0fc6-11f0-b234-07dc7691c360.png.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/64d5/live/83adc4b0-0fc6-11f0-b234-07dc7691c360.png.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/64d5/live/83adc4b0-0fc6-11f0-b234-07dc7691c360.png.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/64d5/live/83adc4b0-0fc6-11f0-b234-07dc7691c360.png.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/64d5/live/83adc4b0-0fc6-11f0-b234-07dc7691c360.png.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/64d5/live/83adc4b0-0fc6-11f0-b234-07dc7691c360.png.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/64d5/live/83adc4b0-0fc6-11f0-b234-07dc7691c360.png.webp" loading="eager" alt="Natasha A five-year-old girl with long blonde hair wearing a yellow gingham dress with yellow bows on it and a frilly white collar. She is smiling and stood in front of a brown wooden door." class="sc-4abb68ca-0 ldLcJe"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-4abb68ca-2 kkAKIJ"&gt;Natasha&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jvncPH"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-1b6a1475-0 feHvAW"&gt;Willow, five, was categorised as being overweight following a health check at primary school&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;A mum was left shocked and upset after her five-year-old daughter came home from school with a letter describing her as overweight.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Natasha, from Blaenavon, Torfaen, was informed Willow was 3ft 8in (112cm) tall and weighed about three stone 7lb (22.6kg) - this meant she was slightly above the "healthy weight" category using the &lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.bbc.co.uk/health/tools/bmi_calculator/bmi.shtml" class="sc-f9178328-0 bGFWdi"&gt;body mass index (BMI)&lt;/a&gt; system.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Wales has a "significant problem" with childhood obesity, according to one expert, with more than 25% of children aged four to five overweight.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;The Welsh government said measuring the height and weight of reception children was important to help give them the best start in life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Despite the intentions, the categorisation shocked Natasha, as Willow takes part in gymnastics, dancing and swimming every week and has a balanced diet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;"I understand why they do it, to gather statistics for an overall population, but it's not accurate in the slightest," she said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;"It's such a demoralising approach, labelling children in such a manner, solely based on BMI.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;"BMI is such an outdated approach, [providing] misleading information. There needs to be multiple factors that can represent a child's health, not just a tick-box exercise."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;BMI is a measure of whether someone is a healthy weight for their height. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;The &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.nhs.uk/conditions/obesity/" class="sc-f9178328-0 bGFWdi"&gt;NHS website states BMI scores &lt;/a&gt;have "some limitations" because the system measures whether a person is carrying too much weight, but not too much fat. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 hoQmHM"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-4abb68ca-1 eOgpjw"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20250409-091508-0ef9b7676-web-2.19.1-12/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-4abb68ca-0 itgEAh hide-when-no-script"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/b881/live/d1edf6e0-0fc6-11f0-b234-07dc7691c360.png.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/b881/live/d1edf6e0-0fc6-11f0-b234-07dc7691c360.png.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/b881/live/d1edf6e0-0fc6-11f0-b234-07dc7691c360.png.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/b881/live/d1edf6e0-0fc6-11f0-b234-07dc7691c360.png.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/b881/live/d1edf6e0-0fc6-11f0-b234-07dc7691c360.png.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/b881/live/d1edf6e0-0fc6-11f0-b234-07dc7691c360.png.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/b881/live/d1edf6e0-0fc6-11f0-b234-07dc7691c360.png.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/b881/live/d1edf6e0-0fc6-11f0-b234-07dc7691c360.png.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Natasha A young girl with tied-back blonde hair wearing a black and pink sparkly gymnastics leotard and swinging from a wooden bar with red gym apparatus behind her. Below her legs, you can see the head of a female instructor who has tied-back brown hair." class="sc-4abb68ca-0 ldLcJe"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-4abb68ca-2 kkAKIJ"&gt;Natasha&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jvncPH"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-1b6a1475-0 feHvAW"&gt;Willow trains twice a week in gymnastics, as well as doing dance, swimming and performing arts &lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Natasha, 29, wants the system overhauled, and has started a petition calling for it to "take in the bigger picture" of lifestyle and health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;The healthcare support worker described being "so disheartened" by the letter seen by BBC Wales.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;It stated calculating children's weight categories could help parents make informed choices on lifestyles.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;The school had told her about health checks taking place last month, which would include eyesight and hearing assessments, as well as measurements.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Natasha believed any results would take a "holistic approach", including questionnaires sent to parents. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;But the way it was done had left her worried about the "negative psychological impact" of the labels. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;"I was angry and so upset," Natasha said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;"I've grown up being told I was overweight and I needed to lose weight, and I've done everything in my power to make sure Willow doesn't have any of that."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 fDtfvH"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-737179d2-0 erjHHi"&gt;Why are children weighed at school?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;The &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://phw.nhs.wales/services-and-teams/child-measurement-programme/how-the-programme-works/" class="sc-f9178328-0 bGFWdi"&gt;Child Measurement Scheme&lt;/a&gt; is Welsh government-led, and coordinated by &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://phw.nhs.wales" class="sc-f9178328-0 bGFWdi"&gt;Public Health Wales&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;It sees school nursing teams measure the height and weight of every reception pupil, unless their parents opt out.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;A letter is then sent to parents, explaining how they can see their child's results.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;At the end of the school year, the anonymised results are analysed for trends at local health board level and national levels.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Public Health Wales said the information was used to "plan services and inform changes to help families enjoy a healthy and active lifestyle".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;In the letter Natasha received, it signposted parents towards its &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://everychild.wales/" class="sc-f9178328-0 bGFWdi"&gt;Every Child Wales&lt;/a&gt; initiative, for "useful information on helping children stay fit and healthy".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 hoQmHM"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-4abb68ca-1 eOgpjw"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20250409-091508-0ef9b7676-web-2.19.1-12/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-4abb68ca-0 itgEAh hide-when-no-script"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/99c2/live/1cdd2950-0fc7-11f0-ac9f-c37d6fd89579.png.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/99c2/live/1cdd2950-0fc7-11f0-ac9f-c37d6fd89579.png.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/99c2/live/1cdd2950-0fc7-11f0-ac9f-c37d6fd89579.png.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/99c2/live/1cdd2950-0fc7-11f0-ac9f-c37d6fd89579.png.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/99c2/live/1cdd2950-0fc7-11f0-ac9f-c37d6fd89579.png.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/99c2/live/1cdd2950-0fc7-11f0-ac9f-c37d6fd89579.png.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/99c2/live/1cdd2950-0fc7-11f0-ac9f-c37d6fd89579.png.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/99c2/live/1cdd2950-0fc7-11f0-ac9f-c37d6fd89579.png.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Natasha A woman with long dark hair and a nose ring wearing a black top. She has her arm round a young blonde-haired girl who is wearing a red velvet dress with a fluffy white collar. There are tables and chairs behind them." class="sc-4abb68ca-0 ldLcJe"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-4abb68ca-2 kkAKIJ"&gt;Natasha&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jvncPH"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-1b6a1475-0 feHvAW"&gt;Natasha says she was "disheartened, angry and upset" when she received the letter from her daughter Willow's school&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Cardiff University's Prof Adrian Edwards, who is director of &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://researchwalesevidencecentre.co.uk/" class="sc-f9178328-0 bGFWdi"&gt;the Health and Care Research Wales Evidence Centre&lt;/a&gt;, said the country had a "significant problem" with childhood obesity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;He added more than 25% of Welsh children aged four to five were overweight, compared to about 11% across the UK and 7% on average in other high-income countries. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;"All the health problems we would recognise and understand - including mental health problems, arthritis, high blood pressure, diabetes, cancer risk and all sorts of things - they are higher risk because of overweight and obesity, which starts in childhood," he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;He admitted some scientific research showed BMI was not always accurate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Prof Edwards cited the example of professional rugby players who can score as obese, "but most of them are actually just full of muscle".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Another example, he said, was children's bodies changing as they grow.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;However, he emphasised the need for "a balance to be struck between accuracy and consistency".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;"They've been doing the same thing over 20, 30 years," he said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;"So, leaving aside the nuances of who might or might not be being incorrectly categorised at the edges, I think it's telling us something about the mainstream, the typical picture.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;"The question is what you do with this information. Is it about diagnosing an individual who should then have some extra attention and support? &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;"Or is it actually about understanding the problem at population level, perhaps without singling out individuals?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 hoQmHM"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-4abb68ca-1 eOgpjw"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20250409-091508-0ef9b7676-web-2.19.1-12/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-4abb68ca-0 itgEAh hide-when-no-script"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/9a66/live/c839edb0-0fcc-11f0-ba12-8d27eb561761.png.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/9a66/live/c839edb0-0fcc-11f0-ba12-8d27eb561761.png.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/9a66/live/c839edb0-0fcc-11f0-ba12-8d27eb561761.png.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/9a66/live/c839edb0-0fcc-11f0-ba12-8d27eb561761.png.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/9a66/live/c839edb0-0fcc-11f0-ba12-8d27eb561761.png.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/9a66/live/c839edb0-0fcc-11f0-ba12-8d27eb561761.png.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/9a66/live/c839edb0-0fcc-11f0-ba12-8d27eb561761.png.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/9a66/live/c839edb0-0fcc-11f0-ba12-8d27eb561761.png.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Cardiff University A man with short grey hair and glasses, wearing a collared white shirt and smiling at the camera." class="sc-4abb68ca-0 ldLcJe"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-4abb68ca-2 kkAKIJ"&gt;Cardiff University&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jvncPH"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-1b6a1475-0 feHvAW"&gt;Prof Adrian Edwards says BMI checks serve the purpose of understanding "the typical picture" which has shown a "significant problem" of childhood obesity in Wales&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;The Welsh government said measuring the height and weight of reception children was "part of our routine child development programme Healthy Child Wales which is important in improving children's health and giving them the best start in life".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;A spokesperson added: "Being consistent in how school nurses measure children allows Public Health Wales to assess trends over time at a population level."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BBC</author><pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2025 06:04:41 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiWkFVX3lxTFAyOWdOQldwZU1jSUIxTTRFYkFaMk1TZ2t4SlIzOFdwdmVCOC1SOVNkYjM4TUl4YXplMURCWWhoZnRGdlp5U2IyTTBrRkZlclpOTW9EWkljWFd4UdIBX0FVX3lxTE1wa0VaMG03VHdmb2tBZm9ncG9jck5rSjBwRVh1QU1jbXNYMjF5eDhHNkdyem93X1UtWEVkVjFiT2pBUTV3UG1pd1pXQ1F2Q3ZLQ1FNYzlxbEtqd0Uwdk9v</guid></item><item><title>Intermountain Health在萨拉托加斯普林斯开设新诊所和癌症中心- KSL新闻 | Intermountain Health breaks ground on new clinic, cancer center in Saratoga Springs - KSL News</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiuwFBVV95cUxPZzA2YmZnR3BVZFF6TEtVLUtySnN2SXExSjdELUZoNm9YLWlVYV9CaEhUUEo1NTBOZkliVk5YNjVNMmk0UVVtVE03SURMb1BkOTctYzBjYWxRelhFcjVBVUh5MW5SaUdreDdNTWhaRDhYcDBmS2RuWl9DQkxVYnYyM0tJaWxibjUwNUZscHBzcmxScURGRG1PeVFoMVhBNDk4ek1KNUlkZGU4SFJ1WkdTemVHYXEtODlwWWJV?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;
                                        Estimated read time: 3-4
                                        minutes&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div id="articleContainer"&gt;&lt;p&gt;SARATOGA SPRINGS — Intermountain Health on Friday broke ground on the site of its new multi-specialty clinic, which will include a dedicated cancer center, for residents of northern Utah County.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Intermountain Saratoga Springs Multi-Specialty Clinic and Cancer Center plans to offer a wide range of specialized services, including OB/GYN care, gastroenterology care, audiology, urology, cardiology and pediatrics services, among others.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The cancer center within the clinic will provide comprehensive cancer care, such as chemotherapy treatments and support services. This will include survivorship services like oncology social work and &lt;a href="https://intermountainhealthcare.org/services/cancer-care/aya" rel="nofollow" target="_blank"&gt;oncology nurse navigators&lt;/a&gt;, who guide patients through the health care system and help manage expectations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The new cancer center will join only two others in the county — located in American Fork and Provo — in hopes of easing the burden on patients who would otherwise need to regularly travel around 20 to 50 miles round trip to receive treatment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Intermountain has a very strong belief that cancer care should be delivered close to home," said Desiree Dougherty, assistant regional service line director for Intermountain Health. "Carrying the burden of cancer ... is time consuming, creates stress, anxiety, time away from work, and they all have to spend hours in centers on days that they feel awful. The care is hard, and the treatments are difficult. So bringing cancer care close to home for these patients is incredibly important so they can have the care that they need with their families close to home."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Laurie and Scott Stone felt the full weight of this burden when Laurie was diagnosed with uterine cancer in 2022. She went through extensive testing and was advised to have a hysterectomy. Following her procedure, doctors determined she would also need radiation therapy, which she received at the Intermountain cancer centers in American Fork and Provo.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This required frequent 25- or 50-mile trips, typically during heavy morning traffic. Two years after Laurie Stone's diagnosis, Scott received abnormal blood test results at his yearly physical and was also diagnosed with cancer. Laurie Stone has now completed treatment and anxiously awaits the five-year mark, where she will be declared cancer free, and Scott Stone is still undergoing treatment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The pair were present at Friday's groundbreaking ceremony and expressed their deep gratitude and love for the medical staff in Intermountain's oncology network who have supported them over the years. While they will still need to travel for the remainder of Scott Stone's treatment, the couple is excited that these services will be available just 5 miles from their home.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I'm so grateful for this center being here closer to home and that our community can take advantage of (it). Thank you very much," said Scott Stone, addressing Intermountain staff.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The multidisciplinary clinic aims to provide more services to northern Utah County because it is one of the &lt;a href="https://www.ksl.com/article/51012325/these-were-utahs-fastest-growing-cities-in-2023--and-the-cities-that-lost-population" rel="follow" target="_blank"&gt;fastest-growing areas&lt;/a&gt; in the state. Saratoga Springs is home to over 59,000 residents as of 2024, &lt;a href="https://www.saratogasprings-ut.gov/DocumentCenter/View/14460/24-25-Citizens-Budget" rel="nofollow" target="_blank"&gt;almost doubling&lt;/a&gt; its population since 2018. Eagle Mountain has around 64,000 residents and &lt;a href="https://eaglemountain.gov/wp-content/uploads/2024/10/EagleMountainCityUT_Demos_2024.pdf" rel="nofollow" target="_blank"&gt;is projected to grow&lt;/a&gt; to nearly 80,000 by 2029.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Our vision for this clinic is simple, which is that we want to bring the full strength of Intermountain cancer services into a space that feels local, personal and healing," said Brandon Barney, medical director of radiation oncology services. "Patients here will have access to the same cutting edge technology that they would get in Salt Lake or at Utah Valley Hospital. That includes treatments with radiotherapy, with chemotherapy ... in-office procedures, radiation treatment planning. There's not really going to be a disease site or a type of cancer that we won't be able to treat here."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The clinic will be located at 392 W. Medical Drive in Saratoga Springs, between Intermountain Saratoga Springs Emergency Department and Surgery Center buildings and plans to open in fall 2026.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="kt_disclaimer"&gt;
                                    The Key Takeaways for this article were generated with the assistance of large language models and reviewed by our editorial team. The article, itself, is solely human-written.
                                &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>KSL News</author><pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2025 03:02:24 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiuwFBVV95cUxPZzA2YmZnR3BVZFF6TEtVLUtySnN2SXExSjdELUZoNm9YLWlVYV9CaEhUUEo1NTBOZkliVk5YNjVNMmk0UVVtVE03SURMb1BkOTctYzBjYWxRelhFcjVBVUh5MW5SaUdreDdNTWhaRDhYcDBmS2RuWl9DQkxVYnYyM0tJaWxibjUwNUZscHBzcmxScURGRG1PeVFoMVhBNDk4ek1KNUlkZGU4SFJ1WkdTemVHYXEtODlwWWJV</guid></item><item><title>密歇根州2家餐厅报告可能暴露于麻疹- MLive.com | Possible measles exposure reported at 2 Michigan restaurants - MLive.com</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiogFBVV95cUxPaU5jcVJNVGxlZWJBb1VtUDRBS2d4N2ZsY0hQd19rWmpwRjJRMDRjVmJLNWtJUFRRTmNjZjZESl8zMDR4Rzhxd2xjSE5uaGtuWU50LXM3RnVQVVpNTTV2VHRENG5rUkV2RFBra1VjRkltTlZrUWdQTDFJenc4RVg4Skx3Q0dvYkdEakZDal83aENOSjh0dEFReHJaZkg3S0FqemfSAbYBQVVfeXFMUGk2aGUzTVYzeUNOd2Jjb2lraF9fa0dlMVRHdUw5VnR1M1d5RVhac1R5MGdnUWt6cDFQVVIzdXVYWEpleGdTTDRWbXZ4X2lRQS1meVp4c2I3LVlabXk0ZkRWNWFLXzZsdkFRWEtLXzNBdU1qLXhSUnl2QU5KZHBac2NtOXdsU290akJpTmRCOEF1ak9WdzJDbWMtYnV4MDZKeS1GVmI2RU8yZERMOVBDa19TcGhSZmc?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content "&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="HEQFXDTUYVBEPLPZ6NXLRZAEHM"&gt;EATON COUNTY, MI – Health officials are investigating a potential case of measles in Eaton County.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-1"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="YGE7JNNMRFA6ZMBNP7I6AV4AAA"&gt;Test results are still pending, but the Barry-Eaton District Health Department is still alerting the public about two restaurants where visitors could have potentially been exposed to the highly contagious disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-2"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="CAFBZIWX6RD77FSLLG4UZFTLZE"&gt;The health department sent an alert out Friday, April 18, to warn the public of the potential exposure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-3"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="ZVJKDK36FBAHNI4L3LGVSETR6E"&gt;People who visited the following locations during the listed times may have been exposed:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-4"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class="article__unordered-list"&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;April 12: King Ocean Crab restaurant on Miller Street in Lansing from 6:30-10 p.m.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;April 13: Bad Brads BBQ on South Baldwin Road in Orion Township from 4:30-7:30 p.m.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-5"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="ZYGHVB7CXVEKDMEZQATWAGUMDE"&gt;Measles is known for being highly contagious, with its ability to live up to two hours in an airspace after an infected person leaves the area. Without immunity, the likelihood of being infected after exposure to the virus is about 90%, according to health officials.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-6"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="7GBM6SFZWZFFNE3LN5B7CH6BBM"&gt;“We are acting out of an abundance of caution to notify the public as quickly as possible,” said Dr. Julie Kehdi, the health department’s medical director. “Measles spreads easily and can have serious health consequences, especially for children and people with weakened immune systems. We encourage anyone who may have been exposed to take action right away and check their vaccination status.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-7" class="middleParagraph"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="SYZLERMAYJARTCUQDYQVE2SQNI"&gt;Health officials say anyone who may have been exposed to measles within the last six days could be able to receive post-exposure treatment that could prevent illness. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-8"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="VDVH6TNS6JDBDAVEVYFWFNCCYI"&gt;Anyone exposed on April 13 should receive post-exposure treatment should be received by Saturday, April 19.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-9"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="YWSFBQKIXBDQ3ALA2Z6QROML4Q"&gt;People are advised to contact their health care provider, pharmacy, or local health department for vaccination and guidance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-10"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="U5YXGRUV5ZCRNN4IQIOBU7GIEI"&gt;For more vaccine information, visit Michigan’s &lt;a href="https://michigan.gov/immunize" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://Michigan.gov/immunize "&gt;webpage on immunization information&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-11"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-enter:VKLCJCP4QRATJCCHDXUEGE23WQ" data-fusion-component="VKLCJCP4QRATJCCHDXUEGE23WQ"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-exit:VKLCJCP4QRATJCCHDXUEGE23WQ" data-fusion-component="VKLCJCP4QRATJCCHDXUEGE23WQ"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-12"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="YSFEVAECVVETDOJCCHTCSB7MQU"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-13"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>MLive.com</author><pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2025 01:06:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiogFBVV95cUxPaU5jcVJNVGxlZWJBb1VtUDRBS2d4N2ZsY0hQd19rWmpwRjJRMDRjVmJLNWtJUFRRTmNjZjZESl8zMDR4Rzhxd2xjSE5uaGtuWU50LXM3RnVQVVpNTTV2VHRENG5rUkV2RFBra1VjRkltTlZrUWdQTDFJenc4RVg4Skx3Q0dvYkdEakZDal83aENOSjh0dEFReHJaZkg3S0FqemfSAbYBQVVfeXFMUGk2aGUzTVYzeUNOd2Jjb2lraF9fa0dlMVRHdUw5VnR1M1d5RVhac1R5MGdnUWt6cDFQVVIzdXVYWEpleGdTTDRWbXZ4X2lRQS1meVp4c2I3LVlabXk0ZkRWNWFLXzZsdkFRWEtLXzNBdU1qLXhSUnl2QU5KZHBac2NtOXdsU290akJpTmRCOEF1ak9WdzJDbWMtYnV4MDZKeS1GVmI2RU8yZERMOVBDa19TcGhSZmc</guid></item><item><title>专家们正在分享可能对您的心理健康产生负面影响的五种食物- BuzzFeed | Experts Are Sharing The Five Foods That Can Actually Have A Negative Impact On Your Mental Health - BuzzFeed</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMifEFVX3lxTFBSVm1ULUwzamxTNmNWd05xcGI3TTU1dGFJRHJfRkpkQXA2Rkl2TEtuN0dqTEhHa2NMWkdxMTgxakdmdXVwT0M1YmJ6VlYwVERndUV3UXFnUGs2cWZQUklqNURmd2NzNTl1MURNcVZkTHpCUnJjYmVXQzlncVY?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="subbuzz buzz-width--standard__subbuzz buzz-type--long__subbuzz subbuzz-text
  subbuzz-index-1
  
  
  
  
  " data-keywords="cleaning" data-module="subbuzz-text"&gt;
  
  &lt;p id="138519339" class="subbuzz-anchor"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;





&lt;p&gt;We rarely think about food in relation to our mental health. We worry about it leading to health issues, such as &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/entry/worst-foods-for-heart-health_l_63e51cdfe4b0255caae9f325" target="_blank" data-skimlinks-tracking="7862681"&gt;cardiovascular&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/entry/worst-foods-for-digestion-health_l_6411d77ce4b0a3902d2e1014" target="_blank" data-skimlinks-tracking="7862681"&gt;gastrointestinal&lt;/a&gt; problems, but did you know that different foods and beverages can exacerbate anxiety spikes and even bouts of depression? &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In fact, there are foods and drinks that therapists and psychiatrists, who have spent their careers advising people on mental wellness, typically avoid ― or consume in moderation ― for the sake of their mental health. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Take this knowledge with a grain of salt. These foods and drinks can be consumed once in a while and not be correlated with negative mental health consequences. Just remember that, as with everything, moderation is key.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Multiple Cups Of Coffee Or Espresso&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;For some people, too much caffeine can have a negative impact on anxiety. “If a person is prone to feeling anxious or has multiple stressors, know that over-caffeination causes an increased cortisol response and can lead to adrenal fatigue, a recipe for persistent stress and burnout, not to mention sleep issues,” said licensed clinical psychologist &lt;a href="https://linkedin-learning.pxf.io/c/2706071/449670/8005?subId1=64667c76e4b035573934d585&amp;amp;u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.linkedin.com%2Fin%2Fdrbrittneyjones%2F" target="_blank" data-skimlinks-tracking="7862681" data-affiliate="true"&gt;Brittney Jones&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC4668773/" target="_blank" data-skimlinks-tracking="7862681" data-affiliate="true"&gt;Research suggests&lt;/a&gt; that consuming more than 250 milligrams of caffeine per day (that’s roughly 2 1/2 cups) could have a negative impact on anxiety, so Jones does her best to keep her coffee consumption under that amount. And for people who get jitters or anxiety spikes from coffee, consuming caffeine in the form of matcha can be a great alternative since it gives many people a feeling of calm alertness &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/28056735/" target="_blank" data-skimlinks-tracking="7862681" data-affiliate="true"&gt;thanks to a compound called L-theanine&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Diet Soda&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you’re looking out for your mental health this summer, you might want to keep your diet soda consumption to a minimum. “Everyone loves a cold diet soda on a warm summer day, but the health concerns outweigh the benefits,” said &lt;a href="https://www.sohomd.com/psychiatrist-dr-jospitre" target="_blank" data-skimlinks-tracking="7862681" data-affiliate="true"&gt;Jacques Jospitre, Jr.&lt;/a&gt;, a board-certified psychiatrist and co-founder of SohoMD. “While we know high-sugar sodas aren’t great for our health, diet sodas might actually be even worse. Many of these contain phenylalanine, which is &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/28198207/" target="_blank" data-skimlinks-tracking="7862681" data-affiliate="true"&gt;an added chemical well-known to mess up brain neurochemistry&lt;/a&gt; by stopping the proper production of serotonin and dopamine, two molecules we need for good mood.”&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Additionally, these drinks have artificial sweeteners like aspartame, “which is a known neurotoxin and &lt;a href="https://www.tandfonline.com/doi/abs/10.1080/1028415X.2017.1288340#:~:text=Aspartame%20acts%20as%20a%20chemical,adverse%20effects%20on%20neurobehavioral%20health." target="_blank" data-skimlinks-tracking="7862681" data-affiliate="true"&gt;may raise stress hormones like cortisol&lt;/a&gt;, as well as increase the amount of free radicals in the brain,” Jospitre said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Alcohol&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;While a drink or two once in a while isn’t the worst thing, &lt;a href="https://www.livebettertherapysolutions.com/about" target="_blank" data-skimlinks-tracking="7862681" data-affiliate="true"&gt;Danielle Tucci&lt;/a&gt;, a licensed professional counselor and the founder of Live Better Therapy Solutions, said she does her best to avoid alcohol when considering her mental health.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BuzzFeed</author><pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2025 00:31:02 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMifEFVX3lxTFBSVm1ULUwzamxTNmNWd05xcGI3TTU1dGFJRHJfRkpkQXA2Rkl2TEtuN0dqTEhHa2NMWkdxMTgxakdmdXVwT0M1YmJ6VlYwVERndUV3UXFnUGs2cWZQUklqNURmd2NzNTl1MURNcVZkTHpCUnJjYmVXQzlncVY</guid></item><item><title>俄勒冈州罕见的疯牛病导致2人死亡- SFGATE | Rare mad cow-like brain disease kills 2 in Oregon - SFGATE</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMilwFBVV95cUxNelJHVE5ScXQxQk52RUEtUzExZnc5NVk1cmg0U3EtazB4Qnd6ZFRabUZORWl3a0h6ODFxZkR6cDJtOUQ5eFVnNEMwZmJKcDZlcXhSSDBFZVhNRHd4X1BxUnQxWjRZcHVsWng3NHVIaEhYZ1loRkdreEZUME52cXhYeEdpeHU3NzlHM1JGdnNiR2FqQVZ4SFBj?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Three cases of a rare and fatal brain disorder have been identified in Hood River County, Oregon, local health officials have confirmed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;In an April 14 &lt;a href="https://www.hoodrivercounty.gov/index.asp?SEC=AF40862A-8B0E-4107-B2B4-956029C71941&amp;amp;DE=11E4744C-DDC6-4DBD-8F95-B86EFBB310E6" data-link="native" class=""&gt;press release&lt;/a&gt;, the Hood River County Health Department confirmed one case and identified two probable cases of &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/creutzfeldt-jakob/about/index.html" data-link="native" class=""&gt;Creutzfeldt-Jakob disease&lt;/a&gt;, or CJD — a rapidly progressive neurodegenerative condition &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/creutzfeldt-jakob/about/index.html" data-link="native" class=""&gt;with a 100% fatality rate&lt;/a&gt;. Two of the individuals have died, officials said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;The disease is &lt;a href="https://www.hopkinsmedicine.org/health/conditions-and-diseases/bse-mad-cow-disease-and-vcjd" data-link="native" class=""&gt;related &lt;/a&gt;to mad cow disease and can lead to symptoms such as confusion, disorientation, hallucinations, seizures, psychological disturbances and a loss of coordination. Most people die within a year once symptoms occur, according to the CDC. One of the CJD cases was confirmed through an autopsy, while the other two are considered presumptive diagnoses, &lt;a href="https://www.oregonlive.com/health/2025/04/2-in-oregon-die-of-rare-brain-disease.html" data-link="native" class=""&gt;the Oregonian &lt;/a&gt;reported.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Trish Elliott, the director of the Hood River County Health Department, told the outlet that presumptive cases can only be confirmed after death through the testing of brain tissue and cerebrospinal fluid. It’s a process that can take several months and must be done out of state.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;“At this time, there is no identifiable link between these three cases,” the health department said in the press release.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;CJD affects approximately &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/creutzfeldt-jakob/hcp/clinical-overview/index.html#:~:text=Key%20points,55%20years%20old%20and%20older." data-link="native" class=""&gt;one to two people&lt;/a&gt; per million globally each year. In the U.S., approximately 350 cases are reported annually, according to the &lt;a href="https://www.ninds.nih.gov/health-information/disorders/creutzfeldt-jakob-disease" data-link="native" class=""&gt;National Institutes of Health&lt;/a&gt;. Hood River County, which has a population of around 24,000, according to &lt;a href="https://www.census.gov/quickfacts/fact/table/hoodrivercountyoregon/PST045223" data-link="native" class=""&gt;U.S. Census Bureau data&lt;/a&gt;, has now seen three cases in the past eight months. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;CJD occurs in several forms. The most common is sporadic, arising without a known cause. The rarest form, variant CJD, results from exposure to prions through external sources, such as eating beef contaminated with bovine spongiform encephalopathy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The risk of getting CJD is extremely low,” the health department emphasized in the press release. “It does not spread through the air, touch, social contact, or water.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;The department said it is conducting an “active and ongoing investigation” in partnership with the Oregon Health Authority and the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>SFGATE</author><pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 23:09:46 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilwFBVV95cUxNelJHVE5ScXQxQk52RUEtUzExZnc5NVk1cmg0U3EtazB4Qnd6ZFRabUZORWl3a0h6ODFxZkR6cDJtOUQ5eFVnNEMwZmJKcDZlcXhSSDBFZVhNRHd4X1BxUnQxWjRZcHVsWng3NHVIaEhYZ1loRkdreEZUME52cXhYeEdpeHU3NzlHM1JGdnNiR2FqQVZ4SFBj</guid></item><item><title>美国24个州的麻疹感染病例达到800例- ABC新闻 | US measles infections hit 800 cases across 24 states - ABC News</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMimwFBVV95cUxPMDNCQ3Ayc2dtUGx0TElmOE56OHV1d0VWLTFXcXhrNzF0ZWJiMkNVSzlRaERMZUZmZ2pRSTM2ZndaeGVRYWZzWUJrNlhUd3dwbDZ3cHNxYW8zLVZGQnBCdFlYbFpqcWlLeGZXM0xmcUFmSTJoOHA4LWlEbzVzbnB2T0lmLXBUVlhla0djZE1RdTVEY204aUUxNTlpQdIBoAFBVV95cUxQaXAyRXVRTmRKRndfdWtkX3UzRU83cmFFTWY0eWd4TjRCV1ZtbWh0dnZhN1c4WUpsMk5GRlpFSHo4aTFYamhuMUFvT3BEenhCcDBId3NSbnZDNE9Zb0RIVnN6ZV83Y1NIR2MwNTJ5X2RpeUpYUDBPUW5tWlNXTGMxQmhPRkNIdGVhWmZ2eDVWMmwwdHUzR1kwU2p0c3MzN0Na?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="xvlfx ZRifP TKoO eaKKC EcdEg bOdfO qXhdi NFNeu UyHES " data-testid="prism-article-body"&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao MvWXB TjIXL aGjvy ebVHC "&gt;The U.S. measles outbreak has reached 800 confirmed cases across 24 states, the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention reported Friday. The &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://www.cdc.gov/measles/data-research/index.html#cdc_data_surveillance_section_10-measles-cases-in-2025"&gt;latest update shows 88&lt;/a&gt; new cases from the previous week, marking what health officials describe as a concerning trend in 2025.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;The current outbreak has claimed two lives, with a third death under investigation, according to state health officials. The surge in cases is nearly triple the total number reported in 2024, when the nation recorded 285 cases.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;If this year's cases continue to grow at the current rate, the U.S. could surpass the 2019 total of 1,274 cases, potentially reaching the highest level since 1992, per data.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="oLzSq QrHMO fnRUo pvsTF EhJPu vPlOC zNYgW OsTsW RMeqy daRVX ISNQ sKyCY eRftA acPPc MENS nFwaT MCnQE mEeeY SmBjI xegrY rPLsU iulOd NIuqO zzscu lzDCc aHUBM IEgzD OjMNy eQqcx SVqKB GQmdz jaoD VWDdR ONJdw vrZxD OnRTz gbbfF roDbV GPGwb oMlSS gfNzt oJhud eXZcf zhVlX "&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="InlineImage GpQCA lZur asrEW " data-testid="prism-inline-image"&gt;&lt;figure class="kzIjN GNmeK pYrtp dSqFO " data-testid="prism-figure"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;div class="nMMea bNYiy Mjgpa dGwha DDmxa jgKNG RGHCC aBIU PriDW lZur " data-testid="prism-caption"&gt;&lt;p class="HXPPJ barbu yKsXL IzgMt VcHIt uhSzI YGNMU cRAsZ xqMcl QtRul "&gt;&lt;span class="hsDdd OOSI GpQCA lZur VlFaz " data-testid="prism-truncate"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="gtOSm FbbUW tUtYa vOCwz EQwFq yCufu eEak Qmvg nyTIa SRXVc vzLa jgBfc WXDas CiUCW kqbG zrdEG txGfn ygKVe BbezD UOtxr CVfpq xijV soGRS XgdC sEIlf daWqJ "&gt;Boxes and vials of the Measles, Mumps, Rubella Virus Vaccine at a vaccine clinic put on by Lubbock Public Health Department, March 1, 2025, in Lubbock, Texas.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="qinlA IpWvx oqZz tylGM lyWxS nWcVF UhTug PPcLh "&gt;&lt;span class="gtOSm FbbUW tUtYa vOCwz EQwFq yCufu eEak Qmvg nyTIa SRXVc vzLa jgBfc WXDas CiUCW kqbG zrdEG txGfn ygKVe BbezD UOtxr CVfpq xijV soGRS XgdC sEIlf daWqJ YNujN JGtjI aZFDu rkKLh "&gt;Jan Sonnenmair/Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Six states are currently battling significant outbreaks, defined as three or more related cases: Texas, New Mexico, Ohio, Kansas, Indiana, and Michigan.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;The virus has been found in 24 states overall, including Alaska, Arkansas, California, Colorado, Florida, Georgia, Hawaii, Kentucky, Maryland, Minnesota, New Jersey, New York, Oklahoma, Pennsylvania, Rhode Island, Tennessee, Vermont, and Washington.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Health officials report that 96% of this year's cases have occurred in unvaccinated individuals or those with unknown vaccination status.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;The surge threatens the nation's measles elimination status, which was achieved in 2000 when the United States recorded no continuous spread over 12 months. The current outbreak, which began in Texas in January, could jeopardize this status if it continues for more than a year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;The CDC notes that the reported numbers likely underrepresent the true scope of the outbreak due to reporting delays.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Measles is a highly contagious viral infection that spreads through coughing and sneezing. According to the CDC, the virus can live up to two hours in the air after an infected person leaves a room.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Early symptoms typically include high fever, cough, runny nose, and watery eyes. The characteristic rash appears three to five days after the first symptoms. A person can spread the virus four days before and four days after the rash appears.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;The CDC emphasizes that the measles, mumps, rubella (MMR) vaccine is highly effective at preventing infection, with two doses being 97% effective against the virus. Children should receive their first dose between 12 to 15 months of age and a second dose between 4 to 6 years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC eTIW sUzSN "&gt;International travel by unvaccinated individuals has historically been a significant factor in bringing measles into the United States. The CDC recommends that all international travelers be fully vaccinated against measles before departure, regardless of their destination.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ABC News</author><pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 22:44:34 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimwFBVV95cUxPMDNCQ3Ayc2dtUGx0TElmOE56OHV1d0VWLTFXcXhrNzF0ZWJiMkNVSzlRaERMZUZmZ2pRSTM2ZndaeGVRYWZzWUJrNlhUd3dwbDZ3cHNxYW8zLVZGQnBCdFlYbFpqcWlLeGZXM0xmcUFmSTJoOHA4LWlEbzVzbnB2T0lmLXBUVlhla0djZE1RdTVEY204aUUxNTlpQdIBoAFBVV95cUxQaXAyRXVRTmRKRndfdWtkX3UzRU83cmFFTWY0eWd4TjRCV1ZtbWh0dnZhN1c4WUpsMk5GRlpFSHo4aTFYamhuMUFvT3BEenhCcDBId3NSbnZDNE9Zb0RIVnN6ZV83Y1NIR2MwNTJ5X2RpeUpYUDBPUW5tWlNXTGMxQmhPRkNIdGVhWmZ2eDVWMmwwdHUzR1kwU2p0c3MzN0Na</guid></item><item><title>哥伦比亚政府因黄热病病例增加宣布卫生紧急状态- CNN | Colombian government declares health emergency due to increase in yellow fever cases - CNN</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiogFBVV95cUxPdGR3b1Q2MGgyYXZwMGotQS1KNWw1bU1JVE4yeURNZ1Y3alkzcGNJd1h1M2c1alk1ZjhPd3Z6M0JhVGF1Z3hZMnQtRTJfeHN2NDhoRFZNcHVxQ3lVbVlSY1UwTTJ5OUE2dmxxNktvWHF2Y1M5QVJKMThlLVJRUUVuZ3lFTGhmU1hFcnk1a0p1aDhXdkFFRklpYmFFUU55WU01cnfSAZgBQVVfeXFMUG9HNVU3TUZ0LXBMTUN1MXFGenZHWnk5b1A2ZnZPZFRSckZjblVPTDFENFN4Q04zM1cycEk0WW1ETFI4UzJtd3ZYV1BaNVZkNXBFR19rMzFneXBNYXZMVHlWN2w1VFI1YlAxRVM3UldEWXhFRGp2V0dST3dVb1JyUFF4WUp4ZlZjbFRCcFJhQlRfNEF5VVVYd3E?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article__content" data-editable="content" itemprop="articleBody" data-reorderable="content"&gt;
                &lt;p data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/source/instances/cm9nawwuz002q26p39ml579wq@published" data-component-name="source" class="source inline-placeholder" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
    &lt;cite class="source__cite"&gt;
      &lt;span class="source__location" data-editable="location"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;span class="source__text" data-editable="source"&gt;CNN&lt;/span&gt;
         — 
    &lt;/cite&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cm9nawwuz002r26p34cji09ri@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Colombia’s health ministry declared a nationwide health emergency on Thursday due to the “active circulation” of yellow fever.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cm9nax59t0002356qhkd5ab7o@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Since September 2024, there have been 75 recorded cases of yellow fever and 34 deaths from the illness, according to the Colombian Health Ministry.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cm9nax59t0003356q2z69kpqr@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Nine of the country’s 32 departments have reported at least one case of yellow fever. Most were detected in rural areas of the Tolima and Meta departments, the Amazon basin, and the Magdalena River region.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cm9nax59t0004356qiu9ijh46@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Cases have also been reported in areas where the virus has not been historically located, such as the coffee-growing Caldas region, according to the president’s office.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cm9nax59t0005356q3p3onppr@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Some regions were already under alert before it was extended nationwide due to the expected surge in travel during Easter weekend. Travel to some zones with a critical virus presence will also be restricted under the health emergency.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cm9nawztv0000356q5dho4m10@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Yellow fever is a disease that is transmitted to humans by the bites of infected mosquitoes.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cm9nb6q6i000r356qr55jrhbd@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Many people do not experience symptoms from the disease, while others experience fever, muscle pain, headache, loss of appetite, nausea or vomiting, &lt;a href="https://www.who.int/news-room/fact-sheets/detail/yellow-fever" target="_blank"&gt;according &lt;/a&gt;to the WHO. In most cases, symptoms disappear after three to four days.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cm9nb6q6i000s356qumns0bf1@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            However, some patients enter a second phase of illness in which they develop jaundice and abdominal pain, among other symptoms. Half the patients who enter this phase die within seven to 10 days, according to the WHO.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cm9nb6q6i000t356qijatq75b@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            There is no specific anti-viral drug treatment for yellow fever; the WHO advises that patients rest, stay hydrated, and seek medical attention as needed.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cm9nax59t0006356q608zid5t@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The office of President Gustavo Petro urged Colombians to receive the single-dose vaccine, which is free and can be administered to anyone older than nine months.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cm9nax59t0007356q8njbgg9f@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Medical teams would be deployed to administer vaccines in the affected areas, the office announced.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cm9nax59t0008356qwca1ajnx@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “In two months, the entire Colombian population must be vaccinated against yellow fever,” Petro said on X. “We must do this, and our health system must guarantee it.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cm9nax59u0009356q0zyq86kj@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Petro added that he would declare an economic emergency due to the situation.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cm9nax59u000a356qcv28tygl@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Petro’s office said that the Ministry of Health and the National Health Institute have deployed more than 20 immediate response teams to investigate the spread of the disease.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cm9nax59u000b356q9kx40fwa@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “We have already asked each territorial entity to have a hospital to which people suffering from the disease can go, so that we can exercise clear and definitive control over them from there,” Health Minister Guillermo Alfonso Jaramillo stated to local media.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cm9nax59u000c356qt22snnp3@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Some opposing political figures argued that the government’s response to the disease comes too late.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cm9nax59u000d356qs07fq088@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “It is unacceptable for the government to declare a health and economic emergency for yellow fever when the crisis started six months ago,” said Senator Paloma Valencia from the Democratic Center party. “Decisions should have been made a long time ago to prevent deaths.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cm9nax59u000e356qqkn0uyu2@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Petro will hold a broadcast cabinet meeting on emergency measures to prevent the spread of the virus and release a new report on the progress of the disease on Monday.
    &lt;/p&gt;

              &lt;/div&gt;
                            &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>CNN</author><pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 22:16:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiogFBVV95cUxPdGR3b1Q2MGgyYXZwMGotQS1KNWw1bU1JVE4yeURNZ1Y3alkzcGNJd1h1M2c1alk1ZjhPd3Z6M0JhVGF1Z3hZMnQtRTJfeHN2NDhoRFZNcHVxQ3lVbVlSY1UwTTJ5OUE2dmxxNktvWHF2Y1M5QVJKMThlLVJRUUVuZ3lFTGhmU1hFcnk1a0p1aDhXdkFFRklpYmFFUU55WU01cnfSAZgBQVVfeXFMUG9HNVU3TUZ0LXBMTUN1MXFGenZHWnk5b1A2ZnZPZFRSckZjblVPTDFENFN4Q04zM1cycEk0WW1ETFI4UzJtd3ZYV1BaNVZkNXBFR19rMzFneXBNYXZMVHlWN2w1VFI1YlAxRVM3UldEWXhFRGp2V0dST3dVb1JyUFF4WUp4ZlZjbFRCcFJhQlRfNEF5VVVYd3E</guid></item><item><title>根据一项新的研究，您不应该尝试低碳水化合物饮食的首要原因- EatingWell | The #1 Reason You Shouldn’t Try a Low-Carb Diet, According to a New Study - EatingWell</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMid0FVX3lxTE1JaDRoN0pkdDZEdHN2X0pGZW1EX3hLblVMcFZjVDZHV092ZFRoVWxlYS1Calo0dC12RjZQZGtMWG96M3VzclVqaXBGMFd1V21PZFF4RWsyS0MxMlBycE5oWkM0Zk9ET3VQV3licTRMSWRVS053ZVBR?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-page_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-page mntl-block structured-content" data-sc-sticky-offset="90" data-sc-ad-label-height="24" data-sc-ad-track-spacing="100" data-sc-min-track-height="250" data-sc-max-track-height="600" data-sc-breakpoint="50em" data-sc-load-immediate="4" data-sc-content-positions="[1, 1250, 1550, 1950, 2350, 2750, 3150, 3550, 3950]" data-bind-scroll-on-start="true"&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-block_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-callout mntl-sc-block-universal-callout theme-blockquote" data-tracking-id="mntl-sc-block-callout" data-tracking-container="true"&gt;
&lt;div class="mntl-sc-block-universal-callout__body"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Takeaways&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Low-carb diets may lead to deficiencies of micronutrients like vitamin C, iron and magnesium.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;While supplements may help, you should consult a doctor or dietitian before starting them.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Eating diverse foods can help ensure you consume a healthy amount of vitamins and minerals.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="theme-blockquote__author_1-0" class="comp theme-blockquote__author mntl-text-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_2-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Rates of obesity are rising, and it seems like more people are trying specialized diets, particularly those that cut back on carbohydrates.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="1"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Currently, more than 40% of adults in the United States experience obesity, and while &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/best-foods-to-eat-for-dinner-for-weight-loss-11696366" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;many aim to lose weight&lt;/a&gt;, keeping that weight off remains a significant challenge as obesity rates continue to grow.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="2"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_3-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_4-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; According to the International Food Information Council, 43% of people believe carbohydrates or sugars are &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/8024124/best-carb-for-weight-loss/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;the main cause of weight gain&lt;/a&gt;. But only 25% of folks see calories from all sources as contributing to weight gain.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="3"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; However, scientific studies suggest that &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/291554/30-day-low-carb-meal-plan-1200-calories/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;cutting carbs&lt;/a&gt; doesn’t offer significant weight loss benefits when the total number of calories consumed is the same.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="4"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; And there are downsides to a low-carb diet, too—some research suggests that cutting back on carbohydrates can lead to inadequacies in key vitamins and minerals.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="5"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_5-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_6-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; To shed more light on those concerns, a group of researchers analyzed data to help figure out if adults on low-carb diets are missing out on some macronutrients and, if so, which ones. They published their work, which also includes insights about how fat may affect macronutrient intake, in the &lt;em&gt;Journal of the Academy of Nutrition and Dietetics&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="4"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_7-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_9-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-how-was-this-study-conducted"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_10-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; How Was This Study Conducted? &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_11-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; This study relies on data collected as part of a large, ongoing health study called the National Health and Nutrition Examination Survey (NHANES), which is conducted by the Centers for Disease Control. These researchers focused on data from adults aged 20 years or older that was collected from 2007 to 2018, which resulted in just over 15,000 participants for the study. On average, the participants were 48 years old.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_12-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_13-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Participants in the study were divided into two main groups based on the percentage of calories they consumed from carbohydrates, which was determined based on food surveys that participants took. The first group included those with a carbohydrate intake of less than 45% of their total energy, referred to as the "restricted carbohydrate" group. The second group included those whose diets met established guidelines for carbohydrates (45% to 65% of energy), as well as for other nutrients like fats, protein and specific fatty acids. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_14-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_15-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Intake of certain nutrients, like vitamins A, B12, C, D and E, as well as folate, iron, calcium, magnesium and zinc, were assessed to see how many people might not be getting enough when following the lower carb dietary pattern. They also checked how many people consume too much sodium. The research analyzed what people get from food alone and, for most nutrients, also included supplements.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_16-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_17-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; To further understand the role of fats, the restricted carbohydrate group was split into smaller subgroups based on how much fat they consumed. These subgroups looked at total fat and the types of fat, such as monounsaturated, polyunsaturated and saturated fats to analyze intakes of certain nutrients. By analyzing these patterns, researchers aimed to identify connections between dietary intake and nutrient deficiencies across the population.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_18-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_20-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-what-did-the-study-find"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_21-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; What Did the Study Find? &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_22-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Compared to the group that followed the recommended dietary ranges, those in the low-carb group were slightly less likely to be women, more likely to have finished college, and had a higher income compared to their household needs. The low-carb group consumed fewer carbohydrates but more protein, more fat and more alcohol compared to the recommended group.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_23-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_24-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; People following a diet low in carbohydrates were more likely to have too little of certain minerals and vitamins compared to those who followed a balanced diet that met all recommended intake ranges. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_25-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_26-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Specifically, the low-carb group was more likely to be deficient in:
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_27-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_28-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;li&gt;Iron &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Magnesium &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Vitamin A &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Folate &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Vitamin C &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Vitamin D &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_29-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_30-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; On the brighter side, the low-carb group was less likely to be deficient in zinc and vitamin B12. Those on a lower carb diet were likely to consume more &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/foods-rich-in-vitamin-k-8635254" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;vitamin K&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/choline-dementia-study-8779484" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;choline&lt;/a&gt; than recommended, but they also ate more sodium than recommended.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_31-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_32-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; When people following a low-carb diet were grouped by how much total fat they ate, further patterns emerged regarding their nutrient levels. For instance, those on a low-carb, low-fat diet were more likely to consume less calcium and vitamin E than recommended. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_33-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_35-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_36-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; And different types of fat were linked to different intakes of certain nutrients as well. For example, the research team investigated how monounsaturated fatty acid (MUFA) intake affected nutrient levels in people on low-carb diets. They found that a low-carb, low-MUFA diet often led to overconsumption of sodium and underconsumption of vitamin E, while a high-MUFA diet supported healthy potassium intake. MUFAs are found in foods &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/is-olive-oil-good-for-you-8766002" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;like olive oil&lt;/a&gt; and avocado. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_37-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_38-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Researchers also looked into similar relationships between some micronutrients and polyunsaturated fats and saturated fat, finding, for example, that a diet lower in saturated fat was more likely to support healthy calcium intake. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_39-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_40-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; These findings suggest that the relationship between carbohydrate restriction and micronutrient inadequacy is dependent on the amount and type of fat intake, which has implications for clinical practice.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_41-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_42-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; It’s important to note a few limitations when considering this data. The information about food intake came from self-reports, which can sometimes be inaccurate due to personal bias or errors in recall. Additionally, participants were grouped into the carb-restricted category regardless of whether they were intentionally following this type of diet or not. Lastly, everyone with a carbohydrate intake below 45% of their total energy was grouped together, but it’s possible that varying levels of carbohydrate restriction could lead to different outcomes.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_43-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_45-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-how-does-this-apply-to-real-life"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_46-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; How Does This Apply to Real Life? &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_47-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; For those considering a low-carbohydrate diet, these findings highlight some practical takeaways that can guide healthier choices. While reducing carbohydrates might seem like a straightforward way to manage weight, it’s essential to understand the potential trade-offs.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_48-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_49-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Cutting back on carbs without carefully planning your diet can lead to deficiencies in essential vitamins and minerals like magnesium, vitamin C and folate. These nutrients play vital roles in energy production, immune function and overall health, so it’s crucial to make adjustments to ensure you’re not missing out on them.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_50-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_51-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Supplementation can be a useful strategy to address nutrient gaps, especially for individuals following more restrictive diet plans. But it’s important to remember that supplementation isn't a one-size-fits-all solution. Consulting with a healthcare provider or a dietitian ensures personalized advice tailored to your specific diet, lifestyle and health needs. They can help assess whether supplements are necessary and recommend the right dosage to complement your diet safely and effectively.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_52-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_53-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; A balanced approach to low-carb eating can make all the difference. Incorporating diverse food groups, such as leafy greens, nuts, seeds and lean proteins, can help mitigate the risk of nutrient deficiencies while still reaping the benefits of carbohydrate reduction. By paying attention to dietary quality and seeking professional input when needed, you can pursue your health goals while maintaining optimal nutrition and well-being.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_54-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_56-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-the-bottom-line"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_57-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; The Bottom Line &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_58-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; A new study in the &lt;em&gt;Journal of the Academy of Nutrition and Dietetics&lt;/em&gt; highlights potential nutritional gaps among people who follow a low-carbohydrate diet. While many people turn to these diets to shed excess weight, it comes with potential downsides, including deficiencies in some vitamins, iron, magnesium and folate. Micronutrient deficiencies can compromise energy levels, immune support and long-term health outcomes. These risks emphasize the necessity of a well-structured diet (or even strategic supplementation) to avoid any nutritional gaps while following a low-carb lifestyle.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_59-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_60-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Ultimately, the takeaway is clear—diet quality matters just as much as diet quantity. For those choosing a low-carb approach, prioritizing nutrient-dense foods is essential to ensure proper health and functionality. This might mean incorporating foods like spinach, avocados, nuts, and berries, which can supply vital vitamins and minerals typically missing from low-carb meal plans. By making informed adjustments, consulting with health professionals and tailoring dietary choices to individual needs, those pursuing low-carb diets can achieve more sustainable and healthful outcomes.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_61-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>EatingWell</author><pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 21:46:18 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMid0FVX3lxTE1JaDRoN0pkdDZEdHN2X0pGZW1EX3hLblVMcFZjVDZHV092ZFRoVWxlYS1Calo0dC12RjZQZGtMWG96M3VzclVqaXBGMFd1V21PZFF4RWsyS0MxMlBycE5oWkM0Zk9ET3VQV3licTRMSWRVS053ZVBR</guid></item><item><title>RFK Jr.对CDC的削减消除了跟踪性传播感染、肝炎爆发的实验室-《华盛顿邮报》 | RFK Jr.’s cuts to CDC eliminate labs tracking STIs, hepatitis outbreaks - The Washington Post</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMinwFBVV95cUxOWk0zSktqd3FVLXVMSFQxWVZaQWxNakt6UUl1MlFJM0RjSzhheEx5NW16N0dORnp4ZDV0UWRJc0FFTWFoaXA3eEdvOHFZWXNKZjVvVkhyY1Jrd3cyWk54emM5XzVJTWxEUWw5VzltSnJzcEpMUW9QaVQ2OGloU2xac2FUNTlNNDlDcTAtNFNWU2xFc254RkhyVWg0LW1IeG8?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="meteredContent grid-center"&gt;&lt;div class="teaser-content"&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="NH4ZSXN6VNEFFLYBYZZJGXDBQY" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Lab scientists at the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention had been analyzing blood samples for weeks to determine how dozens of&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;patients across six states had become infected with &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/health/2024/04/14/hepatitis-infections-deaths-rising/"&gt;viral hepatitis,&lt;/a&gt; a disease that can cause serious liver damage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-subscribe-cta" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="JNPGLJY5B5AY5N5L6LDPZ3ZMAE" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;But their DNA detective work stopped abruptly last week. &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/health/2025/04/01/hhs-senior-leaders-put-on-leave-nih/"&gt;Widespread layoffs&lt;/a&gt; across federal health agencies earlier this month had resulted in the firing of all 27 lab scientists who worked in the only U.S. facility that could perform the sophisticated genetic sequencing needed to investigate hepatitis outbreaks, lab experts said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="F7EKXAAZBRD3ZAAQ2NL6437DYM" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Another lab, the only one in the United States capable of testing for and tracking &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/news/to-your-health/wp/2018/03/29/our-greatest-fear-highly-drug-resistant-gonorrhea-confirmed-by-health-officials/"&gt;antibiotic-resistant gonorrhea&lt;/a&gt;, often called &lt;a href="https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jama/article-abstract/2818437"&gt;“super gonorrhea,”&lt;/a&gt; was also recently effectively shut down.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="CYD3QAS64BCC3LYSK6SBUUF6J4" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;The lab firings were part of the 2,400 staff laid off from the CDC. While officials at the Department of Health and Human Services have said the job reductions are aimed at refocusing the agency “on emerging and infectious disease surveillance, outbreak investigations, preparedness and response,” lab experts say the reductions contradict that goal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="N7BMPVYIB5EYLAWUSKPJKWQK2A" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;“CDC cannot focus on infectious disease prevention and response without all CDC laboratories being intact and fully supported,” wrote Scott Becker, chief executive of the Association of Public Health Laboratories, which represents state and local public health labs across the U.S.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-topic-follow-interstitial" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="XXMIVZASZVFHVHBITOEYQVWB6I" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;The group has written a letter to Health Secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr. asking for the personnel to be reinstated. “Their loss eliminated critical national testing services that do not exist anywhere else within the HHS agencies,” the letter said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="S2XNVI4BSNG5JK3N7JCL5MFZKQ" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;“In essence, we’re flying blind,” Becker said in an interview.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="QZ56U44CNBEFHKOW6Y4BEFITQ4" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;An HHS spokesperson did not respond to a request for comment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="AC7JJQGZIZDZBCWG6P35JTBHPA" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;The increase in hepatitis C infections has been “stupendous in the past 20 to 25 years,” said Judith Feinberg, a professor of medicine and infectious diseases at West Virginia University.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="B3S2W7WYOVAT7PXANRYHJZBVJM" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;“The CDC lab was capable of showing the genetic linkage between isolates of virus … and that helps you control it from public health policy. It helps you understand how and where disease is spreading, how the virus is evolving,” Feinberg said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="RHCACSJPNBA3DASCLBM6WFVQ4Q" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Though hepatitis can be &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/hepatitis/abc/index.htm"&gt;caused&lt;/a&gt; by heavy alcohol use and some medications, it can also be sparked by a virus that causes liver inflammation, jaundice, fever and other symptoms. Tens of thousands of new cases of viral hepatitis occur every year in the U.S., according to the CDC. &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/hepatitis/hcp/clinical-overview/index.html"&gt;Viral hepatitis&lt;/a&gt; kills thousands of Americans every year and is a leading cause of liver cancer. The three most common viruses that cause hepatitis are hepatitis A, hepatitis B and hepatitis C, and depending on the type can be spread through close contact, consuming contaminated food, sharing needles or contact with infected blood.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="IXHNKF7QTVA53F7H562FUTFK7A" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;In recent years, hepatitis C outbreaks have been linked to pain clinics, dialysis facilities, outpatient surgery clinics and prisons, according to CDC data. Other labs can provide testing to confirm whether someone has hepatitis, but they cannot perform the genetic testing to identify whether someone’s infection is part of a transmission cluster, lab experts said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="4KCD5AXOVZATFPON4NHVE4VLCU" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;The CDC’s viral hepatitis lab had already identified nine infected patients in a Florida outbreak and had begun receiving blood samples from additional patients to piece together how the outbreak spread when scientists were fired, according to internal CDC documents and two lab scientists who spoke on the condition of anonymity for fear of retribution. The lab would have used its advanced technology to identify whether additional patients carried the same strain of the virus, which would mean they were part of the same transmission cluster, the employee said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="DBQ4F6X45RCF5F6CSQUFWVNTVY" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Last week, the CDC sent an email to state and local health departments and other partners saying it was no longer providing viral-hepatitis-related laboratory services, according to a copy obtained by The Washington Post. “Specimen submissions will no longer be accepted,” the email said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="MUBMKL6B35CETM2CCAIXSDMY4E" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;It’s unclear how states will handle future cases. A spokesperson for the Florida Department of Health did not respond to request for comment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="RDTSAY2C65CT7LSVTDUKSNJEUQ" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;The CDC’s 77 staff members who worked on preventing sexually transmitted diseases were also fired, including 49 staff who were embedded in state health departments helping with STI outbreak investigations, and all 28 scientists in the lab that provides surveillance for chlamydia, gonorrhea and syphilis, and other sexually transmitted infections in the U.S., according to employees and outside lab experts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="UEC2RGUJ4ZFRFEKWRSMMLQSBCU" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;“They are one of three laboratories in the world and the only in the U.S. that performs extensive antimicrobial susceptibility testing for gonorrhea,” said Kelly Wroblewski, director of infectious-disease programs at the Association of Public Health Laboratories. That’s especially important for “super gonorrhea” that has been able to outsmart all five common drugs used to treat it, she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="LCBPEZRGQJGOBLNCGSAG3D3I6I" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;The information about which antibiotics are no longer working against the disease is then used to update recommendations for doctors treating STIs, she said. The CDC relies on this information to provide the most up-to-date recommendations, she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="OJB73ILR5FCGNATFTA2OEUWRFY" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;More than 2 million sexually transmitted infections were diagnosed and reported in the U.S. in 2023, the latest data available, including more than 600,000 cases of &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/gonorrhea/about/index.html"&gt;gonorrhea, &lt;/a&gt;according to the CDC. While there are signs that the gonorrhea and &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/health/2024/02/01/syphilis-cases-surge-united-states/"&gt;syphilis&lt;/a&gt; epidemics are slowing, chlamydia, gonorrhea and syphilis infections are 90 percent higher than 20 years ago, data shows.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="FR36IWP44FF67GLKDNRTD7VYBU" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Untreated gonorrhea in women can cause serious and permanent health problems. It can cause pelvic inflammatory disease, which can lead to scarring, ectopic pregnancies and infertility.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="U6E7V24HIVCLNE4W6MUECLOLNY" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;The lab’s work was critical for clinicians. Last week, the CDC notified state and local health departments that it was no longer taking any specimens.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="EETPISGXUFH4LD5JRNVWMW7W2U" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;“We have seen highly resistant gonorrhea become a problem in other countries,” said Colleen Kelley, a professor of medicine at Emory University who treats patients with HIV and sexually transmitted infections.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="3MM2VZAHXNBOBBYV4VENVWTSWQ" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Without the lab, Kelley said, “no one will tell us if we are seeing more cases of this, and no one will be there to sound the alarm bells.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 21:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMinwFBVV95cUxOWk0zSktqd3FVLXVMSFQxWVZaQWxNakt6UUl1MlFJM0RjSzhheEx5NW16N0dORnp4ZDV0UWRJc0FFTWFoaXA3eEdvOHFZWXNKZjVvVkhyY1Jrd3cyWk54emM5XzVJTWxEUWw5VzltSnJzcEpMUW9QaVQ2OGloU2xac2FUNTlNNDlDcTAtNFNWU2xFc254RkhyVWg0LW1IeG8</guid></item><item><title>我的孩子们认为我因为“坏”的原因而与他们的父亲离婚。如果他们只知道一半。-石板 | My Kids Believe I Divorced Their Dad for a “Bad” Reason. If They Only Knew the Half of It. - Slate</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMidEFVX3lxTE1zcnE1YlV2VHV0SUU4eXpBbWxEZTB5X1haX2ZQdzdPUF81WHZCdUU2bVR6a182WjhxalpSY3Z2M3NycDdJeWpvMkJMck1DTjk3eWVXdjdLYjI5b3dGSGtBRUt0LU5yU3NWbGRfRDU2YVdXOURN?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article__content" itemprop="mainEntityOfPage"&gt;
          &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="19" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cm9n81g1f00102xks55t31ozu@published"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Slate Plus members get more &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="https://slate.com/human-interest/care-and-feeding"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Care and Feeding&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt; every week. Have a question about kids, parenting, or family life? &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="https://forms.gle/4BXEw8Wtcd7aAyXh9"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Submit it here&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="4" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cm9n89vr3002h35758lqiu8cw@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dear Care and Feeding, &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="179" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cm9n89vu6002i3575frujrgl5@published"&gt;I divorced my children’s dad for a “bad” reason in their minds, and they are so angry, and I’m not sure how to work through it with them. My kids are 18 and 20, and in college. In their narrative (and their dad’s), I filed for divorce the instant the youngest went to college because I hated their grandma and wanted her to die alone. To me, it’s more complicated. In 2023, my MIL moved in with us for emergency caregiving for Alzheimer’s. She and my husband weren’t close. He was a surprise youngest kid and she openly resented him for it in childhood, although she apologized a few years ago. It seemed like he was trying to make it up to her by taking her in. His older siblings suggested a nursing home, and offered to help arrange it. She could afford it, even. Instead, he moved her in without consulting me, and she needed a lot of help. She could be pretty mean even before the dementia removed her filter, so once that happened, things really deteriorated.&lt;/p&gt;



  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="90" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cm9n81g1f00132xksu3l3rbuc@published"&gt;After two years of burnout, anger, and exhaustion, I fell out of love. We had multiple conversations and even marriage counseling about the ways his unilateral decisions were hurting our marriage. The last straw was his refusal to the idea of a home health aide after she accidentally set a small fire and needed daytime supervision. Instead, he suggested I take FMLA (he’s already used his) or go part-time to stay home with her. I realized he wasn’t even trying to look out for his mom’s best interests, or mine.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="98" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cm9n8a3xe002n3575yk95hb1w@published"&gt;I filed for divorce, and he immediately told our kids that it was because I hated Grandma and didn’t want to care for others. It hit on a painful point for me and the kids; I was the primary earner with long hours for all of their middle school years because their dad was unemployed. I never got to spend as much time with them as I wanted, and I know they resent that. So to them, it feels like more of the same. What can I do to make room for their pain but not get excommunicated?&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="1" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cm9n8a3xf002o3575areuxaeo@published"&gt;—Miserable&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="2" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cm9n8a3xf002p3575vi4fybjd@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dear Miserable, &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="86" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cm9n8a3xf002q3575qfs98iuh@published"&gt;Your reasons for leaving the marriage are quite fair; your husband refused to do what was best for his mother (out of a field of options that not everyone has) and instead, chose a situation, without your input, that was untenable for you. Of course, that doesn’t stop your kids from being hurt over the divorce, but you aren’t responsible for their pain. Your children are young adults; they’re old enough to handle the truth about why you split from their father. Be honest with them.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="107" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cm9n8a6gp002u3575dpb5mypl@published"&gt;Talk to them about what life was like with your MIL and their father’s refusal to get her the sort of help she needs. Acknowledge that the idea of you “refusing” to be around may be triggering because of their childhood experiences, but let them know you did everything within reason to make things work, until you simply couldn’t anymore. Be empathetic and let them know that you know the divorce hurts them; give them the space to express their grief while still standing up for yourself. It may take them some time to understand, but hopefully, they’ll come to respect the way you advocated for yourself.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="1" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cm9n8aawh002y3575de8k8ea3@published"&gt; &lt;span class="slate-paragraph--tombstone"&gt;—Jamilah&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  

&lt;/div&gt;

      &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Slate</author><pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 20:45:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMidEFVX3lxTE1zcnE1YlV2VHV0SUU4eXpBbWxEZTB5X1haX2ZQdzdPUF81WHZCdUU2bVR6a182WjhxalpSY3Z2M3NycDdJeWpvMkJMck1DTjk3eWVXdjdLYjI5b3dGSGtBRUt0LU5yU3NWbGRfRDU2YVdXOURN</guid></item><item><title>卫生和工作场所安全官员调查医院工作人员的脑肿瘤- WCVB | Health, workplace safety officials investigate brain tumors in Hospital staff - WCVB</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMikwFBVV95cUxNaGk5eFhOdzdrdTdpbnNFV0VYVUF3aWYxTHJPN1Zra1ZMVDliUGhIUlIyS2c0S182SXZZYWVKbS03MVRPbndsWFVBMml2dlJicUtCb3lEN1VXTHJRR1M2ejFJeXN2RXo3R1BhQUJPOFFTay1WNmg0WXpfZk9FT0M4X0ZObm9teVhGaW9JWVdPbjZfNVU?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="article-content--body-text-raw"&gt;
						Health and workplace safety officials inspected a Massachusetts hospital this week after at least six staff members developed benign brain tumors over several years. Their visits are the latest in a series of investigations seeking answers about the mysterious cases. Affected staff members worked on the fifth floor of Newton-Wellesley Hospital, in the post-partum and labor and delivery units, over many years. Representatives of the Occupational Safety and Health Administration and the Massachusetts Department of Health conducted their inspection of the labor and delivery unit on Wednesday, DPH confirmed. Additionally, DPH's Division of Radiation Control Program was scheduled to visit the hospital on Friday to review information provided by the hospital's radiation safety officer and perform measurements of their own.DPH confirmed their work with OSHA, but the federal agency has not yet responded to a request for a statement. Hospital officials said they conducted their own investigation of the facility and found no evidence that the tumors were caused by the work environment. "Based on these findings, we are confident that no environmental risks are linked to these cases," Mass General Brigham officials said in a statement. Newton-Wellesley Hospital is a part of the Mass General Brigham hospital group. The Massachusetts Nurses Association declined to provide a statement, citing their own ongoing investigation of the situation. Mass General Brigham statement:“The health and wellbeing of our staff, clinicians, and patients is our top priority and we have conducted a thorough investigation into our environment after reports of brain tumors in individuals who have worked in our labor and delivery and post-partum care units at some point over the past 23 years. Based on these findings, we are confident that no environmental risks are linked to these cases. We continue to support our colleagues.This scientific investigation was conducted by external environmental consultants in collaboration with our Department of Occupational Health and Safety, Newton-Wellesley Safety Officer, radiation and pharmaceutical safety offices. Alongside evaluating potential environmental exposures, individuals with concerns were given the opportunity to be interviewed by the Occupational Health and Safety team to evaluate each diagnosis in the context of their individual medical history and risk factors.We continue to collaborate with state and federal regulatory agencies and provide the results of our investigation to the relevant stakeholder groups, including staff and the Massachusetts Nurses Association, and have held multiple forums to meet with clinical and Occupational Health leaders to answer their questions. To be clear, our rigorous investigation has not identified any environmental trigger at Newton-Wellesley Hospital that causes brain tumors. We remain confident that our environment is safe for staff, clinicians, and patients.”-Jonathan Sonis, MD, MHCM, Associate Chief Medical Officer and Vice President of Medical Affairs-Sandy Muse, DNP, FNP-BC, NEA-BC, Chief Nursing Officer and Senior Vice President of Patient Care Services
					&lt;/p&gt;
	
					&lt;div class="article-content--body-text"&gt;
						&lt;strong class="dateline"&gt;NEWTON, Mass. —&lt;/strong&gt; 													&lt;p&gt;Health and workplace safety officials inspected a Massachusetts hospital this week after at least six staff members developed benign brain tumors over several years. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Their visits are the latest in a series of investigations seeking answers about the mysterious cases. &lt;/p&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Affected staff members worked on the fifth floor of Newton-Wellesley Hospital, in the post-partum and labor and delivery units, over many years. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Representatives of the Occupational Safety and Health Administration and the Massachusetts Department of Health conducted their inspection of the labor and delivery unit on Wednesday, DPH confirmed. Additionally, DPH's Division of Radiation Control Program was scheduled to visit the hospital on Friday to review information provided by the hospital's radiation safety officer and perform measurements of their own.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;DPH confirmed their work with OSHA, but the federal agency has not yet responded to a request for a statement. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hospital officials said they conducted their own investigation of the facility and found no evidence that the tumors were caused by the work environment. &lt;/p&gt;


&lt;p&gt;"Based on these findings, we are confident that no environmental risks are linked to these cases," Mass General Brigham officials said in a statement. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="cream-inline-rec" class="cream-inline hidden"&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Newton-Wellesley Hospital is a part of the Mass General Brigham hospital group. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Massachusetts Nurses Association declined to provide a statement, citing their own ongoing investigation of the situation. &lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h2 class="body-h2" id="mass-general-brigham-statement"&gt;Mass General Brigham statement:&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The health and wellbeing of our staff, clinicians, and patients is our top priority and we have conducted a thorough investigation into our environment after reports of brain tumors in individuals who have worked in our labor and delivery and post-partum care units at some point over the past 23 years. Based on these findings, we are confident that no environmental risks are linked to these cases. We continue to support our colleagues.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This scientific investigation was conducted by external environmental consultants in collaboration with our Department of Occupational Health and Safety, Newton-Wellesley Safety Officer, radiation and pharmaceutical safety offices. Alongside evaluating potential environmental exposures, individuals with concerns were given the opportunity to be interviewed by the Occupational Health and Safety team to evaluate each diagnosis in the context of their individual medical history and risk factors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We continue to collaborate with state and federal regulatory agencies and provide the results of our investigation to the relevant stakeholder groups, including staff and the Massachusetts Nurses Association, and have held multiple forums to meet with clinical and Occupational Health leaders to answer their questions. To be clear, our rigorous investigation has not identified any environmental trigger at Newton-Wellesley Hospital that causes brain tumors. We remain confident that our environment is safe for staff, clinicians, and patients.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;-Jonathan Sonis, MD, MHCM, Associate Chief Medical Officer and Vice President of Medical Affairs&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;-Sandy Muse, DNP, FNP-BC, NEA-BC, Chief Nursing Officer and Senior Vice President of Patient Care Services&lt;/p&gt;

							
											&lt;/div&gt;
	
	
						
						
														&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>WCVB</author><pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 19:43:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikwFBVV95cUxNaGk5eFhOdzdrdTdpbnNFV0VYVUF3aWYxTHJPN1Zra1ZMVDliUGhIUlIyS2c0S182SXZZYWVKbS03MVRPbndsWFVBMml2dlJicUtCb3lEN1VXTHJRR1M2ejFJeXN2RXo3R1BhQUJPOFFTay1WNmg0WXpfZk9FT0M4X0ZObm9teVhGaW9JWVdPbjZfNVU</guid></item><item><title>视频显示医生正在治疗儿童麻疹。小RFK后来称赞他是一位“非凡”的治疗师-美联社新闻 | Video shows doctor with measles treating kids. RFK Jr later praised him as an ‘extraordinary’ healer - AP News</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiowFBVV95cUxNOFUzV0RlS3pLMGJLUHhQeTFLa013cV9XOXlCMmw2OGRRNm9nV1U2bjZPUGY5Qmt4VXRzVklhcUhQVUdpd1FIbU50V25xRHF6UzMxand4Sk0yYWdDQnBHbDZsZTA1UHBIQkY2YV9HSmh6NV9JUnNOVVhDZ2NrRzVjYldCeDlseVdWRnBWTEUwYXAzQ0IwVDRLMjlMSWZBMkxnS3pN?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>AP News</author><pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 19:09:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiowFBVV95cUxNOFUzV0RlS3pLMGJLUHhQeTFLa013cV9XOXlCMmw2OGRRNm9nV1U2bjZPUGY5Qmt4VXRzVklhcUhQVUdpd1FIbU50V25xRHF6UzMxand4Sk0yYWdDQnBHbDZsZTA1UHBIQkY2YV9HSmh6NV9JUnNOVVhDZ2NrRzVjYldCeDlseVdWRnBWTEUwYXAzQ0IwVDRLMjlMSWZBMkxnS3pN</guid></item><item><title>为什么橙色的猫几乎总是雄性的，新的基因研究揭示了-每日银河 | Why Orange Cats Are Almost Always Male, New Genetic Research Reveals - The Daily Galaxy</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMie0FVX3lxTFBjcnFsMmUwZk5iUDdwRFVkTDU4YW1IZnBNbEliM0FTT285MHh0Zlkyb0JxSDV5WWJRVDBQeUJLeDREQlFSckQ1MDJxcVJLOUpzRHN3QWQ4aFVsenZaa1k3TUJZdkhyS1U1aG5JdURzYUpzRVIwZGJyR1Rycw?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="dynamic-entry-content"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After more than 60 years of genetic guessing, scientists have finally cracked the code behind what makes orange cats so… orange. In &lt;a href="https://www.biorxiv.org/content/10.1101/2024.11.19.624036v1" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;two separate studies&lt;/a&gt; published on&lt;a href="https://www.biorxiv.org/content/10.1101/2024.11.21.624608v1" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt; &lt;em&gt;bioRxiv&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, researchers have identified a specific &lt;strong&gt;DNA deletion&lt;/strong&gt; on the X chromosome that turns a regular cat into a fiery feline. The discovery sheds new light on how genetics drive fur color—and why orange cats are almost always male.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="code-block code-block-2"&gt;

    
    &lt;ins class="adsbygoogle" data-ad-client="ca-pub-6966113680805338" data-ad-slot="1096651400" data-ad-format="auto" data-full-width-responsive="true"&gt;&lt;/ins&gt;
    
    
&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;The Secret Sits In Silent DNA&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The culprit isn’t a mutation in a typical gene that codes for pigment. Instead, the answer lies in a &lt;strong&gt;non-coding region&lt;/strong&gt;—a stretch of &lt;a href="https://dailygalaxy.com/2024/12/new-dna-study-reveals-neanderthals-survived-interbred-modern-humans/" data-type="post" data-id="73229"&gt;DNA&lt;/a&gt; that doesn’t build proteins but controls how genes behave.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Researchers found that orange cats have a &lt;strong&gt;5,000-base-pair deletion&lt;/strong&gt; just before a gene called &lt;em&gt;Arhgap36&lt;/em&gt;. This deletion causes the gene to become overactive, especially in &lt;strong&gt;melanocytes&lt;/strong&gt;, the pigment-producing &lt;a href="https://dailygalaxy.com/2024/11/after-death-a-new-life-takes-shape-scientists-astonishing-discovery-about-our-cells/"&gt;cells&lt;/a&gt; in skin.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="code-block code-block-3"&gt;


&lt;ins class="adsbygoogle" data-ad-client="ca-pub-6966113680805338" data-ad-slot="4349301016" data-ad-format="auto" data-full-width-responsive="true"&gt;&lt;/ins&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://dailygalaxy.com/2024/11/how-do-cats-actually-sleep/" data-type="post" data-id="72001"&gt;Cats&lt;/a&gt; with this deletion produce more &lt;em&gt;Arhgap36&lt;/em&gt; RNA—up to &lt;strong&gt;13 times more&lt;/strong&gt; than cats without it. That overactivity shifts their fur color from dark black-brown to the reddish-gold we associate with marmalade cats.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;How The X Chromosome Shapes A Cat’s Coat&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The orange gene sits on the &lt;strong&gt;X chromosome&lt;/strong&gt;, which helps explain one of the biggest quirks of orange cats: why most of them are male.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Male cats only have one X chromosome. If they inherit the version with the orange gene, they become fully orange. Female cats, on the other hand, have &lt;strong&gt;two X chromosomes&lt;/strong&gt;—one from each parent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="code-block code-block-3"&gt;


&lt;ins class="adsbygoogle" data-ad-client="ca-pub-6966113680805338" data-ad-slot="4349301016" data-ad-format="auto" data-full-width-responsive="true"&gt;&lt;/ins&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;p&gt;In female cats, one X chromosome randomly turns off in each cell. That leads to a &lt;strong&gt;patchwork of fur colors&lt;/strong&gt;, often creating tortoiseshell or calico coats. Only if a female inherits two copies of the orange gene will she&lt;strong&gt; turn out completely orange&lt;/strong&gt;—a rare event.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;What’s Really Behind Calicos And Tortoiseshells?&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Calicos&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;tortoiseshell cats&lt;/strong&gt; are genetic mosaics, and the orange gene plays a major role in that. But there’s another twist: a &lt;strong&gt;white-spotting gene&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Tortoiseshell cats have intermingled patches of black and orange. Calicos have larger color blocks separated by white fur. That white comes from a gene that affects how pigment cells &lt;strong&gt;migrate and survive&lt;/strong&gt; as the kitten develops.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="code-block code-block-3"&gt;


&lt;ins class="adsbygoogle" data-ad-client="ca-pub-6966113680805338" data-ad-slot="4349301016" data-ad-format="auto" data-full-width-responsive="true"&gt;&lt;/ins&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;p&gt;So even when the orange gene is present, its visual effect depends on how these other pigment genes behave.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Are Orange Cats Really “Goofy”?&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The internet loves to joke that orange cats are lovable but a little less sharp. And while orange tabbies have a reputation for being clingy, chaotic, or not-so-bright, there’s &lt;strong&gt;no science&lt;/strong&gt; to back that up.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href="https://www.genecards.org/cgi-bin/carddisp.pl?gene=ARHGAP36" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Arhgap36&lt;/em&gt; gene&lt;/a&gt; has known roles in development, but in cats, it seems to only activate in skin pigment cells—not the brain. That means orange fur isn’t linked to intelligence or behavior.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="code-block code-block-3"&gt;


&lt;ins class="adsbygoogle" data-ad-client="ca-pub-6966113680805338" data-ad-slot="4349301016" data-ad-format="auto" data-full-width-responsive="true"&gt;&lt;/ins&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;p&gt;Still, human perception plays a big role. Because orange cats are so visually distinct, we might be more likely to &lt;strong&gt;assign personalities&lt;/strong&gt; to them—whether or not those traits are real.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;A New Chapter In Feline Genetics&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;These new studies don’t just solve a long-standing mystery—they mark a &lt;strong&gt;turning point&lt;/strong&gt; in how scientists understand non-coding DNA. For decades, researchers focused mostly on protein-coding genes. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Now, this discovery shows how even the &lt;strong&gt;“quiet” parts of the genome &lt;/strong&gt;can have big effects. And there may be more to uncover. Orange fur was just the beginning. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Daily Galaxy</author><pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 18:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMie0FVX3lxTFBjcnFsMmUwZk5iUDdwRFVkTDU4YW1IZnBNbEliM0FTT285MHh0Zlkyb0JxSDV5WWJRVDBQeUJLeDREQlFSckQ1MDJxcVJLOUpzRHN3QWQ4aFVsenZaa1k3TUJZdkhyS1U1aG5JdURzYUpzRVIwZGJyR1Rycw</guid></item><item><title>美国麻疹总数攀升至800例， 10次爆发- CIDRAP | US measles total climbs to 800 cases, 10 outbreaks - CIDRAP</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiiAFBVV95cUxQOGg2ZThrMHNfOFFCaW1fOGpZWXNlNUJIRWoyRDdHSFVveXpoWFZwYVRmNnNXVTFyLXNnellFSndxa1p0XzdHdzhjazE0WVBtZTNwWWIydW1nd1JrdngzZEJ5UlhxcWdGWDFJLWNNRnR0eWthR21Zbld2VGtzNHV6a1ZGNm5iS2Rn?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="clearfix text-formatted field field--name-field-body field--type-text-long field--label-hidden field__item"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Amid a rising number of outbreaks, including a large one centered in West Texas, the US Centers for Disease Control and Prevention (CDC) in its &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/measles/data-research/index.html"&gt;weekly update&lt;/a&gt; reported 88 more measles cases, pushing the national total to 800.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The pace of activity in the first 4 months of the year is well on track to pass the 2019 total of 1,274 cases, which was the most since the United States officially eliminated the virus in 2000. In its update, the CDC said 94% of cases this year are part outbreaks, which have reached 10 now—3 more than the previous week.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Half of all US states have reported cases, some of which are linked to international travel. Among illnesses reported so far, 96% of patients were unvaccinated or have unknown vaccination status. So far, 85 patients (11%) were hospitalized, with the number of deaths remaining at 3.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Texas nears 600 infections&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the main outbreak hot spot, the Texas Department of State Health Services (TDSHS) today &lt;a href="https://www.dshs.texas.gov/news-alerts/measles-outbreak-2025"&gt;reported&lt;/a&gt; 36 more cases since April 15, boosting the state's total to 597, of which 371 are from Gaines County, though 24 other counties have also reported cases.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In its list of other measles cases, the TDSHS reported 15 case-patients from Upshur County in the eastern part of the state, 2 of whom are Upshur County residents. Officials are examining the residency status of the other patients to determine if the cases are linked to the West Texas outbreak.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Outbreaks in New Mexico, Kansas, and Oklahoma have also been linked to the West Texas outbreak. The &lt;a href="https://www.kdhe.ks.gov/2314/Measles-Data"&gt;Kansas Department of Health and Environment&lt;/a&gt; this week reported 5 more cases, bringing its total to 37 infections in eight counties.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Michigan reports outbreak, Montana reports cases&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yesterday the Michigan Department of Health and Human Services and the Mid-Michigan District Health Department &lt;a href="https://www.michigan.gov/mdhhs/inside-mdhhs/newsroom/2025/04/17/measles-outbreak"&gt;reported&lt;/a&gt; the state's first measles outbreak since 2019, which involves three cases from Montcalm County in the western part of the state. Official added that the outbreak was initially linked to a large ongoing outbreak in Ontario, Canada.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In other outbreak developments, the Montana Department of Public Health and Human Services yesterday &lt;a href="https://www.healthygallatin.org/community-health/communicable-diseases/measles/"&gt;confirmed&lt;/a&gt; the state's first measles cases since 1990. Officials said they are investigating five cases, which include children and adults living in Gallatin County who were exposed to measles while traveling outside of the state.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All were unvaccinated or have unknown vaccination status. Officials said the patients are isolating at home and that so far two potential public exposure sites in Belgrade and Bozeman have been identified. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
      
  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>CIDRAP</author><pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 18:25:52 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiAFBVV95cUxQOGg2ZThrMHNfOFFCaW1fOGpZWXNlNUJIRWoyRDdHSFVveXpoWFZwYVRmNnNXVTFyLXNnellFSndxa1p0XzdHdzhjazE0WVBtZTNwWWIydW1nd1JrdngzZEJ5UlhxcWdGWDFJLWNNRnR0eWthR21Zbld2VGtzNHV6a1ZGNm5iS2Rn</guid></item><item><title>密苏里州首次确认麻疹病例，卫生官员表示- FOX4KC.com | Missouri has first confirmed measles case, health officials say - FOX4KC.com</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMikAFBVV95cUxOSExubG9aQVVnX2pUdm8wSmZHaHotTHJVZTBLTGZRMmJlRWRKNkZHOWs0ams3ZEdGczlTNHZYUktkV0VES1RSWmF1aW56dmpUQVk5c3EtVkhNUzBaOUhSajJGRDVEcWZWZkZYLTBoOVhBWGlaUVg2Y2R6UjJ1WExPbDF6VE1jYlBFS1RCbllVY1fSAZYBQVVfeXFMTl9od2JCamhmSW93eEhtSERhMUI3VFV4bWNwSWlLUU11YmlXNl9YbVNnbDlKY2dnVFlJWnVFX0FfcG94ZGJUMUtMc2hqNVRsQ2s4UFpEWHBCOVZoTTZkMExkSVV1TWJPV3RlTmo0Y1UzbDFicnJtdzhZTkZWYnM5Sk92UWNyRXk2azVwenZiTE5XUlAyMXpR?oc=5</link><description>&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;
    
    
    &lt;noscript&gt;
      
    &lt;/noscript&gt;
  &lt;/body&gt;
</description><author>FOX4KC.com</author><pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 17:25:55 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikAFBVV95cUxOSExubG9aQVVnX2pUdm8wSmZHaHotTHJVZTBLTGZRMmJlRWRKNkZHOWs0ams3ZEdGczlTNHZYUktkV0VES1RSWmF1aW56dmpUQVk5c3EtVkhNUzBaOUhSajJGRDVEcWZWZkZYLTBoOVhBWGlaUVg2Y2R6UjJ1WExPbDF6VE1jYlBFS1RCbllVY1fSAZYBQVVfeXFMTl9od2JCamhmSW93eEhtSERhMUI3VFV4bWNwSWlLUU11YmlXNl9YbVNnbDlKY2dnVFlJWnVFX0FfcG94ZGJUMUtMc2hqNVRsQ2s4UFpEWHBCOVZoTTZkMExkSVV1TWJPV3RlTmo0Y1UzbDFicnJtdzhZTkZWYnM5Sk92UWNyRXk2azVwenZiTE5XUlAyMXpR</guid></item><item><title>女性在选择朋友时部分依靠嗅觉- Ars Technica | Women rely partly on smell when choosing friends - Ars Technica</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMipwFBVV95cUxQSXZrNHNuemNCMEZpRk91T3o0VlI3cGdjVmdhMEhXMURuaWZKMDB3YzZiRy1ob2xlRXJKbENEcFV6RjNCODhnd0JPMGhpNnlpazNXN2Z6eEtIOGEyc2ItR0F1OVNiYnhhOGNtSEtEbFJuSDNVSnVmRXVpRXd6ejd3TXdoamo2Ulhpc2R4cm0xOXR1b0NVUFJlejRmUFpUQ2J0a0dTMmRmSQ?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content post-content-double"&gt;
          
          
&lt;p&gt;For their study, Gaby et al. organized an on-campus "Speed-Friending" event for 40 female volunteers, consisting of four distinct phases. First, participants had their headshots taken. Next, they looked at pictures of all the other women participating and rated friendship potential based solely on visual cues. Then the women wore a T-shirt for 12 hours as they went about their daily activities, which were then collected and placed in plastic bags. Finally, participants rated the friendship potential of anonymized participants based solely on smelling each T-shirt, followed by a live session during which they interacted with each woman for four minutes and rated their friendship potential. This was followed by a second round of smelling the T-shirts and once again rating friendship potential.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The results: There was a strong correlation between the in-person evaluations of friendship potential and those based solely on smelling the T-shirts, with remarkable consistency. And the ratings made after live interactions accurately predicted changes in the assessments made in the final round of odor-based testing, suggesting a learned response element.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Everybody showed they had a consistent signature of what they liked,” &lt;a href="https://news.cornell.edu/stories/2025/04/finding-friendship-first-whiff"&gt;said co-author Vivian Zayas&lt;/a&gt; of Cornell University. “And the consistency was not that, in the group, one person smelled really bad and one person smelled really good. No, it was idiosyncratic. I might like person A over B over C based on scent, and this pattern predicts who I end up liking in the chat. People take a lot in when they’re meeting face to face. But scent—which people are registering at some level, though probably not consciously—forecasts whether you end up liking this person.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The authors acknowledged that their study was limited to college-aged heterosexual women and that there could be differences in how olfactory and other cues function in other groups: older or younger women, non-American women, men, and so forth. "Future studies might consider a wider age range, investigate individuals at different stages of development, focus on how these cues function in male-male platonic interactions, or examine how scent in daily interactions shapes friendship judgments in other cultures," they wrote.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Scientific Reports, 2025. DOI: &lt;a href="http://dx.doi.org/10.1038/s41598-025-94350-1"&gt;10.1038/s41598-025-94350-1&lt;/a&gt;  (&lt;a href="http://arstechnica.com/science/news/2010/03/dois-and-their-discontents-1.ars"&gt;About DOIs&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;/p&gt;


          
                  &lt;/div&gt;

                  
          &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Ars Technica</author><pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 17:16:47 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipwFBVV95cUxQSXZrNHNuemNCMEZpRk91T3o0VlI3cGdjVmdhMEhXMURuaWZKMDB3YzZiRy1ob2xlRXJKbENEcFV6RjNCODhnd0JPMGhpNnlpazNXN2Z6eEtIOGEyc2ItR0F1OVNiYnhhOGNtSEtEbFJuSDNVSnVmRXVpRXd6ejd3TXdoamo2Ulhpc2R4cm0xOXR1b0NVUFJlejRmUFpUQ2J0a0dTMmRmSQ</guid></item><item><title>研究人员表示，气候变化将使大米有毒- Slashdot | Climate Change Will Make Rice Toxic, Say Researchers - Slashdot</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiogFBVV95cUxQSzE0NHo4OW1LcFhZNUllMnRkbUU2TnNqUDg2MDUxWFg3dnFKay12VzdKdXkyWVpLV0pSc3VLeFBPaG5TemZQRm9pYmVrSktVdkd3MU9fUkxabFE5MEFpaW9VQ3BNZUNMTzl2ZHdOWkpvMnhIQkY2dHV3eWpEMkVoVHp2WDRDWDVMZER0Rkh4b1h5SUp0WlR2Yl9obkY4VGM2bUE?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="body" id="fhbody-177059523"&gt;
	
		
	

	
		
		&lt;div id="text-177059523" class="p"&gt;&lt;p&gt;
			
		 	
				Rice, the world's most consumed grain, will &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://arstechnica.com/science/2025/04/climate-change-will-make-rice-toxic-say-researchers/"&gt;become increasingly toxic&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; as the atmosphere heats and as carbon dioxide emissions rise, potentially putting billions of people at risk of cancers and other diseases, according to &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.thelancet.com/journals/lanplh/article/PIIS2542-5196(25)00055-5/fulltext"&gt;new research&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; published this week in The Lancet. From a report:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;i&gt; Eaten every day by billions of people and grown across the globe, rice is arguably the planet's most important staple crop, with half the world's population relying on it for the majority of its food needs, especially in developing countries.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;

But the way rice is grown -- mostly submerged in paddies -- and its highly porous texture mean it can absorb unusually high levels of arsenic, a potent carcinogenic toxin that is especially dangerous for babies.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;p&gt; After growing rice in controlled fields for six years, researchers from Columbia University and international partners found that when both temperature and CO2 increased in line with climate projections, arsenic levels in rice grains rose significantly. "When we put both of them together, then wow, that was really something we were not expecting," said Lewis Ziska, a plant physiologist at Columbia University who led the study. "You're looking at a crop staple that's consumed by a billion people every day, and any effect on toxicity is going to have a pretty damn large effect." &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;

Inorganic arsenic exposure has been linked to cancers, heart disease, and neurological problems in infants. Disease risk rose across all seven top rice-consuming Asian countries analyzed. "This is one more reason to intervene -- to control people's exposure," said co-author Keeve Nachman of Johns Hopkins University. "The No. 1 thing we can do is everything in our power to slow climate change."
		 	
		&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

		

		

		
			
		
	&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Slashdot</author><pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 16:50:16 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiogFBVV95cUxQSzE0NHo4OW1LcFhZNUllMnRkbUU2TnNqUDg2MDUxWFg3dnFKay12VzdKdXkyWVpLV0pSc3VLeFBPaG5TemZQRm9pYmVrSktVdkd3MU9fUkxabFE5MEFpaW9VQ3BNZUNMTzl2ZHdOWkpvMnhIQkY2dHV3eWpEMkVoVHp2WDRDWDVMZER0Rkh4b1h5SUp0WlR2Yl9obkY4VGM2bUE</guid></item><item><title>Z世代和千禧一代工人会接受较低的工资，以换取雇主的一件事-财富 | Gen Z and millennial workers would accept lower salaries in exchange for this one thing from their employers - Fortune</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMigAFBVV95cUxOLXc1QkNnSnlDdk90R0FuVGs3LUYzX3JLMGw1X3ZmcHdCdEgtSVczMTNOOHpwcU9vV3UyMEhvbUtDMVFJRTl0T0JKVDkzSHVOaG9pMWdLbkExd0pEdVgzUUowRWI2RXFTaHNydDRUV19STmpvV2g3QXk0ZkQ5T2ZKcg?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Fortune</author><pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 16:48:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigAFBVV95cUxOLXc1QkNnSnlDdk90R0FuVGs3LUYzX3JLMGw1X3ZmcHdCdEgtSVczMTNOOHpwcU9vV3UyMEhvbUtDMVFJRTl0T0JKVDkzSHVOaG9pMWdLbkExd0pEdVgzUUowRWI2RXFTaHNydDRUV19STmpvV2g3QXk0ZkQ5T2ZKcg</guid></item><item><title>美国麻疹病例一周内上升12% ， 24个州达到800例- Bloomberg.com | US Measles Cases Rise 12% in a Week to Reach 800 in 24 States - Bloomberg.com</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMisAFBVV95cUxOY2gyYjNlRTlFci1JMnJhbGRQRmRNSGJKMWUtczZmWm5ON0ROaTJqLUV5bzE5LTMwaFUwSnpGN1gzZkpqR3hUTk5ibEI0RndmaEtxakk0R0UzUWxFS1hfQUdUWkpUdjlJVmZTMm1MVmhMLU1xUnVwQWoyQUsyQ3FIanQ4TTBWbjVVTVFjbWNjcnRrQnlSVi01N3dSX0I3TDBIdG1NMVZEMlh1NjRnRTEtUg?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="bb-that-category__content"&gt;&lt;p class="bb-that-category__text"&gt;Connecting decision makers to a dynamic network of information, people and ideas, Bloomberg quickly and accurately delivers business and financial information, news and insight around the world&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Bloomberg.com</author><pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 16:20:32 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMisAFBVV95cUxOY2gyYjNlRTlFci1JMnJhbGRQRmRNSGJKMWUtczZmWm5ON0ROaTJqLUV5bzE5LTMwaFUwSnpGN1gzZkpqR3hUTk5ibEI0RndmaEtxakk0R0UzUWxFS1hfQUdUWkpUdjlJVmZTMm1MVmhMLU1xUnVwQWoyQUsyQ3FIanQ4TTBWbjVVTVFjbWNjcnRrQnlSVi01N3dSX0I3TDBIdG1NMVZEMlh1NjRnRTEtUg</guid></item><item><title>更多65岁以上的人正在尝试大麻。以下是有关风险和收益的须知事项-《卫报》 | More people aged 65+ are trying out cannabis. Here’s what to know about the risks and benefits - The Guardian</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMijAFBVV95cUxNb3lONU81eTBzUzZMekRLRHNXOFVKME92V1paSjBuejhONFZuTVBZTm5UMURzNG0wVmJrRzJoNEJpM01IWExEZkZlSllPSXRVb0g4R0doYkhUbVppbG1taVQ1MGNBNnhyekVFV190RXdyMWVnYS1hNk1keWswbU9BWHpSSlpBemZTdktwYg?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body-commercial-selector article-body-viewer-selector dcr-11jq3zt"&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-15rw6c2"&gt;P&lt;/span&gt;olls suggest Americans aged 65 and older are trying cannabis for the first time &lt;a href="https://www.phi.org/press/new-research-shows-older-adults-are-the-fastest-growing-population-to-try-marijuana/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;more&lt;/a&gt; than any other group in the country. This trend is &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/33660625/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;propelled&lt;/a&gt; by decreased stigma and increased legalization, with 24 states and the District of Columbia allowing &lt;a href="https://www.ncsl.org/civil-and-criminal-justice/cannabis-overview" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;recreational use&lt;/a&gt; (in the UK, &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/society/2024/feb/11/wonder-drug-is-the-uk-ready-for-the-green-rush-of-medicinal-cannabis" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;recreational use&lt;/a&gt; is still &lt;a href="https://www.gov.uk/penalties-drug-possession-dealing" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;illegal&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;But there’s something else too. Getting older comes with its challenges, physically and emotionally. Some &lt;a href="https://www.healthyagingpoll.org/reports-more/report/how-older-adults-use-think-about-and-discuss-cannabis" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;people&lt;/a&gt; are &lt;a href="https://www.today.com/video/inside-the-growing-trend-of-seniors-using-marijuana-219283013678" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;betting on cannabis&lt;/a&gt; as a way to navigate these hurdles. Research &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC11589015/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;indicates&lt;/a&gt; older adults primarily use cannabis for health-related issues, like poor sleep, pain and mental health concerns such as anxiety.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="sign-in-gate"&gt;&lt;gu-island name="SignInGateSelector" priority="feature" deferuntil="visible" props='{"contentType":"Article","sectionId":"wellness","tags":[{"id":"wellness/wellness","type":"Keyword","title":"Well actually"},{"id":"society/cannabis","type":"Keyword","title":"Cannabis"},{"id":"science/ageing","type":"Keyword","title":"Ageing"},{"id":"science/drugs","type":"Keyword","title":"Drugs"},{"id":"lifeandstyle/lifeandstyle","type":"Keyword","title":"Life and style"},{"id":"campaign/email/well-actually","type":"Campaign","title":"Well Actually (Newsletter sign up)"},{"id":"type/article","type":"Type","title":"Article"},{"id":"tone/features","type":"Tone","title":"Features"},{"id":"profile/sarah-sloat","type":"Contributor","title":"Sarah Sloat"},{"id":"tracking/commissioningdesk/us-lifestyle-and-wellness","type":"Tracking","title":"US lifestyle and wellness"}],"isPaidContent":false,"isPreview":false,"host":"https://www.theguardian.com","pageId":"wellness/2025/apr/18/benefits-risk-cannabis-older-adults","idUrl":"https://profile.theguardian.com","switches":{"lightbox":true,"prebidCriteo":true,"externalVideoEmbeds":true,"personaliseSignInGateAfterCheckout":true,"abSignInGateMainVariant":true,"prebidAppnexusUkRow":true,"prebidMagnite":true,"commercialMetrics":true,"prebidTrustx":true,"scAdFreeBanner":false,"adaptiveSite":true,"prebidPermutiveAudience":true,"compareVariantDecision":false,"enableSentryReporting":true,"lazyLoadContainers":true,"ampArticleSwitch":false,"remarketing":true,"articleEndSlot":true,"keyEventsCarousel":true,"registerWithPhone":false,"darkModeWeb":true,"targeting":true,"remoteHeader":true,"slotBodyEnd":true,"ampPrebidOzone":false,"extendedMostPopularFronts":true,"emailInlineInFooter":true,"showNewPrivacyWordingOnEmailSignupEmbeds":true,"prebidAnalytics":true,"extendedMostPopular":true,"ampContentAbTesting":false,"imrWorldwide":true,"acast":true,"twitterUwt":true,"abAuxiaSignInGate":true,"prebidAppnexusInvcode":true,"ampPrebidPubmatic":false,"a9HeaderBidding":true,"prebidAppnexus":true,"europeBetaFrontTest2":false,"enableDiscussionSwitch":true,"prebidXaxis":true,"stickyVideos":true,"interactiveFullHeaderSwitch":true,"discussionAllPageSize":true,"prebidUserSync":true,"audioOnwardJourneySwitch":true,"brazeTaylorReport":false,"callouts":true,"sentinelLogger":true,"geoMostPopular":true,"weAreHiring":false,"relatedContent":true,"thirdPartyEmbedTracking":true,"prebidOzone":true,"ampLiveblogSwitch":false,"ampAmazon":false,"prebidAdYouLike":true,"mostViewedFronts":true,"abA9BidResponseWinner":true,"optOutAdvertising":true,"abSignInGateMainControl":true,"googleSearch":true,"brazeSwitch":true,"prebidKargo":true,"consentManagement":true,"idProfileNavigation":true,"confiantAdVerification":true,"discussionAllowAnonymousRecommendsSwitch":false,"absoluteServerTimes":false,"permutive":true,"comscore":true,"ampPrebidCriteo":false,"prebidTheTradeDesk":true,"newsletterOnwards":false,"youtubeIma":true,"webFonts":true,"liveBlogTopSponsorship":true,"lineItemJobs":true,"ophan":true,"crosswordSvgThumbnails":true,"prebidTriplelift":true,"prebidPubmatic":true,"serverShareCounts":false,"autoRefresh":true,"enhanceTweets":true,"prebidIndexExchange":true,"prebidOpenx":true,"prebidHeaderBidding":true,"idCookieRefresh":true,"discussionPageSize":true,"smartAppBanner":false,"historyTags":true,"brazeContentCards":true,"remoteBanner":true,"emailSignupRecaptcha":true,"prebidSmart":true,"shouldLoadGoogletag":true,"inizio":true,"europeBetaFront":true,"prebidBidCache":true},"contributionsServiceUrl":"https://contributions.guardianapis.com","editionId":"US"}'&gt;&lt;/gu-island&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;Dr &lt;a href="https://profiles.ucsd.edu/alison.moore" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;Alison Moore&lt;/a&gt;, a geriatrician and University of California San Diego professor, can see a future in which cannabis plays a part in older patient healthcare. The issue is that current science can’t prove most of the reasons why this group wants to use it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;Despite the lack of evidence, “we do know people find it useful”, she says. “Older adults are the fastest-growing market, and there’s a reason for that.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;We spoke to experts about the benefits and risks of using cannabis as an older adult.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="what-is-cannabis" class="dcr-n4qeq9"&gt;What is cannabis?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;figure id="68fc95e3-56c3-4541-8b04-08917662ad70" data-spacefinder-role="inline" data-spacefinder-type="model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.ImageBlockElement" class="dcr-173mewl"&gt;&lt;figcaption data-spacefinder-role="inline" class="dcr-1tx6u99"&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-1inf02i"&gt;&lt;svg viewbox="0 0 18 13"&gt;&lt;path d="M18 3.5v8l-1.5 1.5h-15l-1.5-1.5v-8l1.5-1.5h3.5l2-2h4l2 2h3.5l1.5 1.5zm-9 7.5c1.9 0 3.5-1.6 3.5-3.5s-1.6-3.5-3.5-3.5-3.5 1.6-3.5 3.5 1.6 3.5 3.5 3.5z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-1qvd3m6"&gt;Cannabis comes in a variety of forms.&lt;/span&gt; Photograph: Don Bartletti/Los Angeles Times via Getty Images&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;Cannabis is a group of &lt;a href="https://www.cancer.org/cancer/managing-cancer/treatment-types/complementary-and-integrative-medicine/marijuana-and-cancer/understanding-cannabis.html" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;plant varieties&lt;/a&gt;, or strains – notably &lt;em&gt;Cannabis sativa&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;Cannabis indica&lt;/em&gt;. Its main chemicals, called cannabinoids, are THC and CBD. THC has a psychoactive effect. CBD does not, but can create a feeling of relaxation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;State laws typically require legal dispensaries to disclose the amounts of THC and CBD in products, explains &lt;a href="https://www.colorado.edu/psych-neuro/angela-bryan" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;Angela Bryan&lt;/a&gt;, a professor at the University of Colorado Boulder who studies the potential risks and benefits of cannabis use among older adults. These amounts are typically shown as a ratio.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;“Regardless of whether someone wants to use cannabis recreationally or medicinally, the recommendation is to start low, go slow,” says Bryan.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="does-cannabis-affect-older-people-differently" class="dcr-n4qeq9"&gt;Does cannabis affect older people differently?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;Cannabinoids such as THC &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC5877694/#:" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;bind&lt;/a&gt; to receptors in the body’s endocannabinoid system, leading to the drug’s effects. This system maintains homeostasis and regulates metabolism, but becomes less efficient with age, Bryan explains. As a result, cannabis is metabolized more slowly. That said, because people &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/wellness/2024/nov/21/how-to-stay-healthy-in-your-50s-ageing" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;don’t age the same&lt;/a&gt;, there will be differences.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;aside data-spacefinder-role="inline" class="dcr-nyoej5"&gt;&lt;svg viewbox="0 0 22 14" class="dcr-scql1j"&gt;&lt;path d="M5.255 0h4.75c-.572 4.53-1.077 8.972-1.297 13.941H0C.792 9.104 2.44 4.53 5.255 0Zm11.061 0H21c-.506 4.53-1.077 8.972-1.297 13.941h-8.686c.902-4.837 2.485-9.411 5.3-13.941Z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;blockquote class="dcr-zzndwp"&gt;If people experience relief, if they find a way to [use cannabis] that fits into their life and is safe, that is fantastic&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;footer&gt;&lt;cite&gt;Angela Bryan, University of Colorado Boulder professor&lt;/cite&gt;&lt;/footer&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;Additionally, THC can accumulate in fat. Because older adults tend to experience an increase in fat mass and a &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/wellness/2025/mar/03/health-tips-70s-longevity" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;decrease in muscle mass&lt;/a&gt;, THC effects are more pronounced, explains Moore.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;Older adults often take multiple medications, so they should consult a healthcare provider before using cannabis, says Moore. Some data suggests people may not adjust prescription doses when adding cannabis, &lt;a href="https://www.frontiersin.org/journals/pharmacology/articles/10.3389/fphar.2024.1282831/full" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;increasing the risk&lt;/a&gt; of harmful side effects like impaired cognition or increased anxiety.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;Cannabis has become &lt;a href="https://kffhealthnews.org/news/article/legal-pot-is-more-potent-than-ever-and-still-largely-unregulated/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;more potent&lt;/a&gt; over the years. Bryan advises starting with low THC before trying stronger options. Low THC may also reduce reactions like paranoia and anxiety, she says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="what-are-the-risks-of-cannabis-use-for-older-adults" class="dcr-n4qeq9"&gt;What are the risks of cannabis use for older adults?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;Before using cannabis, discuss it with your doctor, says Moore. You can go over your medical history, including current and past medications, and why you want to try the drug.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;There is little clarity on which cannabis products are most effective for specific medical needs, says &lt;a href="https://hobi.med.ufl.edu/profile/kaufmann-christopher/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;Christopher Kaufmann&lt;/a&gt;, an assistant professor at the University of Florida College of Medicine. He emphasizes the need for more research on cannabis use, specifically in older adults, who may face greater risks due to conditions like tachycardia and poor blood pressure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;While there’s insufficient evidence for recommending cannabis, doctors can advise on potential benefits and risks. In older adults, common &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S1064748120300828" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;side effects&lt;/a&gt; like dizziness, drowsiness and confusion may increase &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/global/2025/mar/31/falling-how-to-avoid-and-what-to-do" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;fall risk&lt;/a&gt;, and cannabis could worsen cognitive impairment in those already affected, explains Dr Mark Lachs, chief of geriatrics and palliative medicine at Weill Cornell Medicine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;If patients already use cannabis, Moore asks them to bring it to their next appointment to review whether the dosage and method of administration are appropriate. Because products can be mislabeled, she emphasizes the importance of purchasing from licensed dispensaries, where accuracy is more likely.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;Certain forms may suit specific needs better, says Bryan. For instance, smoked products offer faster relief than edibles, making them preferable for immediate pain. But if you have a history of lung disease, avoid vaping and smoking.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;A downside of edibles is that you can’t undo overconsumption. “People tend not to oversmoke,” Bryan says. “They feel the effect they want and stop.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure data-spacefinder-role="inline" data-spacefinder-type="model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.NewsletterSignupBlockElement" class="dcr-173mewl"&gt;&lt;a data-ignore="global-link-styling" href="#EmailSignup-skip-link-23" class="dcr-jzxpee"&gt;skip past newsletter promotion&lt;/a&gt;&lt;aside aria-label="newsletter promotion" class="dcr-av5vqf"&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-1xjndtj"&gt;Practical advice, expert insights and answers to your questions about how to live a good life&lt;/p&gt;&lt;gu-island name="SecureSignup" priority="feature" deferuntil="visible" props='{"newsletterId":"well-actually","successDescription":"Practical advice, expert insights and answers to your questions about how to live a good life"}'&gt;&lt;/gu-island&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-1eusqlu"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Privacy Notice: &lt;/strong&gt;Newsletters may contain info about charities, online ads, and content funded by outside parties. For more information see our &lt;a data-ignore="global-link-styling" href="https://www.theguardian.com/help/privacy-policy" rel="noreferrer" class="dcr-1rjy2q9"&gt;Privacy Policy&lt;/a&gt;. We use Google reCaptcha to protect our website and the Google &lt;a data-ignore="global-link-styling" href="https://policies.google.com/privacy" rel="noreferrer" class="dcr-1rjy2q9"&gt;Privacy Policy&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a data-ignore="global-link-styling" href="https://policies.google.com/terms" rel="noreferrer" class="dcr-1rjy2q9"&gt;Terms of Service&lt;/a&gt; apply.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;p id="EmailSignup-skip-link-23" tabindex="0" aria-label="after newsletter promotion" role="note" class="dcr-jzxpee"&gt;after newsletter promotion&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;h2 id="what-are-the-potential-benefits" class="dcr-n4qeq9"&gt;What are the potential benefits?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;Moore, Kaufmann and colleagues co-authored a 2020 &lt;a href="https://agsjournals.onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/abs/10.1111/jgs.16833" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;study&lt;/a&gt; of 568 adults surveyed at a geriatric clinic, where most used cannabis for health issues like sleeping troubles, aches and anxiety. Three-quarters of participants found it “somewhat” or “extremely” helpful. While such use is common, scientific evidence supporting these health benefits is limited. Research is stronger on cannabis’s &lt;a href="https://www.nccih.nih.gov/health/cannabis-marijuana-and-cannabinoids-what-you-need-to-know" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;effectiveness&lt;/a&gt; for neuropathic pain, spasticity and nausea.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="dc3bf3f1-527a-446f-93b1-4941b1b46ba0" data-spacefinder-role="richLink" data-spacefinder-type="model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.RichLinkBlockElement" class="dcr-1your1i"&gt;&lt;gu-island name="RichLinkComponent" priority="feature" deferuntil="idle" props='{"richLinkIndex":26,"element":{"_type":"model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.RichLinkBlockElement","prefix":"Related: ","text":"Falling can be risky. Here’s how to avoid it and what to do if it happens","elementId":"dc3bf3f1-527a-446f-93b1-4941b1b46ba0","role":"richLink","url":"https://www.theguardian.com/global/2025/mar/31/falling-how-to-avoid-and-what-to-do"},"ajaxUrl":"https://api.nextgen.guardianapps.co.uk","format":{"design":10,"display":2,"theme":4}}'&gt;&lt;/gu-island&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;The gap between self-reported benefits and scientific evidence is partly due to missing data and a reliance on observational studies, which are prone to biases. Bryan calls for more double-blind randomized controlled trials using legal cannabis products, though these are challenging to conduct because of the tightly regulated schedule I status of cannabis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;Self-reported benefits still matter, Bryan says, even if there’s a placebo effect. “If people experience relief, if they find a way to do it that fits into their life and is safe for them, then that is fantastic,” she says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;Moore thinks cannabis has “the potential to address some of the common issues we see with ageing”, but the barriers to studying it have impeded progress. Because short-term use of cannabis &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0306460321004068" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;may improve&lt;/a&gt; positive mood, this might explain why people find it helpful, regardless of whether cause and effect can be validated, she explains.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.aarongreensteinmd.com/#:~:text" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;Aaron Greenstein&lt;/a&gt;, a board-certified geriatric psychiatrist, says patients inquire about cannabis for sleep, pain and general wellbeing. But whether it’s helpful, and how much, can be very subjective, he says, and he’s observed that most of his patients who have hoped cannabis could help with wellbeing end up not sticking with it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;“Part of the fascination with marijuana is that it is advertised as a quick fix,” he says. “But there’s a limit to how effective it can be.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="can-cannabis-help-older-adults-sleep-better" class="dcr-n4qeq9"&gt;Can cannabis help older adults sleep better?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;In a 2020 &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC7572650/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;study&lt;/a&gt; on people aged 21 to 70, Bryan and colleagues found that frequent use of edibles for sleep was linked to poorer sleep over time. She notes this pattern mirrors findings on other sleep aids: they work initially but lose effectiveness eventually. Sparing, as-needed use is generally more helpful.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;The study also found participants, especially older adults, slept better with higher CBD intake. While products with more THC may offer short-term relief, those with high-dose CBD and low-dose THC were better for sleep.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;“A combination of occasional CBD use along with some behavioral changes is probably the best recommendation” for people experiencing persistent, disruptive sleep problems, says Bryan.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;Moore has come across seniors who want to transition from hypnotic medications, like Ambien, to cannabis. But there’s a lack of data comparing the two, she says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;When it comes to improving sleep, there are often more effective alternatives to cannabis and medications such as Ambien, says Lachs. These include options like gabapentin and melatonin, but he particularly recommends behavioral interventions like &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/wellness/2024/sep/23/cbt-i-sleep-therapy" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;CBT-I&lt;/a&gt;, or cognitive behavioral therapy for insomnia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;Ultimately, “the jury is still out on whether cannabis can be used to treat sleep”, says Kaufmann. “There definitely needs to be more studies.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Guardian</author><pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 16:01:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijAFBVV95cUxNb3lONU81eTBzUzZMekRLRHNXOFVKME92V1paSjBuejhONFZuTVBZTm5UMURzNG0wVmJrRzJoNEJpM01IWExEZkZlSllPSXRVb0g4R0doYkhUbVppbG1taVQ1MGNBNnhyekVFV190RXdyMWVnYS1hNk1keWswbU9BWHpSSlpBemZTdktwYg</guid></item><item><title>国际空间站正处于“其存在的最危险时期” ，美国宇航局安全小组警告- Gizmodo | The ISS Is in the ‘Riskiest Period of Its Existence,’ NASA Safety Panel Warns - Gizmodo</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiqAFBVV95cUxPSGp3Q0M4cWJpY0VBWXlXWDBvUUxINHhxdU5idDAybzNnaFA0VzZPaDhld3V1QVlzM0F6VDR0anpDZEE2dVNwTmNobHQ4VU1DUHFvMFl0QldkSlNQY2RtZXRYdVBwMDZIdnVxYjdUeGlybzBMSnI1V2N0anVaeWhRNnlob0RxUFVJbHR2d0paZEw1U09ybnRIVko0Sm9JczlYMEItaUJBb1U?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content prose dark:prose-invert lg:prose-lg lg:leading-[29px] font-serif max-w-none"&gt;
              
              
              &lt;p&gt;The International Space Station (ISS) has been orbiting Earth since 1998, housing groups of astronauts in the microgravity environment around 250 miles above the surface of the planet. All of that time in space has taken a toll on its aging hardware, and the space station is due to retire within the next few years. Until then, however, safety experts are warning of long-running issues that threaten the safety of the ISS, and the crew on board.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;During a meeting of the Aerospace Safety Advisory Panel (ASAP) held on Thursday, members of a NASA safety panel stated that there are growing risks threatening the space station as it nears the end of its use, SpaceNews &lt;a href="https://spacenews.com/nasa-safety-panel-warns-of-increasing-risks-to-iss-operations/"&gt;reported&lt;/a&gt;. “The ISS has entered the riskiest period of its existence,” Rich Williams, a member of the panel, said during the meeting.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;At the top of the list of growing risks is a &lt;a href="https://gizmodo.com/the-iss-is-leaking-air-and-nasa-and-russia-cant-agree-why-2000524781"&gt;leak where air has been escaping at an increasing rate&lt;/a&gt; from a tunnel that connects a docking port to a Russian module. In 2019, Russia’s space agency Roscosmos reported the detection of an air leak found in the vestibule (named PrK) that connects a docking port to the Russian Zvezda module, which the space agency had launched to low Earth orbit in July 2000. The rate of air that has been leaking from Russia’s Zvezda module had doubled from one pound of air per day in 2019 to a little over two pounds around a week before the launch of the Progress MS-26 cargo spacecraft in February 2024.&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;p&gt;Both NASA and Roscosmos have been monitoring the air leak since then, and officials from the two space agencies are scheduled to meet later this month to update mitigation efforts for the growing safety concern, according to Williams. A report issued in late 2024 &lt;a href="https://gizmodo.com/growing-air-leak-in-russian-segment-now-deemed-greatest-iss-risk-report-reveals-2000505190"&gt;elevated the air leak to the highest level of risk&lt;/a&gt; based on its likelihood and severity. In the meantime, the source of the leak remains unknown. The astronauts on board the ISS are prepared to close the hatch to the service module when access is not required in order to minimize the amount of air lost, as well as to isolate the leak itself from the rest of the space station.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Another safety issue addressed during the meeting is the lack of a deorbit plan for the ISS in case of an emergency. NASA is in the process of solidifying &lt;a href="https://gizmodo.com/an-excruciatingly-detailed-breakdown-of-how-nasa-plans-1851545016"&gt;a plan to ditch the nearly one-million pound space station in 2030&lt;/a&gt;, sending it flying through Earth’s atmosphere to mostly burn up from the heat, with its remaining bits ending up at the bottom of the Pacific Ocean in a controlled reentry. But as of now, NASA has no emergency plan in place to deorbit the ISS, and that’s a big problem. If NASA is forced to destroy the space station ahead of its retirement, then it increases the risk of ISS debris falling on inhabited areas.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“If there is a deorbit of the ISS before the [U.S. Deorbit Vehicle] is delivered, the risk to the public from ISS breakup debris will increase by orders of magnitude,” Williams said, according to SpaceNews. &lt;/span&gt;The panel highlighted other issues with the ISS, including having enough spare parts for life support systems on board and delays with cargo deliveries. Williams blamed these issues on “ISS budget shortfall.”&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;p&gt;“As programs near final phases, it is tempting to assume less resources will need to be available,” Williams said. “For the ISS, it is critical to maintain adequate budget and resources until the vehicle is safely reentered.”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
                          &lt;/div&gt;

            &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Gizmodo</author><pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 15:56:18 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiqAFBVV95cUxPSGp3Q0M4cWJpY0VBWXlXWDBvUUxINHhxdU5idDAybzNnaFA0VzZPaDhld3V1QVlzM0F6VDR0anpDZEE2dVNwTmNobHQ4VU1DUHFvMFl0QldkSlNQY2RtZXRYdVBwMDZIdnVxYjdUeGlybzBMSnI1V2N0anVaeWhRNnlob0RxUFVJbHR2d0paZEw1U09ybnRIVko0Sm9JczlYMEItaUJBb1U</guid></item><item><title>常见抗寄生虫药物有望阻止侵袭性皮肤癌的生长- Medical Xpress | Common antiparasitic drug shows promise in halting growth of aggressive skin cancer - Medical Xpress</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMijAFBVV95cUxPMmFhSmo3YjFmeTd6Q1A2bngwMU5PVEJGOGJyRGVLcHFqSkEtSTJZd21KV0lwQzAtNEo1Qy1NSjdEelB6cDZaRm1YTDZSN1dBa25XdXEzT3N6LTVqNkM0QWg0RWJmOGZBdG5RN0p4eGFReFVncFRBV25WcndEdUJpaW96TEFRZC1weGR1aA?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="mt-4 article-main"&gt;
									    
&lt;div class="article-gallery lightGallery"&gt;
    &lt;div data-thumb="https://scx1.b-cdn.net/csz/news/tmb/2025/study-finds-pinworm-me-1.jpg" data-src="https://scx2.b-cdn.net/gfx/news/hires/2025/study-finds-pinworm-me-1.jpg" data-sub-html="Identifying areas of active gene regulation in IMR90 cells expressing MCPyV T antigens. Credit: &amp;lt;i&amp;gt;Journal of Clinical Investigation&amp;lt;/i&amp;gt; (2025). DOI: 10.1172/JCI177724"&gt;
        &lt;figure class="article-img"&gt;
            &lt;img src="https://scx1.b-cdn.net/csz/news/800a/2025/study-finds-pinworm-me-1.jpg" alt="Study finds pinworm medication has potential to treat aggressive skin cancer" title="Identifying areas of active gene regulation in IMR90 cells expressing MCPyV T antigens. Credit: Journal of Clinical Investigation (2025). DOI: 10.1172/JCI177724"&gt;
             &lt;figcaption class="text-darken text-low-up text-truncate-js text-truncate mt-3"&gt;
                Identifying areas of active gene regulation in IMR90 cells expressing MCPyV T antigens. Credit: &lt;i&gt;Journal of Clinical Investigation&lt;/i&gt; (2025). DOI: 10.1172/JCI177724
            &lt;/figcaption&gt;        &lt;/figure&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;A common pinworm medication may stop and reverse cancer growth in Merkel cell carcinoma, an aggressive form of skin cancer, according to research led by University of Arizona Cancer Center researchers and &lt;a href="https://www.jci.org/articles/view/177724" target="_blank"&gt;published in the &lt;i&gt;Journal of Clinical Investigation&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

                                        
                                                                                  
                                         

                                                                                                                                    &lt;p&gt;Merkel cell carcinoma is a rare but fast-growing neuroendocrine cancer that is three to five times more likely than melanoma to be deadly. Response rates to current therapies—surgery, radiation and immunotherapy—are limited, resulting in a need for effective and broadly applicable therapeutics.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Merkel cell carcinoma is increasing in incidence," said senior author Megha Padi, Ph.D., a U of A Cancer Center member and an assistant professor in the U of A College of Science. "Even though it's a rare cancer type, it mimics a lot of properties that other cancers have."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Pyrvinium pamoate, a medication approved by the Food and Drug Administration in 1955 to treat pinworms, has been shown to have antitumor potential in several different cancers, including breast, colorectal, pancreatic and bladder cancers. This is the first time it has been studied in models of Merkel cell carcinoma.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Padi and the research team found that in laboratory models of Merkel cell carcinoma, pyrvinium pamoate inhibited cancer cell growth and reversed the cancer's neuroendocrine features. In mouse models of Merkel cell carcinoma, pyrvinium pamoate reduced &lt;a href="https://medicalxpress.com/tags/tumor+growth/" rel="tag" class="textTag"&gt;tumor growth&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class="article-gallery lightGallery"&gt;
    &lt;div data-thumb="https://scx1.b-cdn.net/csz/news/tmb/2025/study-finds-pinworm-me.jpg" data-src="https://scx2.b-cdn.net/gfx/news/hires/2025/study-finds-pinworm-me.jpg" data-sub-html="MCPyV-perturbed cell model reveals signaling pathways altered during MCC development. Credit: &amp;lt;i&amp;gt;Journal of Clinical Investigation&amp;lt;/i&amp;gt; (2025). DOI: 10.1172/JCI177724"&gt;
        &lt;figure class="article-img text-center"&gt;
            &lt;img src="https://scx1.b-cdn.net/csz/news/800a/2025/study-finds-pinworm-me.jpg" alt="Study finds pinworm medication has potential to treat aggressive skin cancer" title="MCPyV-perturbed cell model reveals signaling pathways altered during MCC development. Credit: Journal of Clinical Investigation (2025). DOI: 10.1172/JCI177724"&gt;
             &lt;figcaption class="text-left text-darken text-truncate text-low-up mt-3"&gt;
                MCPyV-perturbed cell model reveals signaling pathways altered during MCC development. Credit: &lt;i&gt;Journal of Clinical Investigation&lt;/i&gt; (2025). DOI: 10.1172/JCI177724
            &lt;/figcaption&gt;        &lt;/figure&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"This is a hypothesis, but some people think the reason an antiparasitic agent could be effective against cancers is because tumors are a little bit like parasites in our body," Padi said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Parasites and tumors must develop ways to use scarce resources in their host to feed themselves and allow for unlimited multiplication. If the pathways that they have hijacked to feed themselves are the same, then you get lucky, and you have a tumor type that could be amenable to killing by these antiparasitic drugs."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Padi and the research team chose to test pyrvinium pamoate after identifying the Wnt signaling pathway as one of the &lt;a href="https://medicalxpress.com/tags/molecular+mechanisms/" rel="tag" class="textTag"&gt;molecular mechanisms&lt;/a&gt; that drives the transition of normal cells into Merkel cell carcinoma. Pyrvinium pamoate is a known Wnt pathway inhibitor.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Further research is needed to optimize treatment protocols for the development of pyrvinium pamoate as a clinically useful medication for Merkel cell &lt;a href="https://medicalxpress.com/tags/carcinoma/" rel="tag" class="textTag"&gt;carcinoma&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

                                                                                                                                                                            
                                        											&lt;div class="article-main__more p-4"&gt;
												                                                    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;More information:&lt;/strong&gt;
                                                    Jiawen Yang et al, Integrative analysis reveals therapeutic potential of pyrvinium pamoate in Merkel cell carcinoma, &lt;i&gt;Journal of Clinical Investigation&lt;/i&gt; (2025). &lt;a data-doi="1" href="https://dx.doi.org/10.1172/JCI177724" target="_blank"&gt;DOI: 10.1172/JCI177724&lt;/a&gt;
																								
																								&lt;/p&gt;
																							&lt;/div&gt;
                                        											
																					
                                                                                                                        
                                        
                                        &lt;div class="d-none d-print-block"&gt;
                                            &lt;p class="mb-4"&gt;
                                                 &lt;strong&gt;Citation&lt;/strong&gt;:
                                                 Common antiparasitic drug shows promise in halting growth of aggressive skin cancer (2025, April 18)
                                                 retrieved 19 April 2025
                                                 from https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-04-common-antiparasitic-drug-halting-growth.html
                                            &lt;/p&gt;
                                            &lt;p class="border text-muted p-3"&gt;
                                            This document is subject to copyright. Apart from any fair dealing for the purpose of private study or research, no
                                            part may be reproduced without the written permission. The content is provided for information purposes only.
                                            &lt;/p&gt;
                                        &lt;/div&gt;
                                        
									&lt;/div&gt;
								&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Medical Xpress</author><pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 15:55:02 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijAFBVV95cUxPMmFhSmo3YjFmeTd6Q1A2bngwMU5PVEJGOGJyRGVLcHFqSkEtSTJZd21KV0lwQzAtNEo1Qy1NSjdEelB6cDZaRm1YTDZSN1dBa25XdXEzT3N6LTVqNkM0QWg0RWJmOGZBdG5RN0p4eGFReFVncFRBV25WcndEdUJpaW96TEFRZC1weGR1aA</guid></item><item><title>在俄勒冈州的同一个城镇，疯牛病造成两人死亡，三分之一患病- Gizmodo | A Mad Cow-Like Prion Disease Has Killed Two People and Sickened a Third in Same Oregon Town - Gizmodo</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMivwFBVV95cUxOSGhUd3o0R0liOUNHdjhWaFZ0REpZcmNDYmNXblc1R2NUQVhKX1pkalVXQm4wdlZtZjV4b253dVQ0SlNhTUdjeURGWEJhT3JFY2VSSTJpNnhTS1NJajg4LV9MSFRYc3g5N2I3NEpmbFFrNllMaFEyekMyYVZKUUg5Ymk4dDRadkNJTkc5eUZIN3JEbFctNF92RU1rX3FjeHNveFFLTDZranc4TE1jZmJXSk14SHhzdzNRRDFiMnJ5QQ?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content prose dark:prose-invert lg:prose-lg lg:leading-[29px] font-serif max-w-none"&gt;
              
              
              &lt;p&gt;A small Oregon county has been struck by one of the rarest but scariest ailments known to exist. Health officials in Hood River County have reported an unusual cluster of people coming down with Creutzfeldt-Jakob Disease, or CJD.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Three residents in the area have contracted CJD over the past eight months, according to the &lt;a href="https://www.hoodrivercounty.gov/index.asp?SEC=AF40862A-8B0E-4107-B2B4-956029C71941&amp;amp;DE=11E4744C-DDC6-4DBD-8F95-B86EFBB310E6"&gt;Hood River County Health Department&lt;/a&gt;, two of whom are already dead. Local and federal health officials are now investigating the cluster, but they have not identified a link between the cases to date.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p class="not-prose"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/prions/about/index.html"&gt;CJD and similar brain diseases&lt;/a&gt; are caused by a misfolded version of the naturally occurring prion protein. When these rogue proteins come into contact with their harmless brethren, they convert them into more misfolded prions, acting almost like a zombie invasion. The accumulation of prions steadily destroys the brain, though it can take years or even decades for symptoms to appear. Once they do, however, death quickly follows.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Thankfully for humanity, prion ailments are rare (other prion-like diseases might be &lt;a href="https://gizmodo.com/the-molecular-devils-that-cause-the-most-fatal-diseases-ever-known-2000511979"&gt;more common&lt;/a&gt;). While CJD is the most common prion disease, only around 500 new cases of it are estimated to happen in the U.S. annually. This rarity makes three cases showing up so close together in the same relatively small county (roughly 24,000 people live in Hood River) all the weirder.&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;p&gt;CJD can broadly happen in three different ways. It can be passed down from mutations that make the emergence of prions inevitable. It can be transmitted, though usually only through rare scenarios such as close contact with infected brain tissue. Or it can simply occur sporadically for no clear reason.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p class="not-prose"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Most CJD cases fall in the last bucket. But over &lt;a href="https://gizmodo.com/what-happened-to-mad-cow-disease-history-prions-1851242160"&gt;thirty years ago&lt;/a&gt;, there was an outbreak of CJD caused by tainted cow meat (this specific form of CJD came to be known as variant CJD). As it turns out, the cows were infected with their own version of a prion disease—a condition formally called bovine spongiform encephalopathy, but more memorably known as mad cow disease.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The mad cow/vCJD outbreak was contained by the mid-1990s, and only a few hundred people were ever sickened by prion-infected beef. But it showed that prion diseases can be more transmissible than we thought, and even today, scientists still worry about the possibility of similar events happening again. In North America, for instance, a prion disease has been steadily spreading among deer in recent years, though there is &lt;a href="https://gizmodo.com/prions-venison-deer-meat-brain-disease-mad-cow-guide-1851547274"&gt;no solid evidence yet&lt;/a&gt; that it poses a threat to people.&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;p&gt;For that reason, anytime a cluster of CJD does appear, it tends to set off public health alarms. The bunching together of these cases in Hood River, Oregon—one confirmed, two suspected—might simply be pure, if unlucky, coincidence. But it remains important to rule out the scarier scenario. For now, there’s no immediate signs of something more being amiss.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;“At this time, there is no identifiable link between these three cases,” the Hood River County Health Department said in its latest statement on the cluster, released Monday.&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;p&gt;The health department is still monitoring the situation, in conjunction with the Oregon Health Authority (OHA) and Centers for Disease Control and Prevention (CDC). But as they rightly note, the general risk of CJD to the public is very low.&lt;/p&gt;
                          &lt;/div&gt;

            &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Gizmodo</author><pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 15:28:38 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMivwFBVV95cUxOSGhUd3o0R0liOUNHdjhWaFZ0REpZcmNDYmNXblc1R2NUQVhKX1pkalVXQm4wdlZtZjV4b253dVQ0SlNhTUdjeURGWEJhT3JFY2VSSTJpNnhTS1NJajg4LV9MSFRYc3g5N2I3NEpmbFFrNllMaFEyekMyYVZKUUg5Ymk4dDRadkNJTkc5eUZIN3JEbFctNF92RU1rX3FjeHNveFFLTDZranc4TE1jZmJXSk14SHhzdzNRRDFiMnJ5QQ</guid></item><item><title>睡眠专家对晚上锻炼发出严厉警告-每日邮报 | Sleep expert issues stark warning about working out in the evening - Daily Mail</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMimAFBVV95cUxQMGhDLWk3bjZBMUFzQnhoV2V6ejRWQUxSS3AydVdrbXJsNThaanpDUGJ5Q0p3MWoyeF8zN0ZQTWI5VGs5dUQySlVlOFJoMTBCWXozRzNJT1dTdS16a282Mk5OZHdZWHJPcXllSnF0YlYtMXluOTRrblZHTi15U0JWX2tWeG5JbUR4MUJXelBMMi1fdG0wTm8tX9IBngFBVV95cUxQVHNqaWh3WkdabUNwRWctMEJGdWJUSXJYVE50RTdqMDJ4Zy16VkFueThlc1c1ZWxHRTRvemM2NUg3NzBZTElEVE5ta1ZlTzVFQ1ppQU1nNDZqaU1MVkFNQV9wX0NtY3h1MXJOSmI2QU54TGNnaHZMSEJVLXJ6cll0WmJfVTRENXRCM3JMXzBFZWdqMzFRbkZ5OHNlVkE4QQ?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div itemprop="articleBody"&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;You know that feeling when you're done with a workout, feel energized and ready to take on the day? &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Well, what do you do when you workout in the evening, and you have that feeling right as you're supposed to be winding down for bed? &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Did you know that this could be the reason you're not getting a good night's sleep? &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'That post-exercise buzz is one reason why timing your workouts is just as important as doing them in the first place,' sleep expert Dr. Leah Kaylor told DailyMail.com. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'While exercise supports better sleep overall, working out too close to bedtime can interfere with the body's ability to wind down.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Dr. Kaylor explained that our bodies 'activate' when we workout. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Our heart rate increases, our blood circulates, and we release hormones like adrenaline and cortisol. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'These hormones prime you for action, not rest,' she added. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;When you exercise before bed, it could result in you getting a bad night of sleep (stock image) &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;And when you exert energy, your body temperature rises. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Dr. Kaylor said that this can be a problem as a decline in core temperature is a critical signal to your body to initiate sleep.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'If your body is still warm and alert from a late workout, it may take hours to return to a sleep-ready state,' she said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;And if you're thinking, 'Well, I'm exhausted after my workouts and fall asleep easily,' that actually doesn't necessarily mean you're getting good sleep.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Dr. Kaylor explained that even if you fall asleep shortly after an evening workout, there are still lingering elevations of adrenaline and cortisol in your body that can reduce the quality of your sleep. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;These hormones are actively working to give you less time in deep and REM stages of your sleep - something essential for physical recovery, memory processing, and emotional resilience.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;She said when this happens, your sleep becomes lighter, more fragmented and less restorative. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;And it's not just your body that remains active - it's your brain as well as there's a lot more mental engagement that goes into workouts than you'd think.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Working out too close to your bedtime can make your sleep lighter, more fragmented, and less restorative (stock image)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Whether you're focused on your form, tracking your progress, or riding the emotional high of a new personal best, your brain may remain active long after your body stops moving,' Dr. Kaylor explained.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;So if you're someone who only has the time to work out after you're done with the workday, where does that leave you?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'For many people juggling work, family, and daily obligations, the only time available to exercise may be in the evening,' Dr. Kaylor said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'In those cases, there are ways to reap the benefits of movement while minimizing sleep disruption.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;First, she explained that your best bet is to give yourself three hours between your workout and your bedtime.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Dr. Kaylor also suggested 'exercise snacks.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'These are short bursts of physical activity spread throughout the day rather than one long workout,' she dished. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Sleep expert Dr. Leah Kaylor said 'exercise snacks' - short bursts of physical activity spread throughout the day - can be an alternative to long, evening workouts &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Research shows that as long as you're getting 150 minutes of moderate physical activity a week - even if it's done broken up into just 5-10 minutes at a time - you can still reap great health and sleep benefits.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'These micro-workouts provide flexibility, reduce the risk of overtraining, and are particularly useful for beginners, those recovering from injury, or anyone with a packed schedule,' the expert said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Along with this, she said that a proper wind-down routine at bedtime is essential to prepare your body for a good night's sleep. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'By making consistent, intentional choices, you can support your sleep, health, and fitness goals - without needing a perfect schedule or a full hour at the gym,' she said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
            

            
            
            
            
            &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Daily Mail</author><pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 15:01:44 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimAFBVV95cUxQMGhDLWk3bjZBMUFzQnhoV2V6ejRWQUxSS3AydVdrbXJsNThaanpDUGJ5Q0p3MWoyeF8zN0ZQTWI5VGs5dUQySlVlOFJoMTBCWXozRzNJT1dTdS16a282Mk5OZHdZWHJPcXllSnF0YlYtMXluOTRrblZHTi15U0JWX2tWeG5JbUR4MUJXelBMMi1fdG0wTm8tX9IBngFBVV95cUxQVHNqaWh3WkdabUNwRWctMEJGdWJUSXJYVE50RTdqMDJ4Zy16VkFueThlc1c1ZWxHRTRvemM2NUg3NzBZTElEVE5ta1ZlTzVFQ1ppQU1nNDZqaU1MVkFNQV9wX0NtY3h1MXJOSmI2QU54TGNnaHZMSEJVLXJ6cll0WmJfVTRENXRCM3JMXzBFZWdqMzFRbkZ5OHNlVkE4QQ</guid></item><item><title>研究表明，食用油可能会增加患侵袭性癌症的几率- MassLive | Cooking oil could fuel chances of aggressive cancer, study shows - MassLive</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiqgFBVV95cUxPSHBXczJPN3VtY3BSTmUtVzRXb2JrZ2hPOElCdDdlWHFjcm9ZUzU1bjJlZ0lVazE2TlFRQ1dta3FhY2c3djZ3Y1N6Umx0bm9kN0NGT05pT0tWWjdpT20zOExiMlF3ekFJVWUyRm5LSUJHWXNfVWxUSldGTlBEOURwVEp6LUM0VHQyUVlLXzd0akZkUFNhM1FNME13TDFVRFJjakNqY0JpWGc0Z9IBvgFBVV95cUxNRXFjVWNjUTV0TUtSMC1GMEhTWWdfeTY0cVNZMWJOWlF0TC1pY0FEVUN0ams4a1RKdFpMU192Tl83MS1IYlJkelNIbFpsblhxOFZsSkxFN0NDSmM4eWNpaG1SZXh1aFBHbkN2YmNCM2VzdTdzS25IajBrVEh5WDBhTjBwWWdzdGlEZl92bXEyVS1aNHZQV1kxbDh4VUlJd3U0YkNrVFlvdWVQWDhORE1SRXhYdG9TMU9xSkxrSk1n?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content "&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="LGY5DKJMOVEUHN37MCDSYC5RXA"&gt;Consuming too much cooking oil could increase your chances of cancer, a study from Weill Cornell Medicine found.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-1"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="N6Z2XAVBVVFEPH7BVTDEJ26YLI"&gt;The study was published on March 14 in &lt;a href="https://www.science.org/doi/10.1126/science.adm9805" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer" title="https://www.science.org/doi/10.1126/science.adm9805"&gt;Science&lt;/a&gt;, after researchers noticed that linoleic acid, an omega-6 fatty acid found in vegetable and seed oils, can enhance an aggressive subtype of breast cancer called triple-negative breast cancer (TNBC).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-2"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="REEVRDUOSREURHZ26GZMFXWUTA"&gt;TNBC, known for its rapid growth and spread, has limited treatment options. It is more common in women under the age of 40 and accounts for 10% to 15% of all breast cancers, with a 77% survival rate according to the &lt;a href="https://www.cancer.org/cancer/types/breast-cancer/about/types-of-breast-cancer/triple-negative.html#:~:text=Triple%2Dnegative%20breast%20cancer%20(TNBC,%22%20on%20all%203%20tests.)" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer" title="https://www.cancer.org/cancer/types/breast-cancer/about/types-of-breast-cancer/triple-negative.html#:~:text=Triple%2Dnegative%20breast%20cancer%20(TNBC,%22%20on%20all%203%20tests.)"&gt;American Cancer Society&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-3"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="7NMJCQSHZNA5TGGPXCTW4TSQPI"&gt;Linoleic acid is deemed essential for mammals, playing crucial roles in supporting inflammation regulation, skin health and cell membrane structure, according to an article from &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/fat-in-common-cooking-oils-is-linked-to-aggressive-breast-cancer-but-heres-why-you-shouldnt-panic-254255" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer" title="https://theconversation.com/fat-in-common-cooking-oils-is-linked-to-aggressive-breast-cancer-but-heres-why-you-shouldnt-panic-254255"&gt;The Conversation&lt;/a&gt;. However, since the 1950s, people have been eating too much of this fat when using seed oils in fried and ultra-processed foods. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-4"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="CPTETCYFQBFHBIMGRWQ75P2ZBE"&gt;Dr. John Blenis, the study’s senior author and a cancer researcher at Weill Cornell, &lt;a href="https://nypost.com/2025/04/16/lifestyle/cooking-oil-linked-to-aggressive-breast-cancer/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer" title="https://nypost.com/2025/04/16/lifestyle/cooking-oil-linked-to-aggressive-breast-cancer/"&gt;told The New York Post&lt;/a&gt; that “the findings do not warrant blanket avoidance of seed oils, but suggest moderation and selectivity, especially for high-risk individuals.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-5" class="middleParagraph"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="TAPBRJUAYRHSPF6YBXIPCJRATA"&gt;Linoleic acid can be found in seed oils made of canola, corn, cottonseed, grapeseed, soy, sunflower, safflower and rice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-6"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="ZYEUWUWZOZH4VJY6PPIEROXELM"&gt;These oils are high in omega-6 fatty acids but lower in omega-3s. This imbalance can lead to inflammation in the body, The Post explained.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-7"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="G65S56Q7FJHQHNCNGXZG4OBVJ4"&gt;Therefore, the best way to stay healthy, Blenis explained in the New York Post article, is to have “a balanced, whole-food diet” because it’s considered “an important cornerstone of cancer prevention” and is “a strategy everyone can adopt.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-8"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-enter:LY4ZZJMJSJASFICLGQTF4T5YRE" data-fusion-component="LY4ZZJMJSJASFICLGQTF4T5YRE"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-exit:LY4ZZJMJSJASFICLGQTF4T5YRE" data-fusion-component="LY4ZZJMJSJASFICLGQTF4T5YRE"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-9"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>MassLive</author><pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 14:15:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiqgFBVV95cUxPSHBXczJPN3VtY3BSTmUtVzRXb2JrZ2hPOElCdDdlWHFjcm9ZUzU1bjJlZ0lVazE2TlFRQ1dta3FhY2c3djZ3Y1N6Umx0bm9kN0NGT05pT0tWWjdpT20zOExiMlF3ekFJVWUyRm5LSUJHWXNfVWxUSldGTlBEOURwVEp6LUM0VHQyUVlLXzd0akZkUFNhM1FNME13TDFVRFJjakNqY0JpWGc0Z9IBvgFBVV95cUxNRXFjVWNjUTV0TUtSMC1GMEhTWWdfeTY0cVNZMWJOWlF0TC1pY0FEVUN0ams4a1RKdFpMU192Tl83MS1IYlJkelNIbFpsblhxOFZsSkxFN0NDSmM4eWNpaG1SZXh1aFBHbkN2YmNCM2VzdTdzS25IajBrVEh5WDBhTjBwWWdzdGlEZl92bXEyVS1aNHZQV1kxbDh4VUlJd3U0YkNrVFlvdWVQWDhORE1SRXhYdG9TMU9xSkxrSk1n</guid></item><item><title>关于压力的真相：从“好事”的好处到只会让它变得更糟的运动-雅虎 | The truth about stress: from the benefits of the ‘good kind’ to the exercise that only makes it worse - Yahoo</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMihAFBVV95cUxPYVBHZ0FuU0hKQXRsYTZTd1dicWtNenhVVGtQcGVzcEQ4UW1ZTHU2V3dnU21Rd0s3YzY0bTJOeUxMZEZEWHVZYkZSb0VJbDZUV0xhMGxycVlPMVktekVsbndFNjdGTVhBQVhsRDlQZ3VPYkR1bFlNSVVUbzdVcjNtSVo3bGo?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="" data-article-body="true"&gt;&lt;h2 class="mb-4 text-xl font-bold md:text-2xl"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;It’s all in the mind&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;True (up to a point)&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;The way stress manifests is very much bodily, centred around hormones such as cortisol and their effect on us. But this process is triggered by the brain (notably the amygdala and the hypothalamus) and the way our brains react to stress is often set in early childhood, even in the womb. Pregnant women who experience extreme stress can give birth to infants who react more strongly to stress hormones – with increasing evidence suggesting that this causes modifications to the baby’s DNA. Self-actualising your way out of stress is difficult – not least because the causes might be serious and inescapable – but not always impossible. &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/31639385/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Some studies have shown;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Some studies have shown&lt;/a&gt; that if you tell people they are the sort of person who doesn’t feel stress, they experience fewer symptoms. &lt;a href="https://via.library.depaul.edu/cgi/viewcontent.cgi?article=1371&amp;amp;context=csh_etd" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:One US study;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;One US study&lt;/a&gt; found that teenagers growing up with worries about violent crime in a deprived part of Chicago tended to fare better if they simply tried to not think about it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mb-4 text-xl font-bold md:text-2xl"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;It is always bad for you&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;False&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;Stress is central to the human existence, and its most obvious and visceral manifestation – our fight-or-flight response to immediate threat – has evolved to protect us from danger. There is also evidence that it can help us concentrate. A study of &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32076623/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:video game players taking part in a tournament;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;video game players taking part in a tournament&lt;/a&gt; found that those who showed barely any rise in cortisol levels fared the worst, and those with the highest increase performed moderately. Winners tended to have some extra cortisol, but not too much. This hormonal and psychological balancing act is different for everyone, so gauging the “right” amount of stress is difficult. But as a broad guide, stress is less likely to be harmful if it is predictable, and particularly if it is voluntary. Studies have shown that conducting an orchestra makes the body show multiple signs of apparent stress. But this is the stress of exhilaration, which is less likely to cause ill effects.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mb-4 text-xl font-bold md:text-2xl"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;It’s the preserve of &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;male business executives&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;False&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;For decades the study of stress was based entirely around men, and often centred on the better-off. The breakthrough came with a &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/7246835/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:pioneering Swedish study;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;pioneering Swedish study&lt;/a&gt; which found that people who had high demands on their time but little control over their lives tended to be the most stressed. Subsequent research has shown how unavoidable demands, whether through caring responsibilities or having multiple jobs, are especially stressful. These findings are central to much of the understanding about modern stress, particularly that connected to work. Sir Michael Marmot, the pioneering researcher into health inequalities, has argued that jobs like those in an Amazon-type warehouse, where the pace is relentless and every movement is tracked, are “as if we took everything we knew about psychosocial work hazards, put it in a syringe and injected people with it”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mb-4 text-xl font-bold md:text-2xl"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;It’s a new worry&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;False&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;Much of our modern understanding of stress is based on experiments with laboratory rats carried out in the 1930s by Hans Selye, an Austrian–Hungarian doctor and researcher who discovered that repeated and chronic triggering of the body’s hormonal alarm system can harm health. But even the Victorians worried that innovations like rail travel and the telegraph were too much for humans to deal with. George Miller Beard, the highly creative populariser of the disorder he called neurasthenia, used his evocatively titled 1881 book, American Nervousness, to blame stress on everything from science to civil liberties and “the phenomenal beauty of the American girl of the highest type”. Is modern stress any worse? It is certainly different. Compared to a Victorian, a 21st-century Briton has a state-provided safety net, decades’ more life expectancy and a child mortality rate about 60 times lower. There is, however, much focus on whether information overload from things like phones is a new type of stress. It is a reasonable concern, particularly for children – but it’s far from new. The term “information overload” was coined by Alvin Toffler, a US author whose bestselling book Future Shock argued that the pace of change in society caused by things like modern technology was simply too much for people’s brains – in 1970.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mb-4 text-xl font-bold md:text-2xl"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;It’s mainly caused by big worries&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mainly false&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;In his 1972 poem The Shoelace, Charles Bukowski noted that while humans can generally cope with major upheavals, what eventually proves too much is the “continuing series of small tragedies” – everything from the “shoelace that snaps with no time left” to an unexpected bill. He was right; repeated studies have shown that stress tends to affect people most when it is chronic. But it’s also important to note that the scale of a worry is relative. What qualifies as a “minor” stress is entirely personal and subjective, and dependent on everything from personal circumstances and background to income – a single larger-than-expected bill can be catastrophic if you’re poor. There are some ways that stress, or at least its effects, can be mitigated. But don’t let anyone tell you that a particular cause of stress is minor. That is entirely a matter for you and your body.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mb-4 text-xl font-bold md:text-2xl"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Exercise always helps&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;False&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;There are endless studies showing that physical activity can alleviate stress symptoms. But other research has shown that very high-intensity exercise can worsen matters. &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/30345865/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:One study;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;One study&lt;/a&gt; put volunteers through either a gruelling mock job interview process or a physical test using a stationary bike. While post-test questionnaires showed those in the latter group perceived themselves to be less stressed, their cortisol levels were higher, and stayed so for hours after. Cortisol itself is not a problem for the body. It plays a central role in maintaining things like blood glucose levels, and also acts as a hormonal alarm clock, rising gradually during the night to a morning peak to help get us out of bed. The problem comes with the chronic triggering of the body’s stress response. So, how to avoid this with exercise? One tip is to make sure it doesn’t feel like a chore – research has shown this can be particularly stressful. Another is to see if less intensive exercise, perhaps even something like yoga, helps. But as ever, there are no firm rules. Everyone is different.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mb-4 text-xl font-bold md:text-2xl"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You lose weight when stressed&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;True and false&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;Some people lose weight under chronic stress. But around two-thirds of people are more likely to put it on. There are two different factors at work, and one is hormonal. Studies have linked consistently high levels of hormones like cortisol with a propensity to &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC5958156/#:~:text=High%20levels%20of%20cortisol%20can,to%20abdominal%20obesity%20%5B4%5D" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:store fat around the stomach;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;store fat around the stomach&lt;/a&gt;. Also, research has consistently shown that stress tends to push people towards less healthy eating choices. There is an entire sub-genre of studies in which volunteers are placed under artificial stress, presented with a table of various foods, and told to snack as they please. Each time, those exposed to stress gravitate towards fatty, sweet or salty choices, and eat more overall than the control group who were not stressed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mb-4 text-xl font-bold md:text-2xl"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Animals also feel stress&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;True&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt; The same fight-or-flight hormonal alarm system exists in mammals, birds, fish, amphibians and reptiles. And this is not just about existential threats. Studies of baboons have shown that lower‑ranked animals in a troop display higher levels of stress hormones. But what is unique about humans is the idea of chronic anticipatory stress. As Robert Sapolsky, a US biologist who spent two decades studying Kenyan baboons, &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC8040328/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:once joked;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;once joked&lt;/a&gt;: “It is startling to realise that a vast length of time ago, while evading a predator or pursuing a prey, a dinosaur secreted glucocorticoids … [But] no dinosaur ever worried itself sick from perseverating on the absurd idea that an asteroid might strike Earth.” For humans, anticipatory stress serves a purpose. For example, if you were blithely unworried about taking an exam, your study regime might be a bit relaxed. Simply telling people not to worry about future events is pointless, and you should never feel guilty about worrying.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mb-4 text-xl font-bold md:text-2xl"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;It’s your fault you’re stressed&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Very, very false&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;There are two immediate and very obvious reasons why this is wrong. Stress is often imposed by inescapable external factors, and people’s bodily response to it can often be exacerbated by their backgrounds, notably their childhood and infancy. But there is more to it: stress acts in such a way as to make it even harder to escape the circumstances which cause it, like poverty. &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/23990553/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:One US study;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;One US study &lt;/a&gt;found that when poorer people were asked to think about an entirely hypothetical car repair bill, they performed less well in a subsequent cognitive test. Other studies have quantified this effect variously as being about the same as losing an entire night of sleep or shedding close to 15 IQ points. This is not a minor impact.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mb-4 text-xl font-bold md:text-2xl"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;There’s nothing you can do about it&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;True (and yet not)&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;This is correct in the sense that stress can often be imposed by your life circumstances and the preset way your body reacts. But the physical manifestations of stress are more possible to address. For example, while chronic stress can make you more likely to develop metabolic ailments such as type 2 diabetes, being more physically active can reduce this risk again. Some diets can have a similar effect, with studies showing that ones including a lot of green vegetables and foods rich in polyphenols, known for their anti-inflammatory properties, &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/38034010/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:can reduce cortisol levels;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;can reduce cortisol levels&lt;/a&gt;. Psychotherapy can also help with our in-built responses to stress. And research has shown the stress-reducing benefits of everything from more sleep and better-quality social relations to certain music, aromas and, at least in the short term, simple human touch. What works for one person might not for another, but one of the curiosities of stress is that its very slipperiness, the way it presents such a broad front in its impact on humans, also gives lots of ingress points when fighting back.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Stress Tested: How the New Science of Stress Hormones Can Transform Your Health by Dr &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;Richard Mackenzie&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt; and &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;Peter Walker&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt; is published on 24&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt; April (Bluebird&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;, £22). To support the Guardian and Observer, order your copy at &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://guardianbookshop.com/stress-tested-9781035049028/?utm_source=editoriallink&amp;amp;utm_medium=merch&amp;amp;utm_campaign=article" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:guardianbookshop.com;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;guardianbookshop.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;. Delivery charges may apply.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Yahoo</author><pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 14:00:12 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihAFBVV95cUxPYVBHZ0FuU0hKQXRsYTZTd1dicWtNenhVVGtQcGVzcEQ4UW1ZTHU2V3dnU21Rd0s3YzY0bTJOeUxMZEZEWHVZYkZSb0VJbDZUV0xhMGxycVlPMVktekVsbndFNjdGTVhBQVhsRDlQZ3VPYkR1bFlNSVVUbzdVcjNtSVo3bGo</guid></item><item><title>精神分裂症患者髓鞘蛋白受损-神经科学新闻 | Disrupted Myelin Protein Implicated in Schizophrenia - Neuroscience News</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiZ0FVX3lxTFBrOHdFS1ZhTWlzOEZ6SFdqbVdLb280RGE5V2Y1NXp4SkdMcUhxN3gzRkRfQW1ISVpNbEFqZzktVm5BcG1DV3dhOTFSUENYLWZaMDQ4eUdZdjd4R1FldUlHV1VMeWpJWG8?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content body-color clearfix link-color-wrap"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary: &lt;/strong&gt;A new study has identified the protein hnRNP A1 as a key player in the production and maintenance of myelin, the fatty sheath that insulates nerve fibers in the brain. Myelin loss is common in disorders like multiple sclerosis and schizophrenia, and this research shows that hnRNP A1 disruptions can impair myelination at the molecular level, even before behavioral symptoms appear.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Using a rodent model, scientists induced and later reversed demyelination to track the effects on memory, motor function, and social behavior. The findings offer fresh insight into how early molecular changes in myelin-related proteins could contribute to neurodegenerative and neuropsychiatric disorders, potentially opening new avenues for therapeutic intervention.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Facts:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class="wp-block-list"&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Myelin Disruption:&lt;/strong&gt; Disruption of hnRNP A1 impairs myelin production and may play a role in schizophrenia and multiple sclerosis.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Silent Molecular Shifts:&lt;/strong&gt; Changes in myelin-related proteins occurred without immediate behavioral symptoms, suggesting early markers of disease.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Reversibility Observed:&lt;/strong&gt; Restoring myelin reversed behavioral deficits in rodents, underscoring therapeutic potential.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Source: &lt;/strong&gt;FAPESP&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Research published in the &lt;em&gt;Journal of Neurochemistry&lt;/em&gt; has detailed the role of a protein, hnRNP A1, in the formation and stability of myelin, suggesting an important impact on neurodegenerative diseases and mental disorders such as multiple sclerosis and schizophrenia. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The findings pave the way for new research and potential treatments.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Myelin is a fatty substance produced by oligodendrocytes (cells of the central nervous system) that forms a sheath, like a kind of “insulator.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It “protects” the extensions of neurons (axons) and increases the conduction speed of nerve impulses that carry information between neural cells.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Scientific literature has shown that patients with multiple sclerosis and schizophrenia lose myelin (called demyelination), leaving part of the axons “unplugged” and causing damage to brain function.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This rodent study examined changes in proteins essential for myelin production (myelination). The results highlight the involvement of hnRNP A1 in maintaining the integrity of this protective sheath.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;hnRNP A1 regulates the processing of messenger RNA, i.e., it controls how the molecule is cut and assembled (splicing), thereby determining which proteins are produced and in what amounts. Studied for years by this group of scientists at the State University of Campinas (UNICAMP), in the state of São Paulo, Brazil, hnRNP A1 had already figured prominently in previous research carried out on brain tissue from people with schizophrenia and on cells grown in the laboratory.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“When I was a master’s student, I worked with oligodendrocyte predecessor cell lines and their responses to antipsychotics. This protein, hnRNP A1, always appeared. We decided to try to understand its role in oligodendrocytes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“But to do this, we had to use an animal model to induce myelination and understand the process,” explains Caroline Brandão Teles, first author of the article and FAPESP doctoral fellow at the Institute of Biology (IB-UNICAMP).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For researcher Fernanda Crunfli, also from IB-UNICAMP and corresponding author of the paper, myelin has been an important target of study for neuropsychiatric diseases.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“We were able to analyze the demyelination process in the animals and then restore the myelin sheath. This allowed for an interesting study window.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“We did behavioral tests to assess locomotion, short- and long-term memory, and social interaction. When the myelin is restored, all these functions return to the brain,” says Crunfli, who was a FAPESP postdoctoral fellow.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Teles points out that this was one of the results that caught the group’s attention – the fact that the changes were detected at the molecular level, without affecting the animals’ behavior.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“With this molecular and non-behavioral alteration, the work has the interesting potential to pinpoint an important protein in the establishment of schizophrenia. This same animal model is analyzed in research on multiple sclerosis, for example, and when there’s a behavioral study, changes are noted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“In the case of schizophrenia, the fact that the behavior isn’t altered indicates, in my opinion, that this protein is essential in the development of the disease and may have an influence on its genesis,” Professor Daniel Martins-de-Souza, from IB-UNICAMP, Teles’ supervisor and head of the Neuroproteomics Laboratory, told Agência FAPESP.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Schizophrenia is a mental disorder characterized by loss of contact with reality (psychosis), hallucinations, delusions, and impaired cognition, among other symptoms. The exact cause is still unknown, but recent research suggests a combination of hereditary factors and molecular and functional alterations in the brain. Treatment includes antipsychotic medications and psychotherapy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It is estimated that approximately 1.6 million people in Brazil have schizophrenia. Worldwide, the prevalence is about 1% of the world’s population.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For years, Martins-de-Souza’s research group has been working to understand the role of oligodendrocytes in schizophrenia and has managed to map a series of brain proteins that help to unravel the molecular basis of the disorder.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To understand the research&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The group used a rodent (murine) model that has also been studied in cases of multiple sclerosis, a disease characterized by severe demyelination.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;From the eighth week of the experiment, demyelination was induced and continued for another five weeks. The process was then interrupted and the myelin sheath was restored.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;During this time, the researchers analyzed the activity of hnRNP A1. “We saw that the proteins linked to myelin in these animals were all reduced. By disrupting the activity of this protein [&lt;em&gt;hnRNP A1&lt;/em&gt;], we ended up disrupting myelination,” says Teles.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The scientists believe that studying the impact of the protein’s alterations on synaptic transmission and cognitive processes could reveal new therapeutic targets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Funding: &lt;/strong&gt;In addition to the grants, the research was also supported by FAPESP through six other projects (17/25588-1, 19/05155-9, 18/01410-1, 23/08885-3, 18/01669-5 and 23/11514-7).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;About this schizophrenia research news&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="has-background"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Author: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#0c647e696562697e784c6a6d7c697f7c226e7e" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Heloisa Reinert&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Source: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://fapesp.br" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;FAPESP&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Contact: &lt;/strong&gt;Heloisa Reinert – FAPESP&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Image: &lt;/strong&gt;The image is credited to Neuroscience News&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="has-background"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Original Research: &lt;/strong&gt;Open access.&lt;br&gt;“&lt;a href="https://dx.doi.org/10.1111/jnc.16304" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Impacts of hnRNP A1 Splicing Inhibition on the Brain Remyelination Proteome&lt;/a&gt;” by Caroline Brandão Teles et al. &lt;em&gt;Journal of Neurochemistry&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr class="wp-block-separator has-text-color has-pale-cyan-blue-color has-alpha-channel-opacity has-pale-cyan-blue-background-color has-background"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Abstract&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Impacts of hnRNP A1 Splicing Inhibition on the Brain Remyelination Proteome&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Oligodendrocytes, the myelinating cells in the central nervous system, are implicated in several neurological disorders marked by dysfunctional RNA–binding proteins (RBPs).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The present study aimed at investigating the role of hnRNP A1 in the proteome of the corpus callosum, prefrontal cortex, and hippocampus of a murine cuprizone–induced demyelination model.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Right after the cuprizone insult, we administered an hnRNP A1 splicing activity inhibitor and analyzed its impact on brain remyelination by nanoESI-LC-MS/MS label-free proteomic analysis to assess the biological processes affected in these brain regions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Significant alterations in essential myelination proteins highlighted the involvement of hnRNP A1 in maintaining myelin integrity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pathways related to sphingolipid and endocannabinoid signaling were affected, as well as the synaptic vesicle cycle and GABAergic synapses.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Although behavioral impairments were not observed, molecular changes suggest potential links to memory, synaptic function, and neurotransmission processes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These findings enhance our understanding of the multifaceted roles of hnRNP A1 in the central nervous system, providing valuable insights for future investigations and therapeutic interventions in neurodegenerative and demyelinating diseases.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p class="clear"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Neuroscience News</author><pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 13:51:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiZ0FVX3lxTFBrOHdFS1ZhTWlzOEZ6SFdqbVdLb280RGE5V2Y1NXp4SkdMcUhxN3gzRkRfQW1ISVpNbEFqZzktVm5BcG1DV3dhOTFSUENYLWZaMDQ4eUdZdjd4R1FldUlHV1VMeWpJWG8</guid></item><item><title>医生告诉我，我的背痛是正常的......实际上是4期癌症，我有几个月的生命-每日邮报 | Doctors told me my back pain was normal... it was actually stage 4 cancer and I was given months to live - Daily Mail</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMipAFBVV95cUxNMUNhZHVwTEpYaFNyMVdNemJ2QUl2ZkRTcUhPYTNvbHFNR0VRMmQxWmh2cEVaeXg2RHpTSHFmN01hX3dNQjJtUjFfZ2s3dXE2NkJfcVg4TU1pNmNWTEVfREZJSzdNRnBzUnpqN2ItbVRoY0tvV2NlVDh6YjJKdi10cWp3TFp1RHJ1eUxQVWY2djVTcTI2RDA2ZVpPVEVZMGlkOWd4UdIBqgFBVV95cUxPTGdoT0prMUtzLWs5UEUxY2ZTQ1NDcjI3YldSNnJndDBXd3ItUFNkQ1VZeG5mTmVrWXpwOUFRR2ZicXBmQ3pUcnRkbm1naG1KdVdnXzExVHdIUDA5NVVNcko3V1l0NnBzWXVESEptaTRDQk9FejRYSUkzaW9JbVlySkRHdllIS1NEU2NmVDl4NTRqOXd2S2J0eXNOZUgtWGJVbU15cjlxRC16Zw?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div itemprop="articleBody"&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Kate Crawford, from Pittsburgh, &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/pennsylvania/index.html" id="mol-9420ae60-1bac-11f0-8e2e-834760a08e8d"&gt;Pennsylvania&lt;/a&gt;, was 28 with three small children when she first began feeling something was wrong.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Doctors initially dismissed her severe back pain as a common nerve issue — understandable, they said, for a young mom juggling the demands of three small children. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Kate herself assumed the exhaustion and aches were simply part of motherhood.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But the symptoms kept piling up. Alongside the back pain, she developed a persistent cough, stomach issues, and strange bruises that refused to fade.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Still, she chalked it up to fatigue and a lingering cold.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;By the time doctors took a closer look, it was too late. The &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/cancer/index.html" id="mol-26d04ad0-1c58-11f0-805a-97be76b02f96"&gt;cancer&lt;/a&gt;, quietly growing in her breast for years, had already spread.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Tests revealed it had reached both breasts, her spine, liver, and pelvis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;That’s when doctors delivered the devastating news no young mother expects: she had just 18 to 24 months to live.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Kate Crawford was diagnosed with stage 4 breast cancer at 28 years old&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Kate initially blamed her symptoms on being a busy mom of three young kids&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span&gt;That was 12 years ago, and against all odds, Kate, now 41, has survived stage 4 metastatic breast cancer and is on a mission to check things off her bucket list and make lasting memories with her husband and children.  &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span&gt;She said she knows she will never be cured of cancer, but is 'thankful' to still be alive. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Kate is also determined to educate others on the lesser-known signs of cancer and teach them to advocate for themselves. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Looking back, she realizes how her seemingly unrelated symptoms were all subtle signs of cancer.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Kate&lt;/span&gt; used to blamed her upset stomach on a bad diet and when the cough she had wouldn't go away after several months, she thought she 'was having trouble shaking a cold.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'But these were all signs of cancer. I had no clue,' she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Kate continued: 'I just thought I was tired because I was a new mom.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'But it wasn't just exhaustion — I was bone-tired, with belly issues, a cough that lingered for months, and bruises that never went away.' &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;She added: 'If the doctor had just done an x-ray, he would've seen I had cancer. One day, I was a 28-year-old mom of babies, and the next, I was being told I might not be here much longer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'I didn't know what to look for. If I had been more educated in the signs, I might have been able to better advocate for myself. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'It may be too late for me, but it's not for you. If something doesn't feel right, please don't ignore it.' &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Kate said: &lt;/span&gt;'I didn't know the signs. That's what I want people to take away from this. Know your body. Don't ignore your gut. It might just save your life.' &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Kate has undergone 200 cancer treatments, including a double mastectomy &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Kate said less than 13 percent of metastatic breast cancer patients survive as long as she has with the disease&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    
    
    &lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;After her diagnosis of breast cancer, which affects about 317,000 women annually, she immediately started aggressive treatment. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;She has had more than 200 treatments, including a double mastectomy, and has spent nearly a third of her life in a relentless battle for survival. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;While treatable, metastatic breast cancer cannot be cured and about 42,000 women die of the disease each year. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The five-year survival rate for stage 4 breast cancer is 22 percent and Kate said less than 13 percent of metastatic breast cancer patients survive as long as she has with the disease. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;At times her treatment has been far from straightforward. She has had allergic reactions, heart failure and even developed early-stage lung disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But she has kept fighting, adapting her life around the three week treatment cycle and her changing body. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;She said: 'A stage 4 diagnosis means treatment for life and side effects for life. When one thing pops up, you just have to deal with it. Take it one step at a time. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'That time lets me relax and unwind. It reminds me to look for the glimmers.' &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Kate credits her strength to survive to her husband Steve and their children, twins Grace and Lily, now 16, and Stephen, 15, who are constantly at her side. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;And she concentrates on small joys - from floating in a lake on a calm day, laughing with her kids, or discovering a new outfit that fits just right. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;More than a decade after her diagnosis, Kate has adapted her life around the three week treatment cycle and her changing body&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Kate said: 'I just want to keep making memories with my family. That's all I've ever wanted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;And while she enjoys sharing her journey on social media, she warns against toxic positivity. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'I've never tried to sugarcoat my life, but people forget the daily struggles. We hide a lot, not for ourselves but to make others feel better. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'It's ok to feel not ok. You don't always have to be the brave, stoic cancer patient. You can be mad, bitter, sad and still be full of love. That is perfectly ok. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Kate continued: 'Getting diagnosed with cancer is like jumping into a big metaphorical lake full of other cancer patients. We're all in there together, but we can't help each other. We carefully tread water, but we get tired. Sometimes we barely hang on. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'People cheer from the shore. Some get rescued. Others stay. Some never make it out.' &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
            

            
            
            
            
            &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Daily Mail</author><pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 13:34:33 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipAFBVV95cUxNMUNhZHVwTEpYaFNyMVdNemJ2QUl2ZkRTcUhPYTNvbHFNR0VRMmQxWmh2cEVaeXg2RHpTSHFmN01hX3dNQjJtUjFfZ2s3dXE2NkJfcVg4TU1pNmNWTEVfREZJSzdNRnBzUnpqN2ItbVRoY0tvV2NlVDh6YjJKdi10cWp3TFp1RHJ1eUxQVWY2djVTcTI2RDA2ZVpPVEVZMGlkOWd4UdIBqgFBVV95cUxPTGdoT0prMUtzLWs5UEUxY2ZTQ1NDcjI3YldSNnJndDBXd3ItUFNkQ1VZeG5mTmVrWXpwOUFRR2ZicXBmQ3pUcnRkbm1naG1KdVdnXzExVHdIUDA5NVVNcko3V1l0NnBzWXVESEptaTRDQk9FejRYSUkzaW9JbVlySkRHdllIS1NEU2NmVDl4NTRqOXd2S2J0eXNOZUgtWGJVbU15cjlxRC16Zw</guid></item></channel></rss>