<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>GNews Health</title><link>https://news.google.com/</link><description></description><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>世界上第一个，以色列科学家使用基于RNA的基因疗法来阻止ALS恶化-以色列时报</title><link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/in-world-first-israeli-scientists-use-rna-based-gene-therapy-to-stop-als-deterioration/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="the-content"&gt;
					&lt;p&gt;In a groundbreaking study, researchers at Tel Aviv University, leading a large-scale international team of scientists, say they have identified – and neutralized – an RNA molecule that can stop the nerve cell damage that causes paralysis in patients with amyotrophic lateral sclerosis, ALS.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now they hope they can use the discovery to help patients with the fatal illness.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“When we added a specific RNA molecule to human cells and animal models for ALS, the nerve cells stopped degenerating and even regenerated,” said Prof. Eran Perlson from the Gray Faculty of Medical &amp;amp; Health Sciences and the Sagol School of Neuroscience at Tel Aviv University, speaking to The Times of Israel.&lt;/p&gt;
    
    &lt;p id="gpt-passback"&gt;
        
    &lt;/p&gt;
    
    
    
    
    
&lt;p&gt;Their study, recently published in the peer-reviewed journal &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41593-025-02062-6"&gt;Nature Neuroscience&lt;/a&gt;, opens a new avenue for treating the disease.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“We wanted to get to the root of the matter of what causes ALS to enable the development of effective drugs for this incurable disease,” Perlson said. The team used mice that had been genetically modified to serve as a “biological stand-in” for the disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="newsletter newsletter-article" data-website="timesofisrael" data-from="In world first, Israeli scientists use RNA-based gene therapy to stop ALS deterioration"&gt;
	&lt;div class="newsletter-article-inner"&gt;
		&lt;p class="newsletter-article-text newsletter-article-part"&gt;
			&lt;span&gt;Get The Times of Israel's Daily Edition&lt;/span&gt;
			&lt;span&gt;by email and never miss our top stories&lt;/span&gt;
		&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;div class="newsletter-article-form-wrapper newsletter-article-part"&gt;
			
			&lt;div class="newsletter-article-terms"&gt;&lt;p&gt;
				By signing up, you agree to the &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="/terms"&gt;terms&lt;/a&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;p class="newsletter-error newsletter-article-error"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
		
&lt;p&gt;The research was led by Dr. Ariel Ionescu, Dr. Lior Ankol, and lab manager Tal Pery Gradus in collaboration with Dr. Amir Dori, Senior Neurologist and Head of the Neuromuscular Disease Unit at Sheba Medical Center. Additional participants included researchers from the Weizmann Institute of Science, Ben-Gurion University of the Negev, and research institutions in France, Turkey, and Italy.&lt;/p&gt;

	&lt;figure id="attachment_3653563" class="wp-caption  alignnone"&gt;&lt;a href="https://static-cdn.toi-media.com/www/uploads/2025/09/PHOTO-2025-09-30-10-36-42-1-e1759235493237.jpg"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" class="size-large wp-image-3653563" src="https://static-cdn.toi-media.com/www/uploads/2025/09/PHOTO-2025-09-30-10-36-42-1-e1759235493237-640x400.jpg" alt=""&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
		&lt;figcaption class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Michael Podolsky with his cat, a few years before the onset of ALS. Podolsky, 44, was the first named individual with ALS to successfully fight for his right to die in Israel in almost 30 years and the first to donate his organs. He died on September 25, 2025. (Courtesy/Tamar Ashkenazi)&lt;/figcaption&gt;
	&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;About ALS&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ALS, sometimes called Lou Gehrig’s disease, is a fatal neurodegenerative condition that affects motor neurons — the nerve cells that control muscle movement. Over time, the disease causes gradual paralysis of all muscles in the body.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Patients typically lose their ability to walk, speak, swallow, and breathe, often becoming completely paralyzed while their cognitive skills remain intact.&lt;/p&gt;
               
           
           
        
&lt;p&gt;“Most patients die within three to five years of diagnosis, due to paralysis of the diaphragm muscles and respiratory failure,” said Perlson.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are currently some 600 ALS patients in Israel, according to &lt;a href="https://www.timesofisrael.com/circumventing-israeli-law-judge-okays-als-patients-right-to-die/"&gt;Efrat Carmi&lt;/a&gt;, CEO for IsrALS, the Israeli Research Association.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In ALS, the neuromuscular junctions, where nerve fibers meet muscle cells and transmit electrical signals from the brain to the muscles, are disrupted.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Perlson stated that the molecular mechanisms underlying this damage had remained unknown until now.&lt;/p&gt;

	&lt;figure id="attachment_3690407" class="wp-caption  alignnone"&gt;&lt;a href="https://static-cdn.toi-media.com/www/uploads/2025/11/2.-Illustration.jpeg"&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-large wp-image-3690407" src="https://static-cdn.toi-media.com/www/uploads/2025/11/2.-Illustration-640x400.jpeg" alt=""&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
		&lt;figcaption class="wp-caption-text"&gt;An illustration showing the gene therapy’s protective effect on motor neurons, preventing the “fire-like” degeneration characteristic of ALS. (Courtesy/Tel Aviv University)&lt;/figcaption&gt;
	&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;The microRNA that causes trouble in ALS patients&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The current study continues research from Perlson’s lab about microRNAs, the small molecules that regulate the translation of proteins and play an important role in many other cellular processes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In an earlier &lt;a href="https://www.timesofisrael.com/israeli-scientists-say-step-taken-toward-finding-treatment-of-lou-gehrig-disease/"&gt;study&lt;/a&gt;, Perlson and his team found that a protein called TDP-43 formed toxic clusters at the tip of the nerve, where it meets the muscle.&lt;/p&gt;
               
           
           
        
&lt;p&gt;In healthy bodies, the TDP-43 helps regulate how proteins are made in cells. But in ALS, it becomes unstable. To find out why this happens, the researchers studied tissues from ALS patients, mice that mimic having the disease, and human stem cell cultures.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Their experiments revealed that muscle cells produce tiny RNA molecules called microRNA-126.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The muscle cells then send them in tiny bubbles, called vesicles, across the small gap between nerve and muscle cells.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These microRNAs act like messengers that tell the nerve cells when to stop making TDP-43. Without the microRNA, TDP-43 continues to build up and becomes toxic.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“We discovered that in ALS, the muscle produces a smaller amount of microRNA-126,” said Ionescu. The decrease in this microRNA leads to an increase in the dangerous TDP-43.&lt;/p&gt;

	&lt;figure id="attachment_1626732" class="wp-caption  alignnone"&gt;&lt;a href="https://static-cdn.toi-media.com/www/uploads/2017/05/Lou-Geh.jpg"&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-large wp-image-1626732" src="https://static-cdn.toi-media.com/www/uploads/2017/05/Lou-Geh-640x400.jpg" alt=""&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
		&lt;figcaption class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Illustrative image of the neurological process causing Amyotrophic Lateral Sclerosis (ALS), also known as Lou Gehrig’s disease. (Screen capture: Moovly via YouTube)&lt;/figcaption&gt;
	&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The excessive TDP-43 then forms toxic clusters. These clumps attack the mitochondria, the essential molecules inside cells that turn food and oxygen into energy so the cell can work, move, and stay alive.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The damage is so great that it gradually destroys motor neurons, “leaving patients’ muscles paralyzed,” Ionescu said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;However, when the researchers added extra microRNA-126 to tissues from ALS patients and to mice with the disease, the process reversed.&lt;/p&gt;
               
           
           
        

	&lt;figure id="attachment_3690504" class="wp-caption  alignnone"&gt;&lt;a href="https://static-cdn.toi-media.com/www/uploads/2025/11/DSC_3161-contrast-crop-2.jpg"&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-large wp-image-3690504" src="https://static-cdn.toi-media.com/www/uploads/2025/11/DSC_3161-contrast-crop-2-640x400.jpg" alt=""&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
		&lt;figcaption class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Zevik Melamed, Ph.D., Principal Investigator, Laboratory of Molecular and Translational Neuroscience&lt;br&gt;Faculty of Medicine, Hebrew University of Jerusalem. (Courtesy)&lt;/figcaption&gt;
	&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Zevik Melamed, the principal investigator at the Laboratory of Molecular and Translational Neuroscience at Hebrew University of Jerusalem’s Faculty of Medicine, said the study “suggests that protecting communication between muscles and nerves might be just as important as targeting neurons directly.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“This is a real shift in how we think about preventing paralysis in ALS,” Melamed, who was not involved in the study, told The Times of Israel in a written comment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The study can be the basis for gene therapy for ALS, Perlson said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“The next step is taking it to clinical trials,” he said.&lt;/p&gt;

				&lt;/div&gt;

				
				

					
			&lt;div class="crm-post-module in-article-spical-counter bg-blue"&gt;
			

			&lt;p class="crm-post-module__title style-1"&gt;
				You appreciate our journalism			&lt;/p&gt;

			
			&lt;div class="crm-article-popup__content"&gt;
									&lt;img src="https://static-cdn.toi-media.com/www/uploads/2025/05/DH-new-headshot-circular.png" class="attachment-square_large size-square_large wp-post-image" alt="" decoding="async" loading="lazy" title=""&gt;													&lt;p class="crm-article-popup__counter-wrap"&gt;
						&lt;span class="crm-article-popup__counter"&gt;We’re really pleased that you’ve read &lt;strong&gt; &lt;span class="count-num"&gt;X&lt;/span&gt; Times of Israel articles&lt;/strong&gt; in the past month.&lt;/span&gt;
					&lt;/p&gt;
				
				&lt;p&gt;You clearly find our careful reporting valuable, in a time when facts are often distorted and news coverage often lacks context.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Your support is essential to continue our work.&lt;/strong&gt; We want to continue delivering the professional journalism you value, even as the demands on our newsroom have grown dramatically since October 7.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So today, please consider joining our reader support group, &lt;strong&gt;The Times of Israel Community&lt;/strong&gt;. For as little as $6 a month you'll become our partners while enjoying The Times of Israel &lt;strong&gt;AD-FREE&lt;/strong&gt;, as well as accessing exclusive content available only to Times of Israel Community members.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you,&lt;br&gt;&lt;em&gt;David Horovitz, Founding Editor of The Times of Israel&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
							&lt;/div&gt;

			&lt;a href="https://crm.timesofisrael.com/sign-up?utm_campaign=dhmatters&amp;amp;utm_source=website&amp;amp;utm_medium=article_end_counter&amp;amp;utm_content=1964F6" class="crm-post-module__btn"&gt;
				Join Our Community			&lt;/a&gt;

			&lt;a href="https://crm.timesofisrael.com/sign-up?utm_campaign=dhmatters&amp;amp;utm_source=website&amp;amp;utm_medium=article_end_counter&amp;amp;utm_content=1964F6" class="crm-post-module__btn crm-post-module__btn-mobile"&gt;
				Join Our Community			&lt;/a&gt;

			&lt;a class="crm_under_btn_link" target="_blank" href="//crm.timesofisrael.com/sign-in"&gt;Already a member? Sign in to stop seeing this&lt;/a&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
							&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Times of Israel</author><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 15:09:27 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiuAFBVV95cUxObjZPNXljYXcyN2FKZklqWGNtVnpXWk00T3ljV1d5V21vSUpYZXdNLXM4X3dVQ0dPcU00UUE5ejVUR0dHekRFcDdabm0yTm5WeUJVTlpuS3hyUFpVaXk0Q0RNbTFLMTdpV2VMdGF4TUFmMTVVVXFtdjNKMVhzdDRDN1RGX3k3TU54SGVmNVhOQnNYVHZ2eHo2N3dDcXA5VjlscU5MSDRXaWE0MGoyangwVTRlU1BYTzhx0gG-AUFVX3lxTE5qQ2J1eXJXYjdqNHhmaXgzOEc1ZkhxRGhTZTRXZDFQRUNiNmNjbnkwZVJ3Zk82SzNzbk9NV0pLX0R6LUVadGp2SndJa0ZXQTVSZ3daNEhMTzROSDRJZzN1S3J0WUJ5alA3cDZqbTBfS0tYWkZWUFFXTGwwNm96Zy1CM2dmRVE2NTFCdWNmVkZaUTkyNG5qek9qZlhwb0xzUl9HMjE0SDVQYTdHM2hqM0NzZGIwRDlXVEIxUkdFTkE</guid></item><item><title>一种常见的糖尿病药物与女性的“卓越长寿”有关- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/a-common-diabetes-drug-is-linked-to-exceptional-longevity-in-women</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Not only can the drug &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Metformin"&gt;metformin&lt;/a&gt; help to effectively manage type 2  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/diabetes" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73018" data-postid="181787" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;diabetes&lt;/a&gt;, but it may also give older women a better chance of living to the grand old age of 90, according to recent research – thanks, it seems, to a variety of anti-aging effects.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Scientists in the US and Germany used data from a long-term US study of postmenopausal women. Records on a total of 438 people were picked out – half of whom took metformin to treat diabetes, and half who took a different &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/study-confirms-experimental-drug-breaks-record-for-weight-loss-in-clinical-trials"&gt;diabetes drug&lt;/a&gt;, called sulfonylurea.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While there are some caveats and asterisks to the study, those in the metformin group were calculated to have a 30 percent lower risk of dying before the age of 90 than those in the sulfonylurea group.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/after-60-years-diabetes-drug-found-to-unexpectedly-impact-the-brain"&gt;After 60 Years, Diabetes Drug Found to Unexpectedly Impact The Brain&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Metformin has been shown to target multiple pathways of aging and therefore has been postulated as a drug that may extend human longevity," &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1093/gerona/glaf095"&gt;write&lt;/a&gt; the researchers in their published paper.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We found that metformin initiation increased exceptional longevity compared with sulfonylurea initiation among women with type 2 diabetes."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Metformin has been &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/a-common-diabetes-drug-will-be-trialled-as-an-anti-ageing-elixir-from-next-year"&gt;around for decades&lt;/a&gt; and is considered a gerotherapeutic: a drug able to slow down various aging processes in the body. For example, it's been shown to &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.cmet.2016.05.011"&gt;limit DNA damage&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.arr.2022.101621"&gt;promote gene activity&lt;/a&gt; associated with long life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_163572" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-163572" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/06/ElderlyWoman.jpg" alt="Elderly woman" class="wp-image-163572 size-full" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/06/ElderlyWoman.jpg 2000w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/06/ElderlyWoman-642x361.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/06/ElderlyWoman-738x415.jpg 738w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/06/ElderlyWoman-768x432.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/06/ElderlyWoman-1536x864.jpg 1536w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/06/ElderlyWoman-600x338.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 2000px) 100vw, 2000px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-163572" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;The study used age 90 as the marker for 'exceptional' longevity. (&lt;a href="https://unsplash.com/photos/persons-hand-in-shallow-focus-CeZypKDceQc"&gt;Danie Franco/Unsplash&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Previous studies have shown that metformin can &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/common-diabetes-medication-slows-brain-aging-in-monkeys"&gt;put the brakes on&lt;/a&gt; wear and tear in the brain and even reduce the risk &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/cheap-diabetes-drug-slashes-risk-of-long-covid-study-finds"&gt;of long COVID&lt;/a&gt;. However, scientists aren't yet sure that the drug extends lifespan, especially in humans – which is part of the reason for this study.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This research can't prove cause and effect like a randomized controlled trial (RCT) might be able to, because the participants weren't randomly assigned to one treatment or the other – rather, they were following professional advice. What's more, there wasn't a &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/what-is-a-placebo"&gt;placebo group&lt;/a&gt;, given no treatment. The overall sample size wasn't particularly large, either.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study also has its strengths – for example, the average follow-up period was 14 to 15 years, extending far beyond the length a standard RCT would be able to. That's important to understand how any intervention impacts lifespan.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/newsletter?utm_source=promo_health"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/health-newsletter-subscribe-promo-final-642x337.jpg" alt="Subscribe to ScienceAlert's free fact-checked newsletter" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-181305" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/health-newsletter-subscribe-promo-final-642x337.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/health-newsletter-subscribe-promo-final-768x403.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/health-newsletter-subscribe-promo-final-600x315.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/health-newsletter-subscribe-promo-final.jpg 850w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"A key advantage of our analysis was the long follow-up period after treatment initiation enabled by examination of a cohort with extensive follow-up from midlife to ages 90 and older, which is not feasible in typical randomized controlled trials," &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1093/gerona/glaf095"&gt;write&lt;/a&gt; the researchers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/these-five-simple-habits-are-key-to-slowing-aging-experts-reveal"&gt;These Five Simple Habits Are Key to Slowing Aging, Experts Reveal&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;RCTs could follow further down the line to dig deeper into these results, the researchers suggest. In the meantime, with the global population continuing to skew older, studies continue to find ways of &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/a-30-year-study-may-have-found-the-single-best-diet-for-healthy-aging"&gt;keeping us healthier&lt;/a&gt; for longer and &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/scientists-reveal-how-much-sleep-you-need-for-successful-aging"&gt;reducing damage to the body&lt;/a&gt; as we age.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The geroscience hypothesis posits that biological aging is malleable and that slowing biological aging may delay or prevent the onset of multiple age-related diseases and disability," &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1093/gerona/glaf095"&gt;write&lt;/a&gt; the researchers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"A key goal of geroscience is to identify novel therapeutic and preventive interventions that slow biological aging."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The research has been published in the &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1093/gerona/glaf095"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Journal of Gerontology: Medical Sciences&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;An earlier version of this article was published in June 2025.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 12:03:41 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimwFBVV95cUxNbXZqclJUczhJd182Q2N1RWYwVlc0RnoxejNTQlc5cmMtU2ZzZXA4R3JEWWhQVlRsbGJLb0w5Rmo0c0FGMTgxem1Vd1Y5VmZ2bzJKY3BJbUF0SUpDMEJ1bk9NdUhmU1VtWENWRG5TVUlGNk84R2hqWWNPanFPTkNCc2FDOGtPZHREOTlYV29xTnA0clZMVkZ0dmNWRQ</guid></item><item><title>女性高度评价手淫以管理更年期症状-技术网络</title><link>https://www.technologynetworks.com/tn/news/women-rate-masturbation-highly-for-managing-menopause-symptoms-407027</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="inner_content_body_text" id="inner_content_body_text" data-content-id="407027"&gt;
    &lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US"&gt;Many women use exercise, diet changes and supplements for menopause symptoms, but a new study suggests self-pleasure may belong in that toolkit too.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US"&gt;Researchers at the Kinsey Institute surveyed peri- and postmenopausal women and found that &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US"&gt;&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1097/GME.0000000000002675" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;span&gt;masturbation was among the highest-rated symptom-management methods&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US"&gt;. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;h2&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US"&gt;Self-pleasure matters in menopause care&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;




&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US"&gt;Surveys show that almost 90% of medical trainees &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0378512222001803" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;span&gt;feel unprepared to support patients through menopause&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US"&gt;, and many women say they receive little information from their healthcare providers. Although menopause has had a rise in media coverage, research and clinical training still lag behind.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;









&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US"&gt;“Menopause is important to research for many reasons, one of which is that most women going through perimenopause experience several symptoms that have been described by women as ‘highly disruptive and intolerable,’” said the authors of the latest study.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US"&gt;These symptoms range from sleep problems and mood changes to vaginal dryness and pain.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US"&gt;Hormone therapy can be effective, but its use has dropped, with only &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S0378512224000926" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;span&gt;~4% of women in the United States currently prescribed&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US"&gt; it. Concerns dating back to the early 2000s, along with side effects, continue to influence decisions. As a result, many women turn to lifestyle adjustments.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US"&gt;Research outside of menopause has shown that masturbation and orgasm can support sleep, improve mood, reduce pain and increase genital blood flow. One study found that regular masturbation was &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US"&gt;&lt;a href="https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jama/fullarticle/386220" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;span&gt;linked to lower levels of vaginal atrophy&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US"&gt; in postmenopausal women. Even so, no previous work has directly tested self-pleasure as a menopause symptom-relief tool, and medical conversations rarely include it.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US"&gt;“Conversations about menopause often focus on hormone therapy or lifestyle changes, but self-pleasure remains overlooked,” said co-author &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US"&gt;&lt;a href="https://genderstudies.indiana.edu/about/faculty/graham-cynthia.html" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Dr. Cynthia Graham&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US"&gt;, a distinguished professor in gender studies at Indiana University.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US"&gt;Graham and the team set out to learn how often women use masturbation to manage symptoms, how effective they believe it is compared with other approaches and how willing they might be to try it if a clinician suggested it. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;h2&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US"&gt;Masturbation and menopause symptoms&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;




&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US"&gt;The researchers ran an online survey designed to reflect the demographics of women aged 40–65 years across the US. Participants completed questions about menopause symptoms, self-pleasure, sexual history and other symptom-management strategies. Only women who were peri- or postmenopausal were included in the final analysis, resulting in a sample of 1,178 people.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US"&gt;The survey asked about 15 symptom-management strategies, including masturbation, and participants rated how helpful each approach was on a 5-point scale. They also reported which of 19 symptoms improved after masturbation. A set of questions explored doctor–patient conversations about menopause and sexual health.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US"&gt;The team found that masturbation is not widely used as a symptom-management tool. Around 13.5% of perimenopausal women and 9.7% of postmenopausal women said they used it for symptom relief; however, 19.5% of the overall sample had never masturbated.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US"&gt;Yet the women who did use it rated it highly.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US"&gt;Perimenopausal participants gave self-pleasure an average score of 4.35 out of 5, which was similar to partnered sex, sex toy use and hormone therapy, and higher than many lifestyle changes.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;







&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US"&gt;“Nearly one in five perimenopausal and postmenopausal women had noticed that self-pleasure provided symptom relief,” explained the authors.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US"&gt;When asked about specific symptoms, almost half of the perimenopausal women and one-third of postmenopausal women reported improvements in at least one symptom.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US"&gt;Perimenopausal women most often cited improvements in mood swings, falling asleep and irritability, and postmenopausal women pointed to sleep problems and mood shifts.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US"&gt;Smaller groups reported benefits for lubrication, pain, desire and headaches, and only 2.7% reported worsening symptoms, often linked to poor health or difficulty reaching orgasm.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US"&gt;Despite only 7% of perimenopausal and 4% of postmenopausal women having ever discussed masturbation with a clinician, many said they would try it if they knew it could help – and more than half would do so if a clinician recommended it.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;h2&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US"&gt;How self-pleasure could fit into future menopause treatment&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;




&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US"&gt;Self-pleasure is accessible, low-cost, and, based on the findings, may support mood and sleep in menopausal women.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US"&gt;“Our findings suggest masturbation may play a meaningful role in symptom management,” said Graham.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;





&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US"&gt;It could work alongside hormone therapy, lubricants, moisturizers or behavioral approaches, adding another option for women tailoring their own care.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US"&gt;Menopause still receives limited attention in medical training, and sexual well-being is often missing from appointments. This study highlights a need for clearer communication around self-pleasure. Bringing sexual health into routine menopause care may help clinicians offer a broader set of options.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US"&gt;However, all data were self-reported, and therefore, the links between self-pleasure and symptom changes cannot be considered causal. There were no physiological measures to track sleep quality, hormone changes or body temperature, and menopause status was based on participant reports, which can be inaccurate without clinical assessment.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US"&gt;Future work would benefit from controlled studies that test cause and effect, including trials that track sleep latency or hot flash frequency. Physiological monitoring would add clarity, as would long-term studies following women through the menopause transition. Research in different cultural settings is also needed.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US"&gt;“While managing menopause is something that necessitates a custom solution to each woman based on her unique health and needs, doctors and other health care providers should be cognizant of the valuable role that masturbation may play in symptom relief,” the authors concluded.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US"&gt;Reference: &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US"&gt;Lehmiller JJ, Graham CA, Ferrall L, Mendelson EA, Prine MS. The role of masturbation in relieving symptoms associated with menopause. &lt;i&gt;Menopause&lt;/i&gt;. 2025. doi: &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US"&gt;&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1097/GME.0000000000002675" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;span&gt;10.1097/GME.0000000000002675&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;p&gt;                                                                &lt;/p&gt;




&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US"&gt;This article is a rework of a &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US"&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.iu.edu/kinseyinstitute/live/news/47955-new-study-identifies-overlooked-tool-for-menopause" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span&gt;press release&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US"&gt; issued by the Kinsey Institute.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;span lang="EN-US"&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span&gt;Material has been edited for length and content. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;





                

&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Technology Networks</author><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 12:02:56 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMisgFBVV95cUxQOF81enNYQlNtYmpRV0N4cEFvOUpveE5tYWptcTNyM0dnV0hHbDZCNTk5RmFONThRYmp2U3QzbVJsUXh3WWhPaWk4eUlzaHhvVF9HQ05zODJUbEdyZTYtLURLa1lUelJnRkc2N3RoRFFYZXdtREMzaUU3Y1FZa0VTQ29BbVNHeXNnY09VaFo0WWltUGF1NklaUnNiNzFrVUhVRy1HbkJaOHh0TFJwOG1KbGlB</guid></item><item><title>吃土豆如何帮助保护您的心脏并降低疾病风险-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/food-news/how-eating-potatoes-may-help-protect-your-heart-and-lower-disease-risk/articleshow/125382984.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Potatoes rarely make it into conversations about healthy food, mostly because people picture chips, creamy mash or buttery roasted trays at Sunday lunch. Yet the potato itself, before it is drowned in oil or salt, is far more nutritious than many realise. Researchers have been taking a closer look at what this simple root actually offers, and the findings are surprisingly positive. A peer-reviewed study published in &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/38763265/" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;The Journal of Nutrition&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; followed thousands of adults over time and found that people who ate more potatoes had a slightly lower risk of cardiovascular disease and early death. It suggests that the humble potato, when cooked sensibly, might play a small but helpful role in long-term health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="7"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="8"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;The &lt;keyword id="24704376" type="General" weightage="20" keywordseo="health-benefits-of-potatoes" source="keywords"&gt;health benefits of potatoes&lt;/keyword&gt; for long-term heart protection&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="9"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most people associate heart-healthy foods with obvious choices like leafy greens, berries and oats. Potatoes rarely appear on that list, yet they contain nutrients that directly support cardiovascular function. They are naturally high in potassium, a mineral that helps regulate blood pressure by counteracting the effects of sodium. Their fibre content also contributes to smoother digestion and better cholesterol control.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; Researchers who examined dietary data noticed that people who regularly ate potatoes in cooked, non-fried forms often had slightly healthier heart profiles. This does not make potatoes a miracle cure, but it shows that they can fit comfortably into a heart-healthy diet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="13"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="lOvcW vdo_embedd"&gt;&lt;div class="k7lcu"&gt;&lt;p class="efT4r"&gt;What Your Cholesterol Report Is Hiding — The Truth That Could Save Your Heart | Dr Vinayak Agarwal&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="15"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="16"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;How the health benefits of potatoes come from their nutrient-rich profile&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="17"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Potatoes contain &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/topic/vitamin-c" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;vitamin C&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, vitamin B6, magnesium, antioxidants and resistant starch. Each of these plays a different part in keeping the body functioning smoothly. Vitamin C helps protect cells from oxidative stress. B6 contributes to nervous system health and supports metabolism. Resistant starch, which forms when potatoes cool down after cooking, behaves like a prebiotic. It feeds beneficial gut bacteria and improves overall gut balance, which researchers increasingly connect to immune strength, reduced inflammation and chronic disease prevention. When you stop viewing potatoes as empty carbs and start seeing their full nutritional picture, they become far more interesting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="25"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="26"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What research says about the health benefits of potatoes for cancer prevention&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="27"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="29"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some early studies suggest that potato compounds, particularly antioxidants like chlorogenic acid and certain plant chemicals found in coloured potato varieties, may help reduce cellular damage linked with cancer. However, most of these findings come from laboratory research rather than large human studies. Scientists are cautious about drawing strong conclusions, but they agree that including antioxidant-rich foods in the diet supports long-term cell protection. Potatoes can contribute to that mix, especially when eaten alongside vegetables, legumes and whole grains. The important message is balance. Potatoes can play a supportive role, but they should not be seen as a standalone defence against disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="33"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="34"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Why preparation affects the health benefits of potatoes more than people realise&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="35"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many of the negative assumptions about potatoes come from how they are prepared rather than the potato itself. Frying them in oil, covering them in cheese or pairing them with heavy, salty toppings alters their nutritional value dramatically. Steaming, baking, boiling or roasting with minimal oil keeps their natural nutrients intact. Leaving the skin on boosts fibre and mineral content. Even something as simple as letting cooked potatoes cool before eating increases resistant starch levels. The cooking method determines whether potatoes support health or work against it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="40"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="41"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;How the health benefits of potatoes support blood sugar balance and weight control&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="42"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="44"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;People often worry that potatoes raise blood sugar too quickly, but the body’s response depends heavily on how they are cooked, the portion size and what they are eaten with. When paired with protein, vegetables or healthy fats, the rise in blood sugar is steadier and more controlled. Fibre and resistant starch slow digestion and improve fullness, which can support healthier eating patterns and weight balance. These effects contribute indirectly to better heart and metabolic health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="48"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="49"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Simple ways to maximise the health benefits of potatoes in everyday meals&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="50"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Small changes can make potatoes a healthier part of daily meals. Choose baked, roasted or boiled potatoes instead of fried ones. Enjoy them with herbs, olive oil, lemon or yoghurt instead of heavy cream or butter. Pair them with vegetables and lean proteins for balanced meals. Cold potato salads made with light dressings provide extra resistant starch. Eating the skin, when washed properly, ensures you get more fibre, potassium and antioxidants.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="54"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Potatoes will never replace leafy greens or pulses, but they do not need to. Their strength lies in being accessible, versatile and surprisingly nutrient-dense. Current research shows encouraging links between potato consumption and heart health, and early evidence suggests there may also be benefits for cancer prevention. Prepared sensibly, potatoes can be a valuable part of a balanced diet. The next time you add potatoes to your plate, remember they are far more than just a side dish. They can actively support your long-term wellbeing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="59"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Disclaimer: This article is for general informational purposes only and is not a substitute for professional medical advice, diagnosis, or treatment. Always seek the guidance of a qualified healthcare provider regarding any medical condition or lifestyle change.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="61"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Also read| &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/food-news/top-4-foods-women-should-eat-for-hormonal-balance-energy-and-overall-wellness/articleshow/125353420.cms" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;Top 4 foods women should eat for hormonal balance, energy and overall wellness&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="64"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:29:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi6AFBVV95cUxQSkt5TW5OUUV4MXEyUEloaEd2dS04Rmp6OTBJTkhReWN0TGRSSjFfU3I5SVVMN1JQM3VPcFZ0OGFLcDBTbzZmNlBIUDBuRjdwejBxZE9pRG9tX3FzaUg3M1BmeFN5aEpobFFsTXZIWllpQVNab3lnMC1SNVRsM1RuVkV5Slp0RWNGNE5qTkdFeHN6c0pqUG55SVZSNThtRGpuN2w0OGtzMmdCQzJsd3hXY1MxRmpSRWpNOThRSDhQM05LZVhidWZ4cjljeDFpMUlvWjRzRTRMMUYyX3RBZ3F1Y09DZXVMbmhK</guid></item><item><title>缅因州专家警告说，今年的流感季节可能会更糟-波特兰新闻先驱报</title><link>https://www.pressherald.com/2025/11/17/flu-season-could-be-severe-in-maine-and-around-the-u-s/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content"&gt;

		
		&lt;p&gt;A strain of the influenza virus that’s not a precise match for the vaccine has been spreading in the U.K., Canada and Japan, among other countries, and could sicken many in the U.S. this flu season.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“The flu is on our doorstep, and &lt;a href="https://www.pressherald.com/2025/02/19/weekly-influenza-cases-nearly-double-in-maine-in-last-three-weeks/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;soon it will be knocking on our door,&lt;/a&gt;” said Dr. Dora Anne Mills, chief health improvement officer for MaineHealth. “It may be a more severe season than normal.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Mills said H3N2 tends to be a more potent strain, especially in older adults, which can result in more hospitalizations and illness in long-term care facilities. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Maine reported 17,793 flu cases during the 2024-25 flu season, which runs from October through May, according to the Maine Center for Disease Control and Prevention. So far this year, Maine has recorded 90 cases of influenza.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Scientists each February predict what the predominant circulating strains will be for the following influenza season. Because it takes time to manufacture and distribute the vaccines, sometimes the predictions are not exact.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“Every once in a while we see a shift in the virus that makes the vaccine not a great match,” said Anna Krueger, a Maine CDC epidemiologist. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;But the message from public health officials hasn’t varied: Get your flu shot, if you haven’t already.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The dominant circulating strain in the Northern Hemisphere is Influenza A H3N2, according to the World Health Organization. Small variations in the H3N2 strain – called subclades – took scientists by surprise when they &lt;a href="https://www.pressherald.com/2025/01/08/flu-surging-in-maine-covid-19-prevalence-also-very-high/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;emerged at the end of the flu season&lt;/a&gt; in the Southern Hemisphere.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;But that doesn’t mean the flu vaccine doesn’t work at all. It will still offer protection, especially from severe illness, experts say.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Also, Krueger said, other strains of the flu virus, such as Influenza A, H1N1 or Influenza B, may become the predominant strain at any time during flu season.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt; “It’s too early to tell if any one strain will dominate,” Krueger said. “There’s no typical flu season, but many times we will see Influenza A in the early season, and Influenza B later.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Flu cases caused by H3N2 have tripled in the U.K., according to news reports.&lt;/p&gt;


	
	


&lt;p&gt;“Since it’s emerged, (H3N2) is rapidly spreading and predominating in some countries so far in the northern hemisphere,” Dr. Wenqing Zhang, head of the World Health Organization’s Global Respiratory Threats Unit, said Wednesday during a media briefing.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Krueger said people can get the flu shot and the updated &lt;a href="https://www.pressherald.com/2025/09/25/fall-covid-19-shots-available-in-maine-for-adults/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;COVID-19 vaccine&lt;/a&gt; during the same appointment. Both vaccines are widely available at doctor’s offices and pharmacies.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;In addition to getting vaccinated, to avoid flu, “stay home when sick and practice good hand hygiene.” &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Vaccinations are available to protect against RSV, another seasonal respiratory illness. RSV vaccines are available for those 50 and older, and those who are between 32 to 36 weeks pregnant.&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;

	

	
			&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Portland Press Herald</author><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 09:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimgFBVV95cUxQcDFrZnhhVk5YdjdYRV8zLXRONFRLMEJvS3FIQVNsVFJVaGp3NjY0X0NaWXM1bE42YUJBbTJ6Z2xIV09rWFJ4cllqLVVTRmd0ekpWcVE0M1NaYjRUQVdad25PSW1VUF8xelVRbm4zZmY3eXZnZVBvQjE1ZEZsNFZOOVdmRnBIcjBKbWNVT3JYMUpSczJsSlc5TFN3</guid></item><item><title>想要防止大脑衰老吗？尝试认知锻炼：短波- NPR</title><link>https://www.npr.org/2025/11/17/nx-s1-5600899/health-brain-training-workout-science</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="storytext" class="storytext storylocation linkLocation"&gt;
      &lt;div id="resnx-s1-img-5808100" class="bucketwrap image large"&gt;
            
&lt;div class="credit-caption"&gt;
    &lt;div class="caption-wrap"&gt;
        &lt;div class="caption" aria-label="Image caption"&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;
                Cognitive function tends to get worse as we age. But both mental and physical exercise can help fight that decline.
                &lt;b class="credit" aria-label="Image credit"&gt;
                    
                    Flavio Coelho/Getty Images
                    
                &lt;/b&gt;
                &lt;b class="hide-caption"&gt;&lt;b&gt;hide caption&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;
            &lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;


            &lt;b class="toggle-caption"&gt;&lt;b&gt;toggle caption&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;

    &lt;span class="credit" aria-label="Image credit"&gt;
        
        Flavio Coelho/Getty Images
        
    &lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;Scientists have found the first compelling evidence that cognitive training can boost levels of a brain chemical that typically declines as people age. The results of this 10-week study back earlier animal research showing that environments that stimulate the brain can increase levels of certain neurotransmitters. And other studies of people have suggested that cognitive training can improve thinking and memory. So how does it all work? And by &lt;em&gt;how much&lt;/em&gt; does it all work? Here to break everything down and help you understand how to keep your brain sharp is NPR science correspondent &lt;a href="https://www.npr.org/people/2100615/jon-hamilton" target="_blank"&gt;Jon Hamilton&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;   
   &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Interested in more brain science? Email us your question at &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="mailto:shortwave@npr.org" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;em&gt;shortwave@npr.org&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Listen to every episode of Short Wave sponsor-free and support our work at NPR by signing up for Short Wave+ at &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="http://plus.npr.org/shortwave" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;em&gt;plus.npr.org/shortwave&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Listen to Short Wave on &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="https://n.pr/3HOQKeK" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Spotify&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt; and &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="https://n.pr/3WA9vqh" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This episode was produced by Hannah Chinn. It was edited by Rebecca Ramirez. Tyler Jones checked the facts. The audio engineer was Jimmy Keeley.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>NPR</author><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiigFBVV95cUxQNDlxNnF3TjVxNG1zV0ZWeWxsMGUtVGlQWkRyZFp6UW9xV3NpTEQtYUwzM3BiZ3dlV0h1bUpEM0s3RnZYSXJLM19hSlNUM0VoUThfR1ZtNUNyLXdudlFhUGxpZWlLcy02S3FESGZzS0dQY0M2c2NDeERuX2Z3bW10VjNYeFdXV2dyNVE</guid></item><item><title>在北林肯郡和古尔医院发现骨折的人工智能-英国广播公司</title><link>https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/ce9de78gdleo</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Artificial Intelligence (AI) will be used in hospitals to find fractures and dislocations and provide quicker treatment as part of a new trial.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Emergency departments at the Northern Lincolnshire and Goole NHS Foundation Trust will take part in a two-year NHS England pilot scheme starting later this month.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Abdul Khan, a consultant in emergency medicine, said: "Making use of AI technology to assist in identifying potential issues has been shown to help to meet demand across northern Europe and we are excited to see if it has a similar impact here."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The trust said the AI software would be used as an additional tool to assist clinicians with their diagnosis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The trust, which runs hospitals in Scunthorpe, Grimsby and Goole, said the technology would not be used on patients under the age of two, for inpatient and outpatient clinics, or for chest, spine, skull, facial or soft tissue imaging.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Jake Bates, an advanced practitioner reporting radiographer, added: "The way it works is that alongside the standard image, the patient record will also contain a near-instant AI annotated version which will highlight any potential issues which the clinician may want to examine further.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"Every x-ray will still be examined by our clinicians, and they will make the final decision about the diagnosis and the correct course of treatment for that patient."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;&lt;i id="listen-to-highlights-from" class="sc-d16436d-0 iVdNuz"&gt;Listen to highlights from&lt;/i&gt; &lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/p0cjdw6n" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;Lincolnshire on BBC Sounds&lt;/a&gt;&lt;i id=",-watch-the" class="sc-d16436d-0 iVdNuz"&gt;, watch the&lt;/i&gt; &lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b007tp3n" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;latest episode of Look North&lt;/a&gt; &lt;i id="or-tell-us-about-a-story-you-think-we-should-be-covering" class="sc-d16436d-0 iVdNuz"&gt;or tell us about a story you think we should be covering &lt;/i&gt;&lt;a target="_self" href="mailto:eastyorkslincs.news@bbc.co.uk" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BBC</author><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 06:15:39 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiWkFVX3lxTE9JMVI0ZUMzY2FIUVpwTkRWTjFVYXphaWNYVjFaOFFUNFRGa2VwX0FpcG1OT3pOdEFZVVJVeUROYlUtRmZqZnlWcFpBS2VUV2hwcTB0LTRFWXctd9IBX0FVX3lxTE9WY3hqaDd2YkxwZi1BMXl2M2FnUVBySVNwbENzREw2a0lPSkk5bXhSVVUxNERpMUtOdEtZNkw3SFppdXZKdWhQSU1QYXFuX0JmVS1JSjhPM24yb1l6c0M0</guid></item><item><title>医生透露睡前最糟糕的5件事，其中之一是水-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/doctor-reveals-5-worst-things-to-consume-before-bed-and-one-is-water/articleshow/125376258.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;div class="MwN2O"&gt;&lt;div class="vdo_embedd"&gt; &lt;div class="T22zO"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you plan to sleep like a baby, it is crucial to consider what you consume before hitting the pillow. Yes, that’s right. Getting a good night’s sleep is about more than just a comfortable mattress and the right temperature. Everything that leads up to the last few hours before bed really matters, especially what you consume. In a video shared on Instagram, Dr Manan Vora, a leading orthopaedic surgeon and sports doctor, talks about some foods and beverages that one should avoid before going to bed. What are they? Let’s take a look.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="3"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Desserts&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="5"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="7"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Saving some room for dessert during dinner is not a good idea. That post-dinner ice cream or chocolate treat may give you a momentary dopamine hit, but it will be followed by dark circles and brain fog the next day. Though eating desserts, especially ice cream after dinner, is quite normalised, it is not good for sleep. “As tempting as it may be, the sugar and fat content in ice cream can delay digestion and disturb your sleep cycle,” Dr Vora said. The high sugar content will cause blood sugar spikes, and the fat content will significantly slow down digestion. It’s a recipe for disaster.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="13"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Caffeinated drinks&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="15"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="17"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sipping some coffee or tea in the evening may feel relaxing, but it is going to kill your sleep. “Caffeinated drinks like tea and coffee contain caffeine, a stimulant that can keep you awake by increasing brain activity and interfering with your ability to fall asleep,” the doctor said. The caffeine will interfere with your plan to wind down. A recent study by the University of Texas found that nighttime caffeine consumption can &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cell.com/iscience/fulltext/S2589-0042(25)01458-0" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="_blank" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;increase impulsive behaviour&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, potentially leading to reckless actions. This could absolutely explain your urge to buy all the items in your online shopping cart. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For those who struggle with sleep, it is best to avoid caffeine at least four to six hours before bedtime.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="23"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Fried food&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="25"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="27"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Deep-fried food, in general, is not your health’s ally. If at all you are giving in to your cravings, try to avoid eating fried food in the hours leading up to your bedtime. Why? “Fried foods are high in fat and can be difficult to digest, leading to discomfort and potentially disrupting your sleep. Additionally, fried foods may cause heartburn or indigestion, making it challenging to sleep peacefully,” Dr Vora said. So, it may be better to save your broasted chicken or crispy fried dreams for the next day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="31"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Excessive water&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="33"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="35"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;This may come as a surprise, but sometimes even water may work against your sweet dreams. Wait, what? You aren’t supposed to drink water at night? Well, you can consume water, but not in excess. “Surprisingly, consuming large amounts of water before bed can disrupt sleep with multiple trips to the toilet. Try limiting your fluid intake a few hours before bedtime,” the doctor said. Drinking too much &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sleepfoundation.org/nutrition/drinking-water-before-bed" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="_blank" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;water before bed contributes to nocturia&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, a condition of waking up several times a night to urinate, according to the Sleep Foundation. This will be especially prominent for people with certain conditions, such as kidney disease or diabetes, or those who are taking diuretic medicines.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="41"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Alcohol&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="43"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many people believe a nightcap helps them sleep better. But guess what? It’s a misconception. Alcohol does not benefit your body in any way, let alone provide you with restful sleep. “Alcoholic beverages act as diuretics, increasing urine production and leading to frequent trips to the bathroom throughout the night, which can disrupt your sleep,” Dr Vora said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="46"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;So the next time you are planning your dinner, keep these in mind. Because sometimes even the things we assume harmless, in this case, excessive water can really keep you awake all night. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="48"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="49"&gt;&lt;i&gt;Note: The information provided in this article is for educational purposes only and is not intended as medical advice. Always consult a qualified healthcare professional before starting any new medication or treatment, or before changing your diet or supplement regimen.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="50"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="51"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Times of India</author><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 04:51:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi_AFBVV95cUxQODQ2WHhzcnpIaThhWW1ZeElZTDBsUTM2TVRwemZQZzZtdlVaQXRhT04tQVJYLTQ4YUJyTVE2YTVULTdUa2xBd1JTeHhCeWstU0QySHRpRUVjSEV2QzhlTG9sTVFDVzZwbXVWaFNHeXd0R0VpTHBoX2FrZTljM0ZqZ1BiS0xpLVVGY2ZSTEhsakd6dm5WdU04LUloTURmMXFOLVVTbWVXUGd1Rm1Way02ZUdoeGc4Um5hbmtiZjVGaGxHYUdmUzBZMnlfQkY0dUVSMHpjRFhoZXlwT29HbEtKSXZkTFVsMUlqckUxQnl5Zll4bkhwV0FveXI2bkXSAYICQVVfeXFMUHlxT0xrZU9tVzRQb0lySnRoTVBoRzg0Z1JyUU5DNjBXMTRlbzFhUWEtV1NoWjJLdmpWVmpKVldyb1VWN0FfUkFEcnZTRGROampjbnpnYnJzbjZnbk1xa3p3Q3ZNTmF0RlU1SHdvdXJtZFpFeDhxT090TzZ2ZzU5RmlQZ085Uy14aGpPM3hZc25SSDU0NzlYUU9LRG14TWVHMUlaQmx6N0o3bElmZTlaeGRQaFk1X200X0lfT2UzX0NXWUVlMXowOFRxSlRpY01aZXJTVG9PcFMtZ0s4dFpBbllFUzAtX1NxVnBJclhXSGp0VFJtb3ZtRFFmZUFUQXlfNm9R</guid></item><item><title>古印度健康实践真的可以帮助对抗感冒和过敏- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/ancient-indian-health-practice-really-can-help-fight-colds-and-allergies</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;It starts with a slight scratchiness at the back of your throat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Then, a sneeze.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Then coughing, sniffling, and full-on congestion, with or without  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/fever" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73066" data-postid="181652" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;fever&lt;/a&gt;, for a few insufferable days.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Viral upper respiratory tract infections – also known as the &lt;a href="https://my.clevelandclinic.org/health/diseases/12342-common-cold"&gt;common cold&lt;/a&gt; – afflict everyone, &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/4357298/"&gt;typically three times per year&lt;/a&gt;, lasting, on average, nine days.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/rinsing-your-nasal-passages-with-the-wrong-kind-of-water-could-be-deadly"&gt;Rinsing Your Nasal Passages With The Wrong Kind of Water Could Be Deadly&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Colds don't respond to antibiotics, and most &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.2500/aap.2018.39.4117"&gt;over-the-counter medications deliver modest results&lt;/a&gt; at best.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In recent years, research has emerged demonstrating the effectiveness of the ancient practice of &lt;a href="https://www.fammed.wisc.edu/nasal-irrigation/"&gt;nasal saline irrigation&lt;/a&gt; in &lt;a href="https://dx.doi.org/10.1016/j.ijporl.2011.12.022"&gt;fighting the common cold&lt;/a&gt; in both adults and children.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Not only does nasal saline irrigation &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/S2213-2600(24)00140-1"&gt;decrease the duration of illness&lt;/a&gt;, it also reduces viral transmission to other people, &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1007/s00405-024-08518-y"&gt;minimizes the need for antibiotics&lt;/a&gt;, and could even &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.7189/jogh.14.05044"&gt;lower a patient's risk of hospitalization&lt;/a&gt;. Better yet, it costs pennies and doesn't require a prescription.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I'm both an &lt;a href="https://scholar.google.com/citations?user=K5st0T8AAAAJ&amp;amp;hl=en"&gt;adjunct assistant professor of medicine&lt;/a&gt; and a practicing physician. As a family doctor, I see the common cold every day. My patients are usually skeptical when I first recommend nasal saline irrigation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, they frequently return to tell me that this practice has changed their life. Not only does it help with upper respiratory  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/virus" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73053" data-postid="181652" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;viruses&lt;/a&gt;, but it also &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.2500/ajra.2012.26.3787"&gt;helps manage allergies&lt;/a&gt;, chronic congestion, postnasal drip, and &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.21053/ceo.2021.00654"&gt;recurrent sinus infections&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What is nasal saline irrigation?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nasal saline irrigation is a process by which the nasal cavity is bathed in a saltwater solution. In some studies, this is accomplished using a &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/S2213-2600(24)00140-1"&gt;pump-action spray bottle&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In others, &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.7189/jogh.14.05044"&gt;participants used&lt;/a&gt; a traditional &lt;a href="https://www.mayoclinic.org/healthy-lifestyle/consumer-health/multimedia/neti-pot/img-20008137"&gt;neti pot&lt;/a&gt;, which is a vessel resembling a teapot.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_181747" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-181747" class="wp-caption aligncenter"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/covid_virus_neti_pot_642.jpg" alt="neti pot" class="size-full wp-image-181747" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/covid_virus_neti_pot_642.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/covid_virus_neti_pot_642-600x327.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-181747" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Ceramic neti pot. (Betka82/Getty Images)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;The neti pot can be &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1017/S002221512100030X"&gt;traced back to the 15th century&lt;/a&gt;. It garnered mainstream interest in the US in 2012 after Dr. Oz &lt;a href="https://www.oprah.com/health/your-questions-answered/5"&gt;demonstrated it on the "Oprah Winfrey Show&lt;/a&gt;."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But it's not the only device that has historically been employed for such purposes. Ancient Greek and Roman physicians &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1017/S002221512100030X"&gt;had their own nasal lavage devices&lt;/a&gt;. Such practices were even &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/S0140-6736(01)83808-3"&gt;discussed in medical journals&lt;/a&gt; such as &lt;em&gt;The Lancet&lt;/em&gt; over a century ago, in 1902.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;How does nasal saline irrigation work?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nasal saline has a few key benefits. First, it physically flushes debris out of the nasal passage. This not only includes mucus and crust, but also the  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/virus" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73053" data-postid="181652" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;virus&lt;/a&gt; itself, along with allergens and other environmental contaminants.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Second, salt water is slightly lower on the &lt;a href="https://www.usgs.gov/media/images/ph-scale-0"&gt;pH scale&lt;/a&gt; compared with fresh water. Its acidity creates an environment that is &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC2640010/"&gt;inhospitable for viruses&lt;/a&gt; and makes it harder for them to replicate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/newsletter?utm_source=promo_health"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/health-newsletter-subscribe-promo-final-642x337.jpg" alt="Subscribe to ScienceAlert's free fact-checked newsletter" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Third, nasal saline helps restore the actions of part of &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.2500/ajra.2012.26.3787"&gt;our natural defense system&lt;/a&gt;, which is composed of microscopic, hairlike projections called &lt;a href="https://www.britannica.com/science/cilium"&gt;cilia&lt;/a&gt; that line the surface of the nasal passage. These cilia beat in a coordinated fashion to act like an escalator, propelling viruses and other foreign particles out of the body. Nasal saline irrigation helps keep this system running effectively.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What the research shows&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;A study of more than 11,000 people published in &lt;em&gt;The Lancet&lt;/em&gt; in 2024 demonstrated that nasal saline irrigation, initiated at the first sign of symptoms and performed up to six times per day, &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/S2213-2600(24)00140-1"&gt;reduced the duration of symptomatic illness&lt;/a&gt; by approximately two days.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Meanwhile, smaller studies have reported that the reduced duration of illness could be &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1007/s00405-024-08518-y"&gt;as high as four days&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Research has also demonstrated that nasal saline irrigation can help prevent the spread of illness. A study in hospitalized patients showed that after detection of  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/coronavirus" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73041" data-postid="181652" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;COVID-19&lt;/a&gt; via nasal swab, nasal saline irrigation performed every four hours over a 16-hour period &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1007/s00405-024-08518-y"&gt;decreased COVID-19 viral load by 8.9%&lt;/a&gt;. Meanwhile, the viral load in the control group continued to increase during that time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_181710" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-181710" class="wp-caption aligncenter"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/covid_virus_nasal_irrigation_642.jpg" alt="covid virus" class="size-full wp-image-181710" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/covid_virus_nasal_irrigation_642.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/covid_virus_nasal_irrigation_642-600x327.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-181710" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Nasal saline irrigation can decrease COVID-19 viral load. (&lt;a href="https://www.canva.com/photos/MAD6DPSwa6k/"&gt;mapo/Getty Images/Canva&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;The benefits of nasal saline also extend beyond acute infectious illnesses. When performed regularly by patients with &lt;a href="https://my.clevelandclinic.org/health/diseases/8622-allergic-rhinitis-hay-fever"&gt;allergic rhinitis&lt;/a&gt;, also known as hay fever, a  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/meta-analysis" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73088" data-postid="181652" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;meta-analysis&lt;/a&gt; of 10 randomized controlled trials showed that nasal saline irrigation can enable a &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.2500/ajra.2012.26.3787"&gt;62% reduction in the use of allergy medications&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It's also effective for chronic congestion, postnasal drip, and &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.21053/ceo.2021.00654"&gt;recurrent sinus infections&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Why it matters&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Besides helping patients feel better faster, one of the most valuable benefits of nasal saline irrigation is that its use can help &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/S2213-2600(24)00140-1"&gt;decrease unnecessary antibiotic prescriptions&lt;/a&gt;, which are a &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1093/cid/cis509"&gt;major contributor to antibiotic resistance&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It is well established that antibiotics &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1007/s11606-024-08758-y"&gt;do not shorten the duration or reduce the severity&lt;/a&gt; of respiratory tract infections. Despite this, studies have shown that patients are happier when they leave their doctor's office &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1111/j.1553-2712.2009.00522.x"&gt;with an antibiotic prescription in hand&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This may be why &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1542/peds.2011-1337"&gt;10 million inappropriate antibiotic prescriptions&lt;/a&gt; are given each year for viral respiratory tract infections. In one study of more than 49,000 patient encounters for respiratory infections, &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1093/ofid/ofac302"&gt;antibiotics were unnecessarily prescribed&lt;/a&gt; to 42.4% of patients.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One reason patients with upper respiratory viral infections tend to initially feel better with antibiotics is because of their &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC2801304/"&gt;off-target, anti-inflammatory properties&lt;/a&gt;. However, this benefit &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1002/prp2.925"&gt;can be better achieved with anti-inflammatory medications&lt;/a&gt; such as ibuprofen or naproxen, which can be taken in conjunction with nasal saline irrigation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Overall, nasal saline irrigation is a cheap, effective, evidence-based alternative that will not only shorten the duration of illness but also prevent its spread, minimize the need for unnecessary antibiotics, and keep people out of the hospital.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;How to do it&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;For those who want to try it, you don't need anything fancy. Even a neti pot is not necessary. Many pharmacies sell salt water in a container with a nozzle and even spray bottles that can be refilled with a homemade saltwater solution.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You'll mix approximately half a teaspoon of non-iodized salt with 1 cup of water. It's important for your safety that the water be either distilled water or boiled for at least five minutes and then cooled to destroy any harmful bacteria. You can also add a pinch of baking soda to reduce any potential sting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Note that saltier solutions are &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.7189/jogh.14.05044"&gt;not more effective&lt;/a&gt;. However, some studies have suggested that natural seawater, due to its additional minerals such as magnesium, potassium, and calcium, could &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.anorl.2015.08.001"&gt;offer even greater benefits&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Saltwater solutions can also be purchased commercially, which might be worth a try for those with an insufficient response to saline alone.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You can use nasal saline irrigation after any potential exposure to an infectious illness. For best results, you'll want to start irrigating the nasal passage at the first sign of an infection.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You can repeat rinses throughout the day as often as needed for the duration of the illness. At a minimum, you'll want to irrigate the nasal passages every morning and evening.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You can also consider gargling salt water as an adjunctive therapy.&lt;img loading="lazy" decoding="async" src="https://counter.theconversation.com/content/266659/count.gif?distributor=republish-lightbox-basic" alt="The Conversation" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade"&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/profiles/mary-j-scourboutakos-1518645"&gt;Mary J. Scourboutakos&lt;/a&gt;, Adjunct Assistant Professor in Family and Community Medicine, &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/institutions/macon-and-joan-brock-virginia-health-sciences-at-old-dominion-university-6646"&gt;Macon &amp;amp; Joan Brock Virginia Health Sciences at Old Dominion University&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This article is republished from &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com"&gt;The Conversation&lt;/a&gt; under a Creative Commons license. Read the &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/recent-studies-prove-the-ancient-practice-of-nasal-irrigation-is-effective-at-fighting-the-common-cold-266659"&gt;original article&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 03:44:55 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiowFBVV95cUxOQS1mbEtaVlFkTC1iRFpLSHdOSEVvTVBuVU8xNzNSWUxZNEx5cTNrc2tRa3o2QXozOHlGSVJOc19XNXVBR0lTUVFpMmwzbzJxNVZDX2p6NmU4b2VGTXpTWk5ETzBMR254dkFCLUhjZW90dFdIT3RPZ0FYLUFNNGROM2FIVEtrWkZSeUlLNUFwcFdVUUpDZ000RWN3TkVpdWdsMi1V</guid></item><item><title>随着时间的推移，可能会损害肾脏的3个常见（和危险）错误-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/3-common-and-dangerous-mistakes-that-over-time-can-damage-the-kidneys/articleshow/125366246.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kidney health is often overlooked until serious damage has already set in. Some common, everyday habits gradually cause silent damage to your kidneys and increase your chances of developing chronic kidney disease. Nephrologist Dr. Arjun Sabharwal points out three daily mistakes people make that can lead to a gradual decrease in kidney function and affect their overall health:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="3"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="4"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Taking painkillers every day&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="6"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many people turn to over-the-counter painkillers to manage chronic aches and pains. Dr. Sabharwal says frequent use of nonsteroidal anti-inflammatory drugs, also referred to as NSAIDs, can decrease blood flow to the kidneys and cause long-term damage. So this kind of injury, analgesic nephropathy, develops silently. Most people do not notice symptoms until the damage has reached an advanced stage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="11"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="lOvcW vdo_embedd"&gt;&lt;div class="k7lcu"&gt;&lt;p class="efT4r"&gt;Don’t Ignore Silent Kidney Damage: How to Detect Issues Before It’s Too Late | Dr Sanjeev Bagai&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="13"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pain relievers are usually safe if taken infrequently; however, overusing them without medical supervision is dangerous. Other treatment options include physical therapy or stretching exercises, or medications that have a lesser effect on the kidneys. People who may use painkillers often must be tested for kidney function frequently in order to catch early signs of stress or damage to the organs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="16"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="17"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Use of unregulated herbal supplements&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="18"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="20"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many people assume herbal remedies are safe, but Dr. Sabharwal says that some supplements contain heavy metals, such as lead, mercury, or arsenic. The kidneys can, over time, accumulate these toxins and suffer serious damage. In fact, studies reported in PubMed indicate that contaminated herbal products have been associated with acute and chronic kidney disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="22"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;For renal protective purposes, herbal supplements should be selected from some proper and well-regulated sources. One can indicate all types of supplements to a healthcare provider. Avoid untested or unlicensed products and are wary of claims promising quick or miraculous results. Even natural products can have unintended consequences if they contain toxic substances.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="26"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="27"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Ignoring high blood sugar&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="28"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="30"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chronic high blood sugar is a leading cause of kidney diseases. Continuous stress to the filtering units in the kidneys by elevated HbA1c levels can cause impairment in their blood and fluid balancing act. According to Dr. Sabharwal, prolonged, uncontrolled blood sugar greatly increases the risk for diabetic kidney disease. This risk is compounded by frequent use of painkillers or exposure to contaminated supplements.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="34"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Good blood sugar control is important for protecting the kidneys from damage. A healthy diet, regular physical activity, and following medications can help to keep blood sugar levels in control. Regular urine and blood tests are very important for early detection of kidney damage before symptoms appear.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="38"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;How to protect your kidneys&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="40"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kidney damage often occurs silently, with symptoms such as fatigue, swelling, bone pain, or changes in urination not appearing until significant damage is done. According to Dr. Sabharwal, it is advisable to protect kidney function proactively.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="42"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="43"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Key strategies include:&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="44"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Limiting the long-term use of painkillers and finding safer alternatives&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="46"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Avoiding unregulated herbal supplements that may carry heavy metals&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="48"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Management and control of blood sugar levels through lifestyle modifications and medication&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="50"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Early detection of developing renal impairment through regular monitoring of renal function. Being conscious of these habits would make it possible to minimize the danger of kidney disease and assist in long-term health. Awareness and small adjustments daily can bring long-lasting results, ensuring your kidneys continue their performance effectively.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="52"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="53"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 01:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi7gFBVV95cUxPbTRmcmxXQ1VYZk1xc3ZJcDdBek94MUs4SmJxZ0l0Q1BaVFFHekUtOWNTQmp1ZDF6dDBabmRZNURvaFFPVkVBblo2VjBlNm1fYzdJa09fVUtteS1BZTBheGdfcUdWV0dpWGs2MWx0Si1KY0lTWXZXNGU3OUVIRzhRTmZVZ01aUEFRTzhLQzhoSzBfN2RzODVuRWdWSXFDcWdwNE91eU9Ja0VzdVFJdnBFVWtsUjlXb0hVZjhaWXhONTVONGxXRGIyX3pGU2o4aGtZb0xKU2hRemxpdkJXVks0RkVPVGROWThVbWE1UFd3</guid></item><item><title>在长期COVID患者的血液中发现隐藏着奇怪的结构- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/strange-structures-found-lurking-in-the-blood-of-people-with-long-covid</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;A hidden physical change in the body may be helping to drive the &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/revealed-women-face-much-higher-risk-of-long-covid-but-why"&gt;prolonged malaise&lt;/a&gt; some people experience after contracting  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/coronavirus" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73041" data-postid="181528" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;COVID-19&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Analyzing blood samples from patients with &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/life-with-long-covid-comparable-to-parkinsons-and-stroke"&gt;long COVID&lt;/a&gt;, a team of medical researchers has identified unusual microscopic structures that may contribute to symptoms such as &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/covids-hidden-toll-full-body-scans-reveal-long-term-immune-effects"&gt;brain fog and fatigue&lt;/a&gt;. If this is the case, it offers a hopeful target for future treatment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"This study shows a robust association between biomarkers indicative of thromboinflammatory activity and long COVID," &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1002/jmv.70613"&gt;the team writes in a paper&lt;/a&gt; led by geneticist Alain Thierry of Montpellier University in France.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The discovery of these biomarker linkages not only presents a possible novel diagnostic methodology but also novel therapeutic targets, offering prospects for future markedly improved clinical management."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Related: &lt;/b&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/we-just-got-more-evidence-that-long-covid-is-a-brain-injury"&gt;&lt;b&gt;We Just Got More Evidence That Long COVID Is a Brain Injury&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The reason why some people experience symptoms for months to years after a  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/coronavirus" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73041" data-postid="181528" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;SARS-CoV-2&lt;/a&gt; infection is still &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/the-true-extent-of-long-covid-is-still-emerging-but-heres-what-we-know"&gt;something of a medical mystery&lt;/a&gt;, but &lt;a href="https://www.science.org/content/article/what-causes-long-covid-three-leading-theories"&gt;multiple mechanisms&lt;/a&gt; may be at play.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One possibility first raised by physiologist Resia Pretorius of Stellenbosch University in South Africa &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1186/s12933-021-01359-7"&gt;in 2021 is microclots&lt;/a&gt;. These are &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1042/BCJ20220016"&gt;tiny&lt;/a&gt;, abnormally persistent blood clots that are smaller than those seen in conditions such as stroke or thrombosis, yet large enough to hinder blood flow through &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Capillary"&gt;capillaries&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Meanwhile, in 2022, Thierry and his colleagues showed that patients with long COVID have &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1002/jmv.28209"&gt;elevated levels&lt;/a&gt; of neutrophil extracellular traps, or &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Neutrophil_extracellular_traps"&gt;NETs&lt;/a&gt;. These are sticky webs of DNA and enzymes released by white blood cells to capture and contain pathogens invading the body.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Normally, NETs do their job and then quickly break down, but when they are released in large numbers or persist longer than needed, they can contribute to blood flow problems &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1161/ATVBAHA.119.312463"&gt;such as thrombosis and atherosclerosis&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The new research – a collaboration between Pretorius and Thierry – suggests that these two separate markers, NETs and microclots, may interact in the blood of long COVID patients.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_181535" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-181535" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/clot.jpg" alt="" class="size-full wp-image-181535" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/clot.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/clot-600x363.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-181535" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;A long COVID patient's microclot. The green areas are abnormal sticky proteins, while the red and blue parts are cellular material. (&lt;a href="https://www.eurekalert.org/multimedia/1100665"&gt;Dr Chantelle Venter&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers used &lt;a href="https://eng.unimelb.edu.au/nanomaterials/capabilities/cytometry-and-particle-characterisation/imaging-flow-cytometry"&gt;imaging flow cytometry&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Fluorescence_microscope"&gt;fluorescence microscopy&lt;/a&gt; to study blood samples from 50 patients with long COVID and 38 healthy volunteers, focusing specifically on any differences in microclots and NETs. The healthy individuals had been recruited in two separate cohorts, in France and South Africa.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Patients with long COVID, the analysis revealed, had a dramatically higher number of microclots than the healthy controls – a 19.7-fold increase on the median. These clots were also larger than the microclots seen in healthy blood.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;An increase in NETs also correlated with the rise in microclots in long COVID patients. But then the researchers found something new: The NETs appeared to be physically embedded within the microclots, an association that had never before been reported.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Interestingly, t&lt;/span&gt;his association was observed in all the samples, both from the long COVID patients and control groups, which makes sense because the &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1038/s41598-021-81268-7"&gt;NETs' sticky mesh facilitates clotting&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;However, the effect was much more pronounced in the long COVID group. This interaction could make the microclots more resistant to the &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Fibrinolysis"&gt;fibrinolysis process&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; the body uses to break up accumulations of blood material.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/newsletter?utm_source=promo_health"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/health-newsletter-subscribe-promo-final-642x337.jpg" alt="Subscribe to ScienceAlert's free fact-checked newsletter" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-181305" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/health-newsletter-subscribe-promo-final-642x337.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/health-newsletter-subscribe-promo-final-768x403.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/health-newsletter-subscribe-promo-final-600x315.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/health-newsletter-subscribe-promo-final.jpg 850w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"This finding suggests the existence of underlying physiological interactions between microclots and NETs that, when dysregulated, may become pathogenic," &lt;a href="https://www.su.ac.za/en/faculties/science/news/scientists-reveal-another-piece-long-covid-puzzle"&gt;Thierry explains&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So dramatic was the difference that, when the samples were anonymized, an AI agent was able to identify the long COVID patients with 91 percent accuracy. This suggests that microclots and NETs may be a biomarker that doctors could use to diagnose long COVID, a condition that has &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/long-covid-is-likely-going-to-be-with-us-for-a-while-here-s-the-latest-theories"&gt;proven slippery&lt;/a&gt; to pin down &lt;a href="https://my.clevelandclinic.org/health/diseases/25111-long-covid"&gt;using standard tests&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is still early research; more work needs to be done to establish a causal relationship between microclots, NETs, and long COVID. But if researchers can figure out how these blood components affect long COVID, it may be a &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/chronic-pain-treatment-may-offer-hope-for-long-covid-sufferers"&gt;step towards relief&lt;/a&gt; for those living with the condition.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The research has been published in the &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1002/jmv.70613"&gt;&lt;i&gt;Journal of Medical Virology&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 01:05:24 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiogFBVV95cUxNeUtKMnNHekJfdXlkMGphdkZfTFZMc1V5MVYzSVYwTmtTUEZTa3JmdjN1U3hiSnNaeU84dG5TRjJYNjYtcmRhWmpOdXlMMTNwTWdxMVlPVXUxLXh3Sk1wUWtZeHh0b1hzcmZpTjFpc1BWTGxrUEQzeVJ0TGZvekt0VlVIcFJySHFqMDcwcC10UUJGT0JTdXUxV3lRS3FxVUg2QkE</guid></item><item><title>卫生官员警告说，痛苦的疾病将成为这十年的主要威胁： “大量的人类痛苦” -雅虎</title><link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/articles/health-officials-warn-painful-disease-002000994.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="" data-article-body="true"&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Historically, some diseases have been geographically limited, naturally confined to areas of the globe where the weather is right for their spread. Mosquito-borne illnesses such as dengue fever are good examples, because they only proliferate in areas where the temperature and rainfall are beneficial for the mosquito population to grow, as well as for the disease itself to flourish.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;However, as the Earth heats up due to air pollution, more and more of the world fits those conditions — and dengue fever is already becoming a more widespread problem, as a new study covered by the Stanford Report &lt;a href="https://news.stanford.edu/stories/2025/09/dengue-fever-rates-climate-change-study" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:revealed;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;revealed&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="mb-4 text-lg font-bold"&gt;What's happening?&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The study was conducted by researchers at Stanford, Harvard, Arizona State University, and the National Bureau of Economic Research. It was published in September in Proceedings of the National Academy of Sciences.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Researchers examined how much the Earth's rising temperature will increase cases of dengue fever in the future — and how much it already has.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;"The effects of temperature were much larger than I expected," said lead author Marissa Childs, an assistant professor of environmental health at the University of Washington, per the &lt;a href="https://news.stanford.edu/stories/2025/09/dengue-fever-rates-climate-change-study" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Stanford Report;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Stanford Report&lt;/a&gt;. "Even small shifts in temperature can have a big impact for dengue transmission, and we're already seeing the fingerprint of climate warming."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;So exactly how large was that fingerprint? After examining 1.4 million cases of the disease across 21 countries, researchers determined that climate change is responsible for an additional 4.6 million infections each year, representing an 18% increase in the disease's incidence. By 2050, the rate could climb another 49% to 76%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="mb-4 text-lg font-bold"&gt;Why is this result important?&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Dengue fever, also called "breakbone fever," is a painful and potentially serious illness. In severe cases, it can cause debilitating pain and can lead to death. According to the &lt;a href="https://www.who.int/news-room/fact-sheets/detail/dengue-and-severe-dengue" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:World Health Organization;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;World Health Organization&lt;/a&gt;, those who contract it more than once are at greater risk of experiencing a severe case. And as the world heats up, more and more people who have never been exposed to this illness before are now at risk — a fact which has already had a death toll.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;"This is not just hypothetical future change but a large amount of human suffering that has already happened because of warming-driven dengue transmission," &lt;a href="https://news.stanford.edu/stories/2025/09/dengue-fever-rates-climate-change-study" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:said;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;said&lt;/a&gt; senior author Erin Mordecai, a professor of biology from the Stanford School of Humanities and Sciences, per the Stanford Report. "Climate change is not just affecting the weather — it has cascading consequences for human health, including fueling disease transmission by mosquitoes."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="mb-4 text-lg font-bold"&gt;What's being done about dengue fever transmission?&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Recent research into vaccinations has yielded results that promise to reduce the spread of dengue fever worldwide. Some local governments are also working on directly controlling the mosquito population to thereby stop the spread of the disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;However, the only long-term solution for the broader problem of diseases that spread more rapidly in warmer temperatures is to reduce the Earth's temperature by reducing air pollution.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Join our &lt;a href="https://www.thecooldown.com/future-newsletter/?rec9bh39sND8fgERx" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:free newsletter;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;free newsletter&lt;/a&gt; for &lt;strong&gt;good news&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;useful tips&lt;/strong&gt;, and don't miss &lt;a href="https://rb.gy/ivhzmj" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:this cool list;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;this cool list&lt;/a&gt; of easy ways to help yourself while helping the planet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Yahoo</author><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 00:20:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikgFBVV95cUxQUndCb3VRRFRaSl9UTW5OTWtwTndjRHN6RWVEbFpwbnlPcUF0ZGNiTjJLbnhLcTNGdnlJOVpCMy1CVGlKZzdGVFBmT201d3RLaTNkODNLaGpTcF9BSEY2NUJaSEU5ZmhvcnY2UjdJRGxrRzA4clhwWGUzQnA4d2FCM0k2QjFzNG5IdUJHeWJDZDdXdw</guid></item><item><title>我播出的“脑雾”时刻如何引发了一场大辩论- BBC</title><link>https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/c4gpkenx9dzo</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article&gt;&lt;p data-component="headline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 hNbOGD"&gt;&lt;h1 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 idLnWK"&gt;How my on-air 'brain fog' moment sparked a big debate&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="byline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="byline-new" class="sc-7bfdb3c2-0 fYJjWP"&gt;&lt;span data-testid="byline-new-contributors" class="sc-7bfdb3c2-11 ljQVMv"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="byline-new-contributors-contributor-0" class="sc-7bfdb3c2-5 xGeVU"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="sc-7bfdb3c2-7 djOqvY"&gt;Zoe Kleinman&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-testid="byline-new-contributors-contributor-0-role-location" class="sc-7bfdb3c2-8 gvcwmG"&gt;Technology editor&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 gtLOOD"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="hero-image" class="sc-5340b511-1 cMIbKV"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20251110-152207-94080fba49-web-2.33.2-3/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 gUePlo hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/b951/live/f3930a20-c136-11f0-8669-5560f5c90fbe.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/b951/live/f3930a20-c136-11f0-8669-5560f5c90fbe.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/b951/live/f3930a20-c136-11f0-8669-5560f5c90fbe.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/b951/live/f3930a20-c136-11f0-8669-5560f5c90fbe.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/b951/live/f3930a20-c136-11f0-8669-5560f5c90fbe.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/b951/live/f3930a20-c136-11f0-8669-5560f5c90fbe.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/b951/live/f3930a20-c136-11f0-8669-5560f5c90fbe.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/b951/live/f3930a20-c136-11f0-8669-5560f5c90fbe.jpg.webp" loading="eager" alt="BBC BBC technology editor Zoe Kleinman holding notes as she speaks on the BBC News at Ten" class="sc-5340b511-0 hLdNfA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 jVqbAn"&gt;BBC&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;Due to "brain fog" BBC technology editor Zoe Kleinman had to hold notes during a recent live TV report&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;When I rather nervously shared a personal post about dealing with brain fog at work on the social network LinkedIn last week, I had no idea that it would have such an enormous impact.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;It's been &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.linkedin.com/feed/update/urn:li:activity:7393223331946332160/" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;viewed&lt;/a&gt; hundreds of thousands of times. Women have stopped me on the street to talk to me about it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;I've been overwhelmed by hundreds of messages from people sharing support and their own experiences of it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Usually I cover technology news. But given the response, it felt important to talk about this as well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"Brain fog" isn't a medical term. But you may well know exactly what I'm talking about.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;That moment when you suddenly can't remember the word for something really obvious, or you're mid-sentence and you lose your train of thought. It's infuriating, and it can be embarrassing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Where was I?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Ah yes, for me, as a woman in my 40s, it's coincided with perimenopause – the stage in my life where my hormone levels are changing. There can of course be other neurological conditions for which brain fog can be a symptom too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;If you're in a job where public speaking is part of what you do, it can be particularly terrifying.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"I've spent 30 years being professionally articulate," wrote Janet Edgecombe, an internal communications expert.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"All of a sudden I'm forgetting the words for basic things. 'That grey thing in the thingy that we cook chicken on'. My husband replies 'oh, the baking tray in the oven'. Hmm. 'Yeah, that thing'."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 gXrNRM"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 cMIbKV"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20251110-152207-94080fba49-web-2.33.2-3/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 gUePlo hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/6f19/live/402e1e30-c13f-11f0-8717-7b6a6b2fefad.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/6f19/live/402e1e30-c13f-11f0-8717-7b6a6b2fefad.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/6f19/live/402e1e30-c13f-11f0-8717-7b6a6b2fefad.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/6f19/live/402e1e30-c13f-11f0-8717-7b6a6b2fefad.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/6f19/live/402e1e30-c13f-11f0-8717-7b6a6b2fefad.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/6f19/live/402e1e30-c13f-11f0-8717-7b6a6b2fefad.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/6f19/live/402e1e30-c13f-11f0-8717-7b6a6b2fefad.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/6f19/live/402e1e30-c13f-11f0-8717-7b6a6b2fefad.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Getty Images A middle-aged woman holding her head" class="sc-5340b511-0 hLdNfA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 jVqbAn"&gt;Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;Women typically go through perimenopause in their 40s&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;I also heard from teachers, start-up founders having to present pitches for money to investors, women running workshops, delivering speeches – and fellow journalists trying to report live on-air, like me. But of course it can also hit mid-conversation, in a more intimate but no less frustrating way.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;My post was about my decision to hold a page of notes on the BBC News at Ten. A story had broken late in the afternoon, following an already busy day, and by the time we reached 10pm, I knew I was getting tired and I could feel the brain fog.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;I was going to talk about an outage that was affecting dozens of websites and apps, and I planned to use the technical jargon for it, as given by the company affected, and then explain what it actually meant.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;But I just couldn't get the phrase to stick in my head and I knew that without it, I wouldn't manage the rest of what I needed to say.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;I was reporting live from Glasgow. Like many of my professional peers, I do not have, and I've never had, autocue. And so, for the first time, I decided at the last minute to hold a page of notes with the offending phrase on it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;It felt to me at the time like an admission of failure. I have been trained never to use notes – unless there's a specific legal reason why the wording of a statement, for example, has to be precise, or there are a lot of figures to remember.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Even then, I have prided myself on having a good enough short-term memory to get me through.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Using notes is discouraged in the world of public speaking. They are not permitted to anyone giving a 12-minute TED talk. The speaker is expected to memorise their speech.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Looking down the barrel of the camera and clutching that paper, live on TV, felt tough.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;But around 10% of women report &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.fawcettsociety.org.uk/menopauseandtheworkplace" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;leaving their jobs&lt;/a&gt; due to menopause symptoms, according to the Fawcett Society. And research by insurance firm Royal London found that half of women going through it have &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.royallondon.com/about-us/media/Media-Centre/press-releases/press-releases-2023/october/Menopause-talent-drain-half-of-women-going-through-menopause-are-considering-leaving-work/" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;considered giving up work.&lt;/a&gt; I don't want to do that – and so I stuck with my solution.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;To my intense relief, some people said they thought my paper looked authoritative, that they just assumed it was a breaking story and the page contained fresh information. Others asked why I hadn't used a device instead – I suppose I thought the potential of having to fumble with a screen would feel even worse.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"Let's start a movement: Hold your notes," wrote Elisheva Marcus, vice president of communications at the venture capitalist firm Earlybird.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;And so, the hashtag holdthenotes was born.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"Have you ever checked your testosterone levels?" menopause expert Dr Louise Newson asked me.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;She says testosterone – despite its reputation for being a male hormone, and its association with sex drive and libido, is actually an essential brain chemical for both men and women, and levels fall in both genders. One of the results is brain fog.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"It's like you've been drugged," she says. "It's really scary, a lot of people worry they've got dementia."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"I remember when I had my levels done 10 years ago, and I was like 'Thank God, at least I know why I'm feeling so awful'."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;She adds that there are studies dating back to the 1940s indicating that testosterone can improve brain function and &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.newscientist.com/article/2499701-testosterone-helps-libido-in-menopause-can-it-treat-other-symptoms/" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;wellbeing in women&lt;/a&gt; as well as men, but the randomised control studies, where participants are given either a placebo or the product itself in order to see whether it really works, have only focused on improvements to libido.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;NHS-prescribed &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.nhs.uk/medicines/hormone-replacement-therapy-hrt/" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;Hormone Replacement Therapy,&lt;/a&gt; or HRT, is traditionally a combination of oestrogen and progesterone. Testosterone is not routinely included.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Instead doctors can separately prescribe testosterone to female patients, at lower doses than given to men.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 gXrNRM"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 cMIbKV"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20251110-152207-94080fba49-web-2.33.2-3/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 gUePlo hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/cac0/live/39cadac0-c152-11f0-bcb8-25f1327fdf90.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/cac0/live/39cadac0-c152-11f0-bcb8-25f1327fdf90.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/cac0/live/39cadac0-c152-11f0-bcb8-25f1327fdf90.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/cac0/live/39cadac0-c152-11f0-bcb8-25f1327fdf90.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/cac0/live/39cadac0-c152-11f0-bcb8-25f1327fdf90.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/cac0/live/39cadac0-c152-11f0-bcb8-25f1327fdf90.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/cac0/live/39cadac0-c152-11f0-bcb8-25f1327fdf90.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/cac0/live/39cadac0-c152-11f0-bcb8-25f1327fdf90.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Getty Images A woman holding HRT tablets" class="sc-5340b511-0 hLdNfA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 jVqbAn"&gt;Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;Millions of women take HRT medication&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;There are also a myriad of menopause supplements which claim to ease symptoms including brain fog. Estimates vary but it's a multi-billion dollar industry and its booming.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Women spend an average &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.nutraingredients.com/Article/2025/04/21/beauty-supplements-and-the-menopause" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;of £147 per year on supplements&lt;/a&gt; to try to alleviate their menopause symptoms, according to a survey earlier this year by the nutrition news website NutraIngredients.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"They might help a bit," says Dr Newson.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"I do yoga every day, and that helps my brain become clear and focused, but I have a hormone deficiency, I can't eat my way out of it, or exercise my way out of it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"A lot of women spend a fortune trying to improve symptoms of a hormone deficiency with something else."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Dr Joshua Chen is part of the Harvard Medical School-Massachusetts General Hospital Photobiomodulation Research Group. The team is looking at how frequencies of red light can change the mitochondria inside the brain to improve focus.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;He describes it as "like a face mask, but for the brain". It can also, he says, be applied to the Vagus nerve on the neck to reduce stress.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;He has founded a company called Niraxx which markets a headband called a neuro espresso, which is designed to be worn for up to 20 minutes a day. He claims the results are instant. It has to be plugged in – there are no batteries in the device for safety reasons.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 gXrNRM"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 cMIbKV"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20251110-152207-94080fba49-web-2.33.2-3/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 gUePlo hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/be0a/live/1c3a1a50-c136-11f0-8717-7b6a6b2fefad.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/be0a/live/1c3a1a50-c136-11f0-8717-7b6a6b2fefad.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/be0a/live/1c3a1a50-c136-11f0-8717-7b6a6b2fefad.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/be0a/live/1c3a1a50-c136-11f0-8717-7b6a6b2fefad.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/be0a/live/1c3a1a50-c136-11f0-8717-7b6a6b2fefad.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/be0a/live/1c3a1a50-c136-11f0-8717-7b6a6b2fefad.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/be0a/live/1c3a1a50-c136-11f0-8717-7b6a6b2fefad.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/be0a/live/1c3a1a50-c136-11f0-8717-7b6a6b2fefad.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Niraxx A woman wearing the neuro espresso headband made by tech firm Niraxx" class="sc-5340b511-0 hLdNfA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 jVqbAn"&gt;Niraxx&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;The headband made by US tech firm Niraxx uses red light frequencies to try to stimulate the wearer's brain&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Angela Marsh is a registered nurse and a menopause coach. She says her clients often describe brain fog as feeling like they are "living life in soft focus".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"I don't think brain fog is taken seriously enough at all," she says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"Many women feel deeply unsettled by the changes they experience. They think there's something wrong with them or they're 'losing it' when in fact there's a clear biological reason."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;As for me – well, I've booked a blood test to check my hormone levels. I'm going to try some red-light therapy. And you are probably going to see me holding notes a bit more often.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BBC</author><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 00:06:44 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiWkFVX3lxTFBkanptNVlONGJjSllfWHBhb2tKcGYwOWNXZWp2MFFjWEdzQ01wSXFYLVhRSW1nS2hvOGFzR3QwU1FyaDd1V1VaWmE2d05sQ0kwaGVFVS1jcElrUdIBX0FVX3lxTE5pYzFJYlpaRngtXzcyakVOa2V2cVBrMlpST1doTVo5SklrUzI4TWRmWWFzZ3BuTklUTlU2SkpzVXBDTlphSmdsSUV5N2lkZXlORURXWDd5V0tucmFBQ19J</guid></item><item><title>21名医生正在揭示可以在几秒钟内结束生命的“无声医疗条件” - BuzzFeed</title><link>https://www.buzzfeed.com/haein_jung/deadly-medical-conditions-with-zero-symptoms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="subbuzz buzz-width--standard__subbuzz buzz-type--list__subbuzz subbuzz-text
  subbuzz-index-0
  
  
  
  
  " data-module="subbuzz-text"&gt;
  
  &lt;p id="139520327" class="subbuzz-anchor"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



  &lt;h2 class="subbuzz__header subbuzz__header--standard subbuzz__title "&gt;
    

    
      &lt;span class="js-subbuzz__title-text"&gt;Recently, in &lt;a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/AskReddit/" target="_blank"&gt;r/AskReddit&lt;/a&gt;, someone &lt;a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/AskReddit/comments/1o60ft4/whats_one_condition_that_can_have_no_symptoms_but/" target="_blank"&gt;asked&lt;/a&gt;, "What’s one condition that can have no symptoms but kill you instantly?" People wrote in on medical conditions that came out of nowhere and resulted in some unfortunate circumstances. Here's what people said:&lt;/span&gt;
    
  &lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;This article is not to &lt;b&gt;replace seeing a medical professional.&lt;/b&gt; Medical issues are so specific to each individual person and could also indicate that there might be more underlying issues at hand.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BuzzFeed</author><pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 23:31:02 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihwFBVV95cUxORUl4Q0EzQnBqeTlLamdVdlV6X3NoTHNmbE1Gb2dYeWxiN3FUNURxWTVkQ0x6Q2k5WmFXRHE2VVNnczRzVVpjczk0ZGlydDBVRTdDdVg2SDUxWjJfak1TTXUzN1lJdkVzZnJMV2FmR2hnbGc1V2JFb0IyS2ZHb3M4Zk5XbFNVUWM</guid></item><item><title>顶级神经学家分享了3种日常习惯，这些习惯会随着时间的推移损害我们的脑细胞-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/top-neurologist-shares-3-everyday-habits-that-damages-our-brain-cells-over-time/photostory/125364724.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="COQxt" data-ua-type="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alcohol is socially accepted and generally consumed in moderation; however, overindulgence or chronic consumption is ruinous to the brain. Dr. Love points out that alcohol alters how the brain communicates, altering learning, memory, and decision-making. Chronic heavy drinking can even shrink the brain tissue itself and distort neurotransmitter balance, impeding neurons from communicating as they should.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Alcohol also disrupts sleep quality, even though it may get you to sleep quicker, and disrupted sleep amplifies the toxic effect on the brain. Chronic alcohol consumption raises the risk of neurodegenerative diseases and, in severe cases, can result in permanent cognitive impairment. According to Dr. Love, if you can cut down or practice mindful drinking, you can spare your brain from further damage. For people who struggle with alcohol addiction, professional intervention can be life-changing.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 23:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi-gFBVV95cUxOMF9tbzFRcmpFbENYX2tCejVpYWRMbUdwcU80UXdiZHRqSGZHc0ZVbWpNNWNsS0M1UEtIR2NJRmRiVzNucnN2YnhZMGszTm00eE5hZG5Fa24xTDRuclk2Y24yckZSWTdoY3M0Qlk0TXNyYWFfaGVIU3pJdnh6NlZ6d0hjWFRhaXlQU1BLV0hSMEUzOUQ2enFpZUF0ckVmelBjcjJJVHVRSHNXTGZrOG11cmRsQW12QklZVzJwYmVNcGN1bzE3M2pZUkxpWGt5WklGMm92WWxZMXRNTGxHWWJGaS1LY0duQ3lqS2FDWWdmNm5venhnejFIb1BR0gGCAkFVX3lxTE1Sai1sSlpZTW1DUGFQWVRxdEZTRWZ6S1ZBOTROM3hyREtHR05JZkNmcjRUXzhhMy15czV6a1pybktzY2pwQkZyT2FzbkVGTkJOenFkVkNGLTFfRk1EZlUwanpYQkFEa3ZCYkppSFB0NzRzeklUTE9rS3lESHFPQ0JMTGZ3aldpSWRteWtfTkE0N0lOckFXekRxdzZQVnl4N04tbk5EdW9kNm91eFZpc2hsSnlodm5MQ3pQRGZOQVBXMmtTSUxFQjRjdHZ3OUtfNGlfWFBqX0daRmlLX1JRSGYzaEZSZHRkNk4xZllkODZaRHd3YktwcU1YaTZZUld0ZTFDZw</guid></item><item><title>好莱坞的“美丽”死亡让我恶心-每日邮报</title><link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-15234677/George-Clooney-movie-Alzheimers-suicide.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div itemprop="articleBody"&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;A &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/california/index.html" id="mol-18afc350-b40a-11f0-8257-97c609e9cb2c"&gt;California&lt;/a&gt; dementia specialist has issued a stark warning that &lt;a target="_self" href="/tvshowbiz/george_clooney/index.html" id="mol-188557f0-b40a-11f0-8257-97c609e9cb2c"&gt;George Clooney&lt;/a&gt;'s new film could romanticize assisted suicide and send a dangerous message to millions of vulnerable people living with &lt;a target="_self" href="/sciencetech/alzheimers-disease/index.html" id="mol-7c4b55f0-b40a-11f0-8257-97c609e9cb2c"&gt;Alzheimer's&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Patty Mouton, a veteran gerontologist and palliative care expert from Orange County, told the Daily Mail that Clooney's forthcoming movie In Love risks 'glamorizing' death and distorting the painful realities of illness, care, and family duty.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'We have a very, very serious responsibility not to glamorize the notion of going out standing tall instead of on my knees,' Mouton said. 'That's not life. Life is cyclic — it includes vulnerability. To avoid that is to limit our human experience.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Clooney, 64, will star in In Love, based on Amy Bloom's bestselling 2022 memoir In Love: A Memoir of Love and Loss.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The story follows Bloom and her husband, architect Brian Ameche, who was diagnosed with early-onset Alzheimer's and &lt;a target="_self" href="/home/books/article-10834741/A-week-architect-told-dementia-decided-end-life.html"&gt;chose to end his life at the Swiss assisted dying clinic Dignitas&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In the film, Clooney plays Ameche, with Annette Bening as Bloom. Filming begins in New England in November.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;To many, it's a tender love story about autonomy and dignity. Bloom herself called the memoir a reflection on 'truth-telling and the right to face death without shame.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Director Paul Weitz has called the story a 'contemporary fable of love, wit, and existential stakes.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;&lt;p class="clear"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="imageCaption" data-lt-tmp-id="lt-448725" data-gramm="false"&gt;Actors George Clooney and Annette Bening will star as the husband and wife couple grappling with an Alzheimer's diagnose&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption" data-lt-tmp-id="lt-146353" data-gramm="false"&gt;California gerontologist Patty Mouton says Clooney's forthcoming movie In Love risks 'glamorizing' death &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But Mouton isn't convinced. She fears the film's Hollywood gloss and star power will mask the grim emotional and moral costs of assisted suicide — and make it seem like a graceful, noble exit rather than a desperate decision.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'My hope is that the production team will be very, very careful not to emotionally incentivize people to think about assisted suicide in a more positive way,' she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'It's not this convenient way to wrap up a life. It has far, far-reaching ramifications.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The longtime dementia care specialist worries that Clooney's portrayal could make those struggling with Alzheimer's — and their exhausted loved ones — believe that choosing death is an act of courage or love.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'What does it say about people who are not 100 percent strong — physically, emotionally, or cognitively?' she asked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Is it telling them that their lives are no longer worthwhile, and that it's better to just end it before you become inconvenient or expensive?'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Drawing from decades at the bedsides of dying patients, Mouton said decisions like these are never made in isolation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;They're shaped by fear, exhaustion, family tension, and medical bills that average around $70,000 per year for dementia sufferers, straining even premier health insurance plans.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'I've had families say, 'Can't we end this sooner? It's so expensive,'' she revealed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Sometimes the evidence suggests they don't want their inheritance to be diminished by a long, drawn-out caregiving experience.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;She added that society must 'reaffirm its duty' to care for the sick with compassion, not convenience.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'We have a duty to help people understand they're going to be taken care of with love, respect, and dignity,' she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'We must disabuse people of the notion that the only way to live is with complete strength and cognitive ability.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption" data-lt-tmp-id="lt-482900" data-gramm="false"&gt;Clooney, pictured here with wife Amal, is one of Hollywood's most recognizable stars&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption" data-lt-tmp-id="lt-540444" data-gramm="false"&gt;The movie depicts the real-life story of Amy Bloom and her husband Brian Ameche   &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption" data-lt-tmp-id="lt-839163" data-gramm="false"&gt;They travelled to Switzerland's notorious end of life clinic Dignitas, where Brian ended his life &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Her comments come as Alzheimer's cases rise across the US.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;More than 7.2 million Americans currently live with the disease — a figure &lt;a target="_self" href="/health/article-5527593/5-7-million-people-Alzheimers-costing-277-BILLION-year.html"&gt;expected to double by 2050&lt;/a&gt; as the baby boomer generation ages, according to the Alzheimer's Association.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The degenerative brain disorder robs people of memory, reasoning, and independence. It remains incurable.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;And while 12 US states and Washington, DC allow physician-assisted dying, it is reserved for terminally ill, mentally competent adults expected to die within six months.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;None permit it for dementia patients.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Connecticut — where Bloom and her husband lived — bans it altogether.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;That's why the couple traveled to Switzerland, where Dignitas offers assisted death to foreigners who are &lt;a target="_self" href="/health/article-12881125/More-530-desperate-Brits-ended-life-Dignitas-Swiss-clinic-opened-1990s-interactive-globe-reveals-nations-assisted-suicide-service-popular.html"&gt;acting voluntarily and have decision-making capacity&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Dementia is problematic, as sufferers have to make end-of-life decisions before their capacity to consent to an assisted suicide is lost.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Mouton said the growing normalization of procedures, from Europe to Hollywood, risks warping the public's moral compass.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'If we are going to be a civilized society,' she said, 'aren't we judged by the way we treat those who are most vulnerable?'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Mouton said she has never known anyone personally who went to Dignitas, but she has counseled countless families wracked with fear and guilt.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Many, she said, underestimate the emotional toll — or the potential for healing — in caring for loved ones through decline.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption" data-lt-tmp-id="lt-645778" data-gramm="false"&gt;Celebrated American writer Amy Bloom co-wrote the screenplay for the upcoming movie&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="mol-img-group floatRHS"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption" data-lt-tmp-id="lt-963192" data-gramm="false"&gt;Her 2022 book describes how Brian, in his own words, wanted to die 'standing tall, not on his knees' &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;She also warned that those who choose to die early may miss out on medical breakthroughs or moments of grace.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'What if I'm the person who gets into a clinical trial and gets the magic bullet?' she asked. 'What if the next discovery comes six months later, and I've ended my life too soon?'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'When somebody has a diagnosis like dementia, we might miss the opportunity to help the medical community learn more — or even get to a cure,' she added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;For Mouton, end-of-life care isn't just about dying — it's about living meaningfully, right to the end.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'I've seen siblings come together after not speaking for years,' she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'I've seen divorced couples reunite, so one can care for the other because it's the right thing to do. These are extraordinary expressions of love and healing — and we miss them if we just end it.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;She's witnessed patients who, even in their final days, still show small signs of wanting to live — accepting water, or a small bite of food.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Death is inconvenient,' she said. 'We have to accept that.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Mouton doesn't mince words about her opposition to assisted dying.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Suicide has detrimental effects on people,' she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'You can call it empowering, considerate, or intellectually superior. It's still suicide — and it still has really strong, difficult, often negative impacts on the loved ones of the person who's taken their life.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;She believes In Love — with its A-list cast and emotive storytelling — could unintentionally sell suicide as a moral act.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Mouton said she misses the days when films celebrated courage and endurance rather than convenience.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption" data-lt-tmp-id="lt-666036" data-gramm="false"&gt;The nondescript room on the outskirts of Zurich, Switzerland, where Dignitas visitors end their lives&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption" data-lt-tmp-id="lt-401127" data-gramm="false"&gt;Doctor-assisted deaths are widely available in Canada, though heavily restricted in the US  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'I think it was better when we had more movies about courage — doing the right thing under terrible circumstances,' she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'There's life after a diagnosis of dementia. Sometimes people live 12 or 15 years, and they're not debilitated until the very end.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'The danger,' she added, 'is that people won't understand that life isn't over just because you have a serious diagnosis. There's still love. There's still learning. There's still life.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Her warnings echo those of disability rights advocates, who have also sounded alarms about Hollywood's growing fascination with 'beautiful' deaths.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Ian McIntosh, executive director of the advocacy group Not Dead Yet, called In Love 'a disability snuff film by any other name.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Hollywood keeps depicting the everyday experiences of disabled people as a fate worse than death,' he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Million Dollar Baby and Me Before You were panned for glorifying suicide as rational, even noble. In Love will be no different.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Still, end-of-life choice advocates, such as Compassion &amp;amp; Choices, argue that controlled assisted dying offers autonomy and peace, not pressure, and that laws can include strict safeguards to prevent abuse.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Advocates say films like In Love help open long-overdue conversations about dignity, autonomy, and patient rights at the end of life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption" data-lt-tmp-id="lt-214180" data-gramm="false"&gt;In Love is being made by Smokehouse Pictures, the production company co-founded by longtime friends Grant Heslov (left) and George Clooney (right)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Whether to allow assisted dying stirs strong feelings, including in the UK (pictured), where a law change is being debated&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Mouton said she doesn't question Clooney's intentions — only the potential consequences. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;She hopes he and his team remember that behind every Alzheimer's story is not just pain, but resilience.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'It's easy to make a movie about despair,' she said. 'It's harder — and braver — to make one about endurance.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'My message to anyone with dementia is simple,' she concluded. 'You are not a burden. You are loved. You still matter.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Daily Mail</author><pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 22:38:41 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimgFBVV95cUxNQk5zWHp5SG1iRFFWOGwyM1k1ZDBvZFNUS1RYTjc3Ukt4SnY1OF9SekZiQlFodEJmMVFLYmhlUHBLQlBkWGkxMEJJWW80TjE5QWxRT05UWWFRRVRVcFJuRDFLYjZlOEhjZWxuYmJHSTZ3QXpRRUduLXR6Nm9pd0hfcWpWTVNsYmplMkNtMEVGZFNGcDFHWHo0UERn</guid></item><item><title>癌症，马铃薯能让心脏病远离吗？查看健康益处-《经济时报》</title><link>https://m.economictimes.com/news/international/us/cancer-heart-disease-can-be-kept-away-by-potato-check-health-benefits/articleshow/125373117.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div data-brcount="41" class="artText"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Potatoes are a solid source of vitamin C. One medium peeled russet potato offers about 25 per cent of the recommended daily amount. Vitamin C is essential for the growth and repair of tissue. It also acts as an antioxidant, keeping your immune system strong and helping to protect against chronic diseases such as heart disease and cancer, according to NYT News Service report.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-mid-newpos-mgid="mgid_125373117" id="div-mgid-mid-newpos-125373117"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Potatoes are also full of phenolics, a type of polyphenol that helps reduce inflammation, regulate immune function and protect cells from damage. And they contain a modest amount of vitamin B6, which is needed for cardiovascular, immune and mental health, said Mary Ellen Camire, a professor of food science and human nutrition at the University of Maine who has studied potatoes' health benefits, NYT News Service reported.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="E_3" class="etoro"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Potatoes are also full of phenolics, a type of polyphenol that helps reduce inflammation, regulate immune function and protect cells from damage. And they contain a modest amount of vitamin B6, which is needed for cardiovascular, immune and mental health, said Mary Ellen Camire, a professor of food science and human nutrition at the University of Maine who has studied potatoes' health benefits, as per NYT News Service report.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-mid-vdoai="vdoai_125373117" id="div-vdoai-mid-125373117"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-size="[[300, 250], [600, 250], [600, 300]]" data-adsslot="/7176/Economictimes/ET_News/ET_News_InternationalBusiness/ET_ROS_MID_NWS_IBZ_AS_300" data-loc="100" id="div-gpt-ad-858478126-125373117" class="country_specAD"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sweet potatoes tend to get most of the nutritional glory, but regular potatoes (russets, fingerlings, red and Yukon Golds) deserve another look. The tubers help to support your immune system, aid in various bodily functions and keep you energized.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-size="[[300, 250], [600, 250], [600, 300]]" data-adsslot="/7176/Economictimes/ET_News/ET_News_InternationalBusiness/ET_ROS_MID1_NWS_IBZ_AS_300" data-loc="2" id="div-gpt-ad-858478132-125373117" class="country_specAD2nd"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-size="[[300, 250], [600, 250], [600, 300]]" data-adsslot="/7176/Economictimes/ET_News/ET_News_InternationalBusiness/ET_ROS_MID1_NWS_IBZ_AS_300" data-loc="5" id="div-gpt-ad-858478132-125373117" class="country_specAD2nd"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-size="[[300, 250], [600, 250], [600, 300]]" data-adsslot="/7176/Economictimes/ET_News/ET_News_InternationalBusiness/ET_ROS_MID1_NWS_IBZ_AS_300" data-loc="3" id="div-gpt-ad-858478132-125373117" class="country_specAD2nd"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Potatoes often get a bad reputation" because they're commonly eaten in the form of French fries or potato chips, said Tal Kleiner, a clinical nutrition manager at NYU Langone Health. But when they're prepared in a healthy way, potatoes are an "amazing, nutrient-dense" food, she added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Potatoes are high in carbohydrates (a medium-size peeled russet potato has about 35 grams), but that doesn't make them "inherently bad," explained Tara Schmidt, a dietitian and instructor of nutrition at the Mayo Clinic in Rochester, Minnesota -- it just means they may not be considered an "unlimited" food.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Potatoes are complex carbs that take longer for the body to break down and digest than simple carbs, so they provide a steadier source of energy, which helps you feel fueled and fuller for longer, Kleiner said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But certain varieties do have a high glycemic index, meaning they can rapidly spike blood sugar, Kleiner said. Diets rich in foods with a high GI have been linked to an increased risk of diabetes and heart disease. Waxy potatoes, like fingerlings and red potatoes, tend to have a lower GI than russet or Idaho potatoes, she explained, and boiled and roasted potatoes have a lower GI than fried or mashed ones.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To help manage blood sugar spikes and slow digestion, Schmidt suggested "meal balancing" by pairing potatoes with lean protein, healthy fats and nonstarchy vegetables.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;FAQs&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Q1. What do we know about potatoes?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;p&gt;A1. Potatoes are also full of phenolics, a type of polyphenol that helps reduce inflammation, regulate immune function and protect cells from damage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Q2. What do we know about carbohydrates in potatoes?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;p&gt;A2. Potatoes are high in carbohydrates (a medium-size peeled russet potato has about 35 grams), but that doesn't make them "inherently bad," explained Tara Schmidt, a dietitian and instructor of nutrition at the Mayo Clinic in Rochester, Minnesota -- it just means they may not be considered an "unlimited" food.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Economic Times</author><pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 22:36:47 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi3gFBVV95cUxNSWw3SHZ4dzFEVUVTLW8xMFZrejQ5VGZBd09RVzVKdWZ1NHZtTG5ZWTlsa3ZDM1NYZTRSUE15TjJwQjl6dVJYWXhYRV96RFVjVUNDbkRfamlUZXpEZFd0a3lFYUQ0S0dkdGtydWU0Q1RJaHdUVUdBUm8yclhvYXQ1cnh0OFhrZnRwNzQ1bTB6QU5fcGVCa3FFUXpSeVhmX1d2eDl2X01EeGVWemRzNkt2LXdHOVJxNGI5RFFBYUVlY0h0SUxZQmpJVGF1bWZ6bVJPbEEwMEZzbzd6X3NpaHfSAeMBQVVfeXFMTkZiZDYyMVlrNWs1amQzWGJtYzJDRmlrM3VuNm5kU2hQcHJ5eWU5ZWwtQUI2UjUtRkNwd0xwWjFiSW5HVG02dGxjcHY3ZXgwRzhHaTBzYVdqVEFwenBQdXRWbXZvb2dIcHYwbGYwVFB2QkZaR2ctS0I3MDZ0WVY3LXF6MjFHRkJZVUZBZUU3YVFQRVZralF5WXBfVFpGLXVtTW82NmQ1SVFLT0ZyYjB4VVJXYmFCOFp2RHZrY2FaMTYtaGEzLXZEY1VMN0t1c25sWEhSZGtYemh2V2JfTUFqaGlRQ2c</guid></item><item><title>家中的5项NASA日常发明和电子产品- bgr.com</title><link>https://www.bgr.com/2022720/everyday-technology-gadgets-nasa-inventions/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="content" class="article"&gt;
            

            &lt;article class="news-post"&gt;
    
    
    
                &lt;p class="news-article"&gt;
                &lt;h1 class="title-gallery" data-post-id="2022720" id="title-gallery" data-has-pixel-tags="1" data-pixel-tag="bgr" data-author="Andrew Morrisey" data-category="technology" data-content_type="Mini-Feature - List" data-mod_date="2025-11-16" data-layout="Infinite" data-post_id="2022720" data-pub_date="2025-11-16" data-day="Sunday" data-dayhour="Sunday-5PM" data-pubhour="5PM" data-num_slides="6" data-num_words="1100" data-pitcher="Adam De'Seta" data-trello_board="News" data-intent="evergreen" data-ideation="aud-dev-competitor-analysis" data-importanttopic="True"&gt;5 Everyday NASA Inventions And Electronics In Your Home&lt;/h1&gt;
            &lt;/p&gt;

    
                &lt;div class="news-article"&gt;
                
                                
                                &lt;div class="slide-key image-holder gallery-image-holder credit-image-wrap lead-image-holder" data-post-url="https://www.bgr.com/2022720/everyday-technology-gadgets-nasa-inventions/" data-post-title="5 Everyday NASA Inventions And Electronics In Your Home" data-slide-num="0" data-post-id="2022720"&gt;
                                             &lt;picture id="p925e6829d891114f4029b40b5993488a"&gt;
                                                    &lt;source media="(min-width: 429px)" srcset="https://www.bgr.com/img/gallery/5-everyday-nasa-inventions-and-electronics-in-your-home/intro-1762527259.webp" type="image/webp"&gt;
                            &lt;source media="(max-width: 428px)" srcset="https://www.bgr.com/img/gallery/5-everyday-nasa-inventions-and-electronics-in-your-home/intro-1762527259.sm.webp" type="image/webp"&gt;
                        &lt;img class="gallery-image " src="https://www.bgr.com/img/gallery/5-everyday-nasa-inventions-and-electronics-in-your-home/intro-1762527259.jpg" data-slide-url="https://www.bgr.com/2022720/everyday-technology-gadgets-nasa-inventions/" data-post-id="2022720" data-slide-num="0" data-slide-title="5 Everyday NASA Inventions And Electronics In Your Home: " alt="NASA sign at Cape Canaveral"&gt;
                    &lt;/source&gt;&lt;/source&gt;&lt;/picture&gt;
                    &lt;span class="gallery-image-credit"&gt;Delpixart/Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;
                    &lt;/div&gt;
				            &lt;div class="columns-holder "&gt;
                
                
                &lt;p&gt;In 1958, during the height of the Cold War, President Dwight D. Eisenhower signed what was known as the National Aeronautics and Space Act into law. The goal of the legislation was to create an agency dedicated to civilian space exploration and aeronautics research, and from it NASA was formed. The agency been making &lt;a href="https://www.bgr.com/1984386/nasa-voyager-1-discovery-wall-of-fire/" target="_blank"&gt;stunning solar system discoveries&lt;/a&gt; for a long time. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Its logo evokes imagery of rockets lifting toward space and astronauts spacewalking against starry backdrops. But NASA's research and development efforts have also produced technology we use on a daily basis. The demands of space exploration have tasked NASA with finding solutions to problems that don't necessarily exist anywhere else. Equipment must be lightweight but durable, compact but powerful, and capable of functioning reliably in extreme conditions. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yet when solving these problems, NASA engineers create technologies with applications right here on Earth. Devices that help us keep the house clean, tools that ensure the safety of our loved ones, and even our beloved selfie cameras all have NASA's fingerprints on them. NASA classics like freeze-dried ice cream may not currently grace your pantry shelves, but the American space program's influence can be found in plenty of devices elsewhere around the house. Let's explore some of the NASA inventions we use on a daily basis.&lt;/p&gt;

            &lt;/div&gt;
            &lt;/div&gt;

            &lt;div class="news-article"&gt;
                
                &lt;h2 class=""&gt;Cordless vacuums&lt;/h2&gt;
                                &lt;div class="slide-key image-holder gallery-image-holder credit-image-wrap " data-post-url="https://www.bgr.com/2022720/everyday-technology-gadgets-nasa-inventions/" data-post-title="5 Everyday NASA Inventions And Electronics In Your Home" data-slide-num="1" data-post-id="2022720"&gt;
                                             &lt;picture id="pd15483d9f9b7a577c3cf2d2136c5dba5"&gt;
                                                    &lt;source media="(min-width: 429px)" srcset="https://www.bgr.com/img/gallery/5-everyday-nasa-inventions-and-electronics-in-your-home/cordless-vacuums-1762527263.webp" type="image/webp"&gt;
                            &lt;source media="(max-width: 428px)" srcset="https://www.bgr.com/img/gallery/5-everyday-nasa-inventions-and-electronics-in-your-home/cordless-vacuums-1762527263.sm.webp" type="image/webp"&gt;
                        &lt;img class="gallery-image " src="https://www.bgr.com/img/gallery/5-everyday-nasa-inventions-and-electronics-in-your-home/cordless-vacuums-1762527263.jpg" data-slide-url="https://www.bgr.com/2022720/everyday-technology-gadgets-nasa-inventions/" data-post-id="2022720" data-slide-num="1" data-slide-title="5 Everyday NASA Inventions And Electronics In Your Home: Cordless vacuums" alt="Using a cordless vacuum on a hallway carpet"&gt;
                    &lt;/source&gt;&lt;/source&gt;&lt;/picture&gt;
                    &lt;span class="gallery-image-credit"&gt;Nickbeer/Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;
                    &lt;/div&gt;
				            &lt;div class="columns-holder "&gt;
                &lt;p&gt;In order to collect lunar samples from the moon's surface, NASA realized during the Apollo missions of the 1960s and early 1970s that it would need to develop portable, battery-powered tools. NASA's Goddard Space Flight Center partnered with Black &amp;amp; Decker to develop a specialized drill that could operate in zero gravity while maintaining the proper amount of power during an extended runtime. The company's engineers created a computer program capable of optimizing the motor's design, ensuring maximum power output with minimal drain on the drill's power source.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The drill that was developed would go on to lay the foundation for Black &amp;amp; Decker's consumer product lineup. In January of 1979 the company introduced the Dustbuster, the popular handheld vacuum that worked cordlessly to clean stairs, sofas, and hard-to-reach places. The success of the Dustbuster was due in large part to the convenience it provided while keeping the house clean, and over the years that concept has been taken to greater heights. Companies like Dyson and Shark are known for their more sophisticated, full-size cordless vacuums, and the influence of those NASA Apollo missions can even be seen in devices like the &lt;a href="https://www.bgr.com/tech/are-roomba-robot-vacuums-still-worth-it/" target="_blank"&gt;Roomba and other robot vacuum options&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

            &lt;/div&gt;
            &lt;/div&gt;

            &lt;div class="news-article"&gt;
                
                &lt;h2 class=""&gt;Home smoke detectors&lt;/h2&gt;
                                &lt;div class="slide-key image-holder gallery-image-holder credit-image-wrap " data-post-url="https://www.bgr.com/2022720/everyday-technology-gadgets-nasa-inventions/" data-post-title="5 Everyday NASA Inventions And Electronics In Your Home" data-slide-num="2" data-post-id="2022720"&gt;
                                             &lt;picture id="pc0f3def8e5074054fb8439762654263d"&gt;
                                                    &lt;source media="(min-width: 429px)" srcset="https://www.bgr.com/img/gallery/5-everyday-nasa-inventions-and-electronics-in-your-home/home-smoke-detectors-1762527265.webp" type="image/webp"&gt;
                            &lt;source media="(max-width: 428px)" srcset="https://www.bgr.com/img/gallery/5-everyday-nasa-inventions-and-electronics-in-your-home/home-smoke-detectors-1762527265.sm.webp" type="image/webp"&gt;
                        &lt;img class="gallery-image " src="https://www.bgr.com/img/gallery/5-everyday-nasa-inventions-and-electronics-in-your-home/home-smoke-detectors-1762527265.jpg" data-slide-url="https://www.bgr.com/2022720/everyday-technology-gadgets-nasa-inventions/" data-post-id="2022720" data-slide-num="2" data-slide-title="5 Everyday NASA Inventions And Electronics In Your Home: Home smoke detectors" alt="A smoke detector being installed on the ceiling"&gt;
                    &lt;/source&gt;&lt;/source&gt;&lt;/picture&gt;
                    &lt;span class="gallery-image-credit"&gt;Brianajackson/Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;
                    &lt;/div&gt;
				            &lt;div class="columns-holder "&gt;
                &lt;p&gt;While the smoke detector dates all the way back to 1890, it's a good example of a piece of technology NASA improved upon greatly for its own use. In the 1970s NASA partnered with Honeywell Corporation to develop an adjustable smoke detection system for Skylab, the first American space station. With astronauts unable to evacuate to safety in the event of a fire, NASA needed a device reliable enough to warn crews of smoke and toxic gases, yet sophisticated enough not to be triggered by the routine activities going on at Skylab.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The resulting NASA invention was an ionization smoke detector with adjustable sensitivity, which influenced the evolution of home detectors over the years that followed. Honeywell would go on to release a battery backup smoke detector with a self-recharging battery, which became one of the most sophisticated alarm systems available for residential use. To this day, many home smoke detectors use ionization technology similar to what NASA developed.&lt;/p&gt;

            &lt;/div&gt;
            &lt;/div&gt;

            &lt;div class="news-article"&gt;
                
                &lt;h2 class=""&gt;Smartphone cameras&lt;/h2&gt;
                                &lt;div class="slide-key image-holder gallery-image-holder credit-image-wrap " data-post-url="https://www.bgr.com/2022720/everyday-technology-gadgets-nasa-inventions/" data-post-title="5 Everyday NASA Inventions And Electronics In Your Home" data-slide-num="3" data-post-id="2022720"&gt;
                                             &lt;picture id="p0818b82e9641ebdfbf9cfed0eaf761d3"&gt;
                                                    &lt;source media="(min-width: 429px)" srcset="https://www.bgr.com/img/gallery/5-everyday-nasa-inventions-and-electronics-in-your-home/smartphone-cameras-1762527267.webp" type="image/webp"&gt;
                            &lt;source media="(max-width: 428px)" srcset="https://www.bgr.com/img/gallery/5-everyday-nasa-inventions-and-electronics-in-your-home/smartphone-cameras-1762527267.sm.webp" type="image/webp"&gt;
                        &lt;img class="gallery-image " src="https://www.bgr.com/img/gallery/5-everyday-nasa-inventions-and-electronics-in-your-home/smartphone-cameras-1762527267.jpg" data-slide-url="https://www.bgr.com/2022720/everyday-technology-gadgets-nasa-inventions/" data-post-id="2022720" data-slide-num="3" data-slide-title="5 Everyday NASA Inventions And Electronics In Your Home: Smartphone cameras" alt="Pointing the iPhone camera to take a picture"&gt;
                    &lt;/source&gt;&lt;/source&gt;&lt;/picture&gt;
                    &lt;span class="gallery-image-credit"&gt;Grinvalds/Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;
                    &lt;/div&gt;
				            &lt;div class="columns-holder "&gt;
                &lt;p&gt;When you're exploring the unknown, bringing back pictures is imperative, like &lt;a href="https://www.bgr.com/science/nasa-just-snapped-the-closest-photos-of-the-sun-ever-taken/" target="_blank"&gt;NASA's recent close-up photos of the sun&lt;/a&gt;. Early space cameras were large, power-hungry devices that took up a lot of room aboard NASA spacecraft. Photographic equipment would need to be implemented into satellites as well, and by the 1990s, NASA was set on improving image sensors for a new generation of space exploration. The culmination of that research was CMOS (complementary metal-oxide semiconductor) technology developed by a NASA Jet Propulsion Laboratory team.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The key innovation within CMOS technology was the active-pixel sensor. It was capable of boosting image quality while requiring 100 times less power than the then-standard CCD sensor. While the CMOS sensor was immediately beneficial for NASA, it has become transformational for the rest of us, with far more than a billion cameras utilizing CMOS technology manufactured since. CMOS sensors can be found in everything from professional video cameras to vehicle backup cameras, and from the main camera of popular smartphones to the front-facing selfie camera that allows you to video chat with friends and family.&lt;/p&gt;

            &lt;/div&gt;
            &lt;/div&gt;

            &lt;div class="news-article"&gt;
                
                &lt;h2 class=""&gt;Scratch resistant lenses&lt;/h2&gt;
                                &lt;div class="slide-key image-holder gallery-image-holder credit-image-wrap " data-post-url="https://www.bgr.com/2022720/everyday-technology-gadgets-nasa-inventions/" data-post-title="5 Everyday NASA Inventions And Electronics In Your Home" data-slide-num="4" data-post-id="2022720"&gt;
                                             &lt;picture id="p9f6ecfc55b861b77c0c191b0f4a90ea0"&gt;
                                                    &lt;source media="(min-width: 429px)" srcset="https://www.bgr.com/img/gallery/5-everyday-nasa-inventions-and-electronics-in-your-home/scratch-resistant-lenses-1762527269.webp" type="image/webp"&gt;
                            &lt;source media="(max-width: 428px)" srcset="https://www.bgr.com/img/gallery/5-everyday-nasa-inventions-and-electronics-in-your-home/scratch-resistant-lenses-1762527269.sm.webp" type="image/webp"&gt;
                        &lt;img class="gallery-image " src="https://www.bgr.com/img/gallery/5-everyday-nasa-inventions-and-electronics-in-your-home/scratch-resistant-lenses-1762527269.jpg" loading="lazy" data-slide-url="https://www.bgr.com/2022720/everyday-technology-gadgets-nasa-inventions/" data-post-id="2022720" data-slide-num="4" data-slide-title="5 Everyday NASA Inventions And Electronics In Your Home: Scratch resistant lenses" alt="Holding a pair of sunglasses up to the sun"&gt;
                    &lt;/source&gt;&lt;/source&gt;&lt;/picture&gt;
                    &lt;span class="gallery-image-credit"&gt;rizzal syah/Shutterstock&lt;/span&gt;
                    &lt;/div&gt;
				            &lt;div class="columns-holder "&gt;
                &lt;p&gt;While working on a water purification system for spacecraft at the Ames Research Center, NASA's Dr. Ted Wydeven inadvertently discovered the foundation for scratch-resistant plastic lenses. NASA expanded on the discovery to develop an abrasion-resistant coating for astronaut helmets and the plastic surfaces of other space equipment. Meanwhile, eyeglass manufacturers were making a switch to plastic lenses, and in 1983 a company called Foster-Grant obtained a license from NASA to combine its decade of scratch-resistance research with NASA's scratch-resistant coating technology.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The resulting lenses lasted 10 times longer than standard plastic lenses and even surpassed glass in terms of durability. Today, scratch-resistance technology can be found in everything from ski goggles to sunglasses, and if tech like &lt;a href="https://www.bgr.com/1992030/meta-ray-ban-display-glasses-repairability-ifixit-teardown/" target="_blank"&gt;Meta's expensive smart glasses&lt;/a&gt; ever become popular among the masses, it's likely we'll see scratch-resistance incorporated into them as well. What began as a NASA invention to protect astronauts and their equipment from the harshness of space now provides us with protection on our smartphone screens, camera lenses, and other optical equipment in addition to eyewear.&lt;/p&gt;

            &lt;/div&gt;
            &lt;/div&gt;

            &lt;div class="news-article"&gt;
                
                &lt;h2 class=""&gt;Joysticks&lt;/h2&gt;
                                &lt;div class="slide-key image-holder gallery-image-holder credit-image-wrap " data-post-url="https://www.bgr.com/2022720/everyday-technology-gadgets-nasa-inventions/" data-post-title="5 Everyday NASA Inventions And Electronics In Your Home" data-slide-num="5" data-post-id="2022720"&gt;
                                             &lt;picture id="pf0dfad42587589ea7a1a1d6f9bf2b53f"&gt;
                                                    &lt;source media="(min-width: 429px)" srcset="https://www.bgr.com/img/gallery/5-everyday-nasa-inventions-and-electronics-in-your-home/joysticks-1762527270.webp" type="image/webp"&gt;
                            &lt;source media="(max-width: 428px)" srcset="https://www.bgr.com/img/gallery/5-everyday-nasa-inventions-and-electronics-in-your-home/joysticks-1762527270.sm.webp" type="image/webp"&gt;
                        &lt;img class="gallery-image " src="https://www.bgr.com/img/gallery/5-everyday-nasa-inventions-and-electronics-in-your-home/joysticks-1762527270.jpg" loading="lazy" data-slide-url="https://www.bgr.com/2022720/everyday-technology-gadgets-nasa-inventions/" data-post-id="2022720" data-slide-num="5" data-slide-title="5 Everyday NASA Inventions And Electronics In Your Home: Joysticks" alt="Person using a video game controller"&gt;
                    &lt;/source&gt;&lt;/source&gt;&lt;/picture&gt;
                    &lt;span class="gallery-image-credit"&gt;Lee Charlie/Shutterstock&lt;/span&gt;
                    &lt;/div&gt;
				            &lt;div class="columns-holder "&gt;
                &lt;p&gt;In order for astronauts to control spacecraft and equipment while wearing bulky spacesuits, NASA engineers developed joystick technology. Apollo spacecraft used a special joystick with buttons on the hilt. Known as the "picklestick," the joystick sent electrical signals to the Apollo Guidance Computer to give astronauts control of the spacecraft's trajectory. The technology evolved through NASA's programs, and the United States military uses the picklestick and a digital fly-by-wire system in many of its fighter aircraft.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But when it comes to everyday use around the house, joysticks are probably most recognized in the gaming world. They were popularized in the early 1980s on home console controllers, and today joysticks are standard in video game controllers across platforms. Dual joystick controllers allow for the control of characters as well as in-game cameras, and devices like drones utilize joysticks for control as well. The joystick has even evolved into a digital existence, with many mobile games and apps using touch-based controls designed to emulate a joystick.&lt;/p&gt;

            &lt;/div&gt;
            &lt;/div&gt;

    
&lt;/article&gt;                        
            
                            
                           &lt;p id="div-ad-1x1a" class="google-ad-placeholder clear placeholder placeholder-1-1" data-ad-height="any" data-ad-width="any" data-ad-pos="1x1"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

        &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>bgr.com</author><pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 22:17:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMifEFVX3lxTE1ROVdEcVJ5WVZ1VVprb2drQ0ZVaHpGX2RvNEhnU1hSRTFyU3p3a203UzBRQXBNRWpoTVhUNS1WeHRKMXN4QmkwMlFQSnlvVXdvYXdKTXB4bURlNHgycmZURzRJRnZ1V2w3TUN6dU9LZXpOZ0lxcnBsdE5lX0o</guid></item><item><title>生酮饮食安全吗？研究揭示长期生酮饮食的严重副作用-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/is-keto-diet-safe-research-reveals-serious-side-effects-of-long-term-keto-eating/articleshow/125371505.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;p&gt;A new study by researchers at University of Utah Health, published in &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.science.org/doi/10.1126/sciadv.adx2752" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;Science Advances&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, has raised fresh concerns about the long-term safety of the ketogenic diet, one of the world’s most popular approaches for weight loss and metabolic control. While the diet is known for preventing weight gain and improving short-term metabolic markers, the research shows that long-term keto eating may trigger hidden biological changes that disrupt how the body processes fats and sugars. Conducted over many months in mice, the study challenges the widely held belief that extended keto dieting is harmless, revealing metabolic side effects that could carry significant health implications.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="8"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="9"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;The hidden trade-offs of long-term keto diet&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="10"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The ketogenic diet forces the body into ketosis by drastically cutting carbohydrates and increasing fat intake. In this state, the liver produces ketone bodies to fuel the brain and stabilise energy levels. Originally used as a medical therapy for epilepsy, the diet has since grown into a mainstream weight-loss strategy celebrated for quick results and improved blood sugar control.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="12"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="lOvcW vdo_embedd"&gt;&lt;div class="k7lcu"&gt;&lt;p class="efT4r"&gt;Importance of balanced diet for health and wellbeing | Exploring life's every dimension&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="14"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, the new University of Utah Health study suggests that the long-term metabolic consequences of the ketogenic diet may be far more complex than previously understood. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers analysed how prolonged adherence to a high-fat, very low-carbohydrate eating pattern affects the body over extended periods.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="18"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Their findings indicate that, even when the diet helps prevent excessive weight gain and maintains a leaner body profile, it may simultaneously place significant strain on key metabolic systems. Over time, this heavy reliance on dietary fat appears to alter the body’s ability to manage lipids and regulate blood sugar, revealing hidden vulnerabilities that could undermine long-term health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="21"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The body struggled to manage the constant influx of dietary fat, leading to elevated fat levels in the blood and changes in liver function. These shifts hinted at an underlying biological cost that is not immediately apparent during short-term dieting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="23"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="24"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Keto linked to fatty liver disease&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="25"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;One of the most concerning discoveries was the rapid development of fatty liver disease in male mice consuming the ketogenic diet. Fatty liver is a major warning sign of broader metabolic dysfunction and a risk factor for diabetes and heart disease. Interestingly, female mice did not show the same degree of liver fat accumulation, highlighting sex-specific differences that researchers plan to explore in future studies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="29"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to senior author Amandine Chaix, PhD, the liver becomes overwhelmed by the high-fat load, forcing excess fat to build up within liver cells. Over time, this compromises liver function and sets the stage for metabolic disease, despite the mice not gaining significant body weight.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="32"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="33"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Weight loss that hides deeper issues&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="34"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Although the ketogenic diet prevented weight gain in both male and female mice, it did not eliminate deeper metabolic problems. The appearance of lower body weight masked underlying disruptions in glucose regulation and insulin production.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="36"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;After two to three months on the diet, keto-fed mice had unusually low levels of both glucose and insulin when fasting. But when they were given even a small amount of carbohydrates, their blood sugar spiked dramatically and remained elevated for an extended period.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="39"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lead author Molly Gallop, PhD, explained that this indicates an impaired ability to regulate blood sugar. Despite appearing metabolically stable at rest, the mice struggled to handle carbohydrates — a dangerous sign of metabolic inflexibility.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="41"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="42"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Stress inside the pancreas&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="43"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Further investigation revealed that pancreatic beta cells, which produce insulin, were under severe stress. High-fat exposure disrupted how these cells transported and processed proteins, leaving them unable to respond properly when glucose levels rose.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="46"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;This cellular stress likely caused the impaired insulin secretion and unstable blood glucose seen in the mice. Notably, some of these issues reversed once the animals were removed from the ketogenic diet, suggesting that not all effects are permanent — but they are still cause for caution.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="48"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="49"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Implications for human keto dieters&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="50"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Although mice are not humans, the study raises red flags about the long-term metabolic safety of ketogenic diets. Most human studies focus on short-term outcomes such as weight loss or improved glucose control, while long-term biological effects remain largely understudied.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="53"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The new findings highlight that a diet high in fat and extremely low in carbohydrates may strain key organs such as the liver and pancreas if followed for extended periods. They also raise questions about how sex, genetics and lifestyle may influence individual responses to keto.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="55"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="56"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;The bottom line&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="57"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The University of Utah Health study offers an important reminder: while keto can produce impressive short-term results, it is not without risks. Long-term keto eating may trigger hidden metabolic side effects, including fatty liver, impaired blood sugar regulation and cellular stress in key organs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="59"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;As scientists work to better understand the full spectrum of ketogenic diet effects, one message is clear — the diet’s benefits come with trade-offs, and long-term safety is far from guaranteed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="61"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="62"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 21:10:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijAJBVV95cUxOUnVqcHBaRHFlMUJra0FZYnhBakUxX1pCVXpELXJWTFdUcjdkRGxJUUdIYThSTURvMWlmQjliV0Q0S3RLQkRBNTNQUVB1aUtIUHJaWFhtYldHaE5PSHM1dk5XbmFhdmNXN2FXdUxqRHVraU5fa3FDUVptSDAydUpxZUhpUlNxZFR4NXJaZWdIeDJ2eEJGeFcxUHNSS3RMYlhneTc0QjlUYVhwcUZZeDFMcDFrekR6NGdqWXktSEdnVVdkMEV2VW9TVFF6OHR1eF82bWFhMU9xSEVjOEhnZ2pRcDVvNl9sMjF6dUhkYlpmOHEycWVONmQ4UUZCZ0ZWb0VERlVhNEZIZ2VTX0po</guid></item><item><title>4岁男孩被诊断患有儿童痴呆症： “我永远不会听到他的声音” - AOL.com</title><link>https://www.aol.com/articles/4-old-boy-diagnosed-childhood-210000255.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="caas-body"&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure align-caption-with-image"&gt;&lt;div class="no-margin"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="caption-wrapper"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption-collapse"&gt;&lt;p&gt;GoFundMe&lt;/p&gt; Tate was diagnosed with Sanfilippo Syndrome&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;h3&gt;NEED TO KNOW&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul class="caas-list caas-list-bullet"&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tammy McDaid is raising money to secure experimental treatment for her son, Tate, who has a rare and devastating genetic disorder&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sanfilippo Syndrome, often called childhood dementia, causes developmental regression and premature death&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;“My little boy has never spoken a word,” McDaid said, “and now I know I will never get to hear his voice"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;A U.K. mom is racing against the clock to get her son, 4, accepted in a clinical trial to fight his rare, degenerative form of childhood dementia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The next year is quite critical in Tate's life as it's around now that things start to show,” Tammy McDaid told the &lt;a href="https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/cwyn20jg3xwo" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:BBC;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;BBC&lt;/a&gt; about her son, Tate. He was initially diagnosed with &lt;a href="https://people.com/bill-gates-says-he-would-be-diagnosed-with-autism-if-he-were-a-kid-today-8780432" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:autism;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;autism&lt;/a&gt; at age 2, but as his mom, who hails from Swansea, Wales, said, "Deep down I always suspected there was something more.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;An MRI scan in March 2024 showed spaces in Tate's brain that were indicative of dementia, and further testing led to the diagnosis of &lt;a href="https://people.com/her-belly-was-hard-her-diapers-always-full-why-her-mom-knew-something-was-wrong-despite-doctors-dismissals-exclusive-11755313" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Sanfilippo Syndrome;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Sanfilippo Syndrome&lt;/a&gt;. It’s a &lt;a href="https://people.com/mom-thought-baby-facial-feature-was-trait-from-dad-symptom-of-childhood-dementia-exclusive-8642991" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:genetic disorder;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;genetic disorder&lt;/a&gt; that primarily impacts the central nervous system, and causes cognitive, behavioral, and physical symptoms, &lt;a href="https://my.clevelandclinic.org/health/diseases/sanfilippo-syndrome" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Cleveland Clinic;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Cleveland Clinic&lt;/a&gt; explains, which “lead to premature death.” There is &lt;a href="https://people.com/tennessee-make-a-wish-kid-3-received-hot-tub-11808328" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:no cure;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;no cure&lt;/a&gt;, and the only treatment is management of symptoms, which include gastrointestinal and ear, nose, and throat problems, along with intellectual disabilities that worsen over time — hence the nickname “childhood dementia.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure align-caption-with-image"&gt;&lt;div class="no-margin"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="caption-wrapper"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption-collapse"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Getty&lt;/p&gt; Stock image of a mom holding her son's hand.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Children diagnosed with Type A, which Tate has, have a life expectancy of 11 to 19 years. As McDaid wrote in the &lt;a href="https://www.gofundme.com/f/help-give-my-little-boy-a-fighting-chance" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:GoFundMe;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;GoFundMe&lt;/a&gt; established to pay for his care, “My little boy has never spoken a word, and now I know I will never get to hear his voice.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The money McDaid is raising is intended “to explore any possible treatment options abroad,” she wrote. ”These potential trials or therapies could give him more time being mobile &amp;amp; eating food! More days filled with climbing, running, and me living on edge to see where he will escape to next! - but they will be extremely expensive.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Never miss a story — sign up for &lt;a href="https://forms.dotdashmeredith.com/people-news-inline" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:PEOPLE's free daily newsletter;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;PEOPLE's free daily newsletter&lt;/a&gt; to stay up-to-date on the best of what PEOPLE has to offer, from celebrity news to compelling human interest stories.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“If there’s any chance to help him, I have to take it,” McDaid wrote.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While she knows there isn’t a cure, McDaid is hoping to “slow down the regression of [Tate's] mobility, as that is what is going to hit me the hardest," she told the BBC. "He could climb before he could walk. I just want him to be able to do this for as long as possible."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I am so blessed and proud of him. Even though he can't talk, he hugs and kisses me."&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Read the original article on &lt;a href="https://people.com/childhood-dementia-sanfilippo-syndrome-4-year-old-tate-11848011" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:People;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;People&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>AOL.com</author><pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 21:03:49 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMifkFVX3lxTFBfamdZSHdvQXE3Sy1ET1l4b3dvYkpzUzd1eEtJRmhPei1vVWZUTV9hd1pkMEpmMGZWb3NhWDZMaXJNdk5pWnpzMUwtaHNjTS1ERjA2ZnJub0ZKVzVLajY3dTBWVnhZVUotLUpLek1wT1VRQ1NseWlBSHFuR0tKQQ</guid></item><item><title>由营养师创建的7天抗炎高纤维膳食计划- EatingWell</title><link>https://www.eatingwell.com/7-day-anti-inflammatory-high-fiber-meal-plan-11847833</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="mntl-sc-block-universal-table__table-wrapper"&gt;
&lt;table class="mntl-sc-block-universal-table__table"&gt;
&lt;colgroup span="1"&gt;&lt;/colgroup&gt;
&lt;colgroup span="1"&gt;&lt;/colgroup&gt;
&lt;colgroup span="1"&gt;&lt;/colgroup&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th colspan="3" class="mntl-sc-block-universal-table__title"&gt;Meal Plan at a Glance&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th&gt;BREAKFAST/ A.M. SNACK&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th&gt;LUNCH/ P.M. SNACK&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th&gt;DINNER&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;
&lt;tbody data-check="0"&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Frittata, toast &amp;amp; grapes/ Yogurt &amp;amp; raspberries&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Veggie bowls/ Edamame&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Stuffed butternut squash &amp;amp; plums&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Chia pudding/ Energy balls&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Salmon-stuffed avocados &amp;amp; kale salad/ Walnuts&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Lemon chicken &amp;amp; sweet potatoes&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Chia pudding &amp;amp; scrambled eggs/ Ricotta toast&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Bento Box lunch/ Yogurt &amp;amp; plums&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Chickpeas alla Vodka&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Chia pudding/ Smoothie &amp;amp; grapes&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Bento Box lunch/ Edamame&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Pork chops &amp;amp; spinach&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Chia pudding/ Energy ball &amp;amp; orange&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Bento Box lunch/ Walnuts &amp;amp; plum&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Chili&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Smoothie/ Yogurt &amp;amp; plums&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Salmon salad/ Walnuts&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Steak salad &amp;amp; broccolini&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Egg in a hole &amp;amp; grapes/ Energy balls&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Shrimp grain bowls/ Yogurt &amp;amp; raspberries&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Sausage &amp;amp; kale pasta&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_5-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-day-1"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_6-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Day 1  &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure id="mntl-sc-block_7-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image--no-theme no-theme figure-square figure-high-res"&gt; 
&lt;figcaption id="mntl-figure-caption_1-0" class="comp mntl-figure-caption text-utility-100 figure-article-caption"&gt; &lt;span class="figure-article-caption-text"&gt;Cheesy Spinach &amp;amp; Artichoke Stuffed Butternut Squash.&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class="figure-article-caption-owner"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Photographer: Jen Causey, Food Stylist: Margaret Monroe Dickey, Prop Stylist: Priscilla Montiel&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_8-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Breakfast (412 calories) &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_10-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_11-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Morning Snack (145 calories) &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_12-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;li&gt;1 cup raspberries&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;½ cup low-fat plain Greek yogurt&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_13-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_14-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Lunch (673 calories) &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_16-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_17-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Afternoon Snack (64 calories) &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_19-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_20-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Dinner (503 calories) &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_22-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_23-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Daily totals:&lt;/strong&gt; 1,797 cal, 98g fat, 25g saturated fat, 81g protein, 172g carbs, 42g fiber, 1,924mg sodium&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_24-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_25-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;To make it 1,500 calories&lt;/strong&gt;: Omit bread at breakfast and omit A.M. snack.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_26-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_27-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;To make it 2,000 calories&lt;/strong&gt;: Add 1 serving &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/spiced-roasted-walnuts-8756081" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Spiced Roasted Walnuts&lt;/a&gt; to P.M. snack.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_28-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_30-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-day-2"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_31-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Day 2 &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure id="mntl-sc-block_32-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image--no-theme no-theme figure-square figure-high-res"&gt; 
&lt;figcaption id="mntl-figure-caption_2-0" class="comp mntl-figure-caption text-utility-100 figure-article-caption"&gt; &lt;span class="figure-article-caption-text"&gt;Skillet Lemon Chicken with Spinach.&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class="figure-article-caption-owner"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Diana Chistruga&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_33-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Breakfast (452 calories) &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_35-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_36-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Morning Snack (234 calories) &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_38-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_39-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Lunch (477 calories) &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_41-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_42-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Afternoon Snack (183 calories) &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_44-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_45-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Dinner (402 calories) &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_47-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_48-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Daily totals: &lt;/strong&gt;1,748 calories, 101g fat, 26g saturated fat, 77g protein, 156g carbohydrate, 40g fiber, 1,851 mg sodium &lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_49-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_50-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;To make it 1,500 calories&lt;/strong&gt;: Omit P.M. snack. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_51-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_52-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;To make it 2,000 calories&lt;/strong&gt;: Add 2 hard-boiled eggs to P.M snack. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_53-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-day-3"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_54-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Day 3 &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure id="mntl-sc-block_55-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image--no-theme no-theme figure-square figure-high-res"&gt; 
&lt;figcaption id="mntl-figure-caption_3-0" class="comp mntl-figure-caption text-utility-100 figure-article-caption"&gt; &lt;span class="figure-article-caption-text"&gt;Chickpeas alla Vodka.&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class="figure-article-caption-owner"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Photographer: Jen Causey, Food Stylist: Emily Nabors Hall, Prop Stylist: Phoebe Hauser&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_56-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Breakfast (452 calories) &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_58-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_59-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Morning Snack (259 calories) &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_61-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_62-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Lunch (497 calories) &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_64-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_65-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Afternoon Snack (144 calories) &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_66-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;li&gt;½ cup low-fat plain Greek yogurt&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;2 plums&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_67-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_68-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Dinner (495 calories) &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_70-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_71-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Daily totals: &lt;/strong&gt;1,847 calories, 71g fat, 29g saturated fat, 93g protein, 201g carbohydrate, 38g fiber, 1,923 mg sodium &lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_72-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_73-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;To make it 1,500 calories&lt;/strong&gt;: Omit A.M. snack.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_74-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_75-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;To make it 2,000 calories&lt;/strong&gt;: Add 1 medium orange to breakfast and add ½ avocado to lunch.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_76-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-day-4"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_77-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Day 4 &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure id="mntl-sc-block_78-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image--no-theme no-theme figure-square figure-low-res"&gt; 
&lt;figcaption id="mntl-figure-caption_4-0" class="comp mntl-figure-caption text-utility-100 figure-article-caption"&gt; &lt;span class="figure-article-caption-text"&gt;Cucumber Salad, Hummus &amp;amp; Pita Bento Box Lunch.&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_79-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Breakfast (452 calories) &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_81-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_82-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Morning Snack (358 calories) &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_84-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_85-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Lunch (497 calories) &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_87-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_88-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Afternoon Snack (64 calories) &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_90-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_91-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Dinner (460 calories) &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_93-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_94-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Daily totals: &lt;/strong&gt;1,831 calories, 78g fat, 23g saturated fat, 93g protein, 194 carbohydrate, 40g fiber, 1,691 mg sodium &lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_95-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_96-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;To make it 1,500 calories&lt;/strong&gt;: Omit Anti-Inflammatory Lemon-Blueberry Smoothie at A.M. snack.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_97-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_98-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;To make it 2,000 calories&lt;/strong&gt;: Add ½ avocado to lunch and add 1 hard-boiled egg to P.M. snack.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_99-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-day-5"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_100-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Day 5 &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure id="mntl-sc-block_101-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image--no-theme no-theme figure-square figure-high-res"&gt; 
&lt;figcaption id="mntl-figure-caption_5-0" class="comp mntl-figure-caption text-utility-100 figure-article-caption"&gt; &lt;span class="figure-article-caption-text"&gt;Sweet Potato &amp;amp; Black Bean Chili.&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class="figure-article-caption-owner"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Photographer: Antonis Achilleos, Food Stylist: Emily Nabors Hall, Prop Stylist: Kay Clarke&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_102-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Breakfast (452 calories) &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_104-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_105-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Morning Snack (295 calories) &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_107-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_108-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Lunch (497 calories) &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_110-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_111-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Afternoon Snack (243 calories) &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_113-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_114-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Dinner (323 calories) &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_116-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_117-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Daily totals: &lt;/strong&gt;1,810 calories, 70g fat, 20g saturated fat, 73g protein, 244g carbohydrate, 51g fiber, 1,662 mg sodium &lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_118-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_119-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;To make it 1,500 calories&lt;/strong&gt;: Omit A.M. snack.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_120-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_121-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;To make it 2,000 calories&lt;/strong&gt;: Add ½ avocado to lunch.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_122-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-day-6"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_123-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Day 6  &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure id="mntl-sc-block_124-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image--no-theme no-theme figure-square figure-high-res"&gt; 
&lt;figcaption id="mntl-figure-caption_6-0" class="comp mntl-figure-caption text-utility-100 figure-article-caption"&gt; &lt;span class="figure-article-caption-text"&gt;Grilled Flank Steak with Tomato Salad.&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_125-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Breakfast (401 calories) &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_127-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_128-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Morning Snack (144 calories) &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_129-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;li&gt;½ cup low-fat plain Greek yogurt&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;2 plums&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_130-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_131-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Lunch (627 calories) &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_133-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_134-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Afternoon Snack (183 calories) &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_136-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_137-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Dinner (501 calories) &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_139-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_140-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Daily totals: &lt;/strong&gt;1,856 calories, 97g fat, 16g saturated fat, 90g protein, 149g carbohydrate, 35g fiber, 1,443 mg sodium &lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_141-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_142-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;To make it 1,500 calories&lt;/strong&gt;: Omit A.M. snack and P.M. snack.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_143-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_144-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;To make it 2,000 calories&lt;/strong&gt;: Add 2 scrambled eggs to breakfast.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_145-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-day-7"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_146-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Day 7  &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure id="mntl-sc-block_147-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image--no-theme no-theme figure-square figure-high-res"&gt; 
&lt;figcaption id="mntl-figure-caption_7-0" class="comp mntl-figure-caption text-utility-100 figure-article-caption"&gt; &lt;span class="figure-article-caption-text"&gt;"Egg in a Hole" Peppers with Avocado Salsa.&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_148-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Breakfast (390 calories) &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_150-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_151-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Morning Snack (234 calories) &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_153-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_154-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Lunch (429 calories) &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_156-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_157-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Afternoon Snack (146 calories) &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_158-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;li&gt;1 cup raspberries&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;½ cup low-fat plain Greek yogurt&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_159-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_160-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Dinner (578 calories) &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_162-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_163-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Daily totals: &lt;/strong&gt;1,777 calories, 71g fat, 15g saturated fat, 99g protein, 207g carbohydrate, 40g fiber, 2,143 mg sodium &lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_164-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_165-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;To make it 1,500 calories&lt;/strong&gt;: Omit A.M. snack. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_166-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_167-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;To make it 2,000 calories&lt;/strong&gt;: Add 1 serving &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/spiced-roasted-walnuts-8756081" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Spiced Roasted Walnuts&lt;/a&gt; to P.M. snack.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_168-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div id="mntl-sc-block_170-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-faq mntl-sc-block-universal-faq"&gt;&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-faqs-903ebeed-81a7-4abf-95e8-139f979c76d0"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;h2 class="mntl-sc-block-universal-faq__title"&gt;Frequently Asked Questions&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;noscript id="universal-faq-noscript_1-0" class="comp universal-faq-noscript mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block-universal-faq__content_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block-universal-faq__content mntl-accordion js-accordion"&gt;
&lt;li class="accordion__item js-accordion-item " data-ordinal="1"&gt;
&lt;p tabindex="0" class="accordion__header js-accordion-trigger" id="mntl-accordion__item_1-0-section-0"&gt;
&lt;svg class="icon icon-chevron accordion__icon"&gt;
&lt;use xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xlink:href="#icon-chevron" href="#icon-chevron"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;
&lt;/svg&gt;
&lt;span class="accordion__title"&gt;​​Is it OK to mix and match meals if there is one I do not like?&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="accordion__body"&gt;
&lt;div id="mntl-accordion__content_1-0" class="comp mntl-accordion__content"&gt; &lt;div class="faq-accordion__item-answer"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yes! This meal plan is meant to serve as inspiration. It doesn’t need to be followed exactly to reap the benefits. When choosing recipes, we made sure to check the calories, fiber, protein and sodium to align with the parameters of this plan and be within our sodium limits. If you’re making a recipe swap, it may be helpful to choose a recipe with similar calories, fiber, protein and sodium levels. For more inspiration, check out these delicious &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/you-just-started-anti-inflammatory-diet-recipes-to-make-first-8770807" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;anti-inflammatory recipes. &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="accordion__item js-accordion-item " data-ordinal="2"&gt;
&lt;p tabindex="0" class="accordion__header js-accordion-trigger" id="mntl-accordion__item_2-0-section-1"&gt;
&lt;svg class="icon icon-chevron accordion__icon"&gt;
&lt;use xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xlink:href="#icon-chevron" href="#icon-chevron"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;
&lt;/svg&gt;
&lt;span class="accordion__title"&gt;Can I eat the same breakfast or lunch every day?&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="accordion__body"&gt;
&lt;div id="mntl-accordion__content_2-0" class="comp mntl-accordion__content"&gt; &lt;div class="faq-accordion__item-answer"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Definitely, it’s fine to eat the same breakfast or lunch every day. The breakfasts range from 390 to 452 calories while the lunches span 429 to 673 calories. These ranges are fairly close, though if you’re closely monitoring your calories or other nutrients, like protein, you may want to adjust a snack or two.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="accordion__item js-accordion-item " data-ordinal="3"&gt;
&lt;p tabindex="0" class="accordion__header js-accordion-trigger" id="mntl-accordion__item_3-0-section-2"&gt;
&lt;svg class="icon icon-chevron accordion__icon"&gt;
&lt;use xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xlink:href="#icon-chevron" href="#icon-chevron"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;
&lt;/svg&gt;
&lt;span class="accordion__title"&gt;Why is there not a modification for 1,200 calories?&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="accordion__body"&gt;
&lt;div id="mntl-accordion__content_3-0" class="comp mntl-accordion__content"&gt; &lt;div class="faq-accordion__item-answer"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We no longer provide modifications for 1,200-calorie days in our meal plans. The 2020-2025 Dietary Guidelines for Americans suggests that limiting calories to 1,200 per day is too low for most people to meet their nutritional needs, plus it’s unsustainable for long-term health and well-being.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="1"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="accordion__item js-accordion-item " data-ordinal="4"&gt;
&lt;p tabindex="0" class="accordion__header js-accordion-trigger" id="mntl-accordion__item_4-0-section-3"&gt;
&lt;svg class="icon icon-chevron accordion__icon"&gt;
&lt;use xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xlink:href="#icon-chevron" href="#icon-chevron"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;
&lt;/svg&gt;
&lt;span class="accordion__title"&gt;What is an anti-inflammatory diet?&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="accordion__body"&gt;
&lt;div id="mntl-accordion__content_4-0" class="comp mntl-accordion__content"&gt; &lt;div class="faq-accordion__item-answer"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The anti-inflammatory diet focuses on eating foods high in antioxidants like fruits, vegetables, nuts, seeds and beans, as well as healthy fats such as extra virgin olive oil and omega-3 fatty acids found in fish, walnuts and flaxseeds. It limits consuming foods that may promote inflammation, such as ultra-processed foods and added sugar.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;noscript id="accordion-noscript_1-0" class="comp accordion-noscript mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_171-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-how-fiber-helps-reduce-inflammation"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_172-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; How Fiber Helps Reduce Inflammation &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_173-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Some &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/what-is-inflammation-8766645" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;inflammation&lt;/a&gt; can be beneficial to our bodies, like acute inflammation that happens when you are recovering from an injury or infection. However, chronic inflammation is a low-grade, more long-term type of inflammation that is harder to notice and can lead to some negative health implications like higher chronic disease risk. Fortunately, eating an anti-inflammatory diet can help remedy some of the &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/7669105/sneaky-signs-you-could-have-inflammation/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;symptoms&lt;/a&gt; that go with chronic inflammation, like joint pain, brain fog and low energy levels.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_174-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_175-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/287742/10-amazing-health-benefits-of-eating-more-fiber/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Fiber&lt;/a&gt; is a nutrient that most people don’t get enough of, but it’s really important for our health. It helps keep you regular and also supports a healthy gut microbiome, which has been linked with improved immune function, better heart health, reduced risk of cognitive decline and more. Eating enough fiber not only benefits your gut, but additionally can help reduce inflammation. Research shows that higher fiber intake may lower inflammation markers.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="2"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_176-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="mntl-sc-block_177-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-callout mntl-sc-block-universal-callout theme-generic" data-tracking-id="mntl-sc-block-callout" data-tracking-container="true"&gt; &lt;h3 class="mntl-sc-block-universal-callout__heading"&gt;How We Create Meal Plans&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;div class="mntl-sc-block-universal-callout__body"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Registered dietitians thoughtfully create &lt;em&gt;EatingWell’s&lt;/em&gt; meal plans to be easy-to-follow and delicious. Each meal plan meets specific parameters depending on the health condition and/or lifestyle goal it is targeting and is analyzed for accuracy using the nutrition database, ESHA Food Processor. As nutritional needs differ from person to person, we encourage you to use these plans as inspiration and adjust as you see fit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>EatingWell</author><pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 20:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihwFBVV95cUxNZWZmaUYyOUpRTU5KYXBVQ3ZJWWp1MFdHQnh3cV8zRVZKbWNJY1Y4N2ZXekIzNEFZcjgxNVhLd2t6TU9pYmd4eC1aeWhSREU2SHBjc3VJZkxLZ3pXR1N1cVlBUkswSlpYdi1sZ1FwQUpOX1pvNGp0VVVMWlR1UTVaNm1fVXgzRVU</guid></item><item><title>这只可爱、毛茸茸的毛毛虫有毒，出现在德克萨斯州--MySA</title><link>https://www.mysanantonio.com/lifestyle/outdoors/article/fuzzy-venomous-asp-caterpillars-texas-21169271.php</link><description>&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;
    
        
&lt;/body&gt;
</description><author>MySA</author><pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 20:28:28 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiqgFBVV95cUxNLXFCX254Uk9yMktJbTRyWmpMMjVJNlBDVzVLb2VEN1BqbXQ5eVR4LTFFSDNET25NdXJBS2NfMnlnb19FakJpNU5MTVZSWHNLbmp4ekxfV0dKekEzbXhoelVBcnVJUzFhMlVrZDFFY3pxbWdfT0lvVWZGVkcwQ1hLYUlSYzFMMFBsMTNzcEh1eHoxamJ5QzIycml1MjZwVlRwbjhsU3Uwd3hzQQ</guid></item><item><title>生育危机使美国陷入瘫痪......专家概述了如果不紧急解决关键因素的黑暗未来-每日邮报</title><link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-15239723/research-sperm-fertility-crisis-RFK.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div itemprop="articleBody"&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Dr Shanna Swan has dedicated more than two decades of her life to researching America's declining sperm counts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;An environmental medicine doctor at Mount Sinai Medical Center in &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/new_york/index.html" id="mol-7a58ba80-b5c7-11f0-88d5-8501c13cf82e" class=""&gt;New York City&lt;/a&gt;, she has written what are regarded as the most influential studies on the topic. She's authored books and spoken publicly about the issue and subsequent decline in fertility. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;So, when Dr Swan saw that her research had been cited by Health and Human Services Secretary &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/rfk-jr/index.html" id="mol-073860b0-b503-11f0-8458-b7d1037117f2" class=""&gt;Robert F Kennedy Jr&lt;/a&gt; in the days after his comments on October 16, she was thrilled.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/health/article-15202593/American-men-lower-sperm-count-RFK-Jr.html"&gt;RFK Jr said at a press briefing&lt;/a&gt;: &lt;span&gt;'Today, the average teenager in this country has 50 percent of the sperm count, 50 percent of the testosterone, as a 65-year-old man.'  &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span&gt;It was not clear whether RFK Jr was comparing teenagers today to 65-year-olds today or when 65-year-olds were teenagers themselves. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Following the comments, an HHS spokesman told Daily Mail that RFK Jr's comments were based on Dr Swan's &lt;a class="" rel="nofollow noreferrer noopener" target="_blank" href="https://academic.oup.com/humupd/article/23/6/646/4035689"&gt;2017 paper&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Dr Swan told the Daily Mail: 'I am glad that sperm decline is getting some attention... and, you know, I am concerned about &lt;a target="_self" href="/health/fertility/index.html" id="mol-0745ce30-b503-11f0-8458-b7d1037117f2" class=""&gt;fertility&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'I've been doing this research since the late 1990s... so, I am happy to see when anybody, particularly people in authority, recognize that this is a problem.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Dr Shanna Swan, the expert behind the most influential sperm studies, is pictured above at a gala in Los Angeles on October 29, 2014&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    
    
    &lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Dr Swan was the co-author on the  &lt;a class="" rel="nofollow noreferrer noopener" target="_blank" href="https://academic.oup.com/humupd/article/23/6/646/4035689?login=false"&gt;2017 study&lt;/a&gt; that first warned of the 'spermageddon' crisis that researchers say could upend men's fertility. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Analyzing data from 1973 to 2011, the team found that sperm counts had plummeted 52 percent on average during that period, leaving fewer sperm available to fertilize an egg. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;It's one of the leading culprits behind &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/health/article-15047185/ultraprocessed-food-sex-drive.html"&gt;rising cases of male infertility&lt;/a&gt; and researchers blame sedentary lifestyles, higher obesity rates and toxic chemicals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;At the same time, the US total fertility rate has also declined, dropping from 2.52 births per woman in 1970 to 1.62 in 2023, the latest date available, although experts link this to other factors like increased focus on career and concerns over costs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;And other papers have since suggested that sperm counts are not falling by the same magnitude, although they say there also appears to be a modest decline.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The HHS spokesman also cited a separate &lt;a class="" rel="nofollow noreferrer noopener" target="_blank" href="https://academic.oup.com/humupd/article/23/6/646/4035689?login=false"&gt;follow-up 2022 meta-analysis &lt;/a&gt;by Dr Swan that led her to warn sperm counts could reach zero, on average, by 2045, forcing couples to seek fertility treatment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Dr Swan said she was not contacted by HHS for details on her research, although she was pleased to hear it was being cited.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;However, she said it was not entirely accurate, based on her work, to say that the sperm counts of teenage boys today are half of those of 65-year-old men alive today.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The researcher said that what RFK Jr likely meant was that teenagers today have 50 percent lower sperm counts, as well as lower testosterone, today than today's 65-year-olds did when they were teenagers.&lt;/p&gt;
    
    
    &lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Shown above is a stock image of a pregnant woman with her partner&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Testosterone and sperm counts are linked. Doctors say that higher levels of the hormone drive the body to produce more sperm.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Dr Swan said: 'I don't take issue [with RFK Jr's comments].&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Overall... sperm counts have declined by about one percent a year since about 1973, and, if you look more recently, from 2000, then the rate of decline has increased quite a bit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'So, what we are seeing is an increasing rate of decline; they're declining faster in recent years. It looks like testosterone levels are declining too.' &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Warning over the risks posed by falling sperm counts, she said: 'A while ago there was a Danish study that looked at chances of conceiving and how long it would take to get pregnant if sperm count was at a certain level.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'What it showed very dramatically was when sperm got to about 40 million [sperm per milliliter of semen], chances dropped off very fast, down to zero. So, zero sperm, of course, your chance of getting pregnant is zero. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'But that chance climbs up, and when it gets to about 75 million [sperm per milliliter of semen], it levels off, and then it's all good. It doesn't matter if it's 75 or 150 million. It does the job.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'But now, we're getting closer to that point where it's definitely taking longer to get pregnant. Not impossible, but taking longer.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In an interview with&lt;a class="" rel="noreferrer noopener" target="_blank" href="https://www.theguardian.com/society/2021/mar/28/shanna-swan-fertility-reproduction-count-down"&gt; The Guardian&lt;/a&gt; in 2021, Dr Swan warned that sperm counts may be so low that 'most couples may have to use assisted reproduction by 2045.' &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Robert F Kennedy Jr with Donald Trump at the press conference in October, where he warned about the decline in sperm and testosterone levels in men&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Symptoms of low testosterone include low sex drive, fatigue, decreased muscle mass, depression, and weak bones, among others&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Other researchers, however, have previously raised concerns over Dr Swan's research, saying that doctors can find it difficult to accurately count sperm in a sample.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Scientists say the factors driving a reduction in sperm counts and testosterone are broadly similar.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Both are affected by poor diets, obesity, environmental hazards like chemicals and a lack of exercise.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;a class="" rel="nofollow noreferrer noopener" target="_blank" href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0015028224019538"&gt;One paper published this year &lt;/a&gt;by researchers at the Cleveland Clinic and Case Western University suggested sperm counts had dropped by about 0.35 million sperm per milliliter of semen every year globally between 1970 and 2018, when results were adjusted for region and fertility status, in what the researchers called a 'modest annual decline'.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Unadjusted results from the same paper, however, estimated that sperm counts had remained level in the US between 1970 and 2018.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The researchers behind the study said that they did not believe that even a modest decline was likely to lead to a rise in infertility rates.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The paper suggested that the average sperm count was currently around 78 million sperm per milliliter of semen in the US.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;This was well above the threshold where doctors say a man would be considered infertile, at about 15 million sperm per milliliter of semen, and within the World Health Organization's estimate of a healthy sperm count, between 15 and 250 million sperm per milliliter.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Testosterone levels peak in young adulthood, around age 20, but decline by about one percent annually after age 30. This data is from a University of Wisconsin study &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Estimates suggest about nine percent of men in the US are infertile. For a man to be diagnosed with infertility, it means he has a low sperm count or sperm that is not of sufficient quality.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Globally, &lt;a class="" rel="nofollow noreferrer noopener" target="_blank" href="https://bmcpublichealth.biomedcentral.com/articles/10.1186/s12889-023-16793-3"&gt;estimates suggest&lt;/a&gt; that the number of men experiencing infertility has risen 76 percent since the 1990s.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Among women, 13.4 percent are infertile in the US, according to the CDC. Researchers at &lt;a class="" rel="noreferrer noopener" target="_blank" href="https://www.hopkinsmedicine.org/news/newsroom/news-releases/2022/06/us-infertility-rate-plateaus"&gt;Johns Hopkins University&lt;/a&gt; say this level has remained largely unchanged in recent years. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Overall, about one in six couples in the US struggle to conceive. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Dr Jeff Singer, a senior fellow at the Cato Institute in the Department of Health Policy Studies, previously told the Daily Mail: 'What I can say is that Secretary Kennedy has taken a couple of real studies and turned them into a sensational sound bite.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'There's some evidence of modest downward trends across generations, likely tied to lifestyle and health factors, but nothing close to Kennedy's doomsday framing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'His claim badly distorts the data, confusing normal aging with supposed generational collapse.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;America's fertility rate has been in decline since the early 2000s.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Latest data showed the rate was 54.5 births per 1,000 women aged 15 to 44 years in 2023, a three percent decrease from the previous year. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The number of babies born in the US declined to 3.6 million births registered in 2023, the latest year available, down two percent from the previous year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Experts warn that the US is heading for an 'underpopulation crisis' by 2050, when too few people are born to support its current economic system.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;They say that if birth rates continue at their current rate, the natural-born population of the US could be extinct in just 500 years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
            

            
            
            
            
            &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Daily Mail</author><pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 19:58:27 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilwFBVV95cUxNTmJDNldYS3JqUHA1bUpGeTIxVThIa3NReU9CdGVXSTdRWWthdF9EdTRnRXFoUzlrVm5nYTJkQldMbGRORUJfMkZGdUU5VGFVRjZTX1FPQUtodXlPRE9DQVdWYS1NQjBUejBkdGQ4dENsOGZPdzctdUNKbHE1U0paSDBZYUtBMVZJVFRFdFVrYUNmNnRybEdV</guid></item><item><title>50岁后保持真正快乐的人通常会练习这7种日常仪式- VegOut</title><link>https://vegoutmag.com/lifestyle/s-people-who-stay-genuinely-happy-after-well-into-their-50s-and-60s-usually-practice-these-7-daily-rituals/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="page__content mt-4"&gt;
							&lt;p&gt;I used to think happiness after 50 was about having things figured out. Like there was some magical wisdom download that happened when you hit middle age.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Turns out, it's less about having answers and more about having practices.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The people I know who seem genuinely content in their fifties and beyond aren't necessarily the ones who made all the right choices or avoided hardship. They're the ones who showed up for themselves in small, consistent ways.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Today, I want to walk through seven daily rituals that these folks tend to share. Nothing groundbreaking. Nothing that requires a complete life overhaul. Just simple practices that compound over time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;1) They move their bodies without obsessing over it&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here's what I've noticed about the happiest people over 50: they've stopped treating exercise like punishment for existing in a body.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My grandmother is 72 and walks to the food bank every Saturday morning where she volunteers. Not because she's trying to hit 10,000 steps or burn calories, but because she likes the ritual of it. The movement is just part of the activity she loves.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That's the pattern I keep seeing. Movement becomes something you do because it feels good, not because you're trying to fix something.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Maybe it's a morning stretch routine. Maybe it's gardening. Maybe it's dancing in the kitchen while cooking dinner.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The key is that it's integrated into life rather than being this separate thing you have to force yourself to do. There's no guilt when you skip a day, and no medal-chasing when you don't.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Your body at 50 is different than it was at 30, and the people who stay happy seem to have made peace with that reality.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;2) They've learned to say no without explaining themselves&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This one took me way too long to figure out.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For years, I said yes to everything. Every social obligation, every work project, every favor asked of me. And then I'd resent the hell out of it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The happy 50-somethings I know have mastered the art of the simple no. No elaborate justification. No fake excuses. Just "that doesn't work for me" or "I'm not available."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It sounds easy, but it requires you to get comfortable with other people being disappointed in you. Which, as Rudá Iandê writes in "Laughing in the Face of Chaos," "Being human means inevitably disappointing and hurting others, and the sooner you accept this reality, the easier it becomes to navigate life's challenges."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I've mentioned this book before, but his insights about letting go of people-pleasing really shifted something for me. The book inspired me to start viewing my time as actually finite rather than just theoretically finite.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When you're in your twenties, you can kind of pretend you have unlimited energy and time. By 50, that illusion is harder to maintain. The people who stay happy seem to have accepted this and adjusted accordingly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;3) They maintain friendships that feel effortless&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Not all of them. Not even most of them. But a few.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The genuinely happy older folks I know have stopped trying to maintain friendships that feel like work. They've let some relationships fade, and they've stopped feeling guilty about it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What they've kept are the connections that feel easy. The friend you can not talk to for six months and then pick up right where you left off. The person who doesn't need you to perform or pretend.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My partner is 43, and watching him navigate friendships has taught me something important. He has maybe three or four people he actually stays in close contact with. But those relationships are deep. There's no small talk, no catching up for the sake of it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Quality over quantity becomes less of a cliché and more of a necessity as you age. You just don't have the bandwidth to maintain surface-level connections anymore.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And honestly? That's a feature, not a bug.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;4) They cook for themselves regularly&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This might sound boring, but hear me out.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The happiest people over 50 I know tend to cook. Not elaborate Instagram-worthy meals necessarily, but real food that they actually enjoy eating.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There's something grounding about feeding yourself well. It's a small act of self-respect that happens multiple times a day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When I make a big batch of lentil soup or spend Sunday afternoon prepping vegetables from the farmers market, I'm not just making food. I'm creating conditions for my future self to thrive.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The people who stay happy after 50 seem to have internalized this. They're not grabbing takeout every night or eating sad desk lunches. They're actually sitting down, even if just for 15 minutes, to eat something they prepared.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It doesn't have to be fancy. My grandmother's favorite meal is toast with mashed avocado and tomatoes. But she makes it herself, plates it nicely, and sits at her table to eat it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That small ritual matters more than you'd think.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;5) They've developed a practice that isn't about productivity&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Photography for me. Vinyl collecting. Reading fiction that has nothing to do with work.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Happy people over 50 have something they do purely because it brings them joy, not because it's building toward anything.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is harder than it sounds in a culture that monetizes everything. We're trained to turn hobbies into side hustles, to optimize our leisure time, to make everything count toward some larger goal.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But the people who maintain genuine happiness have protected at least one activity from that impulse. They have something they do just because.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My partner brews kombucha on weekends. It's not for Instagram. He's not selling it. He just likes the process of experimenting with flavors and watching the fermentation happen.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When I asked him why he does it, he just shrugged and said "because it's interesting."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That's it. That's the whole reason.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Find your version of that.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;6) They've stopped arguing with reality&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is probably the biggest difference I've noticed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;People who stay happy after 50 have largely given up on the "should" game. Things should be different. People should behave better. Life should be fair.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They've accepted that reality just is what it is, and arguing with it only creates suffering.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I spent my early thirties trying to convince people to go vegan through sheer force of moral argument. I had statistics, footage, all the ammunition I needed to prove I was right.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And I was miserable. More importantly, I wasn't actually helping anyone change.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It wasn't until I stopped fighting reality, stopped insisting the world should already be the way I wanted it to be, that I actually became effective. And much, much happier.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The happy older folks I know have all arrived at some version of this acceptance. They're not passive or resigned. They still work toward things. But they've stopped exhausting themselves by arguing with what already is.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;7) They get outside almost every day&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Even if it's just for ten minutes. Even if it's just to their balcony or front porch.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The pattern is consistent: people who maintain happiness after 50 have some form of daily contact with the outdoors.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There's research backing this up, of course. Nature exposure reduces stress, improves mood, all the things you'd expect. But I think it's more than that.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Getting outside breaks the loop of your own thoughts. It reminds you that you're part of something larger than your immediate concerns and anxieties.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I live in Venice Beach, and my favorite time of day is early morning when I walk down to the water with my coffee. Not to exercise. Not to be productive. Just to remember that the ocean was here before me and will be here after me, and that puts my deadline stress into perspective.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The people who stay genuinely happy seem to have found their version of this. Maybe it's tending a garden. Maybe it's sitting on a park bench. Maybe it's walking their dog.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The specific activity matters less than the regularity of it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Final thoughts&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;None of these rituals are revolutionary. You've probably heard versions of all of them before.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But here's what I've learned from watching people who actually stay happy after 50: it's not about knowing what to do. It's about actually doing it, consistently, without making it into a big dramatic thing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These aren't New Year's resolutions. They're just small choices, repeated daily, that compound into a life that feels good to live.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You don't need to implement all seven tomorrow. Pick one. See how it feels.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The people who stay happy after 50 didn't get there by overhauling their entire lives at once. They got there by showing up for themselves in small ways, over and over, until those ways became who they are.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="vegou-quiz-after-article" id="vegou-2596135571"&gt;&lt;p&gt;				 &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong data-start="380" data-end="431"&gt;If You Were a Healing Herb, Which Would You Be?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p data-start="380" data-end="651"&gt;Each herb holds a unique kind of magic — soothing, awakening, grounding, or clarifying.&lt;br data-start="521" data-end="524"&gt;This 9-question quiz reveals the healing plant that mirrors your energy right now and what it says about your natural rhythm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="653" data-end="734"&gt;✨ Instant results. Deeply insightful.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt; 			&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;						&lt;/div&gt;
					&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>VegOut</author><pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 19:02:24 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi1gFBVV95cUxPVmN6Y2JMUXBwdmhwQjVmSlFYa3hwdHpyeDNfM0I5bVFQUklnR2QxeEpoZ3R1U3ZPRjdqNjlkR3owVmI2MEJoQkctdm8xNGtJY3l5VDdudFlWUXRHTXZZd2JMVmJadG0zS09sVVJaOXR4aU9mU1lIRGNLT0huc2NydFVONElsUEVtdERLV1U5UG9NWFBkb0JUSlBHeE9DWmFvR1p3UmVWX3F3VkZ4Zm9mNnhiZS0tQzh0NmszTHJjdkZWdkxyUmhVdnpGSTJQMGhyNUhrU1pB</guid></item></channel></rss>