<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>GNews Health</title><link>https://news.google.com/</link><description></description><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>联合国表示，如果美国对艾滋病项目的资助不被取代，到2029年将有数百万人死亡-美联社新闻 | UN says if US funding for HIV programs is not replaced, millions more will die by 2029 - AP News</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiqgFBVV95cUxPeHZ5S3VPb1dpQXM1SGpITlJwcVZ2cUx3Y3hHTld0eWxyUUo1N3ZPS21rWTFZb1pfZWVDWmptbllrLUhWLWJVSDNsRFFFUzRyUW1qemtNRUcyN1Z3ekhESEdTQ3huOThoS3dKSF9ud0hNSDNOakNxaGJwSVZTUXVLc3NGbXpmV0g2M0wtU2JYZ1gzNExWMnRWbmhfN05Ydk9XaDRzVXBJeGhuQQ?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>AP News</author><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 13:57:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiqgFBVV95cUxPeHZ5S3VPb1dpQXM1SGpITlJwcVZ2cUx3Y3hHTld0eWxyUUo1N3ZPS21rWTFZb1pfZWVDWmptbllrLUhWLWJVSDNsRFFFUzRyUW1qemtNRUcyN1Z3ekhESEdTQ3huOThoS3dKSF9ud0hNSDNOakNxaGJwSVZTUXVLc3NGbXpmV0g2M0wtU2JYZ1gzNExWMnRWbmhfN05Ydk9XaDRzVXBJeGhuQQ</guid></item><item><title>帮助：许多跌倒是可以预防的。这些建议可能会有所帮助-《西雅图时报》 | Here to help: Many falls are preventable. These tips can help - The Seattle Times</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMirgFBVV95cUxPdVJwbjZFSUIzZzctT0JtQTJRZ09Ud281eTJPc3Q3cFJZSWcwTUJsSGNyVHNfVVhKUkxyREx4Vm54ZmNsZWZRd2hWUmpCWTFrdTFTZkpGaVJrd01rVExDX21yTXFwVW02ODlvOXpHMWVfR2tiVGpnNDVBdG5BclBJZDdoOHdTT19uUUFwTGZZbzdyZ0lxR1VZVlVfQ2t5eFdGZEowUlYzNnVUaC02bkE?oc=5</link><description>&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMirgFBVV95cUxPdVJwbjZFSUIzZzctT0JtQTJRZ09Ud281eTJPc3Q3cFJZSWcwTUJsSGNyVHNfVVhKUkxyREx4Vm54ZmNsZWZRd2hWUmpCWTFrdTFTZkpGaVJrd01rVExDX21yTXFwVW02ODlvOXpHMWVfR2tiVGpnNDVBdG5BclBJZDdoOHdTT19uUUFwTGZZbzdyZ0lxR1VZVlVfQ2t5eFdGZEowUlYzNnVUaC02bkE?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;Here to help: Many falls are preventable. These tips can help&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Seattle Times&lt;/font&gt;</description><author>The Seattle Times</author><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 13:00:05 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMirgFBVV95cUxPdVJwbjZFSUIzZzctT0JtQTJRZ09Ud281eTJPc3Q3cFJZSWcwTUJsSGNyVHNfVVhKUkxyREx4Vm54ZmNsZWZRd2hWUmpCWTFrdTFTZkpGaVJrd01rVExDX21yTXFwVW02ODlvOXpHMWVfR2tiVGpnNDVBdG5BclBJZDdoOHdTT19uUUFwTGZZbzdyZ0lxR1VZVlVfQ2t5eFdGZEowUlYzNnVUaC02bkE</guid></item><item><title>正如鲜为人知的副作用所揭示的那样，人们分享了“Ozempic sex”的经验- UNILAD | People share experiences with ‘Ozempic sex’ as little-known side effect revealed - UNILAD</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMijwFBVV95cUxQNHppUEE3VFN6TEJJTE1rLUhPWllXYWdxMzhBYjRfWFAwRGxmQzYzb09rNGJacXU1SlVIVV85aFR1QTNjaHQyaHEtaVk2aU5kYlJ4MmZsYXVHQ1dIVktKOEFPN3lVaElOa3BDSE1YNlI3enJqU1hXOHZ4dC1RY0RmaEdYcGZmdzVsZGE0M09kRQ?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ozempic users have opened up about an unexpected side-effect of using the medication when it comes to the bedroom. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;Falling into the category of GLP-1 medications, &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.unilad.com/ozempic"&gt;Ozempic&lt;/a&gt; is intended to be used by people with type two diabetes to help lower their blood sugar levels.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;However, it has also become a popular medication used by people who are trying to lose weight, with the &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" target="_blank" rel="noopener" href="https://www.ozempic.com/why-ozempic/what-is-ozempic.html"&gt;website&lt;/a&gt; for the medication explaining: "Ozempic is a medicine for adults with type 2 diabetes that, along with diet and exercise, may improve blood sugar. While not for weight loss, Ozempic may help you lose some weight."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="floating-video-player_container__u4D9_"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;As the &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.unilad.com/drugs"&gt;drug&lt;/a&gt; becomes more popular, users have been opening up about some of the little-known side effects they've noticed, including &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.unilad.com/news/health/ozempic-side-effects-trapped-gas-wind-reddit-767921-20250620"&gt;gas&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.unilad.com/news/health/ozempic-face-mouth-weight-loss-364139-20250627"&gt;sagging skin. &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="article-image_articleImage__eyzAn"&gt;&lt;cite class="image-credit_imageCredit__YMlqS"&gt;Ozempic users have reported a whole host of side effects from the drug (George Frey/Bloomberg via Getty Images)&lt;/cite&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;In one &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.unilad.com/reddit"&gt;Reddit&lt;/a&gt; thread on the r/Ozempic page, one user reported an impact they'd noticed to their sex drive as they wrote: "My sex drive is completely gone."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;Another thread on the site asked users if they'd noticed a change in libido, prompting one woman to reply: "Mine has left the building. I miss it!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;A second responded: "Same. Got nothing. It’s like it has totally just quit and left."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;"I have been on Ozempic for about 3-4 months and I feel like my &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.unilad.com/sex-and-relationships"&gt;sex&lt;/a&gt; drive has disappeared. Anyone else found this?," another Redditor asked as they started a different thread.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;Interestingly, other Ozempic users have reported the opposite result, with one writing: "Mines definitely improved, my hubby loves it. Lol. I went years without any desire at all."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;"Mine has improved greatly, and it was good before," added another.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;Speaking&lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" target="_blank" rel="noopener" href="https://www.wsj.com/health/wellness/weight-loss-drugs-ozempic-wegovy-side-effects-sex-0210c42b?st=es7rd6zzgxu9f2p&amp;amp;reflink=desktopwebshare_permalink"&gt; to &lt;/a&gt;The Wall Street Journal, Dr. James Simon, a reproductive endocrinologist, OBGYN and clinical professor at George Washington University, explained that the impact of GLP-1 mediations on sex drive may come down to biology.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="article-image_articleImage__eyzAn"&gt;&lt;cite class="image-credit_imageCredit__YMlqS"&gt;Some Ozempic users have reported a loss in libido (Getty Stock Photo)&lt;/cite&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;He said: “These drugs do work in the same places that pleasure and sexual interest are located in the human brain—male and female."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;Dr. Taylor Kohn, a fellow in male reproductive medicine and surgery in the Department of Urology at Baylor College of Medicine, also told the publication that in the long run, the cardiovascular benefits associated with weight loss would likely have a positive impact on anyone experiencing erectile dysfunction, saying: “We know that if you reverse cardiovascular disease, erectile dysfunction improves as well.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;When contacted for comment, Novo Nordisk, which manufactures Ozempic, told UNILAD: "Patient safety is of the utmost importance to Novo Nordisk, and we recommend patients take these medications for their approved indications and under the supervision of a healthcare professional.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;"We continuously collect safety data on our marketed GLP-1 medicines and work closely with the authorities to ensure patient safety. As part of this work, we continue to monitor reports of adverse drug reactions through routine pharmacovigilance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;"We recommend that any patient experiencing side effects while taking GLP-1 RA medicines, including Wegovy and Ozempic (semaglutide injection), report them to their healthcare provider and via the &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" target="_blank" rel="noopener" href="https://yellowcard.mhra.gov.uk/"&gt;MHRA Yellow Card scheme. &lt;/a&gt;"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>UNILAD</author><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 10:58:42 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijwFBVV95cUxQNHppUEE3VFN6TEJJTE1rLUhPWllXYWdxMzhBYjRfWFAwRGxmQzYzb09rNGJacXU1SlVIVV85aFR1QTNjaHQyaHEtaVk2aU5kYlJ4MmZsYXVHQ1dIVktKOEFPN3lVaElOa3BDSE1YNlI3enJqU1hXOHZ4dC1RY0RmaEdYcGZmdzVsZGE0M09kRQ</guid></item><item><title>世界贸易组织（ WTOP ）医学博士表示，缩口带的趋势带来了严重的健康风险 | Mouth taping trend poses serious health risks, says Md. doctor - WTOP</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiowFBVV95cUxPRWMtUDBqWFNVdTJtZnZrM0RUb0w3c0ktTE5yWTM2SktWQnhSeGd1T2RhVC1zMnRoYTNVckNtcjJQZ2MwY2ZaN05ha1lqNi16UDNnUmtLU2xzLTN4MlJqRWpySnhtcTlkVG13QXdGakUxM0I3bmlYTEE3T3BWNDdwZUJ3V0dibzdObGRNTUYwNnhLYW1TTzN0OWZ1NHJOUFBRdkRJ?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="schema-summary"&gt;Mouth taping trend to improve sleep quality, athletic performance poses serious health risks, says Maryland doctor.&lt;/p&gt;

            &lt;div id="Entry-content" class="entry-content Entry-content "&gt;
                                                
                                
                &lt;p&gt;The social media trend of mouth taping to improve sleep quality and ultimately boost athletic performance is largely unproven, and potentially dangerous, says Dr. Jennifer Gourdin, a sports medicine physician with Kaiser Permanente in Silver Spring, Maryland.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Mouth taping is when you put a piece of tape across your lips to encourage nose breathing when you’re sleeping,” Gourdin told WTOP. “It’s currently trending on Instagram and TikTok, claiming to improve sleep quality, oxygen levels and reduce snoring.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Gourdin, whose handle on Instagram and TikTok is @drjthesportsdoc, said many of those engaging in mouth taping are athletes. “This is a big deal in the sports field, because improved sleep quality is associated with improved muscle recovery and improved athletic performance.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The theory behind it is that nose breathing during sleep is more efficient, Gourdin said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“When you breathe through your nose, you filter the air. It’s humidified and warm, so you’re less likely to wake up in the middle of the night with dry mouth or bad breath, and you’re less likely to wake up fatigued,” she said. “However, there’s not any strong evidence currently to suggest that this true.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And, the practice of mouth taping poses several risks to many people.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“If you have something like sleep apnea or some other underlying sleep condition, if you have nasal congestion, a deviated septum, or allergy symptoms, taping your mouth could lead to more restricted breathing,” said Gourdin. “It could also lead to dangerous drops in your oxygen levels while you’re sleeping, and in some individuals, it can also lead to panic attacks or anxiety attacks.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A &lt;a href="https://journals.plos.org/plosone/article?id=10.1371/journal.pone.0323643" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;May study in the PLOS One journal,&lt;/a&gt; which reviewed 10 studies on mouth taping, found “very minor improvement in certain outcomes” for people with mild sleep apnea. But the research also found that “there are potential serious detrimental health outcomes to those with nasal obstruction,” who use oral taping as a means to ameliorate their mouth breathing, sleep apnea or sleep-disordered breathing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Gourdin said there are currently no FDA-approved mouth tapes that are safe for people to use.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Instead of resorting to mouth taping, to improve sleep quality, Gourdin suggests trying a cool, calm, dark environment, limiting screen time, and turning of the television and putting your phone away before bed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Have a sleep routine that you go through every night to help you wind down. Limit your intake of caffeine or alcohol before bed. And, for some patients, sleeping on your side can help improve your breathing,” Gourdin said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
                
                
                &lt;p class="After-content"&gt;
                                    &lt;/p&gt;

            &lt;p class="single-page__signature bottom"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Get breaking news and daily headlines delivered to your email inbox by signing up &lt;a href="https://wtop.com/newsletter-signup/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="single-page__signature bottom"&gt;© 2025 WTOP. All Rights Reserved. This website is not intended for users located within the European Economic Area.&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;/div&gt;
            &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>WTOP</author><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 09:22:17 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiowFBVV95cUxPRWMtUDBqWFNVdTJtZnZrM0RUb0w3c0ktTE5yWTM2SktWQnhSeGd1T2RhVC1zMnRoYTNVckNtcjJQZ2MwY2ZaN05ha1lqNi16UDNnUmtLU2xzLTN4MlJqRWpySnhtcTlkVG13QXdGakUxM0I3bmlYTEE3T3BWNDdwZUJ3V0dibzdObGRNTUYwNnhLYW1TTzN0OWZ1NHJOUFBRdkRJ</guid></item><item><title>裸盖菇素能否成为长寿的神奇成分？ -研究发现 | Could Psilocybin Be The Magical Ingredient For A Longer Life? - Study Finds</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMipAFBVV95cUxNSkU3em1DNjZHZU40VkxYQndncFpzOF9FMmhUNTlQT2ZyTjNYRzduTFlMREsydkpMZ05XTUV2cURXNVRUWlhscWtSVFE0WkVvRFNpYTRNT2ZWNzN4VEFyWHNhQ2FlVXNwNGM1MUxZbEtpVUluSENEd1VtUjBRc01yMVNiSFRFNzFBQ0ZKdUpveVpLanpOWG83NU1MMEc2R3hQcEx5TQ?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content"&gt;&lt;div class="post-featured-image"&gt;&lt;picture&gt;
&lt;source type="image/webp" srcset="https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/07/Psilocybin-magic-mushrooms-1200x800.jpg.webp"&gt;&lt;/source&gt;
&lt;img src="https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/07/Psilocybin-magic-mushrooms-1200x800.jpg" alt="Psilocybin magic mushrooms"&gt;
&lt;/picture&gt;
&lt;p class="post-featured-image-caption"&gt;(Photo by Cannabis_Pic on Shutterstock)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-breakthrough-mouse-study-hints-at-psychedelic-compound-yielding-possible-anti-aging-drugs"&gt;Breakthrough Mouse Study Hints At Psychedelic Compound Yielding Possible Anti-Aging Drugs&lt;/h2&gt;







&lt;div class="wp-block-group has-octonary-background-color has-background is-layout-constrained wp-block-group-is-layout-constrained"&gt;
&lt;h3 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-in-a-nutshell"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;In A Nutshell&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;



&lt;ul class="wp-block-list"&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lab studies found that psilocin, the active form of psilocybin, extended the lifespan of human fibroblast cells by up to 57% while preserving telomere length.&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;Aged mice given monthly doses of psilocybin showed a 60% better survival rate than untreated mice, with signs of improved fur quality.&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;The study suggests psilocybin may slow aging at the cellular level by boosting SIRT1, reducing oxidative stress, and preserving DNA stability.&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;Experts caution that these findings are preliminary and must be tested in humans to confirm safety and benefits.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ATLANTA —&lt;/strong&gt; Magic mushrooms could be the unexpected fountain of youth. A groundbreaking study reveals that psilocybin, the mind-altering compound found in these fungi, might do more than produce psychedelic experiences. The research suggests it could actually help people live longer lives. Researchers have discovered this controversial substance extends cellular lifespan and improves survival rates in aging mice, opening an entirely new frontier in anti-aging research.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Most research has focused on &lt;a href="https://studyfinds.org/tag/psilocybin/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;psilocybin’s ability&lt;/a&gt; to treat &lt;a href="https://studyfinds.org/psychedelic-magic-mushrooms-psilocybin-depression/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;depression&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://studyfinds.org/psychedelic-therapy-benefits-risks/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;anxiety&lt;/a&gt;, and other &lt;a href="https://studyfinds.org/psychedelics-mental-health-mysical-experience/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;mental health conditions&lt;/a&gt;. But this study reveals the compound might be working at a much more fundamental level, literally slowing down the aging process itself.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“There was overwhelming clinical evidence that it has benefits for multiple disease indications,” lead researcher Louise Hecker, PhD, tells StudyFinds. “But very little was known about how it affects the body outside the brain.” Our full Q&amp;amp;A with Dr. Hecker can be found at the end of our article.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Published in the journal &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41514-025-00244-x" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;npj Aging&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;, the research represents the first experimental evidence that psilocybin could function as a “geroprotective agent,” essentially a substance &lt;a href="https://studyfinds.org/tag/anti-aging/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;that protects against aging&lt;/a&gt;. A drug already showing promise for treating mental illness might also help people maintain their health and vitality as they age.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Hecker, a former associate professor of medicine at Emory University, and her team tested what they call the “psilocybin-telomere hypothesis.” This theory suggests that psilocybin’s remarkable ability to treat a wide range of conditions, from depression to neurodegenerative diseases, might stem from its effects &lt;a href="https://studyfinds.org/cutting-calories-slow-cell-aging/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;on cellular aging&lt;/a&gt; rather than just brain chemistry.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;div class="wp-block-group has-octonary-background-color has-background is-layout-constrained wp-block-group-is-layout-constrained"&gt;
&lt;figure class="wp-block-image size-large"&gt;&lt;picture fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" class="wp-image-142776"&gt;
&lt;source type="image/webp" srcset="https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/06/Psilocybin-mushrooms-1200x800.jpg.webp 1200w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/06/Psilocybin-mushrooms-475x317.jpg.webp 475w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/06/Psilocybin-mushrooms-768x512.jpg.webp 768w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/06/Psilocybin-mushrooms-400x267.jpg.webp 400w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/06/Psilocybin-mushrooms-378x252.jpg.webp 378w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/06/Psilocybin-mushrooms-276x184.jpg.webp 276w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/06/Psilocybin-mushrooms-600x400.jpg.webp 600w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px"&gt;&lt;/source&gt;
&lt;img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" src="https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/06/Psilocybin-mushrooms-1200x800.jpg" alt="Holding psychedelic psilocybin mushrooms" srcset="https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/06/Psilocybin-mushrooms-1200x800.jpg 1200w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/06/Psilocybin-mushrooms-475x317.jpg 475w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/06/Psilocybin-mushrooms-768x512.jpg 768w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/06/Psilocybin-mushrooms-400x267.jpg 400w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/06/Psilocybin-mushrooms-378x252.jpg 378w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/06/Psilocybin-mushrooms-276x184.jpg 276w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/06/Psilocybin-mushrooms-600x400.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px"&gt;
&lt;/picture&gt;
&lt;figcaption class="wp-element-caption"&gt;Researchers believe psilocybin could be used to treat numerous age-related conditions, if the study’s results are confirmed in human trials. (Photo by Cannabis_Pic on Shutterstock)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;



&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-laboratory-cells-live-57-longer-with-psilocin-treatment"&gt;Laboratory Cells Live 57% Longer With Psilocin Treatment&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The research team examined how &lt;em&gt;psilocin&lt;/em&gt;, the active form of psilocybin that forms when the body breaks down the original compound, affects human cells in laboratory conditions. Using human lung fibroblasts, which are cells that naturally age and stop dividing over time, scientists discovered something remarkable.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Cells treated with psilocin lived significantly longer than untreated cells. At a moderate dose (10 μM), psilocin extended cellular lifespan by 29 percent. When researchers increased the dose to 100 μM, cells lived 57 percent longer than normal.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Researchers write that the psilocin-treated cells remained healthy and active for extended periods, continuing to divide and reproduce normally before eventually reaching the natural end of their lifespan. Importantly, the cells didn’t become &lt;a href="https://studyfinds.org/category/cancer/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;cancerous&lt;/a&gt; — they simply &lt;a href="https://studyfinds.org/intermittent-fasting-slow-aging/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;aged more slowly.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The mechanism behind this cellular age reversal involves several key biological processes. Psilocin increased levels of SIRT1, a protein crucial for regulating cellular aging, &lt;a href="https://studyfinds.org/tag/metabolism/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;metabolism&lt;/a&gt;, and stress responses. It also reduced &lt;a href="https://studyfinds.org/tag/oxidative-stress/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;oxidative stress&lt;/a&gt;, the cellular damage caused by harmful molecules called free radicals. And it helped preserve &lt;a href="https://studyfinds.org/tag/telomeres/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;telomeres&lt;/a&gt;, the protective caps on chromosomes that naturally shorten with age.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;div class="wp-block-group has-octonary-background-color has-background is-layout-constrained wp-block-group-is-layout-constrained"&gt;
&lt;figure class="wp-block-image size-large"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/Telomeres-1-1200x900.jpg" alt="Telomeres are found on both ends of chromosomes, 3d illustration." class="wp-image-130628" srcset="https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/Telomeres-1-scaled.jpg 1200w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/Telomeres-1-475x356.jpg 475w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/Telomeres-1-768x576.jpg 768w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/Telomeres-1-400x300.jpg 400w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="wp-element-caption"&gt;Telomeres are “caps” found on both ends of chromosomes. Telomere length is affected by lifestyle and has direct impact on human health and lifespan. (Image by nobeastsofierce on Shutterstock)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;



&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-aging-mice-show-60-better-survival-rates"&gt;Aging Mice Show 60% Better Survival Rates&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Laboratory cell studies can be promising, but the real test came when researchers moved to living animals. The team studied female mice that were 19 months old, roughly equivalent to humans in their &lt;a href="https://studyfinds.org/tag/older-adults/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;early to mid-60s&lt;/a&gt;. This age was deliberately chosen to test whether psilocybin could work as a realistic anti-aging intervention for older adults.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The mice received either psilocybin or a placebo once per month for 10 months. The dosing strategy started with a lower amount (5 mg/kg) for the first treatment, followed by higher doses (15 mg/kg) for the remaining nine treatments.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;By the end of the study period, 80 percent of the psilocybin-treated mice were still alive, compared to only 50 percent of the control group. That represents a 60 percent improvement in survival rates.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Beyond just living longer, the psilocybin-treated mice &lt;a href="https://studyfinds.org/how-magic-mushrooms-work/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;appeared healthier&lt;/a&gt;. Researchers observed visible improvements in the animals’ fur quality, including new hair growth and less graying compared to the control group.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;div class="wp-block-group has-octonary-background-color has-background is-layout-constrained wp-block-group-is-layout-constrained"&gt;
&lt;figure class="wp-block-image size-large"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/07/Psilocybin-mice-1200x600.jpg" alt="Psilocybin study on mice" class="wp-image-143525" srcset="https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/07/Psilocybin-mice-1200x600.jpg 1200w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/07/Psilocybin-mice-475x238.jpg 475w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/07/Psilocybin-mice-768x384.jpg 768w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/07/Psilocybin-mice-400x200.jpg 400w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="wp-element-caption"&gt;Representative images of mice prior to treatment (19 month) and after the final treatment (28 month) with vehicle or psilocybin. Red arrows indicate regions where hair growth and/or hair color changes were observed. (Credit: Kato et al / npj Aging)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;



&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-how-psilocybin-slows-aging-at-the-cellular-level"&gt;How Psilocybin Slows Aging at the Cellular Level&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;How does a psychedelic compound manage to &lt;a href="https://studyfinds.org/tag/aging/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;slow aging&lt;/a&gt;? The answer likely lies in psilocybin’s interaction with serotonin receptors, particularly the 5-HT2A receptor. These receptors are distributed throughout the body in various cell types including fibroblasts, neurons, heart cells, immune cells, and blood vessel cells.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;When psilocybin activates these receptors, it appears to trigger an array of cellular changes that promote health and &lt;a href="https://studyfinds.org/category/longer-life/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;longevity&lt;/a&gt;. The compound increases production of antioxidant enzymes that protect cells from damage, while simultaneously ramping up SIRT1 activity, a key player in cellular maintenance and repair.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;This systemic approach might explain why psilocybin seems effective against such a wide range of conditions. Rather than targeting specific diseases, it may be addressing the underlying aging processes that make people more susceptible to illness in the first place.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-major-questions-remain-before-human-use"&gt;Major Questions Remain Before Human Use&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Significant questions remain before this research could translate to human applications. The mouse study used only female mice, so researchers don’t yet know whether &lt;a href="https://studyfinds.org/tag/anti-aging/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;the anti-aging effects&lt;/a&gt; apply equally to males. The optimal dosing schedule, age of treatment initiation, and long-term safety of repeated psilocybin use for aging also need further investigation.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Safety considerations are particularly important given that some research suggests delayed cellular aging could theoretically affect cancer risk, though the current study found no evidence of this problem. The researchers noted that treated cells eventually stopped dividing naturally rather than becoming cancerous.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;div class="wp-block-group has-octonary-background-color has-background is-layout-constrained wp-block-group-is-layout-constrained"&gt;
&lt;figure class="wp-block-image size-large"&gt;&lt;picture decoding="async" class="wp-image-143526"&gt;
&lt;source type="image/webp" srcset="https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/07/Psilocin-1200x912.jpg.webp 1200w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/07/Psilocin-475x361.jpg.webp 475w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/07/Psilocin-768x584.jpg.webp 768w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/07/Psilocin-400x304.jpg.webp 400w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px"&gt;&lt;/source&gt;
&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/07/Psilocin-1200x912.jpg" alt="Psilocin molecule" srcset="https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/07/Psilocin-1200x912.jpg 1200w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/07/Psilocin-475x361.jpg 475w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/07/Psilocin-768x584.jpg 768w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/07/Psilocin-400x304.jpg 400w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px"&gt;
&lt;/picture&gt;
&lt;figcaption class="wp-element-caption"&gt;Psilocin molecule. (Credit: Bacsica on Shutterstock)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://studyfinds.org/tag/psilocybin/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Psilocybin&lt;/a&gt; remains a Schedule I controlled substance in the United States, making research difficult and clinical use currently impossible outside of approved trials. The doses used in the mouse study were based on amounts given to humans in clinical trials for other conditions, but optimal anti-aging doses haven’t been established.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Despite these limitations, the research opens an entirely new avenue for &lt;a href="https://studyfinds.org/tag/aging/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;aging research&lt;/a&gt; and potentially therapeutic intervention. The idea that a single compound could address multiple aspects of aging — from cellular health to oxidative stress to DNA protection — is certainly a change to the typical approaches that target individual age-related diseases.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“Given the plethora of positive clinical outcomes already observed for &amp;gt;150 clinical trials, I am very confident that these findings can eventually be translated to humans,” says Hecker, who is now an associate professor at Baylor College of Medicine.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Rather than waiting for people to develop specific conditions and then treating those diseases individually, psilocybin could potentially be used to slow the aging process itself. &lt;a href="https://studyfinds.org/tag/magic-mushrooms/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Magic mushrooms&lt;/a&gt;, once relegated to counterculture experimentation, may hold keys to helping humanity live longer, healthier lives.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Disclaimer:&lt;/strong&gt; This article summarizes findings from an early-stage preclinical study. The results were obtained in laboratory cells and aged mice and have not yet been tested in humans. Psilocybin remains a controlled substance in many countries and is not approved for anti-aging use outside of regulated clinical trials&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;div class="wp-block-group has-octonary-background-color has-background is-layout-constrained wp-block-group-is-layout-constrained"&gt;
&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-studyfinds-q-amp-a-with-lead-researcher-louise-hecker"&gt;StudyFinds’ Q&amp;amp;A With Lead Researcher Louise Hecker&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What first sparked your team’s interest in testing psilocybin for aging rather than psychiatric conditions?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;LH:&lt;/strong&gt; My workout buddy kept asking me questions about psilocybin. Non-scientists always think scientists know everything about all things science. But I initially knew nothing about psilocybin. So I told him I would do some reading on pubmed – the only acceptable platform for scientists to find information. I was immediately blown away by what was known and also what was not known about psilocybin. There was overwhelming clinical evidence that it has benefits for multiple disease indications. But very little was known about how it affects the body outside the brain. One paper (based on an idea) stood out on the “psilocybin-telomere hypothesis” – which postulates that psilocybin interventions may quantifiably impact telomere length. I thought that this could offer a potential explanation for its efficacy across a wide range of clinical indications. This hypothesis is based on a large corpus of studies linking mental health biological aging markers: positive psychological states are associated with longer telomeres and negative psychological states are associated with shorter telomeres. But this “theory” had no scientific evidence to support it. I realized, I can actually test this!&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What was the biggest surprise when you saw the cell lifespan results?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;LH:&lt;/strong&gt; That psilocybin treatment led to such a dramatic impact on cellular life extension and increased survival in aged mice, even when administered late in life. Also that the mice “looked” healthier – that grew back hair and white hair grew back in black.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How confident are you that these effects might translate to humans?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;LH:&lt;/strong&gt; Given the plethora of positive clinical outcomes already observed for &amp;gt;150 clinical trials, I am very confident that these findings can eventually be translated to humans.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;figure class="wp-block-image aligncenter size-full is-resized"&gt;&lt;picture decoding="async" class="wp-image-143529"&gt;
&lt;source type="image/webp" srcset="https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/07/Louise-Heckler.png.webp 1158w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/07/Louise-Heckler-316x475.png.webp 316w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/07/Louise-Heckler-768x1154.png.webp 768w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/07/Louise-Heckler-1022x1536.png.webp 1022w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/07/Louise-Heckler-400x601.png.webp 400w" sizes="(max-width: 1158px) 100vw, 1158px"&gt;&lt;/source&gt;
&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/07/Louise-Heckler.png" alt="Louise Hecker, PhD," srcset="https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/07/Louise-Heckler.png 1158w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/07/Louise-Heckler-316x475.png 316w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/07/Louise-Heckler-768x1154.png 768w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/07/Louise-Heckler-1022x1536.png 1022w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/07/Louise-Heckler-400x601.png 400w" sizes="(max-width: 1158px) 100vw, 1158px"&gt;
&lt;/picture&gt;
&lt;figcaption class="wp-element-caption"&gt;Louise Hecker, PhD, senior author and lead researcher, and former associate professor at Emory University, where the research was initiated and funded. Hecker is currently an associate professor at Baylor College of Medicine (Credit: Louise Hecker)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Could psilocybin’s impact on SIRT1 and oxidative stress explain its mental health benefits too?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;LH:&lt;/strong&gt; Absolutely.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Do you think the telomere-preserving effects could have side effects, such as increased cancer risk?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;LH:&lt;/strong&gt; This is certainly a risk and something that we need to carefully monitor moving forward. Additional studies are needed to evaluate this.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How do you respond to concerns about repeated psychedelic use in an aging population?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;LH:&lt;/strong&gt; An effective anti-aging treatment that could be administered to adults during late life could have significant clinical potential. The dose utilized in mice was modeled based on a clinical trial in patients ranging from 29 and 70 years (three patients were &amp;gt;65 years), where no serious adverse events were reported at the study endpoint or the post-study follow-up (98 days)&lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41514-025-00244-x#ref-CR24" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;&lt;sup&gt;24&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/a&gt;; These findings support the feasibility of psilocybin treatment in older adults. Further, the FDA’s designation of psilocybin as a “breakthrough therapy” underscores its safety profile, as minimal adverse effects have been reported &lt;sup&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41514-025-00244-x#ref-CR25" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;25&lt;/a&gt;,&lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41514-025-00244-x#ref-CR26" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;26&lt;/a&gt;,&lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41514-025-00244-x#ref-CR27" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;27&lt;/a&gt;,&lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41514-025-00244-x#ref-CR28" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;28&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;. However, additional studies are warranted to identify optimized protocols for therapeutic efficacy, including the age of treatment initiation, frequency and dose of treatments, and to determine if treatment impacts maximal lifespan.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What are the biggest regulatory or funding barriers you face to moving this to a human trial?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;LH:&lt;/strong&gt; The schedule I designation remains a significant barrier for research and subsequently clinical development. Further, this impacts funding. The overwhelming majority of psilocybin studies have been from private funding or foundations rather than federal funding. This unfortunately limits research progress.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What do you wish the public would understand about the real state of psilocybin science?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;LH: &lt;/strong&gt;That what we already know about psilocybin is quite amazing! But there is so much more that we do not understand about how it works and it’s potential. It will be important for the federal government to recognize the importance of such work to help propel research progress forward.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Anything else you’d like to add?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;LH:&lt;/strong&gt; This is such an exciting finding, and we hope to share more of our findings with the public soon.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;



&lt;div class="wp-block-group has-quaternary-background-color has-background is-layout-constrained wp-block-group-is-layout-constrained"&gt;
&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-paper-summary"&gt;Paper Summary&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;h4 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-methodology"&gt;Methodology&lt;/h4&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Researchers conducted both laboratory cell studies and animal experiments to test psilocybin’s effects on aging. In cell studies, they treated human lung and skin fibroblasts with psilocin at various doses and measured how long the cells continued to divide before reaching senescence. For animal studies, they gave 19-month-old female mice either psilocybin or placebo once monthly for 10 months, starting with 5 mg/kg for the first dose and using 15 mg/kg for subsequent treatments. The researchers measured survival rates, observed physical changes, and analyzed various cellular markers of aging.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h4 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-results"&gt;Results&lt;/h4&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Psilocin treatment extended cellular lifespan by 29% at moderate doses and 57% at higher doses in laboratory studies. The treated cells showed delayed senescence, increased SIRT1 levels, reduced oxidative stress, and preserved telomere length. In mice, psilocybin treatment resulted in 80% survival compared to 50% in the control group, along with visible improvements in fur quality and reduced graying. The effects appeared to work through serotonin receptor activation and involved multiple anti-aging pathways.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h4 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-limitations"&gt;Limitations&lt;/h4&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The study used only female mice, so sex-specific effects remain unknown. The research was exploratory in nature, and researchers were not blinded to treatment groups due to logistical constraints with handling a controlled substance. The optimal dosing schedule, treatment duration, and long-term safety of repeated psilocybin use for anti-aging purposes require further investigation. The study also didn’t measure maximum lifespan effects or determine the ideal age for treatment initiation.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h4 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-funding-and-disclosures"&gt;Funding and Disclosures&lt;/h4&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The research was supported by the Imagine, Innovate and Impact (I3) Award from Emory School of Medicine, the Georgia CTSA NIH award, a grant from the Emory Woodruff Health Sciences Center for Health in Aging, and Veterans Administration Health System funding. The authors declared no competing interests. Psilocybin and psilocin were obtained from Cayman Chemical under a DEA license.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h4 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-publication-information"&gt;Publication Information&lt;/h4&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The study was published in &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41514-025-00244-x" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;npj Aging&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;, volume 11, article number 55, in 2025. The paper was titled “&lt;em&gt;Psilocybin treatment extends cellular lifespan and improves survival of aged mice&lt;/em&gt;” and was authored by Kosuke Kato, Jennifer M. Kleinhenz, Yoon-Joo Shin, Cristian Coarfa, Ali J. Zarrabi, and Louise Hecker from institutions including Emory University, Baylor College of Medicine, and the Atlanta VA Healthcare System. The paper was received on December 9, 2024, and accepted on June 2, 2025.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Study Finds</author><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 06:58:19 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipAFBVV95cUxNSkU3em1DNjZHZU40VkxYQndncFpzOF9FMmhUNTlQT2ZyTjNYRzduTFlMREsydkpMZ05XTUV2cURXNVRUWlhscWtSVFE0WkVvRFNpYTRNT2ZWNzN4VEFyWHNhQ2FlVXNwNGM1MUxZbEtpVUluSENEd1VtUjBRc01yMVNiSFRFNzFBQ0ZKdUpveVpLanpOWG83NU1MMEc2R3hQcEx5TQ</guid></item><item><title>美国援助削减：南非艾滋病毒/艾滋病患者担心治疗- BBC | US aid cuts: South Africa's HIV/Aids patients worry about treatment - BBC</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiWkFVX3lxTE9wckIwZk1ZQjN0Ui1aUnQxZGtudVozMi1tUGpNS2x6Tk9WUElyU1lhX0lUY3l6R3dHOGQ3SkpmMmVELUtVRkhXMHFoNWZUQWNPWGJpQ3BCNG5BQdIBX0FVX3lxTE1IQW9FMTgwMF9ZRTg0dDRpeDFuSjhnQ2JVTzE3bExKdzZtQ1IyQW9hMldSbXR5aUVIa3VXSzAxVGRVNHhDNFVwRFd4UF9vZ09hU3ZIRHplX2ZubS1vV0Nv?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article&gt;&lt;p data-component="headline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 fDtfvH"&gt;&lt;h1 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 dfvxux"&gt;The US helped successfully tackle Aids - now cuts put that at risk&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="byline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="byline-new" class="sc-801dd632-0 eSlECZ"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="byline-new-contributors" class="sc-801dd632-12 jSIeFi"&gt;&lt;div class="sc-801dd632-5 kRoBHa"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;span class="sc-801dd632-7 lasLGY"&gt;Mayeni Jones&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="sc-801dd632-8 hwLppI"&gt;&lt;span&gt;BBC News, Johannesburg&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 kVRMhO"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="hero-image" class="sc-d1200759-1 kycbVO"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20250701-150711-e3d94715db-web-2.24.1-1/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-d1200759-0 dkIvM hide-when-no-script"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/8aeb/live/f3bc2cb0-5cbf-11f0-a847-6f5cde5d04a4.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/8aeb/live/f3bc2cb0-5cbf-11f0-a847-6f5cde5d04a4.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/8aeb/live/f3bc2cb0-5cbf-11f0-a847-6f5cde5d04a4.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/8aeb/live/f3bc2cb0-5cbf-11f0-a847-6f5cde5d04a4.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/8aeb/live/f3bc2cb0-5cbf-11f0-a847-6f5cde5d04a4.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/8aeb/live/f3bc2cb0-5cbf-11f0-a847-6f5cde5d04a4.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/8aeb/live/f3bc2cb0-5cbf-11f0-a847-6f5cde5d04a4.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/8aeb/live/f3bc2cb0-5cbf-11f0-a847-6f5cde5d04a4.jpg.webp" loading="eager" alt="Reuters A glove-wearing nurse takes a blood sample from a child for an HIV test while the child's mother looks on at a clinic in Diepsloot, north of Johannesburg, South Africa, 12 March2025" class="sc-d1200759-0 dvfjxj"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-d1200759-2 gwFzuU"&gt;Reuters&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Gugu used to collect her antiretrovirals from a USAID-funded clinic in downtown Johannesburg.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;But when President Trump's cuts to aid funding were announced earlier this year, she and thousands of other HIV-positive patients across South Africa suddenly faced an uncertain future.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Gugu was lucky, the clinic where she got the medication that helps suppress her symptoms contacted her before it closed down.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;"I was one of the people who was able to get their medication in bulk. I usually collect a three-month prescription. But before my clinic closed, they gave me nine months' worth of medication."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;She will run out of antiretrovirals (ARVs) in September, and then plans on going to her local public hospital for more.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;A former sex worker, the 54-year-old found out she was HIV-positive after she'd quit the industry.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Ten years ago she got a chesty cough, and initially thought it was tuberculosis. She went to a doctor who told her she had a chest infection and treated her for it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;But when the treatment failed, she went to a clinic to get an HIV test.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;"By then I already assumed that I was HIV-positive, and I told the nurse this."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;She was right, and she has been on ARVs ever since. We're not using her real name at her request.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;She currently works as a project coordinator for an NGO.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;"We help pregnant sex workers get their ARVs, to ensure their children are born HIV-negative. We also do home visits to make sure that the mothers take their medication on time, and to look after their babies when they go for their monthly check-ups."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Many HIV-positive sex workers in South Africa relied on private clinics funded by the US government's now-defunct aid agency, USAID, to get their prescriptions and treatments.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;But most of the facilities closed after US President Donald Trump cut most foreign aid earlier this year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;In a  report due to be released on Thursday, the UN body in charge of fighting HIV/Aids does not single out the US, but says that drastic cuts from a number of donors have sent shockwaves around the world, and &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.unaids.org/en/resources/presscentre/pressreleaseandstatementarchive/2025/july/20250710_global-aids-update-media-advisory" class="sc-f9178328-0 bGFWdi"&gt;the "phenomenal progress" in tackling the illness risks being reversed&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;"New HIV infections have been reduced by 40% since 2010, and 4.4 million children have been protected from acquiring HIV since 2000. More than 26 million lives have been saved," UNAIDS says, warning that if the world does not act, there could be an extra six million new HIV infections and four million Aids-related deaths by 2029.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Gugu believes that many sex workers could be discouraged from going to public hospitals for their HRVs..&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;"The problem with going to public hospitals is the time factor. In order to get serviced at these facilities, you have to arrive at 4 or 5am, and they may spend the whole day waiting for their medication. For sex workers, time is money," Gugu says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;She adds that she recently went to her local clinic with some friends to register her details and build a relationship with staff.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;"The nurse who attended to us was very rude. She told us there was nothing special about sex workers."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;She thinks this could lead to many sex workers defaulting on their medication, "especially because their hospital files contain a lot of personal information, and the concern is that sometimes the nurses at these local clinics aren't always the most sensitive in dealing with this kind of information."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;According to the UN, the US cuts to HIV funding could reverse some of the gains made by what has been called one of the most successful public health interventions in history.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Scientists in the UK-based &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.thelancet.com/journals/lancet/article/PIIS0140-6736(25)01186-9/fulltext" class="sc-f9178328-0 bGFWdi"&gt;Lancet medical journal&lt;/a&gt; last month estimated that USAID funding directly reduced Aids deaths by 65%, or 25.5 million, over the past two decades.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 hoQmHM"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-d1200759-1 kycbVO"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20250701-150711-e3d94715db-web-2.24.1-1/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-d1200759-0 dkIvM hide-when-no-script"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/2175/live/d7846cc0-5cc8-11f0-960d-e9f1088a89fe.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/2175/live/d7846cc0-5cc8-11f0-960d-e9f1088a89fe.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/2175/live/d7846cc0-5cc8-11f0-960d-e9f1088a89fe.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/2175/live/d7846cc0-5cc8-11f0-960d-e9f1088a89fe.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/2175/live/d7846cc0-5cc8-11f0-960d-e9f1088a89fe.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/2175/live/d7846cc0-5cc8-11f0-960d-e9f1088a89fe.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/2175/live/d7846cc0-5cc8-11f0-960d-e9f1088a89fe.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/2175/live/d7846cc0-5cc8-11f0-960d-e9f1088a89fe.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Getty Images Standing at a podium, George W. Bush, in a suit, turns his head as South Africa's Thandazile Darby and Dr Helga Holst, both seated with children, applaud on 1 December 2005 as World Aids Day is commemorated in the Eisenhower Executive Office Building in Washington, DC." class="sc-d1200759-0 dvfjxj"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-d1200759-2 gwFzuU"&gt;Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jvncPH"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 FPsqq"&gt;Former US President George W Bush is widely acknowledged for his commitment to tackling HIV/Aids&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Then-US President George W Bush launched an ambitious programme to combat HIV/Aids in 2003, saying it would serve the "strategic and moral interests" of the US.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Known as the President's Emergency Plan for Aids Relief (Pepfar), it led to the investment of more than $100bn (£74bn) in the global HIV/Aids response - the largest commitment by any nation to address a single disease in the world.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;South Africa has about 7.7 million people living with HIV, the highest number in the world, &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.unaids.org/en/resources/presscentre/pressreleaseandstatementarchive/2025/february/20250225_1-1-million-people-treatment-south-africa" class="sc-f9178328-0 bGFWdi"&gt;according to UNAIDS&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;About 5.9 million of them receive antiretroviral treatment, resulting in a 66% decrease in Aids-related deaths since 2010, the UN agency adds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;South Africa's government says Pepfar funding contributed about 17% to its HIV/Aids programme. The money was used for various projects, including running mobile clinics to make it easier for patients to get treatment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;The Trump administration's cuts have raised concern that infection rates could spike again. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;"I think we're going to start seeing an increase in the number of HIV infections, the number of TB cases, the number of other infectious diseases," Prof Lynn Morris, Deputy Vice-Chancellor of Johannesburg's Wits University, tells the BBC.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;"And we're going to start seeing a reversal of what was essentially a real success story. We were getting on top of some of these things."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Gugu points out that treatment is a matter of life and death, especially for vulnerable populations like sex workers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;"People don't want to default on their ARVs. They're scared that they're going to die if they don't get access to them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;The cuts have also affected research aimed at finding an HIV vaccine and a cure for Aids.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;"There's the long-term impact, which is that we're not going to be getting new vaccines for HIV," Prof Morris adds. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;"We're not going to be keeping on top of viruses that are circulating. Even with new viruses that might appear, we're not going to have the surveillance infrastructure that we once had."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;South Africa has been one of the global leaders in HIV research. Many of the medications that help prevent the virus, and which have benefitted people around the world, were trialled in South Africa.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;This includes Prep (pre-exposure prophylaxis), a medication which stops HIV-negative people from catching the virus.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Another breakthrough preventive drug released this year, Lenacapavir, an injection taken twice a year and that offers total protection from HIV, was also tried in South Africa.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jvncPH"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 FPsqq"&gt;South African academic Prof Abdullah Ely is concerned that research will be affected by the US funding cut&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;In a lab at Wits University's Health Sciences campus, a small group of scientists are still working on a vaccine for HIV. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;They are part of the Brilliant Consortium, a group of labs working across eight African countries to develop a vaccine for the virus.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;"We were developing a vaccine test to see how well that works, and then we would trial it on humans," Abdullah Ely, an Associate Professor at Wits University, tells the BBC in his lab. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;"The plan was to run the trials in Africa based on research carried out by Africans because we want that research to actually benefit our community as well as all mankind."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;But the US funding cuts threw their work into doubt. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;"When the stop order came, it meant we had to stop everything. Only some of us have been able to get additional funding so we could continue our work. It's set us back months, probably could even be a year," Prof Ely says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;The lab lacks funding to carry out clinical trials scheduled for later this year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;"That is a very big loss to South Africa and the continent. It means that any potential research that comes out of Africa will have to be tested in Europe, or the US," Prof Ely says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="embed-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dHQIrb"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;In June, universities asked the government for a bailout of 4.6bn South African rand ($260m; £190m) over the next three years to cover some of the funding lost from the US. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;"We are pleading for support because South Africa is leading in HIV research, but it's not leading for itself. This has ramifications on the practice and policies of the entire globe," says Dr Phethiwe Matutu, head of Universities South Africa. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;South Africa's Health Minister Aaron Motsoaledi announced on Wednesday that some alternative funding for research had been secured. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;The Bill and Melinda Gates Foundation and the Wellcome Trust have agreed to donate 1m rand each with immediate effect, while the government would make available 400m rand over the next three years, he said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;This would bring the total to 600m rand, way below the 4.6bn rand requested by researchers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;As for Gugu, she had hoped that by the time she was elderly, a cure for HIV/Aids would have been found, but she is less optimistic now.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;"I look after a nine-year-old. I want to live as long as I can to keep taking care of him," she tells the BBC. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;"This isn't just a problem for right now, we have to think about how it's going to affect the next generation of women and young people."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 fDtfvH"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 eOFjmw"&gt;You may also be interested in:&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dFZIgd"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-d1200759-1 kycbVO"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20250701-150711-e3d94715db-web-2.24.1-1/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-d1200759-0 dkIvM hide-when-no-script"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/0a19/live/7c722dc0-089d-11ef-b9d8-4f52aebe147d.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/0a19/live/7c722dc0-089d-11ef-b9d8-4f52aebe147d.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/0a19/live/7c722dc0-089d-11ef-b9d8-4f52aebe147d.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/0a19/live/7c722dc0-089d-11ef-b9d8-4f52aebe147d.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/0a19/live/7c722dc0-089d-11ef-b9d8-4f52aebe147d.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/0a19/live/7c722dc0-089d-11ef-b9d8-4f52aebe147d.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/0a19/live/7c722dc0-089d-11ef-b9d8-4f52aebe147d.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/0a19/live/7c722dc0-089d-11ef-b9d8-4f52aebe147d.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Getty Images/BBC A woman looking at her mobile phone and the graphic BBC News Africa" class="sc-d1200759-0 dvfjxj"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-d1200759-2 gwFzuU"&gt;Getty Images/BBC&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BBC</author><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 04:19:40 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiWkFVX3lxTE9wckIwZk1ZQjN0Ui1aUnQxZGtudVozMi1tUGpNS2x6Tk9WUElyU1lhX0lUY3l6R3dHOGQ3SkpmMmVELUtVRkhXMHFoNWZUQWNPWGJpQ3BCNG5BQdIBX0FVX3lxTE1IQW9FMTgwMF9ZRTg0dDRpeDFuSjhnQ2JVTzE3bExKdzZtQ1IyQW9hMldSbXR5aUVIa3VXSzAxVGRVNHhDNFVwRFd4UF9vZ09hU3ZIRHplX2ZubS1vV0Nv</guid></item><item><title>主要研究将4种健康饮食与高达28%的痴呆风险降低联系起来- ScienceAlert | Major Study Links 4 Healthy Diets With Up to 28% Lower Dementia Risk - ScienceAlert</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMinAFBVV95cUxOTjRDc1MyY2ZJVEFuOEhBenVQczhoMFN5MDJjMWdzOHhwQ3ItX3c0Mk1wRjRUVEh1dkNNXy05YTBMeEtURXVkb3YxbjRLWnNtQ1BieEZSRGRNZ0FQQlhCV2FCRlNvVC1vSmVuLVJoOHo0aXFneWtsWWZIZ1hmT2tvWmZIQ2V6WkpGeUkzUlNHVGoxUXF0Y1MwNUJWUFk?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Sticking to the &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mediterranean_diet"&gt;Mediterranean diet&lt;/a&gt;, rich in plants and nuts and low in meat, could drastically reduce your risk of dementia, according to a new study from researchers at Yonsei University in South Korea.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Scientific studies have long shown how our eating habits can affect &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/decades-long-study-links-red-meat-to-up-to-13-higher-dementia-risk"&gt;our chances of developing dementia&lt;/a&gt;. Backing up those previous findings, the new study digs into this association for four specific types of diet across a large sample size, following up with participants for an average of 13.5 years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While it's not enough to prove direct cause and effect between these diets and dementia risk, this study does show a strong association. Further down the line, that might help us understand how &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/alzheimers-isnt-the-only-form-of-dementia-an-expert-explains-the-differences"&gt;different types of dementia&lt;/a&gt; get started, and what steps we could take to slow or prevent it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Considering the lack of a definitive cure for dementia, dietary interventions targeting specific food components, overall diet quality, and inflammatory potential offer promising approaches for early prevention," &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.jnha.2025.100564"&gt;write&lt;/a&gt; the researchers in their published paper.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/scientists-say-this-one-particular-diet-may-slow-the-decline-of-the-brain?utm_source=SA_article&amp;amp;utm_campaign=related_link"&gt;Scientists Say This One Particular Diet May Slow The Decline of The Brain&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers looked at 131,209 individuals aged between 40 and 69 in a public health database, scoring their diets against the Mediterranean diet (MEDAS), the &lt;a href="https://www.webmd.com/alzheimers/what-to-know-about-mind-diet"&gt;Mediterranean-DASH Intervention for Neurodegenerative Delay&lt;/a&gt; (MIND) diet, the Recommended Food Score (RFS), and the Alternative Healthy Eating Index (AHEI).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sticking to any of these four healthy diets was linked to a notable drop in dementia risk – between 21 and 28 percent. RFS adherents showed the best results, followed closely by the MIND diet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Inversely, participants' diets were also scored against another metric, the Energy-adjusted &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Dietary_inflammatory_index"&gt;Dietary Inflammatory Index&lt;/a&gt; (EDII). Higher EDII scores, which indicate pro-inflammatory diets, were linked to a 30 percent increase in dementia risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_167168" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-167168" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/07/MediterraneanGraph.jpg" alt="Dementia risk graph" class="wp-image-167168 size-full" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/07/MediterraneanGraph.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/07/MediterraneanGraph-563x415.jpg 563w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/07/MediterraneanGraph-600x442.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-167168" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;The study mapped adherence to diets, including the Mediterranean diet (MEDAS), against the number of dementia cases over time. (Youn et al., &lt;em&gt;J Nutr. Health Aging&lt;/em&gt;, 2025)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;The healthy diets all focus on whole grains, fruits, vegetables, fish, nuts, and poultry. Fried foods, dairy, and meat are discouraged. It's thought that this helps &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/sticking-to-the-mind-diet-could-reduce-your-risk-of-developing-dementia"&gt;reduce stress inside the body&lt;/a&gt; and thus protect the brain from harm.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The associations between dietary patterns and dementia were stronger in older adults and women and varied between the obese and non-obese groups, highlighting the differential impact of dietary patterns across subgroups," &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.jnha.2025.100564"&gt;write&lt;/a&gt; the researchers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Our findings underscore the potential of dietary interventions as modifiable factors to reduce the risk of dementia, particularly in vulnerable populations."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Despite plenty of progress in our understanding of dementia in recent years, we're still not sure of its precise causes – though we know that &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/eating-nuts-linked-to-lower-risk-of-dementia-study-finds"&gt;diet&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/alzheimers-risk-is-strongly-shaped-by-your-mothers-side-study-finds"&gt;genetics&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/can-a-healthy-lifestyle-beat-alzheimers-like-documentary-claims"&gt;physical exercise&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/one-stage-of-sleep-seems-to-be-critical-for-reducing-risk-of-dementia"&gt;sleep&lt;/a&gt; all play a role.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;With &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/these-15-factors-are-linked-to-early-dementia-risk-a-major-study-found"&gt;so many factors&lt;/a&gt; involved, figuring out how conditions such as  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/go/IaO" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73015" data-postid="167165" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;Alzheimer's&lt;/a&gt; disease develop in some people and not others isn't easy. However, each of these studies helps put together a full picture, as well as suggesting practical ways in which we might help reduce our own personal risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Our study effectively addresses several limitations of previous studies on diet and dementia," &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.jnha.2025.100564"&gt;write&lt;/a&gt; the researchers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Many earlier studies relied on a single dietary scoring system without comparing multiple dietary patterns, or had relatively short follow-up periods, limiting their ability to assess long-term effects."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The research has been published in the &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.jnha.2025.100564"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Journal of Nutrition, Health and Aging&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 03:42:49 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMinAFBVV95cUxOTjRDc1MyY2ZJVEFuOEhBenVQczhoMFN5MDJjMWdzOHhwQ3ItX3c0Mk1wRjRUVEh1dkNNXy05YTBMeEtURXVkb3YxbjRLWnNtQ1BieEZSRGRNZ0FQQlhCV2FCRlNvVC1vSmVuLVJoOHo0aXFneWtsWWZIZ1hmT2tvWmZIQ2V6WkpGeUkzUlNHVGoxUXF0Y1MwNUJWUFk</guid></item><item><title>随着全程疫苗接种率下降，密歇根州的疫苗豁免率上升：州数据-底特律新闻 | Vaccine waiver rates rise in Michigan as full vaccinations dip: state data - The Detroit News</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMi4gFBVV95cUxPUEpjNS1Yb0ZTZEl1VjQzWkdlY2wxNXhaODNIUURVU3NWRVlZZ2J6ZHJWOWdhRXdSd1RSRFNVNzh2UC1xQzdZS0p6bXlkSDdybTM5QldnQUMxakVsVTQ3V19ER19EUHl1b1J3Q3B6UmlDX1FnYU5KR3dPWWFyNG9NUGtKY281WGNhYVg4anJfeVByajZMcUwyVkRmd1ZwVnAwUmNLTmhnVjYxSHAtYUxvSVo0S0EydVJMUmlGYTRZV3lobkpjMUFVRFppaWtUZE1MN0xpS1NVR1F6TWF3MTNmTDlR?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="relative pb-5 w-full font-sans text-primary bg-inherit" data-testid="footer"&gt;&lt;p class="relative w-[1200px] max-w-[90vw] border-t border-button-disabled mx-auto mb-[30px]"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="flex flex-col gap-5 items-center max-w-[1200px] px-5 mx-auto md:px-10 lg:px-[50px]"&gt;&lt;p class="flex justify-center items-center w-full text-sm" data-testid="copyright"&gt;&lt;span&gt;© 2025 The Detroit News, a Digital First Media Newspaper. All rights reserved.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Detroit News</author><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 03:11:46 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi4gFBVV95cUxPUEpjNS1Yb0ZTZEl1VjQzWkdlY2wxNXhaODNIUURVU3NWRVlZZ2J6ZHJWOWdhRXdSd1RSRFNVNzh2UC1xQzdZS0p6bXlkSDdybTM5QldnQUMxakVsVTQ3V19ER19EUHl1b1J3Q3B6UmlDX1FnYU5KR3dPWWFyNG9NUGtKY281WGNhYVg4anJfeVByajZMcUwyVkRmd1ZwVnAwUmNLTmhnVjYxSHAtYUxvSVo0S0EydVJMUmlGYTRZV3lobkpjMUFVRFppaWtUZE1MN0xpS1NVR1F6TWF3MTNmTDlR</guid></item><item><title>这项研究刚刚推翻了我们认为我们所知道的关于跑步伤害的一切- SciTechDaily | This Study Just Overturned Everything We Thought We Knew About Running Injuries - SciTechDaily</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiqAFBVV95cUxOSnVZS1NXZlp5cDRid2paRXIycnE5VE5BcV95MGhNUEZjdVBpaWJvVHMxQ1piOGhaMUpvOVVONDZBNnI3UlY2TXFtSmlXUVUyTVZoclJ6bGtwNVQ2OFJiYjRKLWF5NEd3QmFUVFpaZzkzWFFldVVQVG1Jd013WWdUS0RfUTFuQWdNdUlWeW1zVm02V0dsVEFxaFJqQ0pkVFBtTDl2cWh1VWU?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>SciTechDaily</author><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 02:41:52 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiqAFBVV95cUxOSnVZS1NXZlp5cDRid2paRXIycnE5VE5BcV95MGhNUEZjdVBpaWJvVHMxQ1piOGhaMUpvOVVONDZBNnI3UlY2TXFtSmlXUVUyTVZoclJ6bGtwNVQ2OFJiYjRKLWF5NEd3QmFUVFpaZzkzWFFldVVQVG1Jd013WWdUS0RfUTFuQWdNdUlWeW1zVm02V0dsVEFxaFJqQ0pkVFBtTDl2cWh1VWU</guid></item><item><title>疾病预防控制中心表示，美国麻疹病例达到33年来的最高水平- Axios | U.S. measles cases hit 33-year high, CDC says - Axios</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMif0FVX3lxTE14SXN1ZGd6MF9FUENnZkJDQjZCS1FUQkZSaXRScnhMbURZZ2JERVRMdUg2UVk3bEVBSFdEelh1QjI0aV9MeGVQMkpaTVdBVXlhSlJqYzFESC1IeTBvOElzNVlwTjNaLWYwRUxWNWZGX050VGtleUNOVkMxLW9VcWs?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Axios</author><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 02:13:33 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMif0FVX3lxTE14SXN1ZGd6MF9FUENnZkJDQjZCS1FUQkZSaXRScnhMbURZZ2JERVRMdUg2UVk3bEVBSFdEelh1QjI0aV9MeGVQMkpaTVdBVXlhSlJqYzFESC1IeTBvOElzNVlwTjNaLWYwRUxWNWZGX050VGtleUNOVkMxLW9VcWs</guid></item><item><title>抗抑郁药物戒断是一个主要的公共卫生问题，专家警告- ScienceAlert | Antidepressant Withdrawal Is a Major Public Health Issue, Experts Warn - ScienceAlert</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMinwFBVV95cUxQRkpuZDFGeHNrenB5RWsyNTlWR2VSR0szaUtmWkRJQUNFeTVUc2d1dUxtY3UyOVpXbHBtNGpoTVVVTEdPdV9MZ2h5WXRFako4Zkc5TGdnbTBlU3ZTdzdnVk9xUjd5T0VBSVdYeF9nTHFiRWw4ZDAtenFlQmx0LTNpbWpYZURKNlpvd1V0bHNtTDlyeVJiVE5rRGR6NUUtRWs?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;A &lt;a href="https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jamapsychiatry/article-abstract/2836262"&gt;new review&lt;/a&gt; of antidepressant withdrawal effects – written by academics, many of whom have close ties to drug manufacturers – risks underestimating the potential harms to long-term antidepressant users by focusing on short-term, industry-funded studies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There is growing recognition that stopping antidepressants – especially after long-term use – can cause severe and sometimes &lt;a href="https://journals.sagepub.com/doi/full/10.1177/2045125320967183?rfr_dat=cr_pub++0pubmed&amp;amp;url_ver=Z39.88-2003&amp;amp;rfr_id=ori%3Arid%3Acrossref.org"&gt;debilitating&lt;/a&gt; withdrawal symptoms, and it is now acknowledged by the UK government as a &lt;a href="https://www.gov.uk/government/publications/prescribed-medicines-review-report"&gt;public health issue&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One of the main reasons this issue took decades to recognise after the release of modern antidepressants onto the market is because medical guidelines, such as those produced by Nice (England's National Institute for Health and Care Excellence), had for many years declared withdrawal effects to be &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0165178125001453?via%3Dihub"&gt;"brief and mild"&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This description was based on studies run by drug companies, where people had only taken the medication for eight to 12 weeks. As a result, when patients later showed up with severe, long-lasting symptoms, many doctors &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0022395623001309?via%3Dihub"&gt;didn't take them seriously&lt;/a&gt; because these experiences contradicted what the guidelines led them to expect.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/some-antidepressants-could-speed-decline-in-dementia-patients?utm_source=SA_article&amp;amp;utm_campaign=related_link"&gt;Some Antidepressants Could Speed Decline in Dementia Patients&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Our recent research helps explain this mismatch. We found a clear link between how long someone takes antidepressants and how likely they are to experience withdrawal symptoms – and how severe these symptoms are.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We surveyed &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0165178125001453?via%3Dihub"&gt;NHS patients&lt;/a&gt; and found that people who had used antidepressants for more than two years were ten times more likely to have withdrawal effects, five times more likely for those effects to be severe, and 18 times more likely for them to be long lasting compared with those who had taken the drugs for six months or less.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For patients who used antidepressants for less than six months, withdrawal symptoms were mostly mild and brief. Three-quarters reported no or mild symptoms, most of which lasted less than four weeks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_167368" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-167368" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/07/antidepressant_withdrawal_pill_642.jpg" alt="woman taking a pill" class="wp-image-167368 size-full" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/07/antidepressant_withdrawal_pill_642.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/07/antidepressant_withdrawal_pill_642-533x415.jpg 533w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/07/antidepressant_withdrawal_pill_642-600x467.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-167368" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Withdrawal is milder for those who use antidepressants for less than six months. (&lt;a href="https://www.canva.com/photos/MAFD2YI97-c/"&gt;fizkes/Getty Images/Canva&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Only one in four of these patients was unable to stop when they wanted to. However, &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0165178125001453?via%3Dihub"&gt;for long-term users&lt;/a&gt; (more than two years), two-thirds reported moderate or severe withdrawal effects, with one-quarter reporting severe withdrawal effects.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Almost one-third of long-term users reported symptoms that lasted for more than three months. Four-fifths of these patients were unable to stop their antidepressants despite trying.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;About 2 million people on antidepressants in England have been taking them for over five years, &lt;a href="https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-65825012"&gt;according to a BBC investigation&lt;/a&gt;. And &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/nchs/products/databriefs/db283.htm"&gt;in the US&lt;/a&gt; at least 25 million people have taken antidepressants for more than five years. What happens to people in eight-to-12-week studies is a far cry from what happens to millions of people when they stop.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Studying what happens to people after just eight to 12 weeks on antidepressants is like testing car safety by crashing a vehicle into a wall at 5km/h – ignoring the fact that real drivers are out on the roads doing 60km/h.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;History repeating itself?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Against this backdrop, a review has just been published in &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jama/fullarticle/10.1001/jamapsychiatry.2025.1362?utm_campaign=articlePDF%26utm_medium=articlePDFlink%26utm_source=articlePDF%26utm_content=jamapsychiatry.2025.1362"&gt;JAMA Psychiatry&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;. Several of the senior authors declare payments from drug companies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In what looks like history repeating itself, the review draws on short-term trials – many funded by the pharmaceutical industry – that were similar to those used to shape early treatment guidelines. The authors conclude that antidepressants do not cause significant withdrawal effects.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Their main analysis is based on eleven trials that compared withdrawal symptoms in people who had stopped antidepressants with those who had continued them or stopped taking a  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/what-is-a-placebo" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="102371" data-postid="167350" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;placebo&lt;/a&gt;. Six of these trials had people on antidepressants for eight weeks, four for 12 weeks and just one for 26 weeks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They reported a slightly higher number of withdrawal symptoms in people who had stopped antidepressants, which they say does not constitute a "clinically significant" withdrawal syndrome. They also suggest the symptoms could be explained by the "nocebo effect" – where negative expectations cause people to feel worse.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In our view, the results are likely to greatly underestimate the risk of withdrawal for the millions of people on these drugs for years. The review found no relationship between the duration of use of antidepressants and withdrawal symptoms, but there were too few long-term studies to test this association properly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The review probably underestimates, in our view, short-term withdrawal effects too by assuming that the fact that people experience withdrawal-like symptoms when stopping a placebo or continuing an antidepressant cancels out withdrawal effects from antidepressants. But this is not a valid assumption.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We know that antidepressant withdrawal effects overlap with side-effects and with everyday symptoms, but this does not mean they are the same thing. People stopping a placebo report symptoms such as dizziness and headache, because these are common occurrences.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, as was shown in another &lt;a href="https://www.thelancet.com/journals/lanpsy/article/PIIS2215-0366(24)00133-0/fulltext"&gt;recent review&lt;/a&gt;, symptoms following discontinuation of a placebo tend to be milder than those experienced when stopping antidepressants, which can be intense enough to &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/11448088/"&gt;require emergency care&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So deducting the rate of symptoms after stopping a placebo or continuing an antidepressant from antidepressant withdrawal symptoms is likely to underestimate the true extent of withdrawal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_167367" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-167367" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/07/antidepressant_withdrawal_hospital_642.jpg" alt="back of an ambulance" class="wp-image-167367 size-full" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/07/antidepressant_withdrawal_hospital_642.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/07/antidepressant_withdrawal_hospital_642-533x415.jpg 533w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/07/antidepressant_withdrawal_hospital_642-600x467.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-167367" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Some withdrawal effects are severe enough to require emergency care. (&lt;a href="https://www.canva.com/photos/MAElbkvqYIY/"&gt;Mikhail Nilov/Pexels/Canva&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;The review also doesn't include several well-designed drug company studies that found high rates of withdrawal symptoms. For example, an American &lt;a href="https://linkinghub.elsevier.com/retrieve/pii/S0006-3223(98)00126-7"&gt;study&lt;/a&gt; found that more than 60% of people who stopped antidepressants (after eleven months) experienced withdrawal symptoms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The authors suggest that  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/depression" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73097" data-postid="167350" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;depression&lt;/a&gt; after stopping antidepressants is probably a return of the original condition, not withdrawal symptoms, because similar rates of depression were seen in people who stopped taking a placebo.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But this conclusion is based on limited and unreliable data (that is, relying on participants in studies to report such events without prompting, rather than assessing them systematically) from just five studies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We hope uncritical reporting of a review based on the sort of short-term studies that led to under-recognition of withdrawal effects in the first place, does not disrupt the growing acceptance of the problem and slow efforts by the health system to help potentially millions of people who may be severely affected.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The authors and publisher of the new review have been approached for comment.&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://counter.theconversation.com/content/260708/count.gif?distributor=republish-lightbox-basic" alt="The Conversation" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/profiles/mark-horowitz-1358707"&gt;Mark Horowitz&lt;/a&gt;, Visiting Clinical Research Fellow in Psychiatry, &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/institutions/ucl-1885"&gt;UCL&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/profiles/joanna-moncrieff-104098"&gt;Joanna Moncrieff&lt;/a&gt;, Professor of Critical and Social Psychiatry, &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/institutions/ucl-1885"&gt;UCL&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This article is republished from &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com"&gt;The Conversation&lt;/a&gt; under a Creative Commons license. Read the &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/antidepressant-withdrawal-new-review-downplays-symptoms-but-misses-the-mark-for-long-term-use-260708"&gt;original article&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 01:50:44 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMinwFBVV95cUxQRkpuZDFGeHNrenB5RWsyNTlWR2VSR0szaUtmWkRJQUNFeTVUc2d1dUxtY3UyOVpXbHBtNGpoTVVVTEdPdV9MZ2h5WXRFako4Zkc5TGdnbTBlU3ZTdzdnVk9xUjd5T0VBSVdYeF9nTHFiRWw4ZDAtenFlQmx0LTNpbWpYZURKNlpvd1V0bHNtTDlyeVJiVE5rRGR6NUUtRWs</guid></item><item><title>律师说，前阿拉斯加ICE被拘留者现在因结核病在华盛顿住院-安克雷奇每日新闻 | Former Alaska ICE detainee now hospitalized with tuberculosis in Washington, attorney says - Anchorage Daily News</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMi3wFBVV95cUxNRDVjeFF6Mk02R3FseDdYVGdQNk5DZzVCeW9VQjhheG5ocVEwN1BVUF9fTUhibXFGSXNKSHdsNHBXd2s2OS1vS0VtcUFlRUcySk91c2tyWWpGYlFCckJoYTcxVVhIc1ZSamkzQXptMUp0aE5Vdjk2UXFfZ3NkYWl4dnVSNlhkMHVoTnR0aHNjUDVxOEJiYjR4WE9yUURGcGV1eGpRTWJPQ2dTM2lveFNGcDZRa0JQTW1iQjJyOHcwNVR0NmlSTmZWMWJKaFpEUXh3aVBTMVZfbXQ2MjRfTHUw?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article class="adn-article-body default  teads_enabled"&gt;&lt;figure class="c-media-item"&gt;&lt;img data-chromatic="ignore" alt="" class="c-image" loading="lazy" src="https://www.adn.com/resizer/v2/6R2KKH76IVFPLGI6CH75ZGMELI.JPG?auth=e6cf6043ab6e81dbffee29fe82618a88382718723d497e80aac42de118d88968&amp;amp;width=800&amp;amp;height=532" srcset="https://www.adn.com/resizer/v2/6R2KKH76IVFPLGI6CH75ZGMELI.JPG?auth=e6cf6043ab6e81dbffee29fe82618a88382718723d497e80aac42de118d88968&amp;amp;width=274&amp;amp;height=182 274w, https://www.adn.com/resizer/v2/6R2KKH76IVFPLGI6CH75ZGMELI.JPG?auth=e6cf6043ab6e81dbffee29fe82618a88382718723d497e80aac42de118d88968&amp;amp;width=400&amp;amp;height=266 400w, https://www.adn.com/resizer/v2/6R2KKH76IVFPLGI6CH75ZGMELI.JPG?auth=e6cf6043ab6e81dbffee29fe82618a88382718723d497e80aac42de118d88968&amp;amp;width=768&amp;amp;height=510 768w, https://www.adn.com/resizer/v2/6R2KKH76IVFPLGI6CH75ZGMELI.JPG?auth=e6cf6043ab6e81dbffee29fe82618a88382718723d497e80aac42de118d88968&amp;amp;width=1024&amp;amp;height=680 1024w, https://www.adn.com/resizer/v2/6R2KKH76IVFPLGI6CH75ZGMELI.JPG?auth=e6cf6043ab6e81dbffee29fe82618a88382718723d497e80aac42de118d88968&amp;amp;width=1440&amp;amp;height=957 1440w"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="c-media-item__fig-caption"&gt;&lt;span class="c-media-item__caption"&gt;Anchorage Correctional Complex on Tuesday, June 10, 2025. (Bill Roth / ADN) &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;A man from Peru who was one of roughly 40 federal immigration detainees held in an Alaska jail last month is now hospitalized with tuberculosis in Washington, his attorney said Wednesday.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;Word of the case of the highly infectious disease raised questions among prison rights advocates about the scope of a larger potential outbreak.&lt;i&gt; &lt;/i&gt;State corrections officials on Wednesday said no larger outbreak had taken place, and said the detainees had been thoroughly screened for the illness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;A spokesperson from the Alaska Department of Corrections said there were “no reported cases of (tuberculosis) in any of our facilities” as of Wednesday afternoon. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;The man, a Peruvian asylum seeker, was part of &lt;a href="https://www.adn.com/alaska-news/2025/06/10/dozens-of-ice-detainees-transferred-to-alaska-are-being-held-at-an-anchorage-facility/" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://www.adn.com/alaska-news/2025/06/10/dozens-of-ice-detainees-transferred-to-alaska-are-being-held-at-an-anchorage-facility/"&gt;a group of about 40 men flown to Anchorage&lt;/a&gt; from a Tacoma regional immigration detention center on June 8 as part of a deal between the state and U.S. Immigration and Customs Enforcement to relieve overcrowding amid a nationwide immigration crackdown ordered by the Trump administration. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;The man’s attorney, Sean Quirk, said in an interview Wednesday that the man was housed from about June 8 until June 30 at the Cook Inlet Pretrial Facility with dozens of other detainees. Quirk said he was not notified of his client’s whereabouts&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;during his time in Alaska, when he was transferred out or when he was hospitalized.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;The group was &lt;a href="https://www.adn.com/alaska-news/2025/06/30/ice-detainees-held-at-anchorage-jail-have-been-transferred-out-of-state/" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://www.adn.com/alaska-news/2025/06/30/ice-detainees-held-at-anchorage-jail-have-been-transferred-out-of-state/"&gt;flown back to the Tacoma ICE facility on June 30&lt;/a&gt;. The man was taken to the emergency room Monday, one week after he left Alaska, Quirk said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;Quirk said he couldn’t reach his client for days and eventually learned he might be hospitalized after the man didn’t appear for a virtual hearing. It took a series of phone calls to hospitals in the Tacoma area to locate his client. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;“I started cold-calling hospitals in Tacoma, and I was able to speak to someone,” Quirk said. Eventually he was connected to his client, but not before an ICE agent stationed in a hallway interceded and prevented a nurse from handing the phone over, he said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;It is not clear where the man contracted tuberculosis, how long he had it or who else may have been exposed. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;Tuberculosis is a bacterial infection that primarily affects the lungs. It can be fatal if untreated, and treatment with antibiotics takes months. Alaska’s tuberculosis rates are &lt;a href="https://www.adn.com/alaska-news/2025/02/03/alaskas-tuberculosis-rate-remains-elevated-preliminary-figures-show/" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://www.adn.com/alaska-news/2025/02/03/alaskas-tuberculosis-rate-remains-elevated-preliminary-figures-show/"&gt;among the highest in the nation&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;The federal Centers for Disease Control and Prevention says tuberculosis can be spread from person to person in close environments. Some people have latent tuberculosis in their systems for weeks, months or years. People who have been exposed to tuberculosis should be tested, according to the CDC. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;Tuberculosis is a special threat in jails and prisons due to the cramped quarters for incarcerated people, according to the CDC. &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/tb/risk-factors/correctional-facilities.html" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;In 2023&lt;/a&gt;, 3.6% of all tuberculosis cases in the U.S. involved inmates in a correctional facility at time of diagnosis, according to the agency. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;The American Civil Liberties Union of Alaska said in a statement Wednesday&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;that its attorneys were told by two ICE detainees during their time in Anchorage that they’d tested positive for latent tuberculosis, and that other detainees had been “informed by ICE upon their return to Tacoma on June 30th that they were exposed to tuberculosis while detained in Alaska.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;State Department of Corrections officials called the ACLU statement “categorically false and dangerously misleading.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;All of the ICE detainees who came to Alaska were “screened for tuberculosis upon admission into our care — not by ICE, but by our own qualified medical staff” as part of a standard intake procedure, corrections spokesperson Betsy Holley said in an email. One person underwent additional testing. All subsequent tests for active TB came back negative, according to Holley.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;Latent tuberculosis and active tuberculosis are two different things, the department’s medical chief said in an emailed response to questions. Latent tuberculosis isn’t contagious, doesn’t produce symptoms and isn’t the same thing as active tuberculosis disease. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;“These detainees were housed in a clean, unoccupied unit and kept separate from the general population throughout their short stay — only 23 days in total," Holley wrote. “TB is not transmitted like the cold or flu. It requires prolonged, close contact — typically months — not mere days." &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;The Peruvian ICE detainee remained hospitalized as of Wednesday evening, according to his attorney. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Anchorage Daily News</author><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 01:28:14 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi3wFBVV95cUxNRDVjeFF6Mk02R3FseDdYVGdQNk5DZzVCeW9VQjhheG5ocVEwN1BVUF9fTUhibXFGSXNKSHdsNHBXd2s2OS1vS0VtcUFlRUcySk91c2tyWWpGYlFCckJoYTcxVVhIc1ZSamkzQXptMUp0aE5Vdjk2UXFfZ3NkYWl4dnVSNlhkMHVoTnR0aHNjUDVxOEJiYjR4WE9yUURGcGV1eGpRTWJPQ2dTM2lveFNGcDZRa0JQTW1iQjJyOHcwNVR0NmlSTmZWMWJKaFpEUXh3aVBTMVZfbXQ2MjRfTHUw</guid></item><item><title>自疫情以来，加利福尼亚州的预期寿命仍未反弹-《洛杉矶时报》 | Life expectancy in California still hasn’t rebounded since the pandemic - Los Angeles Times</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMigAFBVV95cUxOS1JRWHBnYnVpck9ZVTJFNXNjTW9xODdKcnIzN0pXME04LUhZbUZhVllLdVEyeHNoX1NWQW13b24zZ0pUeWlVN2ZfSTJqR29ULTlpNXVCUEw2bEFzS2MwYXpSMkdKNW5HN3BONlM1OV8zVFN1UlpyWFFPamkwUWF6Yw?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div data-element="story-body" class="ct-rich-text-children font-cmsFontBrandText font-normal text-lg leading-7.75 [&amp;amp;_&amp;gt;p]:text-cms-story-body-color-text clearfix max-w-170 mt-7.5 mb-10 mx-auto" data-subscriber-content&gt; &lt;p&gt;During the height of the COVID-19 pandemic, the virus caused life expectancy in California to drop significantly. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s now been over two years since officials declared the pandemic-related public health emergency to be over. And yet, life expectancy for Californians has not fully recovered. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Today, however, the virus has been replaced by drug overdoses and cardiovascular disease as the main causes driving down average lifespans.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A new study published in the medical journal JAMA by researchers from UCLA, Northwestern, Princeton and Virginia Commonwealth University finds that  the average life expectancy for Californians in 2024 was nearly a year less than in 2019. The shortfall of 0.86 year signals that only about two-thirds of the state’s pandemic-era losses of 2.92 years have been reversed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Using mortality data from the California Comprehensive Death Files and population estimates from the American Community Survey, the researchers calculated annual life expectancy from 2019 to 2024, breaking the figures down by race, ethnicity, income and cause of death.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Although the COVID-19 virus was the primary factor in life expectancy declines during the pandemic’s peak, accounting for 61.6% of the life expectancy gap, its impact has significantly lessened. In 2024, COVID-19 accounted for only 12.8% of the life expectancy gap compared with 2019, while drug overdoses and cardiovascular disease contributed more — 19.8% and 16.3%, respectively.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For Black and Hispanic Californians, recovery has been even slower. Life expectancy for Black residents in 2024 remained 1.48 years below 2019 levels, while for Hispanic residents it was 1.44 years lower. In contrast, the gap for white residents was 0.63 year, and for Asian residents, who have the highest life expectancy in the state at 85.51 years, it was 1.06 years. Overall, the life expectancy for Black Californians in 2024 was under 73.5 years, more than a dozen years lower than that of Asian Californians.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Janet Currie, a co-author of the study and professor at Princeton University, noted that these disparities are especially striking. “You saw the very big hit that Hispanic people and Black people took during the pandemic,” she said, “but you also see that Black people in particular are still not caught up.” She added that although Hispanic populations saw a faster rebound, they too remain behind.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Income-based disparities in life expectancy persist in stark form. Californians living in the lowest-income census tracts (the bottom quartile) experienced a 0.99-year gap in 2024 compared with 2019, while those in the highest-income quartile had a slightly smaller 0.85-year gap. However, the overall life expectancy difference between these groups, 5.77 years, was nearly identical to the prepandemic gap of 5.63 years, suggesting that income-based health disparities persist even as pandemic impacts recede.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study highlights drug overdoses as a primary post-pandemic-emergency driver of reduced life expectancy. Black Californians and residents of low-income areas were especially affected. In 2023, drug overdoses contributed nearly a full year (0.99 year) to the life expectancy deficit for Black Californians and over half a year (0.52) for residents of low-income areas.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That said, there are signs that state and national efforts to address the overdose crisis may be yielding early results. The number for Black Californians declined to 0.55 year in 2024 while it declined to 0.26 year for residents in low-income areas; in the same time frame, the statewide number dropped from 0.4 year to 0.17 year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Currie attributed the initial surge in overdose deaths in part to the pandemic itself; there were disruptions in access to treatment, and many Californians suffered greater isolation. While she welcomed the recent progress, she cautioned that the share of deaths attributable to overdoses remains high and emphasized that this was “one of the real bad consequences of the pandemic.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Meanwhile, cardiovascular disease is now the leading contributor to life expectancy loss among high-income Californians. In 2024, it accounted for 0.22 year of the gap for the wealthiest quartile, more than COVID-19 did at 0.10 year. The authors note this is consistent with statewide rising rates of obesity, which may be playing a role.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tyler Evans, chief medical officer and chief exeuctive of Wellness Equity Alliance as well as the author of the book “&lt;a class="link" href="https://www.press.jhu.edu/books/title/53697/pandemics-poverty-and-politics?srsltid=AfmBOoooU1gGdWAFwk_WkimSU9rwqT435AXLpbfyOkq9WmhMCKb1GW3E" target="_blank"&gt;Pandemics, Poverty, and Politics: Decoding the Social and Political Drivers of Pandemics from Plague to COVID-19&lt;/a&gt;,” emphasized how the pandemic exacerbated long-standing health inequities. “These chronic health inequities were further amplified as the result of the pandemic,” he said. While investments in social determinants of health initially helped mitigate some of the worst outcomes, he added, “the funding dried up,” making recovery harder for communities already at greater risk of poor outcomes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Evans also pointed to a broader pattern of overlapping health crises that he described as a “syndemic,” a convergence of epidemics such as addiction, chronic disease and poor access to care that interact to worsen outcomes for historically marginalized populations. “Until we invest in that sort of foundation long term, the numbers will continue to decline,” he said. “California should be a leader in health improvement outcomes in the country, not a state that continues to have our survival decline.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Although the findings are limited to California and based on preliminary 2024 data, the study provides an early glimpse into post-pandemic mortality trends ahead of the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention’s national life expectancy dataset, expected to be published later this year. California, home to one-eighth of the U.S. population, provides valuable insight into how racial, ethnic and socioeconomic disparities continue to shape public health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ultimately, the study highlights how although the most visible impacts of COVID-19 may have faded, their ripple effects, compounded by ongoing structural inequities, continue to shape life and death in California. The pandemic may have accelerated long-standing public health challenges, and  the recovery, the study makes clear, has been uneven and incomplete.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Currie warned that further cuts to Medicaid and public hospitals could make these gaps even worse. “We know what to do. We just don’t do it,” she said.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;     &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Los Angeles Times</author><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 00:46:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigAFBVV95cUxOS1JRWHBnYnVpck9ZVTJFNXNjTW9xODdKcnIzN0pXME04LUhZbUZhVllLdVEyeHNoX1NWQW13b24zZ0pUeWlVN2ZfSTJqR29ULTlpNXVCUEw2bEFzS2MwYXpSMkdKNW5HN3BONlM1OV8zVFN1UlpyWFFPamkwUWF6Yw</guid></item><item><title>每个人都应该食用的10种富含纤维的食物，以改善肠道健康-印度时报 | 10 fibre-rich foods that everyone should consume for better gut health - Times of India</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMi_gFBVV95cUxNNktEUTZUVlFaeUROR3ZPcXJjMmZLY19CcldLR1pPOXo3RFlIb3NlM25vcWR0RDV5V0ZIVXNOMVZ6X0NfZEFIYnhnbDlHMENTc3VBeTJuVjh6V1pSM1hOSkhibC00Q3VhNkdZSlpnRnlYLV9uQmVhZEFEWGNRYWtRMS1HZ0RScE9OalJienllWkFQS1h5YUszLTNwdl9NY3R3ZktqU1hCOWo4aGhfSlNOUmZPMUFqTVp0NWVMMm5WU0E2MXFPekxlQ0ZRZWxKc1lualFwV200WkhnVm8taHlJMVl5Qk9nSzRfcEVlX0dvc2xBMXc3UU1DTjNZTXhsQdIB_gFBVV95cUxNNktEUTZUVlFaeUROR3ZPcXJjMmZLY19CcldLR1pPOXo3RFlIb3NlM25vcWR0RDV5V0ZIVXNOMVZ6X0NfZEFIYnhnbDlHMENTc3VBeTJuVjh6V1pSM1hOSkhibC00Q3VhNkdZSlpnRnlYLV9uQmVhZEFEWGNRYWtRMS1HZ0RScE9OalJienllWkFQS1h5YUszLTNwdl9NY3R3ZktqU1hCOWo4aGhfSlNOUmZPMUFqTVp0NWVMMm5WU0E2MXFPekxlQ0ZRZWxKc1lualFwV200WkhnVm8taHlJMVl5Qk9nSzRfcEVlX0dvc2xBMXc3UU1DTjNZTXhsQQ?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;amp-story-grid-layer class="recircular" id="rcontent" template="vertical"&gt;&lt;div class="letterbox"&gt;&lt;p class="mid-heading"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;You may also like&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="rc3 pa"&gt;10 foods that help relieve constipation ...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="rc5 pa"&gt;9 foods that boost liver health&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/amp-story-grid-layer&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 00:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi_gFBVV95cUxNNktEUTZUVlFaeUROR3ZPcXJjMmZLY19CcldLR1pPOXo3RFlIb3NlM25vcWR0RDV5V0ZIVXNOMVZ6X0NfZEFIYnhnbDlHMENTc3VBeTJuVjh6V1pSM1hOSkhibC00Q3VhNkdZSlpnRnlYLV9uQmVhZEFEWGNRYWtRMS1HZ0RScE9OalJienllWkFQS1h5YUszLTNwdl9NY3R3ZktqU1hCOWo4aGhfSlNOUmZPMUFqTVp0NWVMMm5WU0E2MXFPekxlQ0ZRZWxKc1lualFwV200WkhnVm8taHlJMVl5Qk9nSzRfcEVlX0dvc2xBMXc3UU1DTjNZTXhsQdIB_gFBVV95cUxNNktEUTZUVlFaeUROR3ZPcXJjMmZLY19CcldLR1pPOXo3RFlIb3NlM25vcWR0RDV5V0ZIVXNOMVZ6X0NfZEFIYnhnbDlHMENTc3VBeTJuVjh6V1pSM1hOSkhibC00Q3VhNkdZSlpnRnlYLV9uQmVhZEFEWGNRYWtRMS1HZ0RScE9OalJienllWkFQS1h5YUszLTNwdl9NY3R3ZktqU1hCOWo4aGhfSlNOUmZPMUFqTVp0NWVMMm5WU0E2MXFPekxlQ0ZRZWxKc1lualFwV200WkhnVm8taHlJMVl5Qk9nSzRfcEVlX0dvc2xBMXc3UU1DTjNZTXhsQQ</guid></item><item><title>斯坦福大学的研究人员开发了测量生物年龄的新工具-水星新闻 | Stanford researchers develop new tool to measure biological age - The Mercury News</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMipgFBVV95cUxNdlZ3ejY3YXNETTJhbXFjTUgtSDZJV1otcXp1NFp1MFJFU2gzTVNGNnJoZncyTW5HTXpqMXBLdUVQQnNJbERHMnJFWlF5Y0tpaGxZelNFTTRVSHJuNFZDTl9SZzZkVHF6SGI0ekpXRVo4WFpHdllLaFVMZE9uT1BxemJ0cEZxTGV2SUdlVDJBRENxVHBSUE8yaWVwWHotZzdRakxWem930gGrAUFVX3lxTE1sanJpRmNQVF9OdHZ0cHNEUGVKWHFzVDdDdy1hVU5pNkZqUjJPeUxWWkI2RUFhaFRCWWFQZ1k3MFdkaHU0VzVZOTFzRXZ5YVhCY2NFSEFOM0VTRWpQTDVzZGxDOTNvYmFwcXU1cmF0ZUxOWExob3oyckk4bDJUUDBfZG5FRm13ajBBRmNqc3I1SmVMb3VZTTRGNldfVUprR1hLOGI3NFA0NFlpbw?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="body-copy mng-subscriber-content"&gt;&lt;p&gt;The tool, built by a team led by Stanford's Tony Wyss-Coray, uses a single vial of blood to assess the "biological age" of each organ.            &lt;/p&gt;


			&lt;p class="time mng-originally-published"&gt;Originally Published: &lt;time datetime="2025-07-09 03:45:37"&gt;July 9, 2025 at 3:45 AM PDT&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Mercury News</author><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 00:29:19 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipgFBVV95cUxNdlZ3ejY3YXNETTJhbXFjTUgtSDZJV1otcXp1NFp1MFJFU2gzTVNGNnJoZncyTW5HTXpqMXBLdUVQQnNJbERHMnJFWlF5Y0tpaGxZelNFTTRVSHJuNFZDTl9SZzZkVHF6SGI0ekpXRVo4WFpHdllLaFVMZE9uT1BxemJ0cEZxTGV2SUdlVDJBRENxVHBSUE8yaWVwWHotZzdRakxWem930gGrAUFVX3lxTE1sanJpRmNQVF9OdHZ0cHNEUGVKWHFzVDdDdy1hVU5pNkZqUjJPeUxWWkI2RUFhaFRCWWFQZ1k3MFdkaHU0VzVZOTFzRXZ5YVhCY2NFSEFOM0VTRWpQTDVzZGxDOTNvYmFwcXU1cmF0ZUxOWExob3oyckk4bDJUUDBfZG5FRm13ajBBRmNqc3I1SmVMb3VZTTRGNldfVUprR1hLOGI3NFA0NFlpbw</guid></item><item><title>SARAH RAINEY ：专家揭示了你的噩梦的真正含义-《每日邮报》 | SARAH RAINEY: Experts reveal what your nightmares REALLY mean - Daily Mail</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMitgFBVV95cUxPOWxINUVEUThXN2d4eEh3MFQ5cUZmeTIya2dIbmFndnlrR0JjeEZtVVA3MTg2VS1uWUlicW9hY3NqbndaUUdUUlJsWlF4MEFzU2w0TXY0bzlpX1JoaU01YzNvMVRNNEctSjhjeDFITl90aXJRNGV0QVFWNE1pdGNSWGpLN3c0bFNHdHM2bkJsZWJRdF8yeVRQVklySHRqaEg5Z3pyUlhRMV9qZnV4ZzFxVkZQMWs4QQ?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div itemprop="articleBody"&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Heart pounding, sweating, gasping for breath... chances are you've woken up feeling like this at least once in your life – perhaps even in the last week.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Nightmares play havoc with your sleep, transporting you from the comfort and safety of your bedroom to a terrifying dreamscape.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But we all know that bad dreams – whether the bogeyman under the bed, giving a work presentation naked or sitting your finals again – aren't real, so they can't hurt you... right?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Wrong, say experts at Imperial College &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/london/index.html" id="mol-48919910-5d00-11f0-98d4-9b855d0fe0c6"&gt;London&lt;/a&gt;, whose ground-breaking research, presented at the European Academy of Neurology &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/us-congress/index.html" id="mol-4885b230-5d00-11f0-98d4-9b855d0fe0c6"&gt;Congress&lt;/a&gt; a fortnight ago, reveals some alarming truths about what happens when we sleep.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Such is the impact of nightmares on your mental and physical health, they found, that having them frequently – once a week or more – can triple your risk of death before the age of 70.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In fact, bad dreams are 'a stronger predicator of premature death' than other known risk factors, including smoking, obesity and lack of exercise.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The study, which analysed data from more than 2,400 children and 183,000 adults over 19 years, is the first of its kind to link nightmares with biological ageing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Sleep experts cannot overstate how significant this is, with lead researcher Dr Abidemi Otaiku of the UK Dementia Research Institute insisting they constitute 'a public health concern'.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Researchers have found that having nightmares once a week or more can triple your risk of death before the age of 70&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;With one in 20 of us – or 3.5 million people – afflicted by weekly nightmares (and up to half the UK population experiencing them once a month), it's an alarming revelation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;So why do some of us suffer from bad dreams? Are certain nightmares worse than others? And what – if anything – can you do to stop them?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mol-para-with-font mol-style-subhead femail-ccox"&gt;Blowing a fuse while you sleep&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;At a basic physiological level, all mammals, from whales to guinea pigs, experience something akin to dreaming – and are therefore susceptible to nightmares.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In humans, explains Dr Justin Havens, a psychological trauma therapist and leading nightmare expert, dreaming serves as overnight therapy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'We dream for a purpose – it's an evolutionary survival mechanism. We're trying to digest the emotional experiences of the day,' he adds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Nightmares occur when this process doesn't work or is interrupted mid-cycle; like a fuse blowing while you sleep.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Guy Leschziner, professor of neurology and sleep medicine at King's College London, says nightmares evolve from dreams whose subject matter is distressing or traumatic.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'We think that one of the functions of dreaming may be to consolidate memories, but to gradually cause strong emotions linked with these memories to fade,' he explains.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'However, if the emotional content of those dreams or nightmares is very high, you will wake up and this process cannot be completed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'It means that these emotional memories are never properly dealt with and those strong emotions persist.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;And if you think you don't dream, you're wrong. You simply don't remember it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Everyone dreams, for roughly two hours every night, mostly during a deeper stage of sleep called REM ('rapid eye movement') – a period of increased brain activity characterised by quick, darting eye movements beneath closed eyelids.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The last hour of sleep is nearly all REM sleep, so any nightmares you're having when your alarm goes off are likely to linger.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The term 'nightmare' originates from Old English, with 'mare' being a female demon who was thought to sit on the chest and torment sleepers with terrifying dreams and feelings of suffocation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mol-para-with-font mol-style-subhead femail-ccox"&gt;Excess cortisol equals faster ageing&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Scientists are still unsure which parts of the brain serve as the projection booth for nightmares.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But key to what's happening are thought to be the amygdala, found near the brain stem, as well as the prefrontal cortex, located behind the forehead.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The amygdala is, functionally speaking, where your 'demons' are kept; it controls emotions such as aggression, fear, anger and sadness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;When you're awake, the prefrontal cortex stops these feelings from becoming too dominant. But during sleep, it shuts down – meaning the monsters lurking inside your mind come out to play.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Mentally, explains Tom Stoneham, a professor of philosophy at the University of York, the impact of a nightmare can leave your body 'in a high state of emotion'.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'In the immediate aftermath, it is the emotional effects of the nightmare and not the specific content that grips us,' he says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="mol-img-group floatRHS"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Dr Abidemi Otaiku, of Imperial College London, has labelled the significant effects of nightmares 'a public health concern'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Nightmares can trigger feelings of anxiety, depression and general unease – which sometimes last hours or even days.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;A 2020 study in the journal Psychoneuroendocrinology found that participants' moods were notably lower the day after they had a nightmare, compared with days following neutral dreams. There can be profound physical effects, too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Nightmares lead to prolonged elevations of cortisol, a stress hormone closely linked to faster cellular ageing,' explains Dr Otaiku, author of the Imperial study.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;A 2019 study in the journal Psychophysiology found that bad dreams are accompanied by increased activation of the autonomic nervous system (which regulates functions including heart rate, blood pressure, digestion and sexual arousal).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The after-effects of this – increased body temperature, shallow, rapid breathing and muscle tension – can last long after you wake up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mol-para-with-font mol-style-subhead femail-ccox"&gt;The gender gap affecting our sleep&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;According to a 2014 study, women report having more nightmares than men; they're also able to recall them with greater clarity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Female sleepers dream about different things, according to a 2014 paper published in the journal Sleep, with nightmares revolving around interpersonal conflict.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Men, by contrast, are more likely to dream about disasters, earthquakes or wars.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Experts believe the female tendency towards nightmares is related to changes in body temperature and increased hormonal levels during the menstrual cycle, as well as higher average stress levels.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Children are more likely to experience nightmares, too, especially between the ages of three and six.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'We think that some of this may be evolutionary,' says Deirdre Barrett, a dream researcher at Harvard Medical School and editor of Trauma and Dreams.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Children are smaller and are vulnerable to many more threats than adults. Nightmares may partially reflect this vulnerability.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But sleep expert Dr Nerina Ramlakhan says childhood nightmares aren't always cause for concern.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'If they are frequent, they can affect energy levels, ability to concentrate and learn, and increase daytime anxiety,' she explains. 'However, they are also normal and can be related to processing emotions, new experiences and creativity.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mol-para-with-font mol-style-subhead femail-ccox"&gt;Why first-borns have more nightmares&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Scientists think the seeds of future nightmares may be planted early in life, before the age of three-and-a-half – a time from which we usually remember very little.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;If this period is disrupted by a traumatic event, causing fear or stress, our brains develop coping mechanisms – far earlier than normally required – which can upset the delicate balance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;This traumatic event doesn't have to be anything out of the ordinary: it can be as simple as the birth of a sibling, causing the elder child to feel forgotten or unloved.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;A 2017 paper reported that first-born children had frightening dreams more than twice as frequently as later-born siblings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Other causal factors include stress – whether at home or from a busy job – grief, and post-traumatic stress disorder, common in military veterans and victims of violent crimes, among whom the incidence of nightmares rises to between 71 and 96 per cent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Most people will admit to having had a nightmare about falling from a great height; sitting an exam unprepared; being late for something important; being chased; or being unexpectedly naked at work, school or on stage&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Bryony Sheaves, a research clinical psychologist at the University of Oxford, has connected nightmares to three temperamental traits: paranoia; frequent 'de-personalisation' (a feeling of detachment from yourself or your surroundings); and hallucinations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But these don't refer to medical conditions. People vulnerable to nightmares may simply be more suspicious of others, feel stressed in social situations or have vivid, dreamlike imaginations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'In reality, there is not one single cause,' says Dr Sheaves.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mol-para-with-font mol-style-subhead femail-ccox"&gt;The scary dreams that prepare us for real-life horrors&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Stemming from our subconscious, nightmares are very personal – but some bad dreams are, statistically speaking, more common and more likely to recur.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Most searched-for online is the nightmare in which your teeth fall out, said to reflect a life change, recent loss or stressful event.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Second most-frequent are dreams about snakes, reportedly triggered by a personal transformation, such as a new job or house move.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;And third most common are dreams about pregnancy, which are connected to big developments, especially something exciting or unknown.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Then, of course, there are the dreams we've all had at least once: falling from a great height; sitting an exam unprepared; being late for something important; being chased; or finding yourself unexpectedly naked at work, school or on stage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Dr Justin Havens says none of these should be cause for concern – it's the really traumatic, aggressive nightmares that are more likely to do damage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Particularly bad ones, he says, involve 'either dying or being tortured, or nightmares of traumatic events that have already happened'.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Prof Stoneham, however, says nightmares affect us all in different ways.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'A dream of spiders would have very different effects on an arachnophobe, an entomologist and someone who lived in a culture where spiders were eaten or had some other similarly positive role,' he explains.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Indeed, when 'scary' subjects appear in our nightmares, this can sometimes be a good thing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;A 2019 study at the University of Geneva found that bad dreams may help prepare us for frightening real-life situations by activating parts of the brain – the insula and the cingulate cortex – which are responsible for the 'fight or flight' response to danger.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mol-para-with-font mol-style-subhead femail-ccox"&gt;Could you be suffering from a nightmare disorder?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'If nightmares are occurring regularly, then they might be classified as a nightmare disorder,' explains Dr Ramlakhan.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'This is a pattern of repeated frightening and vivid dreams that cause significant emotional distress and impair functioning.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;We are, however, notoriously bad at doing anything about our bad dreams – particularly in the cold light of day. 'No one goes to their GP saying: "Help, I'm having nightmares",' says Dr Havens.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;So when should you worry? 'Nightmare disorder ranges in severity based on the frequency of nightmares,' explains Dr Ramlakhan.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Mild is less than one nightmare per week. Moderate is one or more nightmares per week, but less than nightly. Severe is nightmares every night.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;It can also vary in duration, with chronic nightmare disorder lasting six months or longer. Ultimately, when – or if – you seek help is up to you.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'If they're frequent, disrupting your sleep and your psychological health, and having a big impact on your quality of life, then it's probably worth talking to someone,' explains Prof Leschziner.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mol-para-with-font mol-style-subhead femail-ccox"&gt;The red flags nobody should ignore&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Experts say persistent bad dreams can be warning signs of illness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In 2022, Dr Otaiku found a correlation between frequent nightmares and Parkinson's disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;For sufferers of more severe nightmares, Dr Justin Havens, a psychological trauma therapist, has devised a method called the 'Dream Completion Technique' - which takes just two minutes and can cure bad dreams in a single night&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt; His team looked at data from more than 3,800 men aged 67 or older, with those who reported regular nightmares (at least weekly) more likely to develop Parkinson's and suffer cognitive decline.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Another 2022 paper found that middle-aged adults (average age 50) who reported weekly distressing dreams had a four-fold higher risk of dementia in later life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Last year, Prof Leschziner was involved in a study that linked nightmares to the early stages of autoimmune diseases such as lupus.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Such was the correlation that scientists were able to use bad dreams as an indicator that a sleeper's autoimmune disease was about to flare up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'We know that inflammation or infection anywhere in the body can give rise to nightmares, as in 'fever dreams',' Prof Leschziner explains.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'This may be a diffuse effect of chemicals called cytokines [associated with inflammation] on the brain, resulting in less stable REM sleep.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'An alternative possible explanation is direct inflammation of the brain itself disrupting the brain circuits that regulate sleep and dreaming.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mol-para-with-font mol-style-subhead femail-ccox"&gt;Why a heatwave means less sleep – but fewer nightmares&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;None of us sleeps well during a heatwave, but scientists say we're actually less likely to have nightmares in the summer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Usually, when we dream, our core body temperature is higher – above 38C. During nightmares, this elevates even more as the nervous system makes you sweat, increasing your breathing and raising your heart rate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But the evidence suggests we spend less time in REM sleep when we're hot (or feverish) already because our brain tries to cool our bodies down.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Although there's no reliable evidence to suggest the body can predict a nightmare before it begins, some say they can envisage it before they fall asleep.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Some people might feel a sense of unease, tingling or heightened awareness, but these sensations can also be associated with other sleep phenomena such as hypnagogic [pre-sleep] hallucinations or sleep paralysis,' explains Dr Ramlakhan.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;There are other ways of predicting nightmares – including looking at your family history.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Nightmares and vivid dreams can have a hereditary component,' says Dr Ramlakhan.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Studies indicate that genetics contribute to the frequency and intensity of nightmares.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Indeed, a 2019 research paper by academics at the University of Helsinki found that, in studies of twins, between 36 and 51 per cent were perfectly in-sync when it came to nightmare frequency.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mol-para-with-font mol-style-subhead femail-ccox"&gt;Want to banish bad dreams? Try the 'clock trick'&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'The good news is that nightmares can be prevented and treated,' explains Dr Otaiku.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Simple measures including avoiding scary movies, maintaining good sleep hygiene, managing stress and seeking treatment for anxiety or depression may be effective.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Other experts recommend avoiding alcohol three hours before sleep and caffeine eight hours before sleep, trying yoga or meditation, and ensuring your room is cool, calm and dark.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;For more severe cases, Dr Havens has devised a method called the 'Dream Completion Technique' (&lt;a class="" rel="noreferrer noopener" target="_blank" href="http://stopnightmares.org/"&gt;stopnightmares.org&lt;/a&gt;) – which takes two minutes to do and can cure nightmares in just one night.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;This self-help technique, his version of the more widely known imagery rehearsal therapy (IRT), involves regaining control over your dreams by imagining a new ending – 'completing' the nightmare – and cementing this in your mind before sleep.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Your imagined solution doesn't need to be moral or peaceful or something that could happen in reality,' he explains.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'It can violate the laws of physics, be surreal or feature fictional characters. It can be violent, it can be pure fantasy, or even a little bit silly.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Psychotherapist Dr Stephanie Sarkis uses the 'clock trick', which involves looking for a clock face to snap yourself out of a bad dream. Your brain isn't usually capable of producing a correct one while in a sleep state: the numbers are usually jumbled up or the arms crooked. Seek this out during a bad dream, she recommends, to remind yourself you're still asleep.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;You can teach yourself to do this while awake. If your mind is lucid enough to remember your dreams, there's no reason you can't also do this while asleep. Just by reading this sentence, says Dr Sarkis, you've already planted the idea in your unconscious.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But it's not all about managing your mind. 'Bodily comfort matters, too,' says Prof Stoneham.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Personally, I find that a single painkiller – half a dose – can help by reducing the sensation of stiffness in my joints at night, resulting in a less-disturbed sleep.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
            

            
            
            
            
            &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Daily Mail</author><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 00:26:46 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMitgFBVV95cUxPOWxINUVEUThXN2d4eEh3MFQ5cUZmeTIya2dIbmFndnlrR0JjeEZtVVA3MTg2VS1uWUlicW9hY3NqbndaUUdUUlJsWlF4MEFzU2w0TXY0bzlpX1JoaU01YzNvMVRNNEctSjhjeDFITl90aXJRNGV0QVFWNE1pdGNSWGpLN3c0bFNHdHM2bkJsZWJRdF8yeVRQVklySHRqaEg5Z3pyUlhRMV9qZnV4ZzFxVkZQMWs4QQ</guid></item></channel></rss>