<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>GNews Health</title><link>https://news.google.com/</link><description></description><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>斯德哥尔摩餐厅食物中毒爆发后四人患败血症- BBC</title><link>https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/cjd1g5y8755o</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Four people been diagnosed with sepsis after eating at a luxury restaurant in Stockholm that has been linked to a suspected listeria outbreak.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Health authorities say at least 15 people have been treated or are under observation in hospital after dining at Coco &amp;amp; Carmen, a high-end venue in the Swedish capital's Östermalm district. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Most of the dozens affected are not seriously ill, officials in Stockholm say, and so far none of those admitted to hospital have required intensive care.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;It is rare for food contaminated by listeria, a bacterium, to cause a very serious infection, known as listeriosis. People with listeriosis can develop sepsis - a life-threatening overreaction by the immune system.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;The regional authority confirmed that infection tracing, initially covering guests who ate at the restaurant between 25 and 27 September, had since been widened to include people who dined there from 23 and 24 September.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"Those with ongoing symptoms such as fever, vomiting or diarrhoea are now recommended to visit a hospital emergency room for assessment," Maria Rotzén Östlund, an infectious disease physician, told state broadcaster SVT.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Regional health officials warned in a press release that "a large number of people may have been infected" and emphasised that listeria posed the greatest risk to pregnant women, older people and those with weakened immune systems.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;SVT reports that 80 people have registered having food poisoning after dining at the restaurant with a city tracking tool between last Saturday and Thursday morning. Around 400 people have been contacted for infection tracing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Four people had sepsis but none had needed intensive care, the broadcaster quoted infectious disease specialist Maria Rotzén Östlund as saying.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Coco &amp;amp; Carmen has temporarily closed while an investigation into the cause of the suspected outbreak continues. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;The restaurant said in a statement that it had always passed food safety inspections and was co-operating with the authorities.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"We take this extremely seriously and as the well-being of our guests is our top priority, we have voluntarily closed until further notice," the owners said, adding that they hoped to reopen on 7 October.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Joakim Almquist, the chef and co-owner, told SVT: "The only thing I can do is sincerely apologise, because I suffer with these people."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Listeria is commonly found in soil, water and animals, and can spread through contaminated food, particularly when stored in cold conditions for long periods. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;While most people experience only mild symptoms resembling stomach flu, it can lead to severe illness such as meningitis or sepsis. The incubation period can stretch from several days to three weeks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BBC</author><pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 16:23:18 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiWkFVX3lxTE1VR1plSmJQRzVMbGpvNWtxS2xNSnBVakgzb3BSN3hSajA2OUN3RFBXN1Vtd1BXdDRBdDJvZHhkWkdzeW1rRU1TS3B3SFp4a3o2a0FQeTFsb2dQQdIBX0FVX3lxTE5Nb29WX3o0OFN3c0k2UWpQcEhUUldXWGdwQjdDd0lPMDByWGp2bjUwdElHeXFuQTJrWTUtbGlmV3lWa2tGTnA2emdBQm5OY0lVRVE5bkNrWG1JaGFFUFVB</guid></item><item><title>欧洲医生说，诺和，礼来减肥药应该是肥胖治疗的首选-路透社</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/novo-lilly-weight-loss-drugs-should-be-first-option-obesity-treatments-european-2025-10-02/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Reuters</author><pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 16:10:48 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi5gFBVV95cUxPRnNIcVd2M3JsdmUwcFlzTmlhcFNjbHZpbTdEdWl4ekl5RXdDR3o3eXdZVmxfT3FfSDJiV0t3WG45NU0xYTBnVWUzUHhvSzNneUY0RFoxazZqbnozTHkzMWRlVmR0d3dhcWZRcHRHNmt6S3EzUlh2ZUJmMGFXZXU5Qk96dU1EM1pBQklxdkVUSmV3d3VvdTNNNEIwZlp2QmN6dnM3dDZpMllrc3FPY25ydUFoanl6NmtUY1F2Sk8zMENjQ3Z1X3VoMmxXbGJXZXhDd3V5aUp5NFdBUVdCUmFQd1F5TXc4UQ</guid></item><item><title>新冠疫苗保护孕妇，但现在获得它们可能很难-纽约时报</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/10/02/well/covid-shots-pregnant-women.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The New York Times</author><pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 15:00:08 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMie0FVX3lxTE1BX3RCTWtCdlo2TlBfdDZJaHdXcGlTaG9hTkdJNnJyZWhNLXJlSEV5X2VONENBeHAybFpQSURjc1JvU3E0NTM5am9BT0dkbV9kRW4yOV9qRmhYcGhYN1p1ZUdmVGlIaUtNTEZaM202X0pnZzBTOGdFcm43bw</guid></item><item><title>新冠肺炎疫苗接种说明-派遣</title><link>https://thedispatch.com/article/how-to-get-covid-vaccine-explained/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;section id="article-body" class="tight-template" :class="{'text-size-sm': ui.textSize === 'sm', 'text-size-lg': ui.textSize === 'lg', 'text-size-xl': ui.textSize === 'xl'}"&gt;
    &lt;div class="rich-text core-paragraph"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Trump administration’s vaccine policies are confusing, to say the least, particularly for the COVID vaccine. Health and Human Services Secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr. told a Senate committee last month that anyone who wants a COVID vaccine &lt;a href="https://apnews.com/article/fact-check-kennedy-rfk-congress-senate-vaccines-covid-deaths-hospitals-efa457f139dabcce6f54c0ac2c590512"&gt;can get one&lt;/a&gt;. But senators from both parties said Kennedy’s policies were effectively preventing access to the shot, citing incidents of people being turned away at pharmacies. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class="rich-text core-paragraph"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Centers for Disease Control and Prevention’s Advisory Committee on Immunization Practices (ACIP) met last month, but some of its members—all selected by Kennedy—were themselves confused on how the panel’s actions affected vaccine access. Pharmacists have scrambled to determine if they are authorized to provide COVID vaccines and who is eligible to receive them.  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;    


&lt;div class="rich-text core-paragraph"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;COVID vaccine access involves a complex web of federal law, national public health guidance, and state regulations that has left even health policy scholars scratching their heads. The confusion is partly the product of a national vaccination system that has been largely unified in practice despite legal and technical distinctions between state and the federal authorities. As the Trump administration has leaned into broader skepticism about vaccines and moved to restrict federal approvals and recommendations for the COVID vaccine, the system has begun to fragment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class="rich-text core-paragraph"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Today, the COVID vaccine is broadly accessible on paper, but the confusion surrounding the administration’s policy changes has erected barriers to access in practice, particularly at pharmacies, where roughly &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/covidvaxview/weekly-dashboard/vaccinations-administered-pharmacies-medical.html"&gt;90 percent&lt;/a&gt; of COVID vaccinations last year were administered.  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class="rich-text core-paragraph"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;How did this evolve? The policy changes began in May when Kennedy &lt;a href="https://apnews.com/article/covid-vaccine-pregnant-women-children-70c358cad726e57d680234c3ecdec926"&gt;unilaterally restricted&lt;/a&gt; the CDC’s COVID recommendations. He rescinded the agency’s guidance for routine COVID vaccination for healthy children, but the CDC modified the change days later to recommend that the decision to vaccinate children between 6 months and 17 years old be discussed with a health care provider. Kennedy also rescinded the CDC’s recommendation for pregnant women to receive the COVID vaccine, effectively removing the vaccine from the schedule entirely. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class="rich-text core-paragraph"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Even though the CDC’s guidance involves recommendations rather than mandates, virtually every state pegs its vaccine policies in some way to the CDC immunization schedule and or ACIP recommendations, including what vaccines pharmacists are allowed to administer. After Kennedy’s changes, &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2025/06/12/health/covid-vaccine-pregnant-women#:~:text=Leigh%20Haldeman%2C%2033,get%20the%20shot."&gt;reports&lt;/a&gt; soon emerged of pregnant women being repeatedly denied access to the vaccine at pharmacies despite recommendations from their doctors to get the shot. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class="rich-text core-paragraph"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Unlike physicians, nurse practitioners, and physician assistants, pharmacists’ authority to vaccinate is based on state legislators, state statutes, and state regulations,” Allison Hill, the American Pharmacists Association’s (APhA) director of professional affairs, told &lt;em&gt;The Dispatch&lt;/em&gt;. “Most of those state regulations either allow pharmacists to administer [Food and Drug Administration] approved vaccines or ACIP recommended vaccines.” If healthy pregnant women are a population no longer included in the CDC’s recommendations, then pharmacy access is imperiled. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class="rich-text core-paragraph"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The next big change came in August when this year’s updated COVID shots were coming online. Vinay Prasad, a Kennedy ally and senior Food and Drug Administration (FDA) vaccine official, &lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2025/09/03/health/fda-covid-vaccines-rfk-jr.html"&gt;overruled&lt;/a&gt; agency scientists and approved the vaccines only for people over 65 or those with underlying conditions putting them at risk of severe COVID. The FDA normally determines only whether a vaccine is safe and effective, and doesn’t comment on public health recommendations for the vaccine’s deployment. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class="rich-text core-paragraph"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The change effectively made administering the shot to anyone else “off label.” And because many state regulations prevent pharmacists from providing off-label shots without a prescription, the FDA’s limited approval initially resulted in &lt;a href="https://abcnews.go.com/Health/covid-vaccine-complicated-after-new-fda-restrictions/story?id=125106993#:~:text=In%2041%20states,District%20of%20Columbia."&gt;barriers to access&lt;/a&gt; for healthy people in large states like Florida and New York and more than &lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2025/08/28/well/cvs-pharmacy-covid-vaccine-16-states.html"&gt;a dozen&lt;/a&gt; others. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class="rich-text core-paragraph"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Access was also limited by the timing gap between the FDA’s approval and a subsequent ACIP meeting on September 18-19 to consider recommendations for the year’s updated vaccines. The prevalence of state laws relying on ACIP recommendations meant that many pharmacists could not administer the latest vaccine until the committee recommended the new shots; in 2023, the panel &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/mmwr/volumes/72/wr/mm7242e1.htm#:~:text=COVID%2D19%20vaccines%20protect,and%20might%20be%20updated."&gt;issued&lt;/a&gt; recommendations the day after FDA approval.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;But when ACIP met, its recommendation—that anyone 6 months and older consult with a provider about COVID vaccination—diverged from the FDA’s guidance. ACIP’s recommendation was broader, including healthy people that were excluded by the FDA’s approval. But the committee also added the additional step of a provider consultation for people over 65 before getting the shot whereas the FDA simply approved the vaccine for that cohort.  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class="rich-text core-paragraph"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Public health researchers are uncertain about what ACIP’s updated recommendations mean for healthy pregnant women, a group excluded by Kennedy’s &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/vaccines/hcp/imz-schedules/adult-medical-condition.html#:~:text=Vaccine-,Pregnancy,-Immuno%2Dcompromised%0A(excluding"&gt;changes&lt;/a&gt; to the schedule in May. Jennifer Kates, a senior vice president at the Kaiser Family Foundation, told &lt;em&gt;The Dispatch&lt;/em&gt; that it’s ambiguous, but her understanding of the ACIP vote is that pregnant women are included in the broad recommendation. Dorit Reiss, a law professor at the University of California San Francisco whose work focuses on vaccine legal issues, told &lt;em&gt;The Dispatch&lt;/em&gt; she doesn’t think ACIP intended to include pregnant women in its votes, noting the committee did not expressly address Kennedy’s previous changes. The chair of ACIP’s COVID working group &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/live/_9ChY9SpPlY?feature=shared&amp;amp;t=17474"&gt;seemed to suggest&lt;/a&gt; during the meeting that the votes did not address the issue of vaccination for pregnant women. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class="rich-text core-paragraph"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Dispatch&lt;/em&gt; asked the CDC to clarify whether ACIP’s COVID guidance includes healthy pregnant women. “ACIP’s recommendation applies to all individuals six months and older,” an HHS spokesperson said in response to the request for comment. “It includes an emphasis that the risk-benefit of vaccination in individuals under age 65 is most favorable for those who are at an increased risk for severe COVID-19. High-risk groups [include] those who are pregnant or recently pregnant.”  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class="rich-text core-paragraph"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a result of the cascading uncertainty, &lt;a href="https://www.kff.org/covid-19/tracking-state-actions-on-vaccine-policy-and-access/"&gt;27&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.deseret.com/lifestyle/2025/09/29/dopl-pharmacists-dont-need-prescription-covid-shot-eligible-consumers-utah/"&gt;states&lt;/a&gt; have now changed regulations to safeguard vaccine access, including allowing pharmacists to administer the COVID vaccine without a prescription and re-anchoring vaccine rules to what &lt;a href="https://publications.aap.org/aapnews/news/32835/AAP-releases-evidence-based-immunization-schedule"&gt;medical&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.acog.org/news/news-releases/2025/08/acog-releases-updated-maternal-immunization-guidance-covid-influenza-rsv"&gt;associations&lt;/a&gt; recommend instead of relying on just the CDC or its vaccine advisory panel.  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class="rich-text core-paragraph"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“[States] are giving authority to our pharmacists to do this,” said Kates, who co-authored a recent &lt;a href="https://www.kff.org/covid-19/tracking-state-actions-on-vaccine-policy-and-access/"&gt;analysis&lt;/a&gt; of state vaccine changes. “It’s basically, ‘Here’s our recommendation that they can give COVID vaccines to anyone ages 3 and older. Or, we are changing … our regulation or language” to align with medical groups like the American Academy of Pediatrics and American College of Obstetricians and Gynecologists. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class="rich-text core-paragraph"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;AHIP, the health insurance industry’s trade association, &lt;a href="https://www.ahip.org/news/press-releases/ahip-statement-on-vaccine-coverage"&gt;announced&lt;/a&gt; last month that its members would continue to cover vaccines including COVID and flu shots. The announcement came the day before the ACIP meeting, reflecting both a pointed rebuke of the committee and further fragmentation of vaccine policy. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class="rich-text core-paragraph"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Most people in most states should now technically be able to get the vaccine at a pharmacy. Amy Thibault, a spokeswoman for CVS, said in a statement shared with &lt;em&gt;The Dispatch&lt;/em&gt; that the company’s pharmacies currently offer COVID vaccines to most people without a prescription in 48 states. CVS pharmacies in Georgia and Louisiana still require a prescription until the CDC formally adopts ACIP’s recommendations into the agency’s immunization schedule. Thibault added that the minimum age someone must be in order to get the vaccine at a pharmacy will vary by state rules. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class="rich-text core-paragraph"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thibault also told &lt;em&gt;The Dispatch&lt;/em&gt; that in all 50 states pharmacists are able to fulfill the “clinical decision-making” role of a provider required for COVID vaccination; HHS also said in &lt;a href="https://www.hhs.gov/press-room/acip-recommends-covid19-vaccination-individual-decision-making.html#:~:text=Individual%20decision%2Dmaking%20is%20referred%20to%20on%20the%20CDC%E2%80%99s%20adult%20and%20child%20immunization%20schedules%20as%20vaccination%20based%20on%20shared%20clinical%20decision%2Dmaking%2C%20which%20references%20providers%20including%20physicians%2C%20nurses%2C%20and%20pharmacists."&gt;a statement&lt;/a&gt; that pharmacists can serve in that role. When asked whether the new consultation requirement could create workload problems for pharmacists, she said there shouldn’t be challenges: “It’s simply a conversation between the pharmacist and patient to gauge whether the patient has any questions or concerns.” Hill, the APhA director, agreed, saying the additional burden would be marginal but adding that, “It may take a little bit longer than it used to in pharmacies because the pharmacist has to have a conversation with the patient about their overall health status, underlying conditions, and just discussion about the risk and the benefits of getting the vaccination.” &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class="rich-text core-paragraph"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But despite the state changes, confusion and uncertainty about vaccine eligibility and access are still widespread among pharmacists, doctors, and patients alike. What has emerged on the ground is patchwork access with individual pharmacies and pharmacists coming to different conclusions about administering COVID vaccines. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class="rich-text core-paragraph"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are continued &lt;a href="https://truthout.org/articles/covid-vaccines-are-hard-to-get-even-in-states-that-expanded-access/"&gt;reports&lt;/a&gt; of problems with vaccine access even in states that have adjusted their regulations and at large chain pharmacies, companies presumably best positioned to push out updated guidance to their stores. Independent pharmacy owners also are struggling to track the state and federal changes. “Each store manager is interpreting it differently and maybe each pharmacist is interpreting it differently. In the absence of standard guidance, that’s what happens,” Jennifer Avegno, the director of the New Orleans Health Department, &lt;a href="https://www.wwno.org/public-health/2025-09-25/louisiana-pharmacies-make-their-own-rules-amid-confusing-covid-guidance-its-clear-as-mud#:~:text=Dr.%20Jennifer%20Avegno,that%E2%80%99s%20what%20happens.%E2%80%9D"&gt;said&lt;/a&gt; last week. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class="rich-text core-paragraph"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Much of the problem is likely due to providers’ uncertainty navigating fragmentation in vaccine policy and &lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2025/08/27/well/covid-vaccines-guidelines-fall-2025.html#:~:text=In%20general%2C%20if,policies%20didn%E2%80%99t%20require."&gt;fears&lt;/a&gt; about taking actions &lt;a href="https://www.wwno.org/public-health/2025-09-25/louisiana-pharmacies-make-their-own-rules-amid-confusing-covid-guidance-its-clear-as-mud#:~:text=COVID%20vaccines%20are,in%20doing%20this.%E2%80%9D"&gt;they feel&lt;/a&gt; could expose them to liability or risk their licenses. National emergency authorizations and authorities exercised during the pandemic meant that pharmacists didn’t have to worry about state law versus federal guidance or even insurance coverage. “The fact that states had varying policies before, that didn’t matter in the emergency,” Kates said. “Not only was the government providing free COVID vaccines, but pharmacies, and pharmacists were all protected from any liability concern and given broad emergency authority to vaccinate anyone 3 and older, which helped get people very used to going to pharmacies [for vaccines].”  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class="rich-text core-paragraph"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Beyond access issues, the message coming from public health authorities like ACIP is that the vaccine is not recommended as routine, and Trump administration officials and advisers have &lt;a href="https://thedispatch.com/article/robert-kennedy-senate-hearing-vaccines-cdc/"&gt;amplified&lt;/a&gt; misleading and inaccurate claims about the risks of the vaccine itself. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class="rich-text core-paragraph"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Even before the current administration’s messaging on vaccines, the CDC had already begun moving away from recommending that providers and patients simply discuss whether to get the vaccine—a process known as shared clinical decision-making (SCDM)—because the framework created confusion for doctors and patients. For example, last June, ACIP voted to shift its respiratory syncytial virus (RSV) guidance away from SCDM and to routine recommendation for specific groups. ACIP working group members noted that “[c]ompared to universal recommendations, SCDM does not have a clear call to action” and “not all providers who give vaccines are comfortable with SCDM or feel it is within their scope of practice.” They cited a 2021 &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC8342675/"&gt;physician survey&lt;/a&gt; that found 76 percent of respondents thought that shared clinical decision-making creates confusion and 42 percent said they didn’t know how to implement it as intended by ACIP. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class="rich-text core-paragraph"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In August, Kennedy fired CDC Director Susan Monarez—the administration’s own pick who spent just a month on the job. Monarez testified to Congress that she was fired because she refused to preemptively rubber-stamp ACIP’s upcoming recommendations. Monarez was replaced by a senior Kennedy aide who’s currently serving as acting CDC director. But after the latest ACIP meeting, the panel’s updated COVID recommendations—while narrower than past guidance—are broader than the FDA’s and unlike Kennedy’s May changes to the CDC schedule, they appear to include healthy pregnant women. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class="rich-text core-paragraph"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;More uncertainty about vaccine access could follow if Kennedy decides to reject ACIP’s recommendations or issue new CDC recommendations of his own. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/section&gt;        
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Dispatch</author><pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 14:51:03 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMidkFVX3lxTE5LVTdwVzRDTWkwZlhoaWFlMHMwY09wVl9SOEc5YjFydXg3WGo1bmFRUTA0U1VZWkZERmV1WlhpdWN6a1BuSkdiWnRsdlhTbVB0bDl1ZGNjZENvSS0wZGFyTDhDUVhTYkJEd2I3VkdydHZTcm9DQ3c</guid></item><item><title>FDA负责人表示，预计更年期症状激素治疗的“黑匣子”警告将很快发生变化- CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2025/10/02/health/menopause-hrt-warning-change-makary</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article__content" data-editable="content" itemprop="articleBody" data-reorderable="content"&gt;
                
    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmg9fjumi000x26nq4lln7bmm@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The US Food and Drug Administration plans to make changes soon to the lengthy black box warning on many hormone replacement products for women with menopause symptoms, Commissioner Dr. Martin Makary said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmg9flcji00042e6euz6hjv88@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “We are in serious discussions now about what to do about the black box warning, and I think you’ll hear something on it very soon,” Makary told CNN Chief Medical Correspondent Dr. Sanjay Gupta in the “&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/audio/podcasts/chasing-life"&gt;Chasing Life&lt;/a&gt;” podcast.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmg9flcji00052e6eqyl89zt1@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The black box warning is the strongest type of alert the FDA puts on a drug label. Since 2003, labels of &lt;a href="https://www.fda.gov/consumers/womens-health-topics/menopause" target="_blank"&gt;menopause treatments&lt;/a&gt; that contain estrogen – including pills, patches, sprays and creams – have warned that their use can increase the risk of uterine and breast cancers, as well as strokes and blood clots. The labels also warn about an increased risk of dementia for women over the age of 65.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmg9flcji00062e6eydtauwl4@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The warning was added after &lt;a href="https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jama/fullarticle/195120" target="_blank"&gt;a large government-funded study&lt;/a&gt; found that women taking estrogen pills after menopause had higher risks for some kinds of cancers, heart disease and stroke compared with women who took a placebo. The study participants had an average age of 63, so many were past menopause when they started the therapy.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmg9flcji00072e6erd0ydgwd@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            After the study and the label change, prescriptions for hormone replacement therapy drugs for women dropped by more than 70%, and doctors became reluctant to prescribe them.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmg9flcji00082e6e5s5y60wx@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “It’s really a tragedy.&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;It’s&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;maybe one of the greatest screw-ups of modern medicine,” Makary said. “It’s resulted in 50 million women being denied this incredible therapy.”
    &lt;/p&gt;



    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmg9flcji00092e6ekav5ajnm@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The result has been undertreatment of symptoms that can be debilitating for women in midlife. In the late 1990s, more than 1 in 4 postmenopausal women were taking hormones to manage symptoms such as hot flashes, mood swings and night sweats. By 2020, that number had dropped to about 1 in 25, &lt;a href="https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jama-health-forum/fullarticle/2823976?utm_campaign=articlePDF&amp;amp;utm_medium=articlePDFlink&amp;amp;utm_source=articlePDF&amp;amp;utm_content=jamahealthforum.2024.3128" target="_blank"&gt;one study found&lt;/a&gt;.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmg9flcji000a2e6eeahhqn3l@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Newer analyses of the original study, called the Women’s Health Initiative, have since found that hormone therapy started in women younger than 60, or within 10 years of starting menopause, may safely help manage menopausal symptoms such as hot flashes and poor sleep as long as the women don’t have specific contraindications such as a history of hormone-sensitive breast or uterine cancer.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmg9flcji000b2e6eq8utzfsa@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Makary also said hormone replacement therapy may also have important benefits like reducing bone loss, heart disease risk and memory loss,
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmg9flcji000c2e6efzlmyczo@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “Women live longer and feel better on hormone replacement therapy when started before age 60,” Makary told Gupta.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmg9flcji000d2e6el3zwtay9@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The potential change follows a July &lt;a href="https://www.fda.gov/patients/fda-expert-panels/fda-expert-panel-menopause-and-hormone-replacement-therapy-women-07172025" target="_blank"&gt;meeting of experts&lt;/a&gt;, convened by the FDA, to discuss the benefits and risks of hormone replacement therapy for women. The panelists urged the agency to remove the warning label.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmg9flcji000e2e6e1gf8kh7p@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “I am begging the FDA, and all of us are begging, please remove the box label,” said Dr. JoAnn Pinkerton, a professor of obstetrics and gynecology at the University of Virginia School of Medicine. “And please stop harming women.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmg9flcji000f2e6e2vb3kdk4@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Some women’s health experts&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;say the FDA overstepped when it applied the boxed warning to all forms of estrogen replacement.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmg9flcji000g2e6ebps4216p@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “That is a real mistake,” said Dr. JoAnn Manson, a professor at Harvard Medical School and one of the principal investigators of the Women’s Health Initiative study.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmg9flcji000h2e6ezlo35gk6@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Some forms don’t raise estrogen levels in the blood, so they&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;aren’t likely to raise a woman’s cancer risk.&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;For example, studies have found that low doses of estrogen delivered by tablets, creams or rings in the vagina can safely treat symptoms of dryness, painful sex and urinary tract infections in postmenopausal women, Manson said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmg9flcji000i2e6eo8ak6a09@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The black box warning, though, may stop women from using them.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmg9flcji000j2e6ep9nps398@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “It scares them away. And even after they purchase the product, they just don’t take it,” Manson said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmg9flcji000k2e6evbrrtjuy@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “This is really where women are being tremendously undertreated and are suffering unnecessarily due to a boxed warning that is just class labeling. All hormone therapy products get exactly the same boxed warning, and it is really harming women,” said Manson, who is chief of the Division of Preventive Medicine at Brigham and Women’s Hospital.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmg9flcji000l2e6e9ijl6hnx@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Manson said it would also be reasonable for the FDA to consider removing the warnings on estrogen-containing therapies that are delivered through the skin in patches, sprays or creams to relieve the symptoms of menopause like hot flashes and night sweats. Those deliver hormones into the bloodstream, but observational studies suggest that they have a more favorable balance of risks and benefits than pills, she said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmg9flcji000m2e6ehkbfxnpm@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Manson feels less certain about removing the boxed warning from estrogen-containing pills that are taken by mouth, however.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmg9flcji000n2e6e5thizgat@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “I think that’s where it’s evidence-based and justified,” she said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmg9flcji000o2e6esv56zmbx@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            A &lt;a href="https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jama/fullarticle/2797867" target="_blank"&gt;2022 review&lt;/a&gt; by the US Preventive Services Task Force concluded that, in women who are past menopause, there was no net benefit to taking either estrogen alone – prescribed for women who’ve had their uterus removed – or a combination of estrogen and progestin – which is typically prescribed for women who still have their uterus – to prevent chronic health conditions such as heart disease and dementia.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmg9flcji000p2e6e7a4xb2au@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            What’s less clear is whether a woman who starts hormone therapies in perimenopause need to stay on them long-term to get memory, heart and bone benefits.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmg9flcji000q2e6e33aad8en@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “It’s a very good question,” said Dr. Roberta Diaz Brinton, a neuroscientist who studies estrogen’s effects on the brain at the University of Arizona. “We need to answer that.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmg9flcji000r2e6em089svhi@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Other experts say there’s not enough scientific evidence to support long-term use of hormones to prevent heart disease, Alzheimer’s disease or osteoporosis.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmg9flcji000s2e6ek7txx1zv@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            &lt;a href="https://www.ahajournals.org/doi/10.1161/CIRCULATIONAHA.122.061559" target="_blank"&gt;Four medical societies&lt;/a&gt; — the American College of Obstetricians and Gynecologists, the Menopause Society, the Endocrine Society, and the American Association of Clinical Endocrinology — support the use hormones to alleviate menopausal symptoms, but they don’t recommend continued use for preventing chronic conditions like heart disease.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmg9flcji000t2e6ew8v7t6p6@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Dr. Leslie Cho, who runs Cleveland Clinic’s Women’s Cardiovascular Center, said she’s supportive of the idea of lifting the warning from vaginal estrogen cream. “It’s never made sense on the cream,” she said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmg9flcji000u2e6e83yb1330@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            But Cho said she’s worried that some of the benefits being discussed are drawn from after-the-fact analyses of studies that weren’t designed to look at those outcomes in the first place.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmg9flcji000v2e6e30si3go3@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “I’m so glad to hear the FDA chair talk about this, because then, if that’s the case, they should do a study. They should fund a study,” she said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmg9flcji000w2e6e178cjacs@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            In a world where people can get hormones prescribed over the internet, Cho said she worries too many women could start taking hormones when they have risks like high blood pressure, obesity or high cholesterol that could overshadow the benefits. Even in younger women, studies show hormones may increase the risk of dangerous blood clots, she said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmg9flcji000x2e6e9nbxedog@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “Women have to talk to their physicians about hormone replacement therapy before they believe in all the hype that’s currently ongoing, because so much of it is hype,” she said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

              &lt;/div&gt;
                  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>CNN</author><pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 14:41:11 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMifkFVX3lxTE5ETk01UnNVZXZiSk5NbDhaekZrWmFvZkZnY2ptRXV2dkpfOFNwWGg4TGZVb3gxTUp5cWRRS21qQ1hlY0ZuN3dSU1lTaUZWaDZMQVBXNDQ5MG9weDhQQ2lIQ1VYZS1ZSzNTRXBLUHJzbWsyQUpnY3VFMFJuVmNHZw</guid></item><item><title>大约80%的心脏病是可以预防的：美国医生建议每天养成5种习惯来预防心脏病发作的风险-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/about-80-of-heart-disease-is-preventable-us-doctor-recommends-5-daily-habits-to-prevent-the-risk-of-heart-attack/photostory/124274742.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="COQxt" data-ua-type="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Heart disease continues to be one of the leading causes of death globally, but here’s the hopeful news - an estimated 80% of cardiovascular disease, including heart disease and stroke, is preventable, as per the &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://world-heart-federation.org/what-we-do/prevention/"&gt;&lt;em&gt;World Heart Federation&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. Prevention doesn’t always mean big lifestyle overhauls. Sometimes, it’s about small, thoughtful daily habits that together protect the heart.&lt;br&gt;These habits are not the usual “eat healthy, exercise more” advice repeated everywhere. They involve changes that can fit naturally into life. Here are 5 such habits experts like &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.instagram.com/reel/DPPpdA5DAjT/?igsh=YzBxa3M2eTJjc3pi"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Dr Vass, MD&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, a US-based physician, say can truly make a difference.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 14:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMitgJBVV95cUxOcmhsVmtuVXNBaE1hNDZkMWRsM0hzaVVfakU5RVp6b3R1R2FtV2tYUGNoTXp2VllBNjlRc2prdlY3dnpmc2JwbHVta0Z1U2M0a214RXRWSm5fMmN3cms2cGZIVHl1NDlTYWlwU0RlZFBSenJlLW1OMHVtVTd6aWVkS3dpeDRLa0dKZW8xY2VBU2NMa2tiZVh4b3o0M2FpRVEySEYzVEhrMVVmai1GUTFzanoyOXFCRXhPVnAyZy12Ml9GcEhWWk4xdEEzM0dOWXd5TWV5M2RHYUNFQzN6QkN5YzRSVFRNbDlZMm14OUliaC1aRG5KcVNoSlVubGI4NnF2UkZhSThjOGwwdmdVX0xvRTJvVS1wYUdHTm14Z1lSSWE2aHI3cUhFMW54NV8zcENzZUM3TEZn0gG-AkFVX3lxTE1LTEdJOTlWQUZBeTBmNWNqVExMcGFzNEtuNWJwc0xkdXllT1l6OG1QcjBlQ0Q0WnZfZDVHUXdkbVdGa3FlM3Nrd2ZPbUE2cVd4RFE0TUZld2F6UnRpX09nbkVuVFJEanVPYldIT0ZQTENuTkN2ODRoVGJzSFFHYW5xV1hJdnlhekJCTFppcUtlc0pQb3JHdjE1Z1JXZ1dxZjZuNlc3RmJBWThNZUNhS2lFTWFuWEZPMjUtS1puQ29SajZJWC1IcTd3WE5CTHZSUUNDUURNVVgzMWFTUTcxT2xMOHBwYkNuSWZ4OFVRYW9qQTR6MXlmNThXS0kybm9EZXNmaWV4Y3N4b3dkTVVaWl9rVGZ6U1Jnd0VxMnMyMFp5Ukg1aFZpbGxnV25aclpTaVZUMXNZYUM2akxSNVJBZw</guid></item><item><title>用手机上厕所的时间可能会给您带来真正的痛苦- CNET</title><link>https://www.cnet.com/tech/mobile/toilet-time-with-your-phone-could-give-you-a-real-pain-in-the-butt/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article class="c-ShortcodeContent c-ShortcodeContent-theme:default sm:u-col-2 md:u-col-6 lg:u-col-12"&gt;&lt;p class="u-speakableText-p1"&gt;We use &lt;a href="https://www.cnet.com/tech/mobile/best-phone/" target="_self"&gt;our smartphones&lt;/a&gt; just about everywhere, even in the bathroom, though we may not want to talk about that part. A &lt;a href="https://journals.plos.org/plosone/article?id=10.1371/journal.pone.0329983" target="_self"&gt;recent study&lt;/a&gt; of colonoscopy patients revealed that most used their phones on the toilet at least once a week -- and that those phone-on-the-toilet users showed a 46% increased risk for hemorrhoids.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="u-speakableText-p2"&gt;The cause and effect are clear. Caught up in news or games or social media, bathroom users stay seated on the throne longer, with research showing phone users tend to spend more than 5 minutes doing their business. The study says that hemorrhoids are associated with prolonged sitting on the toilet, as well as constipation and increased straining.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Don't miss any of our unbiased tech content and lab-based reviews. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.google.com/preferences/source?q=cnet.com#link=%7B%22role%22:%22standard%22,%22href%22:%22https://www.google.com/preferences/source?q=cnet.com%22,%22target%22:%22%22,%22absolute%22:%22%22,%22linkText%22:%22Add%20CNET%22%7D" target="_self"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Add CNET&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt; as a preferred Google source.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;The 125 colonoscopy patients at Boston's Beth Israel Deaconess Medical Center Study who participated in the study answered questions about their bathroom phone habits, and endoscopists evaluated their hemorrhoids (just in case you think you have a bad job). Of all the respondents, 66% used smartphones while sitting on the toilet, and those participants tended to be younger than those who didn't. More than one-third (37.3%) of smartphone users spent more than 5 minutes sitting on the toilet per visit, while only 7.1% of those without smartphones spent that long seated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When the numbers were adjusted for age, sex, BMI, exercise activity and "straining and fiber intake," results showed a 46% increased risk for hemorrhoids. Men were more likely than women to spend 6 minutes or more on the toilet, in case you wondered.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Those who used smartphones while on the toilet also admitted to getting less exercise than those who didn't, which the researchers said "could signify a higher level of engagement with technology and a more sedentary lifestyle outside of the toileting environment." (Yes, "toileting environment." Otherwise known as just "the toilet.")&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The most common toilet phone activity was reading news, with 54.3% admitting to doing so, and 44.4% saying they were participating in social media while on the toilet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study didn't directly connect constipation with time spent on the toilet, but Dr. Eamonn Quigley, chairman of gastroenterology at Houston Methodist, &lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2025/09/30/well/phone-use-toilet-hemorrhoids-constipation.html" target="_self"&gt;told The New York Times&lt;/a&gt; that it's likely those who sit hunched over their phones while on the toilet might be more likely to experience constipation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you're grossed out by the idea of your phone being in close connection with toilet time, you're not alone. Doctors told the NYT the obvious: Fecal material can get on your hands while you're wiping and be transferred to your phone, and flushing with the toilet lid open can also spray fecal matter onto your phone. Sure, you wash your hands, but now the stuff is on your phone, so it jumps right back on your hands after you dry them and start scrolling again.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In short, you're probably going to scroll your phone while occupied in the bathroom. But this study notes that you should be aware that the phone's fun distractions might make you sit there longer than you planned, and that could have painful consequences.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>CNET</author><pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 13:27:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiogFBVV95cUxNaW1LV0g3M29NcVROdGxzdy04SzhiVDhQM2JhMlRYWEhGdzEyWmVBb2JFczFHWXBETzlpOEpaXzdiY1ZjNUNmSUx6RGE2dmNtQVNqa0ZSOVh0aDd4Y1lyWU9BRFZlYmd1LXBqQm1Bc1JmVmRycjVnZ1U1M3VLNkZ4N05RZml4OXR5cm9PMEhVR0ItYkl1bFlFNXMtdlh1OW5ybEE</guid></item><item><title>金毛猎犬在湖边的“狩猎姿态”有粉丝称之为“顶级” - DogTime</title><link>https://dogtime.com/news/192225-golden-retriever-hunting-stance-lake-fan-reaction-video</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content wp-block-post-content is-layout-flow wp-block-post-content-is-layout-flow"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You know how every dog has their own “thing?” Some are professional couch potatoes, while others act like wannabe sprinters at the park. Then there’s Oatmeal. Not only is this &lt;a href="https://dogtime.com/dog-breeds/golden-retriever"&gt;Golden Retriever&lt;/a&gt; wholesome and comforting, just like his name, but he’s also an expert in making lake day funnier, as can be seen in this video.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;His mom, who posts about his adventures on @adriaandoatmeal, filmed him in Lake Tahoe, striking poses that honestly make him look more like a human than a dog. The clip has been making the rounds online for all the right reasons, because when Oatmeal decides to put on a show, it’s equal parts impressive and hilarious.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-owner-shows-golden-retriever-s-impressive-skills-in-lake-video"&gt;Owner shows Golden Retriever’s impressive skills in lake video&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-instagram wp-block-embed-instagram"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The video drew over 10.9K likes and plenty of comments from fans who were seriously impressed by Oatmeal’s water skills. Golden Retrievers are bred to be excellent water dogs. They are intelligent, highly trainable, and extremely focused when given a task. Oatmeal is showing off these traits by standing nearly upright in the water, three-quarters submerged.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;He shuffles his feet, balancing exceptionally well. His human is amazed: “Wait, this is actually really impressive,” she says. He then strikes a pose, leading his mom to exclaim, “This is his hunting stance, by the way.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="pb-in-article-content test-1"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Though the hunt is secretive, his mom tries to give him a mission: “Do you want to get that rock for me?” Oatmeal swims right up to her, ready for instructions. While there’s a little mix-up with which rock he’s supposed to grab, his determination doesn’t waver.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;He approaches a rock on the lake bed, feeling it out with a paw. He then dunks his head under the water to grab his prize. “Yay, good boy,” his mom cheers.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The feat is so impressive that even his friend, Crusty Carl, is seen celebrating his success. One fan called it “top-tier hunting stance.” Another commenter was equally impressed by his aquatic gymnastics: “No arm floaties and balancing on back legs is hella impressive.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;



&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>DogTime</author><pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikAFBVV95cUxNSEM0dndYdmVCazh2SGZHQjctZnRFR2dOcl9WSENZMVJEclJRaHRhQmx2b204aG8tOWMxN1MwNlpnOWRHTHRTbVhpemYzZjRyTnBpOFY5enpVY2FPY3FPb2pnVUtqSzJCc2JlMnVTc2N1RXFpVGJaVEtOY01IMHJfNGlZWFpjSldMcVJaU29sblbSAZYBQVVfeXFMUFRlSWhkWTR4UnhxUm5ON0sxc2JYaDRnRVFQM0JwNlBLRm5CNlFtaWVhWmt4dUw3R3FhNlVDM3UwRnE4M2tNbG1UcW5LWFpaUnRZUFgtSFA1OHllRHpsQ1hwNWhKbERXT09XNmV6OTdvS1A5QWdvU3VMMFdPUGNHY2pjRG1oQWlycG0tc194THFxSWtXMWF3</guid></item><item><title>尊敬的医生：大约8个月后，新冠疫苗能为我提供多少保护？ - OregonLive.com</title><link>https://www.oregonlive.com/advice/2025/10/dear-doctor-how-much-protection-does-a-covid-vaccine-give-me-after-about-8-months.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content   "&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="ZOKNW2BPMNHYRPIEAOMPABWEGE"&gt;DEAR DR. ROACH: My daughter was recently visiting and tested positive for COVID. Since my last COVID vaccine was eight months ago, I searched for how much protection I still had and understood the response to be little to none. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-1" data-gaid="inarticle-1"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="5TSLBKBR35BMNJUZR7UGW4SXMQ"&gt;So, why is the recommendation for vaccination only once per year and not more frequent so that we always have some protection? -- B.J.M.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-2" data-gaid="inarticle-2"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="F54ZCL6T75AFVDA2OQLDZP4YEM"&gt;ANSWER: The vaccine ideally provides immunity to an infection. Many of the best vaccines that we recommend provide high-level immunity against getting the disease, although there is no such thing as a perfect vaccine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-3" data-gaid="inarticle-3"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="BAWSEEXUNBD2TA5RTQCIN67YZE"&gt;The mRNA COVID vaccines provide 85% to 90% protection for the first three months or so, but the immunity wanes to only 50% to 60% effectiveness against getting the disease after six to eight months. The vaccine efficacy depends on the particular vaccine and precise variant of COVID. So, you are right that the vaccine you got eight months ago provides little protection against getting the disease now.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-4" data-gaid="inarticle-4"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="2ZROTX76ARAZLF2DUFKNI2OHZA"&gt;However, the vaccine also protects people against severe diseases and the currently circulating variants of COVID, even if it can’t protect you as well in getting the disease at all. The likelihood of hospitalization and death is decreased for much longer after vaccination, especially if a person has had multiple vaccines. This protection extends for a year and possibly longer. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-5" data-gaid="inarticle-5"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="FTMP5S3CSJDERNUMCEWERMWLDU"&gt;Getting vaccines twice yearly is not harmful and would provide more consistent (but still not perfect) protection, but once yearly vaccination does protect against severe diseases, including hospitalization and death.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-6" data-gaid="inarticle-6"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="7KLLF2HTZ5GYJHBEPTDGCTCCVM"&gt;People with immune systems that don’t work perfectly, such as the elderly, and people who are on medicines that affect the immune system (such as organ transplantation, chemotherapy, and some treatments for severe autoimmune diseases) will not respond as well to the vaccine. So, they may particularly benefit from more frequent vaccination.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-7" data-gaid="inarticle-7"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="QTDVVZ4H55BHHAASSR3F6XCJRE"&gt;Another prevention option for people with severe immune system diseases is a monoclonal antibody called pemivibart, which is given by an intravenous infusion. It can be given every three months.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-8" data-gaid="inarticle-8"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="O5Q5AGJ3NFHK7NDYSMN4Z5GKX4"&gt;The decision to get vaccinated should be up to a patient and their physician.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-9" class="middleParagraph" data-gaid="inarticle-9"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-enter:CKO4P4ZQQVGLJG2F6XF7ROMKAI" data-fusion-component="CKO4P4ZQQVGLJG2F6XF7ROMKAI"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-exit:CKO4P4ZQQVGLJG2F6XF7ROMKAI" data-fusion-component="CKO4P4ZQQVGLJG2F6XF7ROMKAI"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-10" data-gaid="inarticle-10"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="KVF24K3KTZDAFKOSBLDSBTYRO4"&gt;DEAR DR. ROACH: A beloved cousin of mine was given the wrong type of blood as a teenager and subsequently died. I, myself, am type O Rh-negative. What are the odds of this happening today, and how can this be prevented? Is this a huge problem in this country, and if one is traveling abroad, how can the hospital staff be alerted? Is the blood tested before every transfusion? -- R.P.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-11" data-gaid="inarticle-11"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="GLK64DJPEJAWLDDYBVZ7VJVFB4"&gt;ANSWER: I am very sorry about your cousin. This is an extraordinarily rare event, with four definite cases occurring in the United States (out of 10 million transfusions) in the most recently reported year. It should never happen; there are supposed to be multiple layers of protection to keep this from occurring. A person who is O-negative, like you, is at the highest risk for a transfusion reaction as you can only safely get O-negative blood.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-12" data-gaid="inarticle-12"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="5CRPQSSZWRBGXFFHR37I4NCTJQ"&gt;Blood is absolutely tested before every transfusion with limited exceptions. In a true emergency, sometimes O-negative blood is given without crossmatching. This is only the case when a person is at a very high risk of dying before crossmatching can be done. This reduces the risk of severe transfusion reactions, but there are other blood antigens beyond the ABO system.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-13" data-gaid="inarticle-13"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="HMCN6ISRCJEDTKYJK3P2QP3WBU"&gt;While developed countries have similar policies to the U.S., it is possible that the blood supply will not be as safe in underdeveloped countries.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-14" data-gaid="inarticle-14"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="NILFEPP65BBUZNVHCDXETUAVXU"&gt;* * *&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-15" data-gaid="inarticle-15"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="4K7MDEJVLZDFBHKWPZC7WFEBL4"&gt;&lt;i&gt;Dr. Roach regrets that he is unable to answer individual letters, but will incorporate them in the column whenever possible. Readers may email questions to &lt;/i&gt;&lt;a href="mailto:ToYourGoodHealth@med.cornell.edu"&gt;&lt;i&gt;ToYourGoodHealth@med.cornell.edu&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;i&gt; or send mail to 628 Virginia Dr., Orlando, FL 32803.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-16" data-gaid="inarticle-16"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="AUMP2LSRGJBWVFXGMISV4TEA2E"&gt;&lt;i&gt;(c) 2022 North America Syndicate Inc.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-17" data-gaid="inarticle-17"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="U7EQ3GITRJHTXMWUUBM53ZNYZM"&gt;&lt;i&gt;All Rights Reserved&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-18" data-gaid="inarticle-18"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--center skimlinks"&gt;If you purchase a product or register for an account through a link on our site, we may receive compensation.&lt;span&gt; By using this site, you consent to our &lt;a href="https://www.advancelocal.com/advancelocalUserAgreement/user-agreement.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;User Agreement&lt;/a&gt; and agree that your clicks, interactions, and personal information may be collected, recorded, and/or stored by us and social media and other third-party partners in accordance with our &lt;a href="https://www.advancelocal.com/advancelocalUserAgreement/privacy-policy.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Privacy Policy.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>OregonLive.com</author><pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMixwFBVV95cUxOLTBPSVVhQUQ5ejVRUTFfRHNORXZYSWhPOFlHUURPYkRtZkdGTm1ZUS0tSlJhaFdFZndER2V4ekc1Tmpvb2tuZm5lS3MxdGpMT056WC1FOVBDRzVHNVdhcERXQ2Z3cS1LQkN5X0hjMHVXcGdtZTZTT1VGRG1FRlZQM3N5RG1SSGdiMjRXLV9XNlctYllSS2NndFZVSm5XX3pvVmoyQ2hQSkpLcmxkZmM3d0xFSFdKYWtSNWx0eDh5bUxaNmp0VUNN0gHbAUFVX3lxTE12dTNGNHVtaVVzVDVnN2NxcU1QSWRyOE9PbzJrajhLYTh2RkNmS3puWWdheXl4VlJPUVJvdHVzM0F6ZW4zdlp0WGtfbVktZWJhX2tURGZnMVd5NHJWY3U1VmNWSWhYOUt1QjAwcHN3Zk45Z1B0cHMtNmZjVFM4ZE9zU0c1OHc5TWpyalJHaktOTXlhWHh6THBwakpvZUlLbUZUTWRfbUtrdzg5Y3V4Z2Q1cUd5VDZsdWxZQ0t5REhxY280d1A3b2l4akpZdERkNEdGQVV1NjVsYUIzdw</guid></item><item><title>27岁的女性在采用“水果主义”饮食后在巴厘岛酒店房间饿死|热门-印度斯坦时报</title><link>https://www.hindustantimes.com/trending/woman-27-starves-to-death-in-bali-hotel-room-after-adopting-fruitarian-diet-101759408401001.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="detail " dataid="/trending/woman-27-starves-to-death-in-bali-hotel-room-after-adopting-fruitarian-diet-101759408401001.html"&gt; &lt;div class="storyParagraphFigure"&gt; &lt;p&gt;A 27-year-old woman died of starvation in a Bali hotel room after following an extreme “fruitarian” diet that left her severely malnourished.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;figure class=""&gt; &lt;span class=""&gt; &lt;picture&gt; &lt;source media="(max-width:767px)" srcset="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/10/02/550x309/Karolina_Krzyzak_1759408689691_1759408698294.jpg" alt="At the time of her death, the 27-year-old weighed just 22 kilograms. (Instagram/@carolina.mariie)" title="At the time of her death, the 27-year-old weighed just 22 kilograms. (Instagram/@carolina.mariie)"&gt;&lt;/source&gt; &lt;img src="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/10/02/550x309/Karolina_Krzyzak_1759408689691_1759408698294.jpg" alt="At the time of her death, the 27-year-old weighed just 22 kilograms. (Instagram/@carolina.mariie)" title="At the time of her death, the 27-year-old weighed just 22 kilograms. (Instagram/@carolina.mariie)"&gt; &lt;/picture&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;figcaption&gt;At the time of her death, the 27-year-old weighed just 22 kilograms. (Instagram/@carolina.mariie)&lt;/figcaption&gt; &lt;/figure&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;p id="readMoreFTUser"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;According to a &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/36883444/student-who-adopted-fruitarian-diet-at-brit-uni-starves/" target="_blank" class="backlink" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="report"&gt;report &lt;/a&gt;by The Sun, the woman, identified as Karolina Krzyzak, had checked into the Sumberkima Hill resort in December 2024 and requested a villa with a pool. Hotel staff were immediately alarmed upon her arrival, as workers reported she was “emaciated” with sunken eyes and protruding collarbones. She had grown so weak that one evening, she had to be escorted back to her room by the night clerk as she was unable to do so herself, the staff recalled.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="mt-10 mb-10 htEchoRecirculationWidget"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="mt10 mb10 htEchoArticlePromo"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="predictorShow mb20" data-vars-predictor="true" data-vars-quiz="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="quizShow mb20" data-vars-minimized="false" data-vars-predictor="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Her deteriorating health was also evident. Her fingernails had turned yellow, her teeth had begun to rot, and her body showed signs of severe nutrient deficiency. Concerned for their guest, the hotel employees requested Karolina to seek medical help multiple times. However, each request was met with the same declinatory answer.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Then, three days into her stay, hotel workers grew concerned after receiving a message from one of Karolina’s local friends who had not heard from her since her arrival. The hotel staff rushed to check on her, but when they entered her room, they found her motionless and unresponsive. She was later declared dead from malnutrition.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;(Also Read: &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/trending/14yearold-girl-dies-after-secret-breast-enlargement-surgery-father-demands-investigation-101758815083551.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="14-year-old girl dies after secret breast enlargement surgery, father demands investigation"&gt;14-year-old girl dies after secret breast enlargement surgery, father demands investigation&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;Is a fruitarian diet dangerous?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to The Sun, at the time of her death, Karolina was suffering from osteoporosis and an albumin deficiency, both linked to prolonged malnutrition. Her friends said that she had long struggled with body image issues and had battled anorexia during her teenage years.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Then, while studying in the UK, she developed an interest in yoga and veganism, which eventually led her towards “fruitarianism” - a restrictive diet that relies almost entirely on raw fruit.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Over time, her social media posts reflected her deteriorating health, prompting her parents and friends to repeatedly urge her to seek treatment. However, despite several interventions from loved ones, she refused to abandon her extreme dietary practices.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;At the time of her death, the 27-year-old weighed just 22 kilograms.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Hindustan Times</author><pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 12:39:31 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi0gFBVV95cUxQbVNZcTY3V1h6dUZsR0JTUXZkaUJoc3kzU3E3cXhLMkJsYkVQMXBzbFU0RjlQTmFfMDZUcGpoRmxjVVhIaWVqWHNhd0RINUNsbzg5MjIwbzdJQkRtMWxwdTVXRVZSUzdIeDlsZHEzY2ZoOEtXUV9YTXQ2VXItR0pOWE82ZjFPbVprZmFNNVVuTlBCamFSU19hVVdkUG5Md1lLMFFwUl94OVZWSEoyNUx2STcwZGFKMHRnemFQNDZubTJrSTI0SG9VNXpESVZMaEdid2fSAdcBQVVfeXFMT3B0SzhTekgwVE1pczkwZlRFMjhPZW1ieTJOOTdtTFA1YkdBRkhmYm0tcFJuOTQzeC1SLUlwa3l3WVd6azZfTXA0eEo4TXFPdDRKVEVVNVhUTzZwblRhWUxGS0psR0pJcEJTdFFyZDhLU2h4LVlfRGVKdGdoUnJySXRFNmhpOXZIZ1hoR1U4Z3ctcnhEUXIyZ1J2VzFYMHEtQXFGamZ1cHAycmVKcklFRW1HVjhTU3d0UFRKeFR4cjJDamRFOUhCS2hiejhlaGY4Z3RoOUxlUlk</guid></item><item><title>新的疫苗接种图揭示了疫情爆发的风险。您的县受到保护吗？ -今日美国</title><link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/investigations/2025/10/02/vaccination-rates-drop-maps-outbreak-risks/86224099007/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="gnt_ar_b"&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;Vaccination coverage is eroding across the United States at the same time measles cases are surging, according to new county-level data compiled from state health agencies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;Measles outbreaks are infecting more people this year than in any year since the early 1990s and have already killed three. So far in 2025, all but eight states have reported measles cases, a disease the U.S. declared eliminated in 2000. Nearly 92% of these cases were among the unvaccinated or people with unknown vaccination status. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;Federal data released in July showed that childhood vaccination rates, which had remained steady for years, have declined, while the share of children exempted for religious and philosophical reasons has increased. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;“What we see is that as trust erodes, as vaccination rates drop, the first thing that you see are measles outbreaks,” said Adam Ratner, a member of the American Academy of Pediatrics’ Committee on Infectious Diseases. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;Ratner said the outbreaks should act as a public health warning system, signaling that other diseases could follow. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;“You have to look beyond that, because the diseases that are also vaccine-preventable, but maybe are a little less contagious than measles, are the ones that you'll see after that,” he said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;To assess coverage at the local level, Johns Hopkins University compiled &lt;a href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/CSSEGISandData/MMR_data/refs/heads/main/mmr_data_sources.csv" data-type="link" data-id="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/CSSEGISandData/MMR_data/refs/heads/main/mmr_data_sources.csv" data-t-l=":b|z|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;data&lt;/a&gt; from state health agencies that, in the absence of a federal database, sheds light on how vulnerable communities are to outbreaks. USA TODAY later expanded this effort by adding data for states missing from the university's database and filling gaps.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;An analysis of this combined data, covering counties in 41 states, showed that routine vaccine coverage among children has slipped in most counties, leaving more communities vulnerable today than before the pandemic. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;In at least three out of four counties, vaccination coverage is below 95%, an immunity threshold experts say is needed to prevent widespread outbreaks. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;“The fact that there are so many counties below this threshold means there is a lot of exposure risk,” said Lauren Gardner, director of Johns Hopkins University's Center for Systems Science and Engineering. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;“It doesn’t mean there’s definitely going to be an outbreak, but the risk is higher if a case is introduced in a community,” she added. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;Experts also warn that when coverage falls below 90%, the risk of outbreaks rises sharply. Children who are immunocompromised or too young to be vaccinated rely on community immunity, they say. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;Today, about 63% of counties meet that minimum threshold, compared to 84% before the pandemic.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;The data, together with interviews with public health experts, underscore that skepticism around the COVID-19 vaccine has seeped into broader attitudes toward immunization, worsened by the spread of misinformation and disinformation. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;Vaccine skeptics falsely claim that the measles vaccine causes autism, a &lt;a href="https://publichealth.jhu.edu/2025/the-evidence-on-vaccines-and-autism" data-type="link" data-id="https://publichealth.jhu.edu/2025/the-evidence-on-vaccines-and-autism" data-t-l=":b|z|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;claim repeatedly disproven by extensive scientific research&lt;/a&gt;. Regardless, rising vaccine skepticism has discouraged parents from vaccinating their children against dangerous diseases. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;A September &lt;a href="https://www.kff.org/public-opinion/new-kff-washington-post-survey-explores-parents-trust-in-and-confusion-about-childhood-vaccines-as-the-trump-administration-revamps-federal-policies/" data-type="link" data-id="https://www.kff.org/state-health-policy-data/a-look-at-recent-changes-to-state-vaccine-requirements-for-school-children/" data-t-l=":b|z|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;Kaiser Family Foundation–Washington Post survey&lt;/a&gt; found that 9% of parents believe the false claim linking the MMR vaccine to autism, and nearly half are unsure what to believe. About one in six parents reported delaying or skipping vaccines (excluding seasonal flu and COVID-19), often citing safety concerns or distrust. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;Parents who identify as Republican, younger, or homeschool their children are among the most likely to delay or skip vaccines, the survey found. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;The Centers for Disease Control and Prevention &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/measles/hcp/vaccine-considerations/index.html" data-type="link" data-id="https://www.cdc.gov/measles/hcp/vaccine-considerations/index.html" data-t-l=":b|z|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;recommends two doses of the MMR vaccine&lt;/a&gt; for children: first at 12–15 months, then at 4–6 years. The agency also recommends vaccines for polio, chickenpox, and hepatitis B, a viral infection affecting the liver. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;Public health experts say these recommendations are facing challenges under Health Secretary &lt;a target="_blank" href="/news/politics/robert-f-kennedy-jr/" data-autotag="1eef402e-8d6b-4ca9-ae4b-46a1674522c3" rel="noopener" data-t-l=":b|e|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;Robert F. Kennedy Jr.&lt;/a&gt;, an outspoken vaccine critic. Kennedy fired all 17 members of the CDC’s Advisory Committee on Immunization Practices (ACIP) in June, replacing some with vaccine skeptics. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;The ACIP has &lt;a href="/story/news/health/2025/09/18/rfk-vaccine-panel-hepatitis-b-mmrv-babies/86199355007/" data-type="link" data-id="https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/health/2025/09/18/rfk-vaccine-panel-hepatitis-b-mmrv-babies/86199355007/" data-t-l=":b|e|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;already changed the MMRV (measles, mumps, rubella, and varicella) vaccine schedule&lt;/a&gt;, removing the recommendation for children under 4. The committee also considered changes to hepatitis B recommendations, but a vote was delayed. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;Experts warn these shifts could add confusion and further erode vaccination rates, even as clarity on vaccine safety and access remains critical. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;To that end, Ratner said, granular data collected by Johns Hopkins University and USA TODAY is important for identifying vulnerable populations. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;“Often people will look at state rates, which are important,” Ratner said. “But really what we find is that what matters is much more local rates — at the level of the county or even smaller.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;The Johns Hopkins University-USA TODAY data is based on county-level vaccination compliance among kindergarteners — and, in a few cases, K–6 or K–12 students — covering either MMR vaccinations or all doses required for school enrollment.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;There are caveats: record collection varies by state, so state-by-state comparisons should be made cautiously. Because some agencies track students’ compliance with vaccine requirements — not actual vaccination status — the true vaccination rate could be lower than reported in those instances. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;For example, Oregon excludes exempted students in completion rates, while Wisconsin doesn’t. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;“A student can be compliant with the school law either by being up to date on vaccines or by submitting a waiver, so school compliance rates could be higher than the vaccination rate of the school population,” said Jennifer Miller, spokesperson for the Wisconsin Department of Health Services. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;Measles once sickened millions of Americans and killed hundreds each year. In the 1960s, the U.S. launched its vaccination program, eventually eradicating measles before the turn of the century. By 1980, all 50 states had adopted school vaccine mandates, requiring children to be vaccinated before enrollment. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;Measles is particularly dangerous because it can spread before symptoms appear. Even with a low fatality rate, the virus can cause lasting complications, including brain damage, neurological problems, and blindness. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;As of September 30 this year, the U.S. has reported nearly 1,550 measles cases, surpassing totals from any outbreak since the early 1990s. Only 2019, when the disease spread through unvaccinated communities in New York, comes close. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;The first outbreak in 2025 occurred in the Mennonite community in Gaines County, Texas, where vaccination rates are low. The virus then spread across West Texas, New Mexico, and Oklahoma. Gaines County has reported 414 cases this year, nearly a quarter of the national total. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;There, vaccination coverage among kindergartners has averaged around 82.4% in recent years, 12.6 points below what experts call community immunity. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;Before the COVID-19 pandemic, 57% of counties were considered fully protected against outbreaks. That figure has since dropped to 25%.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;The decline in coverage spanned nearly three-quarters of counties, with each experiencing an average four-point drop. Only two states, Connecticut and Maryland, now have every county above the immunity threshold, while nine in 10 counties in Maine and New York meet it. No counties clear the bar in Alaska, Hawaii, Idaho, Utah, or Wisconsin — the same states with high exemption rates. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;In July, the CDC estimated that &lt;a href="/story/life/health-wellness/2025/08/25/kids-back-to-school-vaccine-rates-exemptions/85629130007/" data-type="link" data-id="https://www.usatoday.com/story/life/health-wellness/2025/08/25/kids-back-to-school-vaccine-rates-exemptions/85629130007/" data-t-l=":b|e|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;nearly 286,000 kindergarteners lacked proof of completing the MMR vaccine&lt;/a&gt; series during the 2024–25 school year. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;Meanwhile, more parents are exempting their children from vaccination on religious or philosophical grounds, though medical exemptions have remained flat. Non-medical exemption rates rose to 3.4% in 2024–25, up from 2% a decade ago. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;Even small increases can have a big impact, said Elizabeth Williams, senior policy manager at Kaiser Family Foundation’s Program on Medicaid and the Uninsured. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;“Every increase reduces the ability to reach the threshold that scientists believe protects the community,” Williams said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;Experts recommend keeping exemption rates below 5%, yet 17 states now exceed that level. Idaho leads at 15%, followed by Utah and Oregon at 10% each, and Arizona and Alaska at 9%. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;“Rising exemption rates are concerning; especially if you work under the assumption that a child who has an exemption on file with their school is unvaccinated,” said AJ McWhorter, a spokesperson for Idaho Department of Health and Welfare.   &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;“During a vaccine-preventable disease outbreak, then there are more children who would be at risk for contracting the disease and who would presumably need to be excluded from school,” McWhorter said.   &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;Policy shifts may further lower vaccination rates. Many states have introduced changes that make it easier for families to obtain waivers. Florida &lt;a href="/story/news/politics/2025/09/03/ron-desantis-florida-vaccine-requirements/85956743007/" data-t-l=":b|e|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;plans to remove the mandate entirely&lt;/a&gt; from public schools. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;Since 2021, lawmakers nationwide have &lt;a href="https://www.ncsl.org/state-legislatures-news/details/vaccine-policy-remains-a-topic-of-interest-for-state-legislatures" data-type="link" data-id="https://www.ncsl.org/state-legislatures-news/details/vaccine-policy-remains-a-topic-of-interest-for-state-legislatures" data-t-l=":b|z|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;introduced over 2,500 vaccine-related bills&lt;/a&gt;, almost half targeting requirements like mandates or school exemptions, according to the National Conference of State Legislatures.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;These state-level changes, alongside the shift in federal guidance, continued misinformation and access challenges, will make the situation worse, epidemiologists at the Oregon Health Authority said in an email. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;Public health is a community responsibility, Gardner, the Johns Hopkins expert, said. “Everyone has to be in on it, because otherwise it doesn't really work.”   &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_s gnt_ar_s0"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_s gnt_ar_s25"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_s gnt_ar_s50"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_s gnt_ar_s75"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_s gnt_ar_s100"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>USA Today</author><pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 12:10:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiuAFBVV95cUxQbS1JbmVXYi0yMXRjalRVNFY0NDRudmhQZ2FOckdWajY1SzR0VDB4bElwVnJ1R3BDamk3N3BCV0ZYckt4d0o3MG05UnVub2lCRVJ3S2xDWTktSE5mWjJuSlV5R3pkV0NuLXN5ckh3WnBlYVItX2tidDBRa254Q3ZERDR3VnVIRDVtTjVMMTBVQXJnd2Q1UEtXbjFUNHlfTFhwLXZsRnV4dWkwckYwdTU3MWtRYnhOMjJy</guid></item><item><title>为什么被曼巴咬很糟糕- Gizmodo</title><link>https://gizmodo.com/why-getting-bit-by-a-mamba-sucks-extra-bad-2000666473</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content prose dark:prose-invert lg:prose-xl "&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;New research reveals that three venomous snake species—including one of the most venomous snakes in the world—are even worse than we thought. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;As if &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.britannica.com/animal/mamba"&gt;&lt;span&gt;mambas&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;—large, highly venomous arboreal snakes in sub-Saharan Africa—weren’t bad enough, researchers have discovered that the venoms of three mamba species have a nasty one-two-punch attack that explains why antivenoms sometimes don’t work. The study reveals that the venoms are more neurologically complex than previously believed, with significant implications for antivenom treatments. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="not-prose my-8 -mx-5 xs:max-w-xs xs:mx-auto"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“The Black Mamba, Western Green Mamba and Jamesons Mamba snakes aren’t just using one form of chemical weapon, they’re launching a coordinated attack at 2 different points in the nervous system,” Bryan Fry, a biologist at the University of Queensland and a co-author of a study published late last month in the journal &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.mdpi.com/2072-6651/17/10/481"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Toxins&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;, said in a university statement. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;h2&gt;The solution to a clinical mystery&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Mamba snake bites are responsible for 30,000 deaths every year, according to the statement. If you’re unlucky enough to be bitten by one of the aforementioned three mamba species, you’ll experience flaccid or limp paralysis. The good news is that limp paralysis is treatable by current antivenoms. The bad news is that, according to the study, these venoms then attack another part of the nervous system, triggering spastic paralysis. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“The venom first blocks nerve signals from reaching the muscles but after the antivenom is administered, it then overstimulates the muscles. It’s like treating one disease and suddenly revealing another,” Fry explained. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The study solves an enduring mystery regarding mamba victims; some patients initially seem to get better with antivenom but then start experiencing painful, uncontrolled spasms. Before this study, the researchers thought it was only the fourth species of mamba—the Eastern Green Mamba—capable of triggering spastic paralysis. Talk about a nasssssty sssssurprise. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;h2&gt;A call for specialized antivenom&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;But wait, there’s more bad news!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“We also found the venom function of the mambas was different depending on their geographic location, particularly within populations of the Black Mamba from Kenya and South Africa,” Lee Jones, a co-author of the study and a PhD candidate at the University of Queensland, said in the statement. “This further complicates treatment strategies across regions because the antivenoms are not developed to counteract the intricacies of the different venoms.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Researchers should now seek to create specialized antivenoms to improve outcomes, Fry said. Investigating venom dynamics and the limits of current antivenoms has obvious implications for snakebite treatment, the researcher concluded. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;“This kind of translational venom research can help doctors make better decisions in real time and ultimately save lives.”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;P.S. What’s a snake’s favorite dance? The mamba!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;      &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Gizmodo</author><pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 11:50:50 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMifkFVX3lxTE1QMW1fa2lRYW9fUzZEVUU1bXBCWjVkVDdvWS1TN1BYMWZCbGpISXhwOVoyRFFya1pfMWt0LU5XVkpydGtEY0piWllESWNIRjBmM1Z5UGJUc2xmMzlMcTdwTzFoYUpjVzN3VHV5QXV2TnBnczVUR2F6LW1RajlKZw</guid></item><item><title>独家：前CDC主任谈论她被解雇的原因-自然</title><link>https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-025-03179-1</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article__teaser" data-test="access-teaser"&gt; &lt;figure class="figure"&gt;&lt;picture class="embed intensity--high"&gt;&lt;source type="image/webp" srcset="//media.nature.com/lw767/magazine-assets/d41586-025-03179-1/d41586-025-03179-1_51502938.jpg?as=webp 767w, //media.nature.com/lw319/magazine-assets/d41586-025-03179-1/d41586-025-03179-1_51502938.jpg?as=webp 319w" sizes="(max-width: 319px) 319px, (min-width: 1023px) 100vw,  767px"&gt;&lt;/source&gt;&lt;img class="figure__image" alt="Susan Monarez poses for a portrait leaning on a wooden bridge with an old stone building behind her" loading="lazy" src="//media.nature.com/lw767/magazine-assets/d41586-025-03179-1/d41586-025-03179-1_51502938.jpg"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;p class="figure__caption u-sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span class="mr10"&gt;Susan Monarez was fired from her role as director of the US Centers for Disease Control and Prevention after refusing to strip staff members of their jobs.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Credit: Alyssa Schukar for &lt;i&gt;Nature&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/picture&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;When &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-025-03014-7" data-track="click" data-label="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-025-03014-7" data-track-category="body text link"&gt;Susan Monarez&lt;/a&gt; took the helm of the beleaguered US Centers for Disease Control and Prevention (CDC) in late July, she had her work cut out for her. Public trust in the agency had dropped considerably since the start of the COVID-19 pandemic. And US health secretary &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-025-00439-y" data-track="click" data-label="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-025-00439-y" data-track-category="body text link"&gt;Robert F. Kennedy Jr, who oversees the CDC&lt;/a&gt;, had called the agency a “cesspool of corruption” that needed to be fundamentally rebuilt.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Less than a month into Monarez’s tenure, US President Donald Trump fired her. She had lost the trust of Kennedy, who only a month earlier had said he had “full confidence” in her ability to lead the agency and that she had “unimpeachable scientific credentials”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This conflict spilled into public view when each presented their version of events to US senators at separate hearings on Capitol Hill in Washington DC. Monarez was dismissed, she said, for refusing to fire top scientists at the agency or pre-approve vaccine recommendations without first considering the relevant scientific data. &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-025-02845-8" data-track="click" data-label="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-025-02845-8" data-track-category="body text link"&gt;Kennedy testified that Monarez had told him that she wasn’t trustworthy&lt;/a&gt;, so he ousted her.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kennedy had also told Monarez that CDC employees were “killing children and they don’t care”, were “bought by the pharmaceutical industry” and “forced people to wear masks and social distance like a dictatorship”, she testified. These alleged comments came after a deadly shooting at the CDC headquarters in Atlanta, Georgia, soon after she became director. The gunman, who targeted the campus to protest &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-021-00290-x" data-track="click" data-label="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-021-00290-x" data-track-category="body text link"&gt;COVID-19 vaccines&lt;/a&gt;, killed police officer David Rose and shattered some 150 windows. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The past few months, Monarez says, have included both “the highlights of my professional career” and the “absolute worst days of my life”. In an exclusive interview — her first since she became CDC director — she tells &lt;i&gt;Nature&lt;/i&gt; about the consequential decisions that cost her the job and what’s next for public health in a politicized world.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The CDC director is an “inherently political position, but that doesn’t mean that it has to be politically compromised”, says Monarez, who is an immunologist and microbiologist. “The CDC is far too important to just give up on.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Before our call, you sent me a photo that seems to be of you as a child with your father and siblings sitting on a tractor with a barn in the background. What was that about?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;I grew up in rural America, in a family that didn’t have many resources — my dad was a dairy farmer. You live without expecting to have the privileges and material possessions that so many people have. We just knew that you worked hard. You got up early and you treated people with kindness. We lived at or below the poverty line for a long time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;My parents, they’re still alive, thankfully. But they’ve never been wealthy, and they don’t have the advantages of immediate access to high-quality health care, and so I see them still struggling today. When we’re talking in Washington DC, we have to remember that there are millions and millions of Americans like my parents. We can’t leave them behind.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Before the CDC, you worked at the &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-023-00817-4" data-track="click" data-label="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-023-00817-4" data-track-category="body text link"&gt;Advanced Research Projects Agency for Health&lt;/a&gt; (ARPA-H), a government agency supporting high-risk, high-reward biomedical research. How did that work inform your priorities for CDC?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;So much of what we built at ARPA-H was free from all of the bureaucratic impediments. We gave ourselves permission to ask: ‘What if we could change the world?’ I wanted to bring that mindset to CDC.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Just eight days into your tenure, there was a deadly shooting at CDC headquarters that terrified many members of your staff. Tell me about that experience.&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The first week was probably one of the highlights of my entire professional career — meeting hundreds of CDC employees who wanted to make a difference and change the world. I got on the plane to come back to [Washington] DC. And I finally got WiFi just before we landed, and all these texts had started coming through: ‘Something’s happening here, we’re hearing there’s a shooter.’ &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;article class="recommended pull pull--left u-sans-serif" data-label="Related"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-025-03014-7" class="u-link-inherit" data-track="click" data-track-label="recommended article"&gt;&lt;img class="recommended__image" alt="" src="//media.nature.com/w400/magazine-assets/d41586-025-03179-1/d41586-025-03179-1_51459098.jpg"&gt;&lt;p class="recommended__title u-serif"&gt;Three ways ex-CDC chief says that Trump team is sidelining science&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was the most surreal, painful change between this extraordinary enthusiasm of ‘we’re going to change the world with the most amazing people’ to ‘has anyone been killed?’&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;[As I spoke to more CDC staff,] it looked like most were OK, but highly traumatized, because so many people were literally in the line of fire. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;My father — after we lost the farm — became a police officer. It was so near and dear to my heart, the willingness of these police officers to sacrifice themselves. I couldn’t stop thinking about Officer Rose losing his life. It could have been my dad. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This wasn’t an abstract, faraway thing. These were real humans who were targeted with real bullets that were not intended for buildings — they were intended to cause harm. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What do you make of Kennedy’s characterizations of CDC employees, such as his suggestion they have been ‘bought by the pharmaceuticals industry’?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;I did not meet a single human that embodied that rhetoric. They could be making a lot more money [in the private sector].&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I am worried about the context that we’re placing on our public-health officials, who just want to help people. To contextualize it any other way is to do them such an extraordinary disservice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;How are we going to incentivize our best and our brightest to contribute to public health, which is thankless? And what happens if we don’t?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;You also testified that Kennedy had asked you to pre-approve vaccine recommendations that hadn’t yet been made. Was that the main sticking point for you?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;And firing scientists without cause. [At CDC, I] had been with selfless, brilliant, amazing people who just wanted to contribute to wellness. We had already started talking about, ‘How do we restore public trust?’ because ‘just trust us’ doesn’t work any more. So it was [against] that backdrop and then being told I had to fire these people without cause that — as a human, I wouldn’t do that. And as a leader, I wouldn’t do that.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And being asked to commit [wholeheartedly] without evidence — I would never do that, as a scientist. You have to gather the right data.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;[Emily Hilliard, a spokesperson for Kennedy’s agency, the Department of Health and Human Services, said in a statement to &lt;i&gt;Nature&lt;/i&gt; last month that Monarez “acted maliciously to undermine the president’s agenda and was fired as a result”. Kennedy conceded, in remarks to Congress, that he had asked Monarez to fire CDC staff members.]&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;At least ten states say they can no longer trust the CDC and have formed their own alliances, one on the West Coast and one in the Northeast. What do you make of these efforts?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;These states are worried about the people who live in their communities. They’re worried about whether they will be able to help to prevent public-health harms. I understand their concerns. It is a reflection of [how much some people can trust] what’s emanating from the federal government.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Isn’t this in some ways playing directly into what this administration is pushing for — a dismantling of the federal government in favour of states’ rights? Is that compatible with the fundamental principles of public health?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Public health doesn’t respect state boundaries. We do need to find a way to work together. I’ll go back to my own upbringing. The rural community where I grew up could easily be left behind [if access to high-quality healthcare is available in one state but not another] and we don’t want that.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
                        &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Nature</author><pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 11:24:01 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiX0FVX3lxTFAyXzBySWVyVXYzejlLQm1WUDNGX3I3RWJ1UWk3WUQ1Wk9Pc1VwRmtTZnQzZFpOTDhuNnR0QnhTNGtKemRRTGRyVzl4cllnSXdPZzJmdDhGQkZRa3RJY3Vv</guid></item><item><title>蔗糖实际上比高果糖玉米糖浆更健康吗？ - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffpost.com/entry/is-cane-sugar-healthier-than-high-fructose-corn-syrup_l_68cc1c8fe4b0aa8d99fe99fc</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;section class="entry__content-list js-entry-content js-cet-subunit"&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Coca-Cola has announced it’s releasing&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2025/07/22/food/coca-cola-cane-sugar-launch-earnings" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name=" a new Coke product" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68cc1c8fe4b0aa8d99fe99fc" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.cnn.com/2025/07/22/food/coca-cola-cane-sugar-launch-earnings" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="0"&gt; a new Coke product&lt;/a&gt; this fall that’s sweetened with cane sugar rather than high-fructose corn syrup. The announcement followed a July Truth Social post in which &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://truthsocial.com/@realDonaldTrump/posts/114864763487869986" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="President Donald Trump " data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68cc1c8fe4b0aa8d99fe99fc" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://truthsocial.com/@realDonaldTrump/posts/114864763487869986" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="1"&gt;&lt;span&gt;President Donald Trump &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;claimed he convinced Coke to change its product.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;To be fair, we don’t know whether Trump thinks cane sugar just tastes better, or whether he wanted to improve Coke’s nutritional profile, or if the decision was driven by political reasons. But regardless,&lt;span&gt; this move has been hailed as a victory by Health and Human Services Secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr. and his Make America Healthy Again Commission.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;But is cane sugar really any better than high-fructose corn syrup (HCFS), from a nutritional perspective? The evidence strongly points to no. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Here’s why: While HFCS definitely doesn’t do any favors for human health, neither does cane sugar. Too much added sugar — regardless of which type or what food it’s in — can cause spikes in blood sugar levels and has been linked with many different chronic health conditions, from type 2 diabetes to &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0002916524000017" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="heart disease" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68cc1c8fe4b0aa8d99fe99fc" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0002916524000017" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="2"&gt;&lt;span&gt;heart disease&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; and &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.thelancet.com/journals/lancet/article/PIIS0140-6736(16)30617-1/abstract" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="obesity" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68cc1c8fe4b0aa8d99fe99fc" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.thelancet.com/journals/lancet/article/PIIS0140-6736(16)30617-1/abstract" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="3"&gt;&lt;span&gt;obesity&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;. Soda, which is loaded with added sugars, is an &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://ajph.aphapublications.org/doi/full/10.2105/AJPH.2012.300974" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="unhealthy" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68cc1c8fe4b0aa8d99fe99fc" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://ajph.aphapublications.org/doi/full/10.2105/AJPH.2012.300974" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="4"&gt;&lt;span&gt;unhealthy&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; food choice whether it’s sweetened with high-fructose corn syrup or cane sugar. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure class="cli cli-image js-no-inject"&gt;&lt;p class="cli-image__spacer"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="cli-image__source-wrapper"&gt;&lt;div class="cli-image__credit" aria-label="Image Credit: Maria Korneeva via Getty Images"&gt;&lt;p class="credit-container"&gt;&lt;span class="credit"&gt;Maria Korneeva via Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption class="cli-image__caption caption-cli"&gt;Coca-Cola has announced it's releasing&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2025/07/22/food/coca-cola-cane-sugar-launch-earnings" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name=" a new Coke product" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68cc1c8fe4b0aa8d99fe99fc" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.cnn.com/2025/07/22/food/coca-cola-cane-sugar-launch-earnings" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="5"&gt; a new Coke product&lt;/a&gt; this fall that’s sweetened with cane sugar rather than high-fructose corn syrup.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“Replacing cane sugar with high-fructose corn syrup does not have any meaningful effect on health — including blood pressure, glucose metabolism or any measure of cardiometabolic health,” said &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://nutritionwithmaddie.com/about" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Maddie Pasquariello" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68cc1c8fe4b0aa8d99fe99fc" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://nutritionwithmaddie.com/about" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="6"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Maddie Pasquariello&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;, a New York City-based registered dietitian (RD).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Here’s what you need to know about cane sugar and HFCS — and why one isn’t really any healthier than the other, with expertise shared by registered dietitians. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What’s the difference between high-fructose corn syrup and cane sugar?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;From a chemistry standpoint, high-fructose corn syrup and cane sugar are both sugars, and they’re pretty similar, including containing the same number of calories &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;— about 4 per gram.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Let’s start with cane sugar. As the name implies, cane sugar is made from the sugarcane plant, and is made up of sucrose, the most common type of sugar. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://pubchem.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/compound/sucrose" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Sucrose" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68cc1c8fe4b0aa8d99fe99fc" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://pubchem.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/compound/sucrose" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="7"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Sucrose&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; is formed through the joining of two simple sugars — glucose and fructose (both monosaccharides) — which makes it a disaccharide.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;blockquote class="cli cli-pullquote"&gt;&lt;p class="cli-pullquote__placeholder"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="cli-pullquote__content"&gt;&lt;p class="cli-pullquote__quote accent-cli"&gt;“Replacing cane sugar with high-fructose corn syrup does not have any meaningful effect on health.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="cli-pullquote__attribution caption-cli"&gt;- Maddie Pasquariello, RD&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.fda.gov/food/food-additives-petitions/high-fructose-corn-syrup-questions-and-answers" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="High-fructose corn syrup" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68cc1c8fe4b0aa8d99fe99fc" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.fda.gov/food/food-additives-petitions/high-fructose-corn-syrup-questions-and-answers" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="8"&gt;High-fructose corn syrup&lt;/a&gt; is a sweetener made from corn syrup. Nutritionally, HFCS is very similar to table sugar (sucrose), which is also made of glucose and fructose in roughly a 50/50 split. &lt;span&gt;However, unlike sucrose, which is a disaccharide (where the two sugars are bonded together), HFCS contains glucose and fructose as individual monosaccharides. In high-fructose corn syrup, “the two are not bonded together and the ratio might be slightly different than 50/50 in the overall product,” Pasquariello said.&lt;/span&gt; Because of its sweetness, stability and low cost, HFCS is commonly used in the food industry, especially in sodas, packaged snacks, condiments and desserts. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Are there health benefits to consuming drinks made with cane sugar rather than high-fructose corn syrup?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Despite any claims you may have heard from cane sugar advocates&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt; — such as those &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://x.com/SecKennedy/status/1946694089954771123" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="calling" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68cc1c8fe4b0aa8d99fe99fc" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://x.com/SecKennedy/status/1946694089954771123" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="9"&gt;&lt;span&gt;calling&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; high-fructose corn syrup &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/health/2025/07/22/coke-cane-sugar-health-rfk-jr/" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="poison" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68cc1c8fe4b0aa8d99fe99fc" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.washingtonpost.com/health/2025/07/22/coke-cane-sugar-health-rfk-jr/" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="10"&gt;&lt;span&gt;poison&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;, or suggesting it is uniquely harmful to the liver and more strongly linked to chronic illnesses like obesity and type 2 diabetes —&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;there aren’t any benefits to consuming cane sugar rather than HFCS. Both sweeteners have similar effects on the body when consumed in similar amounts. “Your body cannot tell the difference once they are broken down and enter the bloodstream,” Pasquariello said. “Calorically, metabolically — it doesn’t matter.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;According to&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.fda.gov/food/food-additives-petitions/high-fructose-corn-syrup-questions-and-answers" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="the FDA" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68cc1c8fe4b0aa8d99fe99fc" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.fda.gov/food/food-additives-petitions/high-fructose-corn-syrup-questions-and-answers" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="11"&gt; &lt;span&gt;the FDA&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;, high-fructose corn syrup isn’t any less safe&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt; in terms of how it’s metabolized by the body &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;than cane sugar and other common sweeteners like honey. Some critics have&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cspi.org/article/high-fructose-corn-syrup" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="blamed HFCS for rising obesity rates" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68cc1c8fe4b0aa8d99fe99fc" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.cspi.org/article/high-fructose-corn-syrup" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="12"&gt; &lt;span&gt;blamed HFCS for rising obesity rates&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;, pointing to a trend of rising obesity rates at the same time as increasing consumption of HFCS. But nutrition experts say that claim is unfounded. In the book “&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.awin1.com/cread.php?awinmid=92005&amp;amp;awinaffid=837483&amp;amp;campaign=&amp;amp;clickref=68cc1c8fe4b0aa8d99fe99fc&amp;amp;ued=https%3A%2F%2Fbookshop.org%2Fp%2Fbooks%2Funsavory-truth-how-food-companies-skew-the-science-of-what-we-eat-marion-nestle%2F12787680&amp;amp;platform=pl" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Unsavory Truth:" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68cc1c8fe4b0aa8d99fe99fc" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.awin1.com/cread.php?awinmid=92005&amp;amp;awinaffid=837483&amp;amp;campaign=&amp;amp;clickref=68cc1c8fe4b0aa8d99fe99fc&amp;amp;ued=https%3A%2F%2Fbookshop.org%2Fp%2Fbooks%2Funsavory-truth-how-food-companies-skew-the-science-of-what-we-eat-marion-nestle%2F12787680&amp;amp;platform=pl" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="13"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Unsavory Truth:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; How Food Companies Skew the Science of What We Eat,” nutritionist and public health expert Marion Nestle pointed out that while the increasing use of high-fructose corn syrup in the food supply occurred alongside increasing obesity rates, this is an association, but not necessarily a cause. “In reality, both sucrose and HFCS are sugars,” she wrote. “Both are best consumed in small amounts.” &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Added sugars contain calories, but other than that they’re &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC4975866/" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="devoid of vitamins and minerals" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68cc1c8fe4b0aa8d99fe99fc" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC4975866/" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="14"&gt;&lt;span&gt;devoid of vitamins and minerals&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; that support healthy bodily functioning. Consuming a beverage sweetened with 25 grams of added sugar from cane sugar has the same impact on the body as a beverage sweetened with 25 grams of added sugar from HFCS. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S2161831322011085" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Research shows" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68cc1c8fe4b0aa8d99fe99fc" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S2161831322011085" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="15"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Research shows&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; that when comparing cane sugar (sucrose) and high-fructose corn syrup, there aren’t significant differences in terms of the body’s metabolic or endocrine responses and adverse health outcomes like obesity. Because of this, removing HFCS from food production wouldn’t have a meaningful impact on the metabolism, health or obesity rates of Americans, explained RD &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.missouristate.edu/StrategicCommunication/profile-display.aspx?p=JaimeGnau" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Jaime Gnau" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68cc1c8fe4b0aa8d99fe99fc" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.missouristate.edu/StrategicCommunication/profile-display.aspx?p=JaimeGnau" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="16"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Jaime Gnau&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;, clinical assistant professor in the School of Health Sciences at Missouri State University. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“What makes a difference for health is your overall added sugar consumption on a long-term basis — not the source of the sugar,” Pasquariello said. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Simply put: swapping out high-fructose corn syrup for cane sugar likely isn’t going to benefit your health. But cutting back on sugar-sweetened beverages and &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://policysearch.ama-assn.org/policyfinder/detail/H-150.919%20?uri=%2FAMADoc%2FHOD.xml-H-150.919.xml" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="limiting added sugars" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68cc1c8fe4b0aa8d99fe99fc" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://policysearch.ama-assn.org/policyfinder/detail/H-150.919%20?uri=%2FAMADoc%2FHOD.xml-H-150.919.xml" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="17"&gt;&lt;span&gt;limiting added sugars&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; will — and this includes any form of sugar, from cane sugar or HFCS to agave, honey, maple syrup or coconut sugar. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“Switching to a beverage with less added sugar would be of much more benefit than changing the type of sugar in the drink,” said &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://wexnermedical.osu.edu/mediaroom/expertslisting/kris-dilley" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Kristine Dilley" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68cc1c8fe4b0aa8d99fe99fc" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://wexnermedical.osu.edu/mediaroom/expertslisting/kris-dilley" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="18"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Kristine Dilley&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;, a registered dietitian nutritionist (RDN) at The Ohio State University Wexner Medical Center.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why does overall sugar intake matter?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;According to the &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.dietaryguidelines.gov/sites/default/files/2021-11/DGA_FactSheet_AddedSugars_2021-06_508c.pdf" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Dietary Guidelines for Americans" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68cc1c8fe4b0aa8d99fe99fc" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.dietaryguidelines.gov/sites/default/files/2021-11/DGA_FactSheet_AddedSugars_2021-06_508c.pdf" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="19"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Dietary Guidelines for Americans&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;, added sugars should be limited to less than 10% of someone’s daily caloric intake, which amounts to about 50 grams of sugar per day for someone who’s eating a 2,000 calorie diet. And that’s the upper limit — they actually recommend aiming for even less. Meanwhile, the &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.heart.org/en/healthy-living/healthy-eating/eat-smart/sugar/added-sugars" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="American Heart Association " data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68cc1c8fe4b0aa8d99fe99fc" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.heart.org/en/healthy-living/healthy-eating/eat-smart/sugar/added-sugars" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="20"&gt;&lt;span&gt;American Heart Association &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;suggests even stricter limits for added sugars — 24 grams per day for women and 36 grams per day for men.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div id="support-huffpost-entry-support-huffpost-mid-article" class="cli support-huffpost-mid-article primary-cli cli cli-text cli-support-huffpost hidden"&gt;&lt;div class="cli-support-huffpost__content-wrapper"&gt;&lt;p class="cli-support-huffpost__title default-title"&gt;&lt;span class="cli-support-huffpost__title--first"&gt;20 Years Of&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="cli-support-huffpost__title--second"&gt;Free&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="cli-support-huffpost__title--third"&gt;Journalism&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="contributor-once-variation"&gt;&lt;p class="cli-support-huffpost__title"&gt;&lt;span class="cli-support-huffpost__title--first"&gt;Your Support&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="cli-support-huffpost__title--second"&gt;Fuels&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="cli-support-huffpost__title--third"&gt;Our Mission&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="contributor-canceled-variation"&gt;&lt;p class="cli-support-huffpost__title"&gt;&lt;span class="cli-support-huffpost__title--first"&gt;Your Support&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="cli-support-huffpost__title--second"&gt;Fuels&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="cli-support-huffpost__title--third"&gt;Our Mission&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="cli-support-huffpost__container"&gt;&lt;div class="cli-support-huffpost__message-container"&gt;&lt;div class="cli-support-huffpost__message support-huffpost__message--main"&gt;&lt;p class="cli-support-huffpost__sub-headline"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For two decades, HuffPost has been fearless, unflinching, and relentless in pursuit of the truth. Support our mission to keep us around for the next 20 — we can't do this without you.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="cli-support-huffpost__message variation contributor-once-variation"&gt;&lt;p&gt;We remain committed to providing you with the unflinching, fact-based journalism everyone deserves.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thank you again for your support along the way. We’re truly grateful for readers like you! Your initial support helped get us here and bolstered our newsroom, which kept us strong during uncertain times. Now as we continue, we need your help more than ever. &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/support" class="cli-support-huffpost__message__link js-entry-link" data-vars-item-name="we're offering an ad-free experience" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="main" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="/support" data-vars-target-content-type="feed" data-vars-type="web_internal_link" data-vars-subunit-name="support-huffpost-mid-article" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="24"&gt;We hope you will join us once again&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="cli-support-huffpost__message variation contributor-canceled-variation"&gt;&lt;p&gt;We remain committed to providing you with the unflinching, fact-based journalism everyone deserves.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thank you again for your support along the way. We’re truly grateful for readers like you! Your initial support helped get us here and bolstered our newsroom, which kept us strong during uncertain times. Now as we continue, we need your help more than ever. &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/support" class="cli-support-huffpost__message__link js-entry-link" data-vars-item-name="we're offering an ad-free experience" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="main" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="/support" data-vars-target-content-type="feed" data-vars-type="web_internal_link" data-vars-subunit-name="support-huffpost-mid-article" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="24"&gt;We hope you will join us once again&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;a class="cli-support-huffpost__support-button accent-button" href="https://www.huffpost.com/support?utm_campaign=mid-article-web" data-vars-item-name-overwritable="support-huffpost" data-vars-item-name="Support HuffPost" data-vars-item-type="button" data-vars-unit-name="main" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="/support" data-vars-target-content-type="feed" data-vars-type="web_internal_link" data-vars-subunit-name="support-huffpost-mid-article" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="23"&gt;Support HuffPost&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p class="support-huffpost-login"&gt;Already contributed? &lt;a class="js-entry-link-no-impression" href="https://login.huffpost.com/login?dest=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.huffpost.com%2Fentry%2Fis-cane-sugar-healthier-than-high-fructose-corn-syrup_l_68cc1c8fe4b0aa8d99fe99fc%3Fhp_auth_done%3D1" data-vars-item-name="Log in to hide these messages" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68cc1c8fe4b0aa8d99fe99fc" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="/login" data-vars-target-content-type="utility" data-vars-type="web_internal_link" data-vars-subunit-name="support-huffpost-mid-article" data-vars-subunit-type="component"&gt;Log in to hide these messages.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;And added sugars add up quickly. Just a 12-ounce can of Coca Cola contains &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.coca-cola.com/us/en/brands/coca-cola/products/original" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="39 grams" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68cc1c8fe4b0aa8d99fe99fc" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.coca-cola.com/us/en/brands/coca-cola/products/original" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="21"&gt;&lt;span&gt;39 grams&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; of added sugars, and rarely is that the only sugar someone is consuming in a day. Added sugar is found in high amounts in all sorts of processed foods, from cereal to yogurt to condiments. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“Overconsumption of added sugar has negative outcomes for body weight, blood pressure, insulin sensitivity, and other cardiometabolic risk factors,” Pasquariello said. “The use of cane sugar in a sugar-sweetened beverage instead of HFCS doesn’t make it any less likely to be over-consumed.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Of course sugar isn’t always a bad thing. “Sugar provides fast energy and is a great tool for endurance athletes to perform their best,” Gnau said. “The more active you are, the more energy you need.” Still, most Americans are consuming too much sugar &lt;/span&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span&gt;and&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;span&gt; not moving enough. According to &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/active-people-healthy-nation/php/why-be-active/index.html" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="the CDC" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68cc1c8fe4b0aa8d99fe99fc" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.cdc.gov/active-people-healthy-nation/php/why-be-active/index.html" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="22"&gt;&lt;span&gt;the CDC&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;, just 1 in 4 Americans meet physical activity guidelines. And if you’re not moving enough and providing your body with a way to use energy from high added sugar intake, health risks rise, Gnau added. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>HuffPost</author><pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 11:00:18 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMisAFBVV95cUxObkxWQVR3Z1FBWXQzVFFlWTE5RkY5Y1JraVpCRzVLakxOMWlBZzhLNVZnbUladGxET1N3bV9ZY3diUTJUbHJIcHFMLU9VSnU3VklwdmVSS0Z1M3didWxuYmRFZ096TDBubnFiVzFHTEFWdzJ2U0hINUVNZFEwaTVvOFlDZENMS0VybEJiNTVZVGdmSHJWaUU2bHhxSDhHdERYQ1pLaWIwUlVweGpoaEg2RdIBtgFBVV95cUxPUmRCc0NpMlJwb2MxREZrcXp2SHRhWVo1WFJUQk5teThXeGtKRlIxaWZXWTdYR2ZEZWo1R3NDQ215U3NEc2NRLUtCYjhWWDkxdmotWGxVTTlrQlRkVFdwSHFpcE5mY20xQ1l0OVVvakVnQms0dWV2TmJWZzd6QmxqZ2x4dk5rOUhySVlNU0pmQXROcExlN1B2STJUcEtzN093UnQ5SE94OE1xakpVVjBkTWhoOElpUQ</guid></item><item><title>在感冒和流感季节您可以做的最糟糕的事情- HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffpost.com/entry/worst-things-cold-flu-season_l_68d95052e4b040e2851e5164</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;section class="entry__content-list js-entry-content js-cet-subunit"&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s officially fall, which means crisp air, cozy sweaters, autumn leaves ― and a fresh wave of colds and flu.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“It’s almost inevitable that we will come into contact with at least one of the common respiratory viruses each cold and flu season,” &lt;a href="https://nyulangone.org/doctors/1831552298/andrew-b-fleming" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Dr. Andrew Fleming" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68d95052e4b040e2851e5164" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://nyulangone.org/doctors/1831552298/andrew-b-fleming" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="0"&gt;Dr. Andrew Fleming&lt;/a&gt;, section chief of infectious diseases and immunology at New York University Langone Brooklyn, told HuffPost. “A well-maintained immune system can halt these viruses before an infection sets in.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Between the unpleasant symptoms and schedule disruption, getting sick is hardly anyone’s idea of a good time. That’s why it’s crucial to do what you can to prevent the spread of germs, strengthen your body’s defenses and otherwise decrease your risk of infection.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“While most people who get a cold or the flu ultimately do just fine, these illnesses can be deadly to others,” said &lt;a href="https://www.nationaljewish.org/doctors-departments/carrie-a-horn" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Dr. Carrie Horn" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68d95052e4b040e2851e5164" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.nationaljewish.org/doctors-departments/carrie-a-horn" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="1"&gt;Dr. Carrie Horn&lt;/a&gt;, the chief medical officer at National Jewish Health. “And sometimes even otherwise young and healthy people can develop complications from a simple cold like pneumonia that could become serious.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;With that in mind, acting with awareness about illness isn’t just about protecting yourself, but also protecting your community. In fact, it’s a matter of etiquette. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“These protocols are not just about health ― they are about civility,” said &lt;a href="https://fromtheinsideoutsoe.com/about-founder/" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Jackie Vernon-Thompson" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68d95052e4b040e2851e5164" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://fromtheinsideoutsoe.com/about-founder/" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="2"&gt;Jackie Vernon-Thompson&lt;/a&gt;, the founder of From the Inside-Out School of Etiquette. “We never know how severely another person may be affected by a virus. Some may recover quickly, while others may face serious complications. Practicing mindfulness during this season reflects true etiquette: showing genuine concern for the well-being of others. Extending such care is not only proper etiquette ― it is kindness in action.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Below, find doctors’ and etiquette experts’ breakdown of the things you want to avoid doing during cold and flu season ― and what you should do instead. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Neglecting Rest&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“A primary mistake is to neglect rest and ‘power through’ when you feel symptoms emerging,” said &lt;a href="https://doctors.hackensackmeridianhealth.org/provider/nora-zabel-tossounian/1316569" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Dr. Nora Tossounian" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68d95052e4b040e2851e5164" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://doctors.hackensackmeridianhealth.org/provider/nora-zabel-tossounian/1316569" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="3"&gt;Dr. Nora Tossounian&lt;/a&gt;, an internal medicine specialist with Hackensack Meridian Health. “Your immune system requires significant energy to fight off an infection, and depriving your body of sleep and recovery time severely compromises its ability to do so.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Indeed, Fleming pointed to the many studies showing that sleep deprivation impairs components of the immune system that fight viruses.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“One study showed that those who got less than seven hours of sleep a night had an almost three times higher risk of getting the common cold compared to those who had eight or more hours of sleep,” he said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Getting enough sleep is not just about fighting off an active infection.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“When you’re run down, you’re more susceptible to getting sick,” said &lt;a href="https://www.webmd.com/bio/neha-pathak-md" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Dr. Neha Pathak" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68d95052e4b040e2851e5164" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.webmd.com/bio/neha-pathak-md" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="4"&gt;Dr. Neha Pathak&lt;/a&gt;, WebMD’s chief physician editor of health and lifestyle medicine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Going Places While You’re Sick&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“One of the worst things you can do during cold and flu season is not to stay at home when you are sick, or to attend gatherings where you know others are sick,” said family medicine physician &lt;a href="https://familydoctor.org/media_ambassadors/michael-richardson/" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Dr. Michael Richardson" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68d95052e4b040e2851e5164" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://familydoctor.org/media_ambassadors/michael-richardson/" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="5"&gt;Dr. Michael Richardson&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Going out in public ― whether it’s to your job, the grocery store or a social gathering ― while you know you’re sick exposes your whole community to your illness. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“If you have a fever, cough, runny nose, sore throat, or body aches, please stay home unless it is absolutely necessary that you go out,” Horn echoed. “Viral illnesses are contagious, and the best thing to do is limit the chance of spreading it to others.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;As a parent and health professional, Richardson also emphasized the importance of keeping sick kids out of school whenever possible. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“It’s very difficult to prevent transmission in the school system,” he said. “And even if it’s inconvenient, it’s extremely important to keep your child home from school if they have a fever. Children may return to school 24 hours after the fever has subsided.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Forgetting To Wash Your Hands&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Germs spread so easily from surfaces to hands and then to your face,” Pathak said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;That’s why skipping hand-washing is a bad idea, especially during cold and flu season. Instead, this should be a frequent practice. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Hand-washing is one of the best ways to avoid getting sick,” Horn said. “Always wash your hands before you eat or after you have been out and about touching things in public.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Overlooking Nutrition And Hydration&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Poor nutrition and dehydration work against you,” Tossounian said. “Your body needs the vitamins, minerals, and hydration from a healthy diet to mount an effective defense, not the inflammatory effects of processed foods and sugar.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;That’s why you should prioritize healthy eating with plenty of immunity-boosting nutrients like vitamin C. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Don’t let yourself get dehydrated,” Horn advised, adding that it’s especially important to drink water and eat nourishing foods when you’re feeling sick. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fleming similarly pointed to the role of heavy alcohol consumption, which can be dehydrating and otherwise impact your immunity. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“Both binge drinking and regular heavy alcohol use suppress the immune system and make us more susceptible to respiratory &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;viruses,” he said. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure class="cli cli-image js-no-inject"&gt;&lt;p class="cli-image__spacer"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="cli-image__source-wrapper"&gt;&lt;div class="cli-image__credit" aria-label="Image Credit: juanma hache via Getty Images"&gt;&lt;p class="credit-container"&gt;&lt;span class="credit"&gt;juanma hache via Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption class="cli-image__caption caption-cli"&gt;There are many things you can do to prevent the spread of germs, strengthen your body’s defenses and otherwise decrease your risk of infection.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Frequently Touching Your Face&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“On the germ-spreading front, one of the most detrimental habits is infrequent handwashing combined with unconsciously touching your face,” Tossounian said. “Viruses enter your body through the mucous membranes of your eyes, nose and mouth, and your hands are the primary vehicle for getting them there.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Touching your face is a common habit that can be hard to break, but try to at least reduce the frequency with which you do it. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“It’s good to minimize touching your face,” Horn said, adding that you might also consider washing your hands before or after you touch your nose or mouth.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ignoring Basic Cough And Sneeze Etiquette&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The most basic actions can really be effective,” said &lt;a href="https://providers.emoryhealthcare.org/provider/sarah-catherine-dupont/2287396" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Dr. Sarah Dupont" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68d95052e4b040e2851e5164" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://providers.emoryhealthcare.org/provider/sarah-catherine-dupont/2287396" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="6"&gt;Dr. Sarah Dupont&lt;/a&gt;, a family medicine physician at Emory Healthcare and assistant professor at Emory University School of Medicine. “Cover your cough, discard used tissues. All the things your mom taught you as a kid.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Remember the “vampire sneeze” and “vampire cough” tip. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Being mindful of others can help reduce transmission of viruses in many ways,” Fleming said. ”Cover your cough or sneeze with your elbow, even if you are not sure you are sick. Wash your hands after covering a cough or blowing your nose. ”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;This applies to your time in and out of your own home. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“At home, disinfect surfaces often to reduce the risk of spreading germs to loved ones,” Vernon-Thompson advised. “This is often overlooked. However, be mindful of those in your home.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Skipping Your Vaccines&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Don’t skip the flu shot,” Dupont said. “Vaccination is the absolute best way to prevent the flu or make the infection less severe.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;To decrease your risk of getting the flu and transmitting it to others, the &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/entry/best-time-flu-shot-2025_l_68c96720e4b056d71f628e99" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-internal-link" data-vars-item-name="recommended time to get your shot" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68d95052e4b040e2851e5164" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="68c96720e4b056d71f628e99" data-vars-target-content-type="buzz" data-vars-type="web_internal_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="7"&gt;recommended time to get your shot&lt;/a&gt; is September or October. The vaccine can also help reduce the length of your illness. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Flu shots are safe, offer an added boost of protection against getting the flu and reduce symptom severity and duration if you do contract the flu,” Richardson said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;He also recommended that adults get the latest COVID vaccine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Thankfully, I’m not seeing as much life-threatening illness as in years past, but COVID can still be debilitating, especially for people with pre-existing conditions like asthma,” Richardson noted. “I’ve seen patients with asthma who have had worsening symptoms that last for months beyond the infection.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Neglecting Masks And Hygiene When You Go Out&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“If you do have to go out and about while ill, please wear a mask to decrease the risk of transmitting anything to others,” Horn said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;People with weakened immune systems may want to get into the habit of wearing a mask in public places during cold and flu season. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Not everyone has paid sick leave or the ability to stay home from their jobs,” Smith said. “For those who must work, there are things you can do to mitigate and minimize the spread of any creeping crud.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;She recommended taking medications to reduce your symptoms, being diligent about mask-wearing and handwashing, and warning those who work near you that you’re feeling under the weather so that they can keep their distance. Also, avoid sharing food or utensils. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Don’t visit grandma if you’re sick,” Dupont said. “Or, if you can’t visit at any other time, at least wear a mask, avoid hugs and kisses, and try to hang out in a well-ventilated area, like outside. Older adults, especially those living in communities with a lot of other older adults, are at much higher risk of being hospitalized if they catch the flu.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Vernon-Thompson similarly recommended reconsidering physical greetings if you’re feeling a little under the weather or visiting someone else who is. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Instead of shaking hands, a gracious alternative is to place your right hand over your heart, offer a slight nod, and warmly say, ‘It is so nice to see (or meet) you,’” she said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Not Going To The Doctor When You Aren’t Getting Better&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“If a fever is lasting more than three days, if you are having trouble breathing, or if you have chronic medical conditions that could be worsened from a viral illness, it helps to go see your doctor earlier rather than later,” Horn said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you have been feeling unwell without improvement, consider reaching out to a health care professional. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div id="support-huffpost-entry-support-huffpost-mid-article" class="cli support-huffpost-mid-article primary-cli cli cli-text cli-support-huffpost hidden"&gt;&lt;div class="cli-support-huffpost__content-wrapper"&gt;&lt;p class="cli-support-huffpost__title default-title"&gt;&lt;span class="cli-support-huffpost__title--first"&gt;20 Years Of&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="cli-support-huffpost__title--second"&gt;Free&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="cli-support-huffpost__title--third"&gt;Journalism&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="contributor-once-variation"&gt;&lt;p class="cli-support-huffpost__title"&gt;&lt;span class="cli-support-huffpost__title--first"&gt;Your Support&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="cli-support-huffpost__title--second"&gt;Fuels&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="cli-support-huffpost__title--third"&gt;Our Mission&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="contributor-canceled-variation"&gt;&lt;p class="cli-support-huffpost__title"&gt;&lt;span class="cli-support-huffpost__title--first"&gt;Your Support&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="cli-support-huffpost__title--second"&gt;Fuels&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="cli-support-huffpost__title--third"&gt;Our Mission&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="cli-support-huffpost__container"&gt;&lt;div class="cli-support-huffpost__message-container"&gt;&lt;div class="cli-support-huffpost__message support-huffpost__message--main"&gt;&lt;p class="cli-support-huffpost__sub-headline"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For two decades, HuffPost has been fearless, unflinching, and relentless in pursuit of the truth. Support our mission to keep us around for the next 20 — we can't do this without you.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="cli-support-huffpost__message variation contributor-once-variation"&gt;&lt;p&gt;We remain committed to providing you with the unflinching, fact-based journalism everyone deserves.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thank you again for your support along the way. We’re truly grateful for readers like you! Your initial support helped get us here and bolstered our newsroom, which kept us strong during uncertain times. Now as we continue, we need your help more than ever. &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/support" class="cli-support-huffpost__message__link js-entry-link" data-vars-item-name="we're offering an ad-free experience" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="main" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="/support" data-vars-target-content-type="feed" data-vars-type="web_internal_link" data-vars-subunit-name="support-huffpost-mid-article" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="9"&gt;We hope you will join us once again&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="cli-support-huffpost__message variation contributor-canceled-variation"&gt;&lt;p&gt;We remain committed to providing you with the unflinching, fact-based journalism everyone deserves.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thank you again for your support along the way. We’re truly grateful for readers like you! Your initial support helped get us here and bolstered our newsroom, which kept us strong during uncertain times. Now as we continue, we need your help more than ever. &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/support" class="cli-support-huffpost__message__link js-entry-link" data-vars-item-name="we're offering an ad-free experience" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="main" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="/support" data-vars-target-content-type="feed" data-vars-type="web_internal_link" data-vars-subunit-name="support-huffpost-mid-article" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="9"&gt;We hope you will join us once again&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;a class="cli-support-huffpost__support-button accent-button" href="https://www.huffpost.com/support?utm_campaign=mid-article-web" data-vars-item-name-overwritable="support-huffpost" data-vars-item-name="Support HuffPost" data-vars-item-type="button" data-vars-unit-name="main" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="/support" data-vars-target-content-type="feed" data-vars-type="web_internal_link" data-vars-subunit-name="support-huffpost-mid-article" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="8"&gt;Support HuffPost&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p class="support-huffpost-login"&gt;Already contributed? &lt;a class="js-entry-link-no-impression" href="https://login.huffpost.com/login?dest=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.huffpost.com%2Fentry%2Fworst-things-cold-flu-season_l_68d95052e4b040e2851e5164%3Fhp_auth_done%3D1" data-vars-item-name="Log in to hide these messages" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68d95052e4b040e2851e5164" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="/login" data-vars-target-content-type="utility" data-vars-type="web_internal_link" data-vars-subunit-name="support-huffpost-mid-article" data-vars-subunit-type="component"&gt;Log in to hide these messages.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“There are medications to treat the flu and COVID, and they work best when given early in the course of the illness,” Horn said. “They are most effective for people who are immune suppressed or have chronic underlying medical conditions, but they can shorten the duration of illness for everyone.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>HuffPost</author><pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 11:00:18 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijwFBVV95cUxOMVNIYkZWWVRYTVdvMlZ0bV9Cbk1OeFpGelRIWkJjLV91MUZWTVlybW9QSGNwVDloeHRSY1pZUktRb3VRUVpINnFfRTY5M3pWaUdOUVMyUUdQSUc5RjVhbjBXZG9vNzBIcW0yZXhQMktHRVVrZU9ZUjI2MDVoX3JwTjV1QU1WWmpsaFNYdFl3d9IBlAFBVV95cUxOY3B1d05ubXljZUNwRGFsQlJ1NnowZEs1ME5qQUJwNmhxU0w1bDVLTEFtbVo0U190cEdXOUtCdS1EOFcwR3ktRllEU05LMUs4bWFra2NXSnotblQxTzJIeng5LVk4eUc3Ry0yX3lBYzFNZlZuZ285aUZfT0x2Y29NYmFQeUg0U25wSUFkRTFTTUVYMkVZ</guid></item><item><title>年轻人的癌症激增是海市蜃楼吗？ - vox.com</title><link>https://www.vox.com/health/463399/cancer-cases-awareness-young-adults-colon-breast</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="zephr-anchor" class="_1agbrix10"&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup duet--article--standard-paragraph _1agbrixi lg8ac51 lg8ac50 xkp0cg1"&gt;Five years ago, when actor Chadwick Boseman &lt;a href="/culture/21406391/chadwick-boseman-dead-black-panther-tchalla-cancer"&gt;died&lt;/a&gt; at age 43 from colon cancer, it was a genuine shock. Last summer, when Catherine, Princess of Wales, was &lt;a href="/the-highlight/24093360/early-cancer-young-adults-colon-stomach-research"&gt;diagnosed with cancer&lt;/a&gt; at age 42, it was tragic, but it landed a bit differently. At that point, it was clear her diagnosis was part of a &lt;a href="/the-highlight/24093360/early-cancer-young-adults-colon-stomach-research"&gt;clear narrative&lt;/a&gt;: More and more relatively young adults are developing cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup duet--article--standard-paragraph _1agbrixi lg8ac51 lg8ac50 xkp0cg1"&gt;But now, a more complicated story is emerging.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup duet--article--standard-paragraph _1agbrixi lg8ac51 lg8ac50 xkp0cg1"&gt;According to a new study published in &lt;a href="https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jamainternalmedicine/article-abstract/2839347"&gt;&lt;em&gt;JAMA Internal Medicine&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, some of the rise in early-onset cancer is a diagnostic mirage: Doctors are finding cases that would never have led to serious illness anyway. Younger adults — those under 50 — are indeed being diagnosed with cancer at nearly twice the rate they had been in 1990: 60 cases per 100,000 people, up from 30. But the number of metastatic cases, those that are more likely to be aggressive and/or were detected late, has not increased at nearly the same speed. The death rate for the eight cancers covered in the study has remained flat over the last 35 years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup duet--article--standard-paragraph _1agbrixi lg8ac51 lg8ac50 xkp0cg1"&gt;“Overall, the rise in early-onset cancer appears to be less an epidemic of disease and more an epidemic of diagnosis,” the authors — researchers from Harvard, Brigham Women’s Hospital in Boston, and the University of Texas at Austin — write in their paper’s conclusion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup duet--article--standard-paragraph _1agbrixi lg8ac51 lg8ac50 xkp0cg1"&gt;This surprised me. I’m a bit of a hypochondriac, and I’m an adult under 50, and so when I read a headline about the uptick of cancer among my own generation, I certainly think, &lt;em&gt;Oh no, more young adults are getting sick and dying from cancer. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup duet--article--standard-paragraph _1agbrixi lg8ac51 lg8ac50 xkp0cg1"&gt;But there are ways to double-check that assumption — which is exactly what this new paper tries to do.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup duet--article--standard-paragraph _1agbrixi lg8ac51 lg8ac50 xkp0cg1"&gt;The authors decided to look deeper into the overall rising rate of cancer incidence among middle-aged adults and focus specifically on rates of metastatic cancer and death rates, metrics that correlate with more serious illness. And the findings suggest something else besides exposure to new toxins (whether &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC7904962/"&gt;pollution&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href="https://www.aicr.org/resources/blog/ultra-processed-foods-and-cancer-whats-the-connection/"&gt;ultra-processed foods&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S0024320524005277"&gt;microplastics&lt;/a&gt;) could be contributing to the surge of cancer diagnoses among younger people.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup duet--article--standard-paragraph _1agbrixi lg8ac51 lg8ac50 xkp0cg1"&gt;It may be that at least &lt;em&gt;part&lt;/em&gt; of the story is that we have simply improved our ability to detect cancer. That would frame the recent rise in cases a little differently: Perhaps cancer rates among relatively young adults are soaring because we are catching more cancers that were always out there but used to escape diagnosis, sometimes until it was too late.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup duet--article--standard-paragraph _1agbrixi lg8ac51 lg8ac50 xkp0cg1"&gt;That would be welcome news. But this is a complicated story. Let’s get into it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p id="how-to-think-about-this-important-new-study-on-early-onset-cancer" class="_7ka5u1 _7ka5u0 duet--article--standard-heading xkp0cg1"&gt;&lt;h2 class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup"&gt;How to think about this important new study on early-onset cancer&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup duet--article--standard-paragraph _1agbrixi lg8ac51 lg8ac50 xkp0cg1"&gt;The new study examined eight categories of cancer that have been the fastest-rising over the past few decades: thyroid, colorectal, endometrial, kidney, anal, pancreatic, myeloma, and small intestinal. The combined incidence for those cancers has doubled since the 1990s — but the overall mortality rate has barely budged: 5.9 deaths per 100,000, identical in 2022 as it was in 1992.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup duet--article--standard-paragraph _1agbrixi lg8ac51 lg8ac50 xkp0cg1"&gt;This pattern is particularly apparent for breast cancer, still the most common form for people under 50. While the number of excess diagnoses compared to historical trends has increased substantially since the 1990s, the number of excess deaths compared to the historical average is actually down.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup duet--article--standard-paragraph _1agbrixi lg8ac51 lg8ac50 xkp0cg1"&gt;“The excess diagnoses similarly likely reflect the increased screening intensity in younger patients (i.e., more mammograms, ultrasonography, and magnetic resonance imaging) than an increase in the occurrence of clinically meaningful breast cancer,” the study’s authors write.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup duet--article--standard-paragraph _1agbrixi lg8ac51 lg8ac50 xkp0cg1"&gt;There is nuance to the findings: Death rates for colorectal cancers, the subject of &lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2024/03/27/well/colon-cancer-symptoms-treatment.html"&gt;much of the recent media coverage&lt;/a&gt;, and uterine cancers have noticeably increased over the study period, for example, even as mortality has fallen for other diseases. When I asked researchers who were unaffiliated with the findings, they emphasized that there are clearly at least some cancers that are genuinely becoming more common and leading to serious illness and death. Grouping all cancers together risks masking those more specific trends.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup duet--article--standard-paragraph _1agbrixi lg8ac51 lg8ac50 xkp0cg1"&gt;“I think we should focus more on the individual cancers and what’s going on with them and try not to lump them all together when making the overall inferences,” Timothy Rebbeck, a cancer researcher affiliated with Harvard and Dana Farber, told me.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup duet--article--standard-paragraph _1agbrixi lg8ac51 lg8ac50 xkp0cg1"&gt;He said the paper raised important points that should continue to be investigated, but added that “I hope the field and the public do not interpret this single paper as an indictment that increases in early onset cancer are either unimportant or not worthy of a better understanding.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup duet--article--standard-paragraph _1agbrixi lg8ac51 lg8ac50 xkp0cg1"&gt;There are other limitations and alternative explanations for the study’s findings. For example, it is possible that perhaps we &lt;em&gt;are&lt;/em&gt; getting more serious cancers earlier in our lives, but faster detection is preventing cases from becoming metastatic or leading to death. The flat mortality rates may also reflect &lt;a href="/health/415812/cancer-death-rates-myeloma-immunotherapy-smoking"&gt;the many improvements in cancer treatment&lt;/a&gt;, such as recent breakthroughs with immunotherapy drugs that have sent survival rates soaring.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup duet--article--standard-paragraph _1agbrixi lg8ac51 lg8ac50 xkp0cg1"&gt;The paper’s researchers argue against both. They point out that previous research into specific cancers, such as &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC7232665/"&gt;thyroid cancer&lt;/a&gt;, has already found evidence of overdiagnosis. On the possibility that serious cases are being caught earlier, the authors argue that we should then see a decrease in cancers diagnosed after age 50 — but that hasn’t happened.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup duet--article--standard-paragraph _1agbrixi lg8ac51 lg8ac50 xkp0cg1"&gt;But other experts do see the evidence differently: Rebbeck told me he thought that both improved treatment and earlier detection that staves off serious illness probably explain at least some of the study results. But we need to know more, he emphasized.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup duet--article--standard-paragraph _1agbrixi lg8ac51 lg8ac50 xkp0cg1"&gt;So what are we, the potential patients, to think about this? As a young person prone to health anxiety — I’m 37 — that is an urgent question to me.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup duet--article--standard-paragraph _1agbrixi lg8ac51 lg8ac50 xkp0cg1"&gt;First, one study is never the final answer in medical research. The findings here suggest overdiagnosis may explain some of the rise in early-onset cancer, but we need more research to be sure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup duet--article--standard-paragraph _1agbrixi lg8ac51 lg8ac50 xkp0cg1"&gt;And second, people should be aware that certain cancers &lt;em&gt;do&lt;/em&gt; appear to be occurring more frequently and with serious clinical consequences. You should know the &lt;a href="https://cancer.osu.edu/for-patients-and-caregivers/learn-about-cancers-and-treatments/cancers-conditions-and-treatment/cancer-types/gastrointestinal-cancers/colon-cancer?utm_campaign=med-chri_patient-awareness_evergreen_gi-colon&amp;amp;utm_medium=cpc&amp;amp;utm_source=google&amp;amp;utm_term=colon%20cancer%20symptoms&amp;amp;gad_source=1&amp;amp;gad_campaignid=18004402751&amp;amp;gbraid=0AAAAAoebTA2I9FSgOFaepKlEK0aIE5stC&amp;amp;gclid=CjwKCAjw_-3GBhAYEiwAjh9fUNGfo6ualsEDneTKycQx4rcspartyJJBoipGfJieSgpRZ-ZdHvhHnBoCpYsQAvD_BwE"&gt;colon&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://my.clevelandclinic.org/health/diseases/16409-uterine-cancer"&gt;uterine cancer&lt;/a&gt; symptoms to watch out for, &lt;a href="https://cancerprogressreport.aacr.org/progress/cpr20-contents/cpr20-preventing-cancer-identifying-risk-factors/"&gt;the risk factors&lt;/a&gt; to avoid — and, as always, talk with your doctor if you have concerns.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup duet--article--standard-paragraph _1agbrixi lg8ac51 lg8ac50 xkp0cg1"&gt;But it &lt;em&gt;is&lt;/em&gt; worth asking ourselves whether we all need a mindset adjustment. This is not the first research to raise the possibility that we are too aggressive about diagnosing issues without a clear clinical imperative for doing so. &lt;a href="/health/414241/medical-diagnosis-cancer-autism-long-covid"&gt;I interviewed Dr. Suzanne O’Sullivan earlier this year&lt;/a&gt;, who wrote an entire book on the subject.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup duet--article--standard-paragraph _1agbrixi lg8ac51 lg8ac50 xkp0cg1"&gt;She wrote specifically about cancer overdiagnosis and the mental and financial burden placed on the patients who are told they have cancer, even if that cancer might not actually be a threat to their well-being, the kind of cases contemplated in this new study.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup duet--article--standard-paragraph _1agbrixi lg8ac51 lg8ac50 xkp0cg1"&gt;“Within the medical community, this has been well-known for a long time, but it just doesn’t leak into the general conversation,” she told me. “The bottom line is if you screen healthy people for an illness, any illness, be it cancer or high blood pressure, diabetes, then you will be picking up borderline cases and overtreating them.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup duet--article--standard-paragraph _1agbrixi lg8ac51 lg8ac50 xkp0cg1"&gt;Doctors are under pressure to deliver concrete answers to patients, but even something like a cancer diagnosis — which feels like it should be black or white, yes or no — requires interpretation. A few abnormal cells on a scan or a blood test could be the start of a deadly tumor, or they might never develop into anything serious.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup duet--article--standard-paragraph _1agbrixi lg8ac51 lg8ac50 lg8ac5a xkp0cg1"&gt;These findings are a reminder that detection is not the same as diagnosis — and while we have been conditioned to demand certainty from modern medicine, we ought to be aware of the uncertainties.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>vox.com</author><pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiigFBVV95cUxNa0I4dGhjNk01LVlZdUg5NmljZUlSZDloaFVrdy1PQUdrUnBrZ0ZGOGJ0aUhTbDFSdERmeVZEOHVia19hYWZ6aW9aSFl6bTFKZTNjSU94dmFQalV4OEtYVGFSUFZBeDB5NnBnZVVMXzlWdUpwN1p4TFBxeXNyZGppUmhqVHMzLWd3UkE</guid></item><item><title>新型冠状病毒的严重程度如何？ Stratus变异症状和建议-《每日电讯报》</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/health-fitness/conditions/cold-flu/why-so-many-people-have-covid-and-how-to-avoid-new/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="component article-body-text    " data-test="article-body-text"&gt;
  
  

	

	
	

	
	



  
  
    &lt;p&gt;With winter fast approaching, many of us have already been struck with runny noses, dry coughs and fevers. Right now, chances are these symptoms are caused by Covid, with levels of the pandemic-causing virus among the highest they have been all year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Here, the scientists explain exactly why Covid is on the rise again and, vitally, how to avoid it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="u-heading-size-medium u-heading-style-normal"&gt;Why do so many people have Covid&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Infection rates always go up because of one of three reasons,” says Paul Hunter, a professor in medicine at the University of East Anglia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s either because immunity to Covid among the population has fallen; a new and more infectious variant is spreading; or behaviour has changed in a way that increases the risk of exposure to the virus, he explains. All three factors are currently at play, to some extent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="u-heading-size-medium u-heading-style-normal"&gt;The new ‘Stratus’ variant&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;XFG, a sub-variant of the once infamous Omicron, was first &lt;a class="ck-custom-link" href="https://www.who.int/docs/default-source/coronaviruse/25062025_xfg_ire.pdf"&gt;detected&lt;/a&gt; in January. This strain of the virus, which has been nicknamed Stratus, is currently responsible for the majority of Covid cases in the UK and has two main variants – XFG and XFG.3. The former is responsible for 38.3 per cent of UK Covid cases and the latter 32.8 per cent, according to UK Health Security Agency (UKHSA) data. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Stratus” is also responsible for over 60 per cent of Covid cases globally, according to the &lt;a class="ck-custom-link" href="https://data.who.int/dashboards/covid19/summary"&gt;World Health Organization&lt;/a&gt;, which is actively monitoring the variant.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“It has become dominant because it is more infectious (able to bypass existing immunity to some degree) than prior variants,” explains Prof Hunter.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“But its relative growth advantage is only about 31 per cent, which is not great compared to many previous variants,” he notes. For comparison, the Omicron variant, which caused chaos when it swept the world in late 2021, had a growth advantage of around 200 per cent when it emerged. “So it will be contributing to the growth in cases but I suspect not the main driver.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While Covid infections are now asymptomatic in many people, there have been reports that an XFG infection may be more likely to cause a hoarse, scratchy or raspy voice. Other common symptoms are still a cough, fever and change of taste or smell, according to the NHS.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I have seen the comments on hoarseness but given we see and diagnose such a small proportion of infections now and then usually only the more severe cases, I am not convinced,” Prof Hunter says. “Also adenoviruses [a cause of the common cold] are almost as common in lab tests and they do cause hoarseness.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="u-heading-size-medium u-heading-style-normal"&gt;Immunity against Covid is low&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Covid cases are no longer being tracked as thoroughly as they were during the pandemic, when tests were dished out for free. However, monitoring shows that cases are currently at their highest level this year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Figures, compiled by the UKHSA, show that around nine per cent of all Covid tests taken in the week to &lt;strong&gt;September 7&lt;/strong&gt; were positive, which is the highest level seen since last November. The figures show that 10.8 per cent of people tested in GP practices were infected, while 8.9 per cent of swabs among hospital patients were positive.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Reporting rates have been around base levels for almost a year now and so population immunity will be relatively low,” Prof Hunter says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;After becoming infected with Covid, the immune system develops antibodies against it. These are fighter cells that recognise and neutralise the virus when the body comes into contact with it again. “Immunity to infection probably lasts only a few months on average,” Prof Hunter notes, after which point the body is once again vulnerable to infection.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I think that is probably the major factor,” fuelling the current upward trend in infections, he says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="u-heading-size-medium u-heading-style-normal"&gt;Schools reopening&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Schools reopening earlier this month could further encourage the spread of the virus, notes Prof Peter Openshaw, a respiratory physician and mucosal immunologist at Imperial College London. This could mean that, by October, cases are even higher.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“It may be that during October we’re going to be seeing a lot more Covid around,” he says. “There was quite a peak in October 2024 and then it settled around Christmas time and was replaced by influenza. It could be that we’re going to see more cases but I think we’ll have to wait and see.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The big question is how high will reporting levels go and when they will peak,” Prof Hunter adds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="u-heading-size-medium u-heading-style-normal"&gt;How to avoid it&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Short of isolating yourself at home, there’s unfortunately no magic bullet that will guarantee that you won’t catch Covid or other respiratory viruses.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, regular hand washing and sanitising communal surfaces, such as trays on aeroplanes and trays, as well as gym equipment can reduce your risk of becoming infected.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“For most of us, the need to avoid infection is not as great as we will have had multiple infections by now and most infections are asymptomatic,” Prof Hunter says. “On average in England, we will have had about four infections each by now.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, older and medically vulnerable people should remain more cautious, he says. “Wear masks if in crowded environments, accept the offer of a vaccine if made and discourage visits from people who are suffering from a respiratory infection.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Covid autumn vaccination booster programme launches on October 1. Care home residents, over-75s and anyone aged over six months who is immunocompromised is eligible for the jab.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The vaccines that are on offer are extraordinarily effective,” Prof Openshaw says. “If you’re offered a vaccine, I would definitely take it and I personally have taken every offer of the vaccines I’ve been made.” The jab can reduce the likelihood of outbreaks and prevent the virus from causing serious illness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="u-heading-size-medium u-heading-style-normal"&gt;What to do if you get Covid&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;“For most people, the most effective way to get over Covid is to rest at home and drink plenty of fluids and remain vigilant for worsening symptoms,” says Dr Adrian Hayter, medical director for clinical policy at the Royal College of General Practitioners.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Over the counter medications – paracetamol or ibuprofen – can help alleviate symptoms such as aches, a sore throat or a blocked nose, and increasing airflow by sitting upright and breathing slowly can help with feelings of breathlessness.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Additionally, a small group of people remain eligible for antivirals, which are medicines that stop Covid from growing and spreading through the body, including those who have certain immune conditions, blood disorders or receiving specific cancer treatments.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“If someone has concerns for their health, or if their condition is getting worse or not improving, they should seek health advice to determine whether further treatment is needed,” Dr Hayter says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He advises people with Covid symptoms to stay at home and avoid contact with other people for at least three days, while the infected should steer clear of people who have a weak immune system for 10 days.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The condition is highly infectious, and some people can be particularly vulnerable to the worst effects, which is why it’s important that we take appropriate measures to avoid transmission,” he says.&lt;/p&gt;
  
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Telegraph</author><pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 09:36:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMitAFBVV95cUxNcHlPQkYxMUpDOGUxUzJsV1lrYzh6Q1YyVGFTR09hMHIwZlFneHZvbG5hcVZUWHlrbm5OYmlTdWVWY1l3ZGZOU0tQWWdvd0FBQ1BIRXQ3Y3NXdkRDZHdON1U0b05ESkMxQ3BuYnphdktrTmpGdUNmVUlGMU1wc0xuRUxJSXFYdUZvcTdqTTNnbEhseTd6ZG82clFZRlFsLW5jRF9Ua0hJYmpON2JKVzY0NEYyNjQ</guid></item><item><title>解决前列腺癌治疗的斗争- Bloomberg.com</title><link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2025-10-02/focal-therapy-for-prostate-cancer-care-is-an-emerging-new-treatment</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;section class="box main"&gt;
                &lt;h2 class="main__heading"&gt;We've detected unusual activity from your computer network&lt;/h2&gt;
                &lt;p class="continue"&gt;To continue, please click the box below to let us know you're not a robot.&lt;/p&gt;
                &lt;p id="px-captcha"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;/section&gt;
            &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Bloomberg.com</author><pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 09:00:11 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiugFBVV95cUxOWE1fWThrUW5sb3FYdVMxNXBDVDU1VDZyMEVJbjktODVuVG5JVDdwT2MyYUp6ZC0zMEJ5eFVwSDlLcWNyQ1p5UFN1dXpvd2dGUU9BdHY4Q1dYVDVySG5tb0UxSmdNVEpNZkN5NXMybW4yWUdaNGQ4YWtpV0ZDeDFKaXZIbEJlbXIzN29sTm8tVDNjWVlzUWQ5aUg4ZFRIU01GcDNOeWotVkpqeHhJbUxiUGoyaWt1ZUM3Ymc</guid></item><item><title>想要减少早晨的疼痛吗？您可能需要改变睡眠方式- NPR</title><link>https://www.npr.org/2025/10/02/nx-s1-5435668/sleep-body-pain-minimize-morning-aches-soreness</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="storytext" class="storytext storylocation linkLocation"&gt;
      &lt;div id="resg-s1-91426" class="bucketwrap image x-large"&gt;
            
&lt;div class="credit-caption"&gt;
    &lt;div class="caption-wrap"&gt;
        &lt;div class="caption" aria-label="Image caption"&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;
                Sleeping in an awkward position for many hours at night can cause morning aches and pains. One way to guard against them is to focus on your sleep posture, say medical experts.
                &lt;b class="credit" aria-label="Image credit"&gt;
                    
                    Meredith Miotke for NPR
                    
                &lt;/b&gt;
                &lt;b class="hide-caption"&gt;&lt;b&gt;hide caption&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;
            &lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;


            &lt;b class="toggle-caption"&gt;&lt;b&gt;toggle caption&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;

    &lt;span class="credit" aria-label="Image credit"&gt;
        
        Meredith Miotke for NPR
        
    &lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;Ever wake up with a sore lower back or achy shoulders that just ruin the rest of your day? Or get up from bed and try to greet the morning, only to find your neck is too stiff to turn to the window?&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Morning muscle pain along your spine is often the result of hours of improper support while sleeping, says &lt;a href="https://restorativesleepmedicine.com/about-us/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Ellen Wermter&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, a nurse practitioner who runs &lt;a href="https://restorativesleepmedicine.com/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Restorative Sleep Medicine&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, a sleep clinic in Virginia. One easy way to guard against it, say medical experts, is to focus on your sleep posture.&lt;/p&gt;   
   
   

   &lt;p&gt;Sleeping in an awkward position tends to create gaps between your body and your pillow or mattress, Wermter says. "Your soft tissue is going to want to sag into those gaps, and the muscles tense to make up for that" in order to protect against potential injury.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Over the course of a night, that muscle tension can cause inflammation and pain, Wermter says — and bad sleep from all that tossing and turning to find a more comfortable position.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Whether you sleep on your back, side or stomach, experts share advice for those looking to minimize morning aches and pains.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;h2 class="edTag"&gt;Sleep the same way you stand &lt;/h2&gt;   &lt;div id="resg-s1-91427" class="bucketwrap image x-large"&gt;
            
&lt;div class="credit-caption"&gt;
    &lt;div class="caption-wrap"&gt;
        &lt;div class="caption" aria-label="Image caption"&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;
                When you sleep the way you stand, it reduces the possibility of muscle strain, says &lt;a href="https://restorativesleepmedicine.com/about-us/" target="_blank"&gt;Ellen Wermter&lt;/a&gt;, a nurse practitioner who runs &lt;a href="https://restorativesleepmedicine.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Restorative Sleep Medicine&lt;/a&gt;, a sleep clinic in Virginia. This illustration offers guidance on how to sleep in a position that follows the natural curvature of your spine.
                &lt;b class="credit" aria-label="Image credit"&gt;
                    
                    Meredith Miotke for NPR
                    
                &lt;/b&gt;
                &lt;b class="hide-caption"&gt;&lt;b&gt;hide caption&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;
            &lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;


            &lt;b class="toggle-caption"&gt;&lt;b&gt;toggle caption&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;

    &lt;span class="credit" aria-label="Image credit"&gt;
        
        Meredith Miotke for NPR
        
    &lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;The best defense against an achy neck or back&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;in the morning is to sleep just like you stand, Wermter says.&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;When you sleep in a position that follows the natural curvature of your spine, it reduces the possibility of muscle strain.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;While lying down, your body should form a straight line from the top of your head to your tailbone. Wermter suggests placing&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;your ears over your shoulders and your shoulders over your hips. Point&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;your chin straight ahead, not tucked into your chest or stretched up toward the sky. Aim for symmetry with your arms for proper circulation.&lt;/p&gt;   
   

   &lt;p&gt;If you're a back sleeper, this tip will be easier to follow. But if you're a side or stomach sleeper, you may need to adjust your sleep space for better spinal alignment — or even train yourself to sleep in this position, Wermter says.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;h2 class="edTag"&gt;Avoid sleeping on your stomach &lt;/h2&gt;   &lt;p&gt;While this position can open up airways for struggling snorers, it's often associated with its potential downsides, Wermter says. That includes neck, back and shoulder aches, and fragmented sleep from switching positions more often throughout the night.&lt;/p&gt;   
   &lt;p&gt;When you sleep on your stomach, it's easy to overextend your neck, she says. Creating breathing room for yourself often pulls your neck out of that ideal spinal alignment.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;div id="resg-s1-91451" class="bucketwrap image x-large"&gt;
            
&lt;div class="credit-caption"&gt;
    &lt;div class="caption-wrap"&gt;
        &lt;div class="caption" aria-label="Image caption"&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;
                Pillow height, or loft, is important to maintaining proper sleep posture and preventing neck pain. &lt;strong&gt;The left column&lt;/strong&gt; shows improper pillow height for back sleepers, side sleepers and stomach sleepers, respectively. &lt;strong&gt;The right column&lt;/strong&gt; demonstrates the proper pillow height for a neutral spine for each sleeping position.
                &lt;b class="credit" aria-label="Image credit"&gt;
                    
                    Meredith Miotke for NPR
                    
                &lt;/b&gt;
                &lt;b class="hide-caption"&gt;&lt;b&gt;hide caption&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;
            &lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;


            &lt;b class="toggle-caption"&gt;&lt;b&gt;toggle caption&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;

    &lt;span class="credit" aria-label="Image credit"&gt;
        
        Meredith Miotke for NPR
        
    &lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;h2 class="edTag"&gt;Choose the right pillow for your head  &lt;/h2&gt;   &lt;p&gt;It's important to rest your head on something that supports your spine and promotes maximum restfulness at night, says &lt;a href="https://fabianmorales.com/meet-fabian" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Dr. Fabian Morales&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, a sports medicine physician.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Back sleepers: &lt;/strong&gt;Morales suggests a pillow with medium firmness and loft, or something with an ergonomic design. "A good orthopedic pillow designed to support the curvature of the neck can minimize your risk of neck pain down the line. It reduces pressure on the neck and supports alignment," he says.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Side sleepers: &lt;/strong&gt;To find a pillow with the right loft for side sleeping, "measure from the bend of your neck to the edge of your shoulder," Wermter says. The ideal pillow will support your head without pushing your head and neck further up.&lt;/p&gt;   
   

   &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Stomach sleepers:&lt;/strong&gt; If you're stuck on stomach sleeping, Wermter says it might be best to go without a pillow to avoid extra strain on your neck. If you do need some cushion, aim for low-loft options to keep your spine aligned.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Replace your pillows every few years or as soon as you notice your pillow starts to lack support, Morales says. Pillows hold on to dirt and dust — and they lose their structure over time, which can lead to aches and pains.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;h2 class="edTag"&gt;Support any gaps with smaller pillows &lt;/h2&gt;   &lt;div id="resg-s1-91429" class="bucketwrap image x-large"&gt;
            
&lt;div class="credit-caption"&gt;
    &lt;div class="caption-wrap"&gt;
        &lt;div class="caption" aria-label="Image caption"&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;
                Pillows can be used to support proper sleep posture for back sleepers, side sleepers and stomach sleepers.
                &lt;b class="hide-caption"&gt;&lt;b&gt;hide caption&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;
            &lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;


            &lt;b class="toggle-caption"&gt;&lt;b&gt;toggle caption&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;When your spine isn't properly supported, pain is likely to follow, Wermter says. That's why it's important to align and cradle the entire length of your spine — not just your head and neck — to make up for any gaps between your body and the mattress. Use smaller pillows or even rolled up blankets or towels.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Back sleepers:&lt;/strong&gt; Be mindful of any gaps at the small of your back or under your knees, which can be a source of lower back pain. Add support to those areas as needed, Wermter says.&lt;/p&gt;   
   &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Side sleepers: &lt;/strong&gt;Many side sleepers like placing a small pillow between the knees or hugging a body pillow to align the hips and reduce pressure in the hips and lower back, she says.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Stomach sleepers:&lt;/strong&gt; Wermter says just sleeping on a flat surface is fine for stomach sleepers, but some may find that a thin pillow under the hips and stomach can reduce strain on the back.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;h2 class="edTag"&gt;Opt for a mattress that's not too soft and not too firm &lt;/h2&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Evaluate the quality of your mattress and replace your bed every seven years at most, says Wermter. If a mattress is too soft, the heavier parts of your body can sink and your spine will likely get out of alignment. If a mattress is too firm, it can create those pain-inducing gaps between body and bed.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;h2 class="edTag"&gt;Try other pain relief remedies &lt;/h2&gt;   &lt;p&gt;What should you do if you have a great sleep setup and you still wake up with an achy back or a crick in your neck?&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;It's a very common experience, especially as we age and our spines experience more wear and tear, says &lt;a href="https://nyulangone.org/doctors/1417115767/charla-r-fischer" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Dr. Charla Fischer,&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; an&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;orthopedic spine surgeon at NYU Langone Health.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;That kind of muscle pain can be, well, a pain in the neck — but is usually not cause for major concern. Consult a medical professional if you have consistent pain for a week or more; experience numbness, tingling or weakness in the neck, arms or hands; or if you just have concerns, Fischer says.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Otherwise, don't forget the power of basic pain relief remedies. Take &lt;a href="https://www.npr.org/2025/04/18/nx-s1-5254350/advil-tylenol-which-painkiller-take-when" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;u&gt;over-the-counter anti-inflammatory medication&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, massage the area, do gentle stretches, or place ice or heating packs in 20- to 30-minute bouts on your body.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Don't underestimate the power of a hot shower, she says. "It can go a long way in calming down those unhappy muscles."&lt;/p&gt;   
   &lt;p class="hr"&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This story was edited by Malaka Gharib. The visual editor is Beck Harlan. We'd love to hear from you. Leave us a voicemail at 202-216-9823, or email us at LifeKit@npr.org.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Listen to Life Kit on &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="http://n.pr/3LdRb0X" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt; and &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="http://n.pr/3K3xVln" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Spotify&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;, and sign up for our &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="http://n.pr/3xN1tB9" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;em&gt;newsletter&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;. Follow us on Instagram: &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/nprlifekit" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;em&gt;@nprlifekit&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>NPR</author><pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 09:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilwFBVV95cUxNZzdDdlFPeGcxYk5LQ182Z3I3RGRjZzhENmd4aDZRclFoeXJERUtSZmZwVkxtckpJeGRwWWRYY0d2SzJkUUFtUDc1Z3Z3SjFVX0VSZWlBc083ckRSM2FHQ1BJN2ZiMmhvMTI2NWR3elRvVTRQcGtTSDY2UEVPekVSTFMxQmpNUHNWY2E4MGRUeDBmNkE0by1v</guid></item><item><title>Staunton诊所的所有者被州委员会吊销了护理执照- The News Leader |弗吉尼亚州斯汤顿</title><link>https://www.newsleader.com/story/news/local/2025/10/02/owner-of-staunton-clinic-has-her-nursing-license-suspended-by-state/86457728007/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="gnt_ar_b"&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;A nurse practitioner and owner of A Family Care Clinic, formerly located on Lambert Avenue in Staunton, had her license suspended last week by the state following allegations she improperly prescribed opioids and failed to engage in proper practices regarding the management of chronic pain for several of her patients.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;On Sept. 26, the Virginia Committee of the Joint Boards of Nursing and Medicine suspended the license of Amy E. Kubler, an advanced practice registered nurse, concluding "that a substantial danger to public health or safety warrants this action," according to the Virginia Department of Health Professions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The News Leader | Staunton, VA</author><pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 08:42:46 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi0AFBVV95cUxPemo1WTRWQXpvSUh2QzJJNWhYZFV1d1RkTlVVUW96SmdHcTJua21SMVkxY3kwNkFsR0tYenI5RGJwUjFIWXVoMkhIT1lWYWpkcHF2MWIzNUxIMk9Ga1hzN2k5S285SnhLcVZBQ1Fsd1drRmVXQjJVdWVXWHBZajRmZFp0UlVqei1XeVZSZFUtN2pfeHNSRmRaeG1ncUtnNUNla2xYV1VYUkZvcTIwcHUyMFBxMHpGUjQ4Tl9XZ1NtcTdoRUtaSkVycVNYNmtGU0tv</guid></item><item><title>这种欧盟禁止的化学物质与帕金森病有关- Euronews.com</title><link>https://www.euronews.com/health/2025/10/02/industrial-chemical-banned-in-the-eu-linked-to-parkinsons-disease</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p&gt;S:E]���pQ�a��������p��K`pL�?L�v\����_����J��p�%��&amp;amp;\=��Is=�r����:@ -6��&amp;gt;���T9�_��-�I�~��/��˧c��?.�d����d�D]S}JS�ߌ�$�
�(�Cs�c�{��uz�������7��Qn��g2��t��hz�5�5/���H ɠ " �w���
� ��]wrh{��c,@2�4���8��pcJ�}��{�_�x�Ьa���DvԊ�\�&amp;lt;��hw����7�~���l��N"��8�!�&amp;gt;���W��g�� Y �b�"��;3$E�D�+*C��)��!u�i$�\���?�x�3�C
ݺ[���+�~�������$i��c���s��LG� t����}MA=n��*�35J���CYdj����ρ��YK��/�����U�"�R�s�dL����V� �3=C���yk; ��a������j��S3�Xe:{���m�F�ǀB`.o���o���߄x p���a�W��d1��Qt�o�l����/�e&amp;lt;�N� ��:R�F�~��&amp;lt; �AbM�����w0��`��B��u�ה�UQ���K���/����H�����[����A*&amp;amp;d��ם��z&amp;gt;י�Yѷ֨�#�c ��5A����C�[z?!=9��:���F}W�x���ܹCe�O���!�Io�M�?�﹆�:g����/㹠�Zw^YR���B�����I�QmK~%�&amp;lt;	�`Eb��ԯ����ZI����i���I�LE�(�h����4�l�0����OQ��"(�ѵ2��h��R�B|{��@�kb3���v4a�g?���
��}�UC�30q��H��d��{�@ �Ew�&amp;lt;���w,!����wg�辣eF��!��̏�;E�#�#���)�"�
w����s�f�i��F�QC=�%w]�3����QW�C#�r��h�k���5 ���+��Q�?��2p�σ�=�ڕW�q��#*t��d@�{�D�tG�(���nq��H(#|M�:��7	oE[e�����z2o!�Y������Xiuxz�%�A�^�@ZT3 ���g]Q#{ԪR�F�c��x���'�PF!�a[w;R�K�c #&amp;gt;^��J����v�N��� G��W�r���q���%�\tl�������tat�"g��A��j&amp;lt;��-�&amp;amp;�����N���8]���x:�I�f��h����I1�M�D���b*q"8�B.�I:��"��X��x6����U��9ð�:��L��q����e�l&amp;gt;�4���y���*��P�$���������&amp;lt;��5��&amp;amp;z���������ٕ�;�� ,�&lt;l&gt;&lt;/l&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Euronews.com</author><pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 06:00:52 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMirAFBVV95cUxPRV83Y2Jzazh5VFY5Z3MybFJxM0M4R3ZEWjJlY05KQUIyM3BaZGFIdlVod21kRkhsVEQ1cGg3cDFhRzVXVGpobHVPZXBXVXctYlVqdzBIek9lalNtdzdfWm1tNkxWVUpvcjExSVRybS12N0tJR1oxTG9QM0pqQ3ZSRGJwR3pRazhzQ0hZM3ExY3F1Ym0wamVKTHhvZ1BjT0lKWWdhU3hNTnVZU1dB</guid></item><item><title>心脏病警报：超过99 ％的心脏病早期预示着问题-以下是值得关注的内容-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/more-than-99-of-heart-conditions-come-with-early-warning-signs-new-study-finds/articleshow/124219979.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;div class="MwN2O"&gt;&lt;div class="vdo_embedd"&gt; &lt;div class="T22zO"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to a new study published on Monday in the Journal of the American College of Cardiology, before a heart attack, stroke or other cardiovascular disease hits there are almost always warning signs. Yes, your body gives you signals. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="3"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Researchers analysed data from two groups: more than 600,000 cases of cardiovascular disease in South Korea and another 1,000 cases in the United States. They analysed what percentage of those cases were preceded by traditional risk factors for cardiovascular disease, including blood pressure levels, blood sugar, cholesterol and smoking.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="5"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="lOvcW vdo_embedd"&gt;&lt;div class="k7lcu"&gt;&lt;p class="efT4r"&gt;Heart Attack Warning Signs That Women May Confuse With Menopause Symptoms&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="7"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to the data, in more than 99% of cases of cardiovascular disease, heart failure or stroke, the patient had at least one of the risk factors before the incident occurred.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="10"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/blood-type-a-linked-to-higher-stroke-risk-find-out-where-your-blood-group-stands/articleshow/124227869.cms" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;Blood type A linked to higher stroke risk: Find out where your blood group stands&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="12"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/can-geomagnetic-storms-affect-your-blood-pressure/articleshow/124226871.cms" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;Can geomagnetic storms affect your blood pressure?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="14"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/what-does-magnesium-deficiency-look-like-in-women-know-common-symptoms/photostory/124241743.cms" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;What does magnesium deficiency look like in women? Know common symptoms&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="16"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Even ‘mild’ elevations of these 4 factors should be addressed with lifestyle treatments or medications,” said Dr Philip Greenland, one of the study’s lead authors, in an email to CNN Health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="18"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div data-pos="0" class="id-r-component QbQNS undefined  
        "&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;img alt="Patient had at least one of the risk factors before the incident occurred" msid="124220155" width="" title="Image credits: Getty Images" placeholdersrc="https://static.toiimg.com/photo/83033472.cms" imgsize="23456" resizemode="4" offsetvertical="0" placeholdermsid="" type="thumb" src="https://static.toiimg.com/photo/83033472.cms" class="" data-src="https://static.toiimg.com/photo/imgsize-23456,msid-124220155,resizemode-4/patient-had-at-least-one-of-the-risk-factors-before-the-incident-occurred.jpg" data-api-prerender="true"&gt;&lt;p class="q3gJl"&gt;Image credits: Getty Images&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="20"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;As per Dr Susan Cheng, professor and vice chair of research affairs in the department of cardiology at the Smidt Heart Institute at Cedars-Sinai Medical Center in Los Angeles, the new study is particularly important because it reinforces that doctors and patients can manage risk factors for almost all cases of heart disease. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It is unique because scientists looked at patients' medical data, rather than their diagnosis and the presence of risk factors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="24"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div data-type="in_view" class="  "&gt;&lt;div class="EEW3_ timeline_pollWrapper_as " data-scrollga="scroll#poll_view"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="hLnAH"&gt;Poll&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="KEEGr"&gt;Do you believe that managing lifestyle factors can prevent cardiovascular disease?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="26"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;So, if clinicians and patients want to mitigate heart disease risk, the best course of action is likely to continue encouraging management of risk factors like blood sugar, blood pressure, cholesterol and smoking, said Cheng.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="28"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;In addition to clinical risk factors studied in the research, it is also important to improve your lifestyle risk factors. Maintaining good sleep, exercise, nutrition, a healthy weight and low levels of stress are key to lowering cardiovascular disease risk. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="30"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="31"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Times of India</author><pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 05:42:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiigJBVV95cUxNcEprbV9tUEstbXF6NXZfd2lvcUhBR1BrcldpdzVWN1A3NF82c1F2bDVxWGNoSkVCSXoyb1dBaVB5N1pQQkd1YVFCRl9OX2tUbzcxWFU5cFpHMlUxVldpMHFELTMtQ1JnV1NZb1o4Vlc2YWxUa1ZkZDBfTy1QdEttRlBUSExHUk1qdHBfWHlTUjBOa0hqclk0alZSR1llRnJtem4wRHNnbFNqMmRsZkUzN3JFcWQxVGMwN3RfUGwzY25FWXhybjBDeUQydUpuTzVTZ2RqLXRKSWR5VjRtdjRLTFNYRVdod3gyRHYxelFBcm5ZZ21TbWtsOUQxdmM3cE55Y3RJUUNDQzZkd9IBjwJBVV95cUxNV2prRkFRaGFrWW5yTVpHZm5mQnpxZ0Q3V0x4UGZLNElXOW1WZ3RPdDVyVUprSFJmdnpwQlB0VUhnNHlkNmRPOEhvOXdiSThNenFOaDc5LXhYXzBTUElhV1U3RC1EVnQ3UDBQZ3JZcDFFWHIxd0U0Sm5wTExIRzkxQXVPdXlZUXhYQmhqNDJfM3djMUxZSmN5MmxZMGhWZkE4a2dFV3NPa1hBNVduRkNzb1ZJRXFVeHJyb1BCUTZ0SDhTckdUVHFKQVdRYU5PaDhPWFVLcm8xM2R6NmdEcGxIVGxIV3lNM1RpT0ZDZHU1Z0hXZkdfTDZiX3JEX2Zvc3hRUVh0VHNrUkk5SlQ4Xzdr</guid></item><item><title>男子说，多年“不必要的” UHCW化疗夺走了他的青春-英国广播公司</title><link>https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/cdjzpllmke3o</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article&gt;&lt;p data-component="headline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 bPbmDW"&gt;&lt;h1 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 jRDKjj"&gt;'Years of unnecessary chemotherapy stole my youth'&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 kSquvq"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="hero-image" class="sc-5340b511-1 ilsLtA"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20250919-090805-05e5ba0164-web-2.30.1-2/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 hagXkB hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/272a/live/8a2bf180-9cfd-11f0-9297-a5fd92668561.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/272a/live/8a2bf180-9cfd-11f0-9297-a5fd92668561.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/272a/live/8a2bf180-9cfd-11f0-9297-a5fd92668561.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/272a/live/8a2bf180-9cfd-11f0-9297-a5fd92668561.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/272a/live/8a2bf180-9cfd-11f0-9297-a5fd92668561.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/272a/live/8a2bf180-9cfd-11f0-9297-a5fd92668561.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/272a/live/8a2bf180-9cfd-11f0-9297-a5fd92668561.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/272a/live/8a2bf180-9cfd-11f0-9297-a5fd92668561.jpg.webp" loading="eager" alt="BBC A close-up on a man's face and neck. He has brown hair and stares into the camera. The background is blurred but a red-brick house is visible behind him, as are several cars on a drive." class="sc-5340b511-0 bGQwLJ"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 lha-dta"&gt;BBC&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 etSgSK"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 jFVvLh"&gt;Jonathan Jones was given chemotherapy tablets for 16 years, but NHS guidelines say they should usually only be taken for six months&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;A brain cancer patient who says he was prescribed chemotherapy tablets for 16 years, even though NHS guidelines say they should usually only be taken for six months, has said he feels his youth was stolen from him. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Jonathan Jones was diagnosed with anaplastic astrocytoma in 2007 when he was 17 and took temozolomide tablets until November 2023, when he was 33.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Since he has raised his case with lawyers, more than 30 other brain cancer patients at University Hospitals Coventry and Warwickshire (UHCW) have raised similar concerns. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;The NHS trust said it was committed to providing the safest possible care and had commissioned an independent inquiry.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Prof Ian Brown, the oncologist who oversaw Mr Jones's care, is being investigated by the General Medical Council (GMC). The BBC has attempted to contact the retired professor several times.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Mr Jones, now aged 36, said: "I lost my freedom, I couldn't do anything at the time. I had 16, 17 years taken away from me."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;The landscape gardener from Lichfield, Staffordshire, said he had had dental problems, joint pain and anxiety issues since being diagnosed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 bPbmDW"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 fsBZby"&gt;'If you don't carry on, you'll die'&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Talking about the impact on his life, he said: "I was off [work] every single month for seven days and I couldn't get employed, so financially that was a problem.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"The pain I suffered at home… I'd stay in bed, I'd have panic attacks. Sickness, tiredness. I didn't really go out much.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"It caused a lot of stress for my family as well." &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Mr Jones was told he would need to stay on his tablets to stay alive, and when he questioned the treatment, he said the reply was: "Do you want to die? If you don't carry on taking the chemo, you'll die."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Guidelines say temozolomide should usually be taken post radiotherapy &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://products.mhra.gov.uk/search/?search=Temozolomide&amp;amp;page=2" class="sc-f9178328-0 jZoZnB"&gt;for six cycles&lt;/a&gt;. This is usually over six months.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;There are a wide range of side effects associated with temozolomide, including muscle weakness, memory issues and, in rare cases, secondary cancers and liver damage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Another patient, Samantha Smith from Bromsgrove, Worcestershire, says she took temozolomide for six-and-a-half years while under the direction of Prof Brown at UHCW.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;She said she had suffered from teeth and gum decay, mobility issues and chronic fatigue.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Ms Smith said: "You never expect anybody to turn around and say to you 'by the way, you've had too much'.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"I get a lot more lethargic now. I can't move as much as I used to… it's difficult now to walk downstairs on my own. I fall a lot."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 etSgSK"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 jFVvLh"&gt;Samantha Smith said she was more lethargic and fell over a lot, after six-and-a-half years of taking temozolomide&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Law firm Brabners says it has obtained data, using Freedom of Information requests that shows UHCW spent more than £3.6m on temozolomide between 2009 and 2024 – more than 10 times that of comparable NHS hospitals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;In a statement, UHCW said: "The Trust is committed to providing the safest possible care.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"We have comprehensively reviewed and spoken to all individuals who were receiving temozolomide (TMZ) treatment at the end of 2023 to ensure appropriate support and care plans are in place."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;It added: "A high-grade brain tumour is an extremely complex condition and all modes of treatment – surgery, chemotherapy and radiotherapy – carry the risk of complications and side effects.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"National Institute for Health and Care Excellence guidelines recognise that clinicians can exercise professional judgement appropriate to individual circumstances when offering treatment to patients.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"We have commissioned the Royal College of Physicians to conduct an independent review of a representative cohort of patients who received greater than 12 cycles of adjuvant TMZ between 2017 and 2023.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"As this process is ongoing, it would be inappropriate to comment further at this stage."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;A statement from the GMC said: "Dr Ian Brown is currently registered with a licence to practise but with interim conditions on his registration pending the conclusion of a GMC investigation. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"The interim restrictions were first imposed on Dr Brown's practice on 23 August 2024."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BBC</author><pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 05:11:52 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiWkFVX3lxTE9zdTFySXVlajdTYlBtbmNvUEpzZHJpX2pDWmhRbVlUSV9YQklwWmtYeXNUSExYaXVCUE53bDNNdHdYNU9MS056b1dzZ25IdjRrd1kxNUl0bWZTQdIBX0FVX3lxTE80cklybUh6Q1ZuTU1JTVQwYTFHYnJmT0ZPbGhwcWZocTAwNW0xaHgxZW1iYTdHNmVoUnBuWmROWnJWVjFxeEI1Y0laX2ZmWHhTWGV3OU5FVGUyMEZsSnVR</guid></item><item><title>咖啡因袋可以一次包装2杯咖啡。这就是它们存在风险的原因。- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/caffeine-pouches-can-pack-2-coffees-in-1-hit-heres-why-theyre-a-risk</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;A new  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/how-does-caffeine-wake-you-up" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73115" data-postid="176148" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;caffeine&lt;/a&gt; craze is brewing on social media – no kettle required. Caffeine pouches promise a fast, discreet hit of energy without the faff of brewing  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/how-does-caffeine-wake-you-up" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73115" data-postid="176148" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;coffee&lt;/a&gt; or cracking open an energy drink.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But while they may look like a harmless pick-me-up, experts warn they carry real risks, especially for teenagers and people with underlying health conditions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.bmj.com/content/390/bmj.r1712?hwshib2=authn%3A1758028919%3A20250915%253A086ccafc-48fc-48e2-80a6-86d64763ae1e%3A0%3A0%3A0%3AEezbRMu3mBW%2Fye%2FBad3NnA%3D%3D"&gt;Caffeine pouches&lt;/a&gt; look and work a lot like &lt;a href="https://ashscotland.org.uk/briefing/nicotine-pouches/"&gt;nicotine pouches&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/white-snus-why-tobacco-free-doesnt-mean-risk-free-252085"&gt;or snus&lt;/a&gt;. Each small, pillow-shaped packet contains micro-ground caffeine, flavourings and sometimes herbs or  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/what-are-vitamins-and-do-we-really-need-to-take-them" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73116" data-postid="176148" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;vitamins&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/anti-anxiety-chill-out-drinks-are-storming-the-market-are-they-safe"&gt;Anti-Anxiety 'Chill-Out Drinks' Are Storming The Market. Are They Safe?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Slip one under your lip and the caffeine goes straight into the bloodstream through your gums – bypassing the digestive system. The result? A jolt of energy that lands far quicker than a cup of coffee or tea.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Caffeine perks us up by &lt;a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/books/NBK430790/"&gt;blocking adenosine&lt;/a&gt;, a brain chemical that makes us feel sleepy. People have long used coffee, tea and energy drinks to &lt;a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/books/NBK430790/"&gt;stay awake, sharpen focus and boost performance&lt;/a&gt;. Pouches simply offer a hands-free, no-spill shortcut.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some gym-goers and shift workers like the convenience, &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/can-coffee-improve-your-workout-the-science-of-caffeine-and-exercise-92366"&gt;while athletes value&lt;/a&gt; caffeine's ability to &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/29876876/"&gt;increase endurance&lt;/a&gt; by making the brain register less fatigue and pain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Their discreet design is also a selling point for teenagers, who may use them to stay alert in class or during exams. That worries experts: some fear caffeine pouches could be a gateway to nicotine or other stimulants, and some young users are even pairing them with nicotine pouches, doubling the stimulant load.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;TikTok has super-charged their popularity, with influencers showing them off in classrooms, gyms and gaming sessions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Potent little packets&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Depending on the brand, each pouch delivers 25mg to more than 200mg of caffeine. For comparison, a typical mug of instant coffee contains about 100mg, a mug of tea 75mg and a can of cola around 40mg. Some pouches therefore pack the caffeine punch of two cups of coffee in one hit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;How much is too much? For healthy adults, the &lt;a href="https://www.efsa.europa.eu/en/efsajournal/pub/4102"&gt;recommended daily limit&lt;/a&gt; is around 400mg. Pregnant women are advised to stay below &lt;a href="https://www.efsa.europa.eu/en/efsajournal/pub/4102"&gt;200mg per day&lt;/a&gt; because higher intakes can increase the risk of &lt;a href="https://www.rcm.org.uk/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/caffeine-in-pregnancy.pdf"&gt;complications such as low birth weight or pregnancy loss&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There's little data on safe levels for children, but the &lt;a href="https://www.food.gov.uk/business-guidance/guidance-for-food-business-operators-on-food-supplements-containing-caffeine"&gt;European Food Safety Authority&lt;/a&gt; recommends a lower limit of 3mg of caffeine per kilogram of body weight – roughly 45–150mg per day depending on age and size. Children's smaller bodies and developing systems make them more sensitive to caffeine's effects.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A single pouch with 200mg of caffeine can easily push a teenager well beyond that limit. And because the drug is absorbed so quickly, side-effects, such as &lt;a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/books/NBK430790/"&gt;jitteriness, anxiety, insomnia and heart palpitations&lt;/a&gt;, can hit harder.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Caffeine may give a short-term buzz, but it can also disturb sleep, create a cycle of fatigue and &lt;a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/books/NBK430790/"&gt;lead to dependence&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Who's most at risk&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Moderate caffeine is generally safe for most adults, but certain groups are more vulnerable. People with &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC5445139/"&gt;mental health conditions&lt;/a&gt; may be especially sensitive.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;By blocking adenosine and boosting dopamine activity, caffeine can &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC10867825/"&gt;worsen anxiety&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC11376648/"&gt;or psychosis&lt;/a&gt; and even increase the risk of relapse in conditions &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S019188691000591X"&gt;such as schizophrenia&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC4578903/"&gt;bipolar disorder&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It can also make &lt;a href="https://www.medicalnewstoday.com/articles/271707"&gt;other addictive substances&lt;/a&gt; feel more rewarding, potentially nudging people toward substance use disorders. The science isn't yet clear enough to set a safe limit for these groups.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Those with &lt;a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/books/NBK202224/"&gt;heart problems&lt;/a&gt; also need to be cautious. Caffeine temporarily raises heart rate and blood pressure, adding stress to the heart. Some people experience palpitations, and &lt;a href="https://www.internationaljournalofcardiology.com/article/S0167-5273(13)00298-2/abstract"&gt;athletes&lt;/a&gt; who mix high doses of caffeine with intense exercise may face an elevated risk of heart issues.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Extreme cases are rare, but there have been documented &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC5445139/"&gt;caffeine-related deaths&lt;/a&gt;, usually involving supplements or highly concentrated products: reminders of how potent this commonplace stimulant can be.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;h2&gt;A regulatory blind spot&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the UK, caffeine pouches occupy a legal grey zone. They're neither food nor medicine, so they escape the usual safety checks and labelling rules. Shoppers can't always be sure how much caffeine they're getting – or what other ingredients might be mixed in.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Health experts are calling for clearer warnings and age restrictions, particularly as many brands use fruity flavours and bright packaging designed to catch the eye of younger consumers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Caffeine pouches may be fashionable and convenient, but their rapid absorption and high potency make it easy to overshoot safe limits, especially for teens. An occasional pouch might not be harmful for most adults, but they're no risk-free substitute for coffee or tea.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As with any stimulant, moderation isn't just sensible, it's essential.&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://counter.theconversation.com/content/263933/count.gif?distributor=republish-lightbox-basic" alt="The Conversation" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" loading="lazy"&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/profiles/dipa-kamdar-1485027"&gt;Dipa Kamdar&lt;/a&gt;, Senior Lecturer in Pharmacy Practice, &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/institutions/kingston-university-949"&gt;Kingston University&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This article is republished from &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com"&gt;The Conversation&lt;/a&gt; under a Creative Commons license. Read the &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/caffeine-pouches-deliver-a-fast-hit-and-hidden-risks-263933"&gt;original article&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 04:38:11 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMingFBVV95cUxQcXNKb2Mwbm94eUlWbHdXZlJ6d3B4VGZwMS1faUJ2cVljLWRxQUszTDQxSWRYRE05UGxncndIOXZ3LVlXSzVoX1kzeFc4MVR4VGFYQ0d3VWZURnNFT0cyMVo5cDQ4djNIX3JEOUk1bHhGX2xLVlZ5UjJ4cUFrRHp5WE5Sdi1GWnMyYm10TDVVQThOQi1iazh1aUtYMzgtZw</guid></item><item><title>研究发现，当您睡眠不佳时，您的大脑看起来会变老- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/your-brain-looks-older-when-youve-slept-poorly-study-finds</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;We spend nearly a third of our lives asleep, yet sleep is anything but wasted time. Far from being passive downtime, it is an active and essential process that helps restore the body and protect the brain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When sleep is disrupted, the brain feels the consequences – sometimes in subtle ways that accumulate over years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.ebiom.2025.105941"&gt;new study&lt;/a&gt;, my colleagues and I examined sleep behaviour and detailed brain  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/magnetic-resonance-imaging" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73063" data-postid="176129" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;MRI&lt;/a&gt; scan data in more than 27,000 UK adults between the ages of 40 and 70. We found that people with poor sleep had brains that appeared significantly older than expected based on their actual age.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/one-stage-of-sleep-seems-critical-for-reducing-risk-of-dementia"&gt;One Stage of Sleep Seems Critical For Reducing Risk of Dementia&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What does it mean for the brain to "look older"? While we all grow chronologically older at the same pace, some people's biological clocks can tick faster or slower than others.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;New advances in brain imaging and  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/artificial-intelligence" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73092" data-postid="176129" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;artificial intelligence&lt;/a&gt; allow researchers to estimate a person's brain age based on patterns in brain MRI scans, such as loss of brain tissue, thinning of the cortex, and damage to blood vessels.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In our study, brain age was estimated using over 1,000 different imaging markers from MRI scans. We first trained a  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/artificial-intelligence" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73092" data-postid="176129" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;machine learning&lt;/a&gt; model on the scans of the healthiest participants – people with no major diseases, whose brains should closely match their chronological age. Once the model "learned" what normal ageing looks like, we applied it to the full study population.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_176138" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-176138" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/sleep_study_mri_scans_642.jpg" alt="mri scans of a brain" class="wp-image-176138 size-full" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/sleep_study_mri_scans_642.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/sleep_study_mri_scans_642-600x374.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-176138" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Brain aging was estimated from over 1,000 different imaging markers. (&lt;a href="https://www.canva.com/photos/MADnBGtNmtE/"&gt;LarisaBozhikova/Getty Images/Canva&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Having a brain age higher than your actual age can be a signal of departure from healthy ageing. &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41380-018-0098-1"&gt;Previous research&lt;/a&gt; has linked an older-appearing brain to faster cognitive decline, greater dementia risk, and even higher risk of early death.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sleep is complex, and no single measure can tell the whole story of a person's sleep health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Our study, therefore, focused on five aspects of sleep self-reported by the study participants: their chronotype ("morning" or "evening" person), how many hours they typically sleep (seven to eight hours is considered optimal), whether they experience insomnia, whether they snore, and whether they feel excessively sleepy during the day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These characteristics can interact in synergistic ways. For example, someone with frequent insomnia may also feel more daytime sleepiness, and having a late chronotype may lead to shorter sleep duration.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;By integrating all five characteristics into a "healthy sleep score", we captured a fuller picture of overall sleep health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;People with four or five healthy traits had a "healthy" sleep profile, while those with two to three had an "intermediate" profile, and those with zero or one had a "poor" profile.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When we compared brain age across different sleep profiles, the differences were clear. The gap between brain age and chronological age widened by about six months for every one point decrease in healthy sleep score.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On average, people with a poor sleep profile had brains that appeared nearly one year older than expected based on their chronological age, while those with a healthy sleep profile showed no such gap.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We also considered the five sleep characteristics individually: late chronotype and abnormal sleep duration stood out as the biggest contributors to faster brain ageing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_176139" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-176139" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/working_late_night_642.jpg" alt="woman working late" class="wp-image-176139 size-full" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/working_late_night_642.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/working_late_night_642-600x374.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-176139" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Late chronotypes, or late owls, are at risk of faster ageing brains. (&lt;a href="https://www.canva.com/photos/MAEJTZj5ENo/"&gt;M_a_y_a/Getty Images Signature/Canva&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;A year may not sound like much, but in terms of brain health, it matters. Even small accelerations in brain ageing can compound over time, potentially increasing the risk of cognitive impairment, dementia, and other neurological conditions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The good news is that sleep habits are modifiable. While not all sleep problems are easily fixed, &lt;a href="https://newsinhealth.nih.gov/2021/04/good-sleep-good-health"&gt;simple strategies&lt;/a&gt;: keeping a regular sleep schedule; limiting  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/how-does-caffeine-wake-you-up" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73115" data-postid="176129" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;caffeine&lt;/a&gt;, alcohol, and screen use before bedtime; and creating a dark and quiet sleep environment can improve sleep health and may protect brain health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;How exactly does the quality of a person's sleep affect their brain health?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.thelancet.com/journals/laneur/article/PIIS1474-4422(18)30450-2/abstract"&gt;One explanation&lt;/a&gt; may be inflammation. Increasing evidence suggests that sleep disturbances raise the level of inflammation in the body. In turn, inflammation can harm the brain in several ways: damaging blood vessels, triggering the buildup of toxic proteins, and speeding up brain cell death.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/better-sleep-could-help-your-brain-flush-out-dementia-linked-toxins"&gt;Better Sleep Could Help Your Brain Flush Out Dementia-Linked Toxins&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We were able to investigate the role of inflammation thanks to blood samples collected from participants at the beginning of the study. These samples contain a wealth of information about different inflammatory biomarkers circulating in the body.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When we factored this into our analysis, we found that inflammation levels accounted for about 10% of the connection between sleep and brain ageing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Other processes may also play a role&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another explanation centres on the &lt;a href="https://www.science.org/content/article/sleep-ultimate-brainwasher"&gt;glymphatic system&lt;/a&gt; – the brain's built-in waste clearance network, which is mainly active during sleep. When sleep is disrupted or insufficient, this system may not function properly, allowing harmful substances to build up in the brain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yet another possibility is that poor sleep increases the risk of other health conditions that are themselves damaging for brain health, including &lt;a href="https://alz-journals.onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/full/10.1002/alz.12482"&gt;type 2 diabetes&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jamapsychiatry/fullarticle/2797529"&gt;obesity&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href="https://academic.oup.com/eurheartj/article/44/7/573/6964658"&gt;cardiovascular disease&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Our study is one of the largest and most comprehensive of its kind, benefiting from a very large study population, a multidimensional measure of sleep health, and a detailed estimation of brain age through thousands of brain MRI features.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Though &lt;a href="https://academic.oup.com/sleep/article-abstract/40/1/zsw032/2661823?redirectedFrom=fulltext"&gt;previous research&lt;/a&gt; connected poor sleep to cognitive decline and dementia, our study further demonstrated that poor sleep is tied to a measurably older-looking brain, and inflammation might explain this link.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Brain ageing cannot be avoided, but our behaviour and lifestyle choices can shape how it unfolds. The implications of our research are clear: to keep the brain healthier for longer, it is important to make sleep a priority.&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://counter.theconversation.com/content/265309/count.gif?distributor=republish-lightbox-basic" alt="The Conversation" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" loading="lazy"&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/profiles/abigail-dove-2481902"&gt;Abigail Dove&lt;/a&gt;, Postdoctoral Researcher, Neuroepidemiology, &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/institutions/karolinska-institutet-1250"&gt;Karolinska Institutet&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This article is republished from &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com"&gt;The Conversation&lt;/a&gt; under a Creative Commons license. Read the &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/poor-sleep-may-make-your-brain-age-faster-new-study-265309"&gt;original article&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 01:28:54 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikAFBVV95cUxNcUw0VlJobGFUeWJ3R2tySXZ4ZGtIeHFWZElQR2N5VXFwMExydmdKRGlHOGpPR0tpM2NzSTV2a0Q2bjZ1S3Z6WU15UjdlMnRkbGtEc1Y3MkRRZFRDdEFidkk1YVJhMnRmRFFTUjlBM0t1bjRUODdvWVBOZXNYZGFYLTU0MzdsWWhRV2VlM3BvQ3U</guid></item><item><title>25%的男性前列腺增大50 ：现在可以做些什么来预防它-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/25-of-men-will-have-an-enlarged-prostate-by-50-what-can-be-done-now-to-prevent-it/photostory/124256849.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="COQxt" data-ua-type="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;A healthy lifestyle, and hearty diet goes a long way in preventing &lt;a href="https://www.urologyhealth.org/urology-a-z/b/benign-prostatic-hyperplasia-(bph)%5B10"&gt;prostate&lt;/a&gt;. However, this must be adapted at a young age, since the condition cannot be reversed per se. Physical exercise helps maintain blood circulation and hormone equilibrium, which helps control prostate enlargement. A balanced weight achieved through proper eating habits decreases insulin resistance and inflammation, which are linked to BPH development. The reduction of caffeine and alcohol consumption together with spicy food intake, helps reduce urinary symptoms. Drinking enough water throughout the day helps control nighttime urination, but avoid drinking too much before bedtime. The management of stress together with sufficient sleep duration plays essential roles in maintaining prostate health. Basic changes in daily habits, create an effective method to protect prostate health naturally.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 23:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi_AFBVV95cUxOUGFTVmxXYWRzNkRWNTRGZnQ5WHl4QTlJR3pGWGxrMGZlaVE5ZWd6R1ZSMnJqNE5TSVRLZzJBbW5Lb0lSY1h0Wm5QNGswbnBvczBMMFk5TERyOFR1V0FQZE5rdmFrMVhRTDZNdktoSVFvRWVGdEF2UWZXdnY5QUtEV2FTLXZuYk14RHZFYnhGZ2owNndmVk8zT0FueE1SMWVkZkh0b0ZEaGQycHYzeGtVMVdjUFhrQlhGNTRaS21EWXNvNmtnZXBsbnc3U2hwR3c0YlNnZnN5QnZOcDZWdUVIajFXSmJKaklSYzZMcVhwQTZPRm8zbDdfTHpxSXTSAYQCQVVfeXFMTWZHZ29OVWZuUFZYSG15QXJySm81ZUkySjlOakxpWU5tdFJJRjBNZlkta0o0cU16Mk9WUGcwWDN1R29ySXB1bjFnNllXaGdyeGRXYnI5MmNqanpsenlBRzN5dWVFSUVlMGlBYkkzU0JaZHpUWmlyQWVNeGJYQUVDSUFPNlBEampaSk96b09TS0RqMGhnZDJaU2ktbEU4Umc4dnlzWXV0aVNvQnFZcHowTWc3elFmNGM5NmhCdGM0ODJjMWpNRHIyVWZRbWhTV2xCQTBHUm40T2loTVpObXZ0dThRTWpLelp1cWpYS2diTEFUeXVWUW9CMlJqRVdEdk02VmxZU1g</guid></item><item><title>食用油：我应该用橄榄油煎炸吗？如何选择合适的瓶子- BBC</title><link>https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/cj3y7j2dz44o</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article&gt;&lt;p data-component="headline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 bPbmDW"&gt;&lt;h1 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 jRDKjj"&gt;Should I use olive oil for frying? How to choose the right cooking oil&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 ERpRj"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="hero-image" class="sc-5340b511-1 ilsLtA"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20250919-090805-05e5ba0164-web-2.30.1-2/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 hagXkB hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/cecb/live/f253c650-9dea-11f0-b3aa-f94b46cdf49f.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/cecb/live/f253c650-9dea-11f0-b3aa-f94b46cdf49f.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/cecb/live/f253c650-9dea-11f0-b3aa-f94b46cdf49f.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/cecb/live/f253c650-9dea-11f0-b3aa-f94b46cdf49f.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/cecb/live/f253c650-9dea-11f0-b3aa-f94b46cdf49f.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/cecb/live/f253c650-9dea-11f0-b3aa-f94b46cdf49f.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/cecb/live/f253c650-9dea-11f0-b3aa-f94b46cdf49f.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/cecb/live/f253c650-9dea-11f0-b3aa-f94b46cdf49f.jpg.webp" loading="eager" alt="Getty Images Assorted healthy vegetable oil bottle collection on wooden table in a old fashioned kitchen with low key illumination: Olive oil, hazelnut oil, almond oil, coconut oil and sesame oil" class="sc-5340b511-0 bGQwLJ"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 lha-dta"&gt;Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Supermarket shelves are packed with oils from budget bottles of sunflower and vegetable oil to pricier olive, avocado and coconut oils claiming health benefits.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Oils and fats have been at the centre of nutritional debate for years and to understand why it matters, it helps to look at the different types of fat they contain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Not all fats behave the same way in the body - some raise cholesterol while others help lower it. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Cholesterol is a natural fatty substance produced in the liver and can also be found in some of the foods we eat. Too much bad cholesterol can lead to a build-up of fatty deposits inside the walls of blood vessels, causing them to become narrowed or blocked. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;With so many shifting messages, knowing which product to pick can often feel overwhelming.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Nita Forouhi, Professor of Population Health and Nutrition at the University of Cambridge, &lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/articles/5d6Xw8BbzfGb2s3SMJDdFMd/which-oils-should-we-be-using-for-cooking" class="sc-f9178328-0 jZoZnB"&gt;tells the BBC's Sliced Bread podcast&lt;/a&gt; that no single oil holds the magic key to health and debunks three common myths about cooking oils.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 bPbmDW"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 fsBZby"&gt;1. Use sunflower and vegetable oil for cooking&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jHorPx"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 ilsLtA"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20250919-090805-05e5ba0164-web-2.30.1-2/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 hagXkB hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/7744/live/e1651960-9deb-11f0-b3aa-f94b46cdf49f.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/7744/live/e1651960-9deb-11f0-b3aa-f94b46cdf49f.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/7744/live/e1651960-9deb-11f0-b3aa-f94b46cdf49f.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/7744/live/e1651960-9deb-11f0-b3aa-f94b46cdf49f.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/7744/live/e1651960-9deb-11f0-b3aa-f94b46cdf49f.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/7744/live/e1651960-9deb-11f0-b3aa-f94b46cdf49f.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/7744/live/e1651960-9deb-11f0-b3aa-f94b46cdf49f.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/7744/live/e1651960-9deb-11f0-b3aa-f94b46cdf49f.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Getty Images Close-up of a shopper holding a bottle of cooking oil in a supermarket aisle, focusing on food choices, daily shopping, and consumer lifestyle." class="sc-5340b511-0 bGQwLJ"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 lha-dta"&gt;Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 etSgSK"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 jFVvLh"&gt;Vegetable and sunflower oil is also a good budget option, costing around £2 a litre &lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Rapeseed oil (commonly sold as vegetable oil) and sunflower oils often get bad press with some claiming they are ultra-processed and can cause inflammation which can be damaging to cardiovascular health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;But, there isn't evidence to back this up. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;In fact, these oils contain a low amount - 5-10% -  of unhealthy saturated fats and are high in healthier mono- and polyunsaturated fats. Polyunsaturated fats (including omega-3 and omega-6) are essential for brain and heart health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Forouhi says that these oils are "absolutely good for us".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;She explains that they can offer a reduction in disease risk "when saturated fats [which can raise bad cholesterol] like butter, lard or ghee are replaced with these oils".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;At around £2 per litre in most supermarkets it's also a more budget friendly option  for cooking at home.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 bPbmDW"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 fsBZby"&gt;2. Margarine can help reduce bad cholesterol&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jHorPx"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 ilsLtA"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20250919-090805-05e5ba0164-web-2.30.1-2/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 hagXkB hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/204f/live/dcc67a60-9ef0-11f0-928c-71dbb8619e94.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/204f/live/dcc67a60-9ef0-11f0-928c-71dbb8619e94.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/204f/live/dcc67a60-9ef0-11f0-928c-71dbb8619e94.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/204f/live/dcc67a60-9ef0-11f0-928c-71dbb8619e94.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/204f/live/dcc67a60-9ef0-11f0-928c-71dbb8619e94.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/204f/live/dcc67a60-9ef0-11f0-928c-71dbb8619e94.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/204f/live/dcc67a60-9ef0-11f0-928c-71dbb8619e94.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/204f/live/dcc67a60-9ef0-11f0-928c-71dbb8619e94.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Getty Images Stock photo shows a close up image of a knife running through margarine with a spot of sunlight pouring in." class="sc-5340b511-0 bGQwLJ"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 lha-dta"&gt;Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 etSgSK"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 jFVvLh"&gt;Modern day margarines have close to zero amounts of trans fats in&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Margarine has had a bad reputation for years and many of us believe we should steer clear of it. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;That's because it used to contain harmful trans fats which are strongly linked with cardiovascular disease but modern day margarines "have close to zero amounts of trans fats" according to Forouhi. "So it can actually be part of a healthy diet and reduce the bad cholesterols."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Butter also isn't off the menu entirely. "If you love butter, for instance on your toast, by all means have it," says Forouhi. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;You can use both margarine and butter for cooking, but Forouhi recommends sometimes swapping them out for oil instead which has less saturated fat in. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;UK health guidelines advise to keep your saturated fat intake below 10% of calories and this is easier to do if you're using oil to cook with instead of butter.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 bPbmDW"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 fsBZby"&gt;3. Olive oil isn't suitable for deep frying &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jHorPx"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 ilsLtA"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20250919-090805-05e5ba0164-web-2.30.1-2/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 hagXkB hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/4198/live/01c15600-9ef1-11f0-92db-77261a15b9d2.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/4198/live/01c15600-9ef1-11f0-92db-77261a15b9d2.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/4198/live/01c15600-9ef1-11f0-92db-77261a15b9d2.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/4198/live/01c15600-9ef1-11f0-92db-77261a15b9d2.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/4198/live/01c15600-9ef1-11f0-92db-77261a15b9d2.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/4198/live/01c15600-9ef1-11f0-92db-77261a15b9d2.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/4198/live/01c15600-9ef1-11f0-92db-77261a15b9d2.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/4198/live/01c15600-9ef1-11f0-92db-77261a15b9d2.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Getty Images A stock photo shows a woman pouring a big bottle of sunflower oil into a deep wok pan on an electric hob with cooking ingredients all around her and her kitchen cabinets and oven in the background." class="sc-5340b511-0 bGQwLJ"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 lha-dta"&gt;Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 etSgSK"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 jFVvLh"&gt;Use sunflower or vegetable oil if you're deep frying food &lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Oils behave differently when heated which makes some of them unsuitable for frying.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Extra virgin olive oil, for example, is packed with antioxidants and beneficial compounds but its low smoke point means it is better for salad dressings or drizzling over food rather than deep frying.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;A smoke point is the point at which the fats in the oil start to break down and nasty compounds are released which can make the oil taste bitter, burnt or unpleasant. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Restaurateur Tim Hayward says for shallow frying he uses a basic olive oil.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;But for deep frying something like chips or battered fish, vegetable or sunflower oil is best as they withstand higher temperatures without breaking down. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Some studies have also shown that oils heated to above their smoke point release toxic chemical by-products. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;But Professor Forouhi says that type of cooking in the home is not very common and that long-term health studies still show that vegetable oils "without exception are related with better outcomes for chronic diseases."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 bPbmDW"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 fsBZby"&gt;Which oils should I be using? &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;If you're looking for a simple kitchen strategy:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class="sc-6f869981-0 bYhyhr"&gt;&lt;li class="sc-734a601e-0 NnDUj"&gt;For everyday cooking: Sunflower or rapeseed oil are affordable, healthy, and versatile. You could also use a basic olive oil&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul class="sc-6f869981-0 bYhyhr"&gt;&lt;li class="sc-734a601e-0 NnDUj"&gt;For salads and finishing dishes: Extra virgin olive oil adds flavour and health benefits&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul class="sc-6f869981-0 bYhyhr"&gt;&lt;li class="sc-734a601e-0 NnDUj"&gt;For deep frying: Stick with a high smoke point oil like vegetable or sunflower&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul class="sc-6f869981-0 bYhyhr"&gt;&lt;li class="sc-734a601e-0 NnDUj"&gt;For flavour variety: While they may not have the same health benefits as olive oil, you could use sesame, coconut or avocado oils for cold dishes if you like the flavour&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Overall, Professor Forouhi says it is better to look at your whole diet rather than obsess over which bottle to buy. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"I would recommend going with what taste and cost considerations you have and experiment with different types of oil that will bring you some health benefits," she explains. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;&lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.bbc.co.uk/newsletters/zyxfdnb" class="sc-f9178328-0 jZoZnB"&gt;Sign up here&lt;/a&gt; to receive our weekly newsletter highlighting uplifting stories and remarkable people from around the world.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BBC</author><pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 23:06:27 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiWkFVX3lxTE5tVHI1Rmhkbzk3V0JYem5PM01rMVBBZnNsc2F2LXNNZ01jOVlkZ204Um9wZVBMYkhwUUlkczJzbU1pdUJ5U2lHWmZXSE52aXdLa0w0UnpQeWk2Z9IBX0FVX3lxTE55dDVfT0JGZjZWNkMzOUdqYU4zMFprbW52VDVfWEhWd1Vxa1RleWxfVF80LU9PVXZ3UU1MQnM2WURpMEttMTNsRVF0NnVXNVhqSjJKbk9iaDA5NDVZemVF</guid></item><item><title>我应该使用橄榄油油炸吗？如何选择合适的食用油- BBC</title><link>https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/cj3y7j2dz44o</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article&gt;&lt;p data-component="headline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 bPbmDW"&gt;&lt;h1 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 jRDKjj"&gt;Should I use olive oil for frying? How to choose the right cooking oil&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 ERpRj"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="hero-image" class="sc-5340b511-1 ilsLtA"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20250919-090805-05e5ba0164-web-2.30.1-2/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 hagXkB hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/cecb/live/f253c650-9dea-11f0-b3aa-f94b46cdf49f.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/cecb/live/f253c650-9dea-11f0-b3aa-f94b46cdf49f.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/cecb/live/f253c650-9dea-11f0-b3aa-f94b46cdf49f.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/cecb/live/f253c650-9dea-11f0-b3aa-f94b46cdf49f.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/cecb/live/f253c650-9dea-11f0-b3aa-f94b46cdf49f.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/cecb/live/f253c650-9dea-11f0-b3aa-f94b46cdf49f.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/cecb/live/f253c650-9dea-11f0-b3aa-f94b46cdf49f.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/cecb/live/f253c650-9dea-11f0-b3aa-f94b46cdf49f.jpg.webp" loading="eager" alt="Getty Images Assorted healthy vegetable oil bottle collection on wooden table in a old fashioned kitchen with low key illumination: Olive oil, hazelnut oil, almond oil, coconut oil and sesame oil" class="sc-5340b511-0 bGQwLJ"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 lha-dta"&gt;Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Supermarket shelves are packed with oils from budget bottles of sunflower and vegetable oil to pricier olive, avocado and coconut oils claiming health benefits.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Oils and fats have been at the centre of nutritional debate for years and to understand why it matters, it helps to look at the different types of fat they contain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Not all fats behave the same way in the body - some raise cholesterol while others help lower it. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Cholesterol is a natural fatty substance produced in the liver and can also be found in some of the foods we eat. Too much bad cholesterol can lead to a build-up of fatty deposits inside the walls of blood vessels, causing them to become narrowed or blocked. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;With so many shifting messages, knowing which product to pick can often feel overwhelming.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Nita Forouhi, Professor of Population Health and Nutrition at the University of Cambridge, &lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/articles/5d6Xw8BbzfGb2s3SMJDdFMd/which-oils-should-we-be-using-for-cooking" class="sc-f9178328-0 jZoZnB"&gt;tells the BBC's Sliced Bread podcast&lt;/a&gt; that no single oil holds the magic key to health and debunks three common myths about cooking oils.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 bPbmDW"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 fsBZby"&gt;1. Use sunflower and vegetable oil for cooking&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jHorPx"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 ilsLtA"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20250919-090805-05e5ba0164-web-2.30.1-2/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 hagXkB hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/7744/live/e1651960-9deb-11f0-b3aa-f94b46cdf49f.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/7744/live/e1651960-9deb-11f0-b3aa-f94b46cdf49f.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/7744/live/e1651960-9deb-11f0-b3aa-f94b46cdf49f.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/7744/live/e1651960-9deb-11f0-b3aa-f94b46cdf49f.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/7744/live/e1651960-9deb-11f0-b3aa-f94b46cdf49f.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/7744/live/e1651960-9deb-11f0-b3aa-f94b46cdf49f.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/7744/live/e1651960-9deb-11f0-b3aa-f94b46cdf49f.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/7744/live/e1651960-9deb-11f0-b3aa-f94b46cdf49f.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Getty Images Close-up of a shopper holding a bottle of cooking oil in a supermarket aisle, focusing on food choices, daily shopping, and consumer lifestyle." class="sc-5340b511-0 bGQwLJ"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 lha-dta"&gt;Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 etSgSK"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 jFVvLh"&gt;Vegetable and sunflower oil is also a good budget option, costing around £2 a litre &lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Rapeseed oil (commonly sold as vegetable oil) and sunflower oils often get bad press with some claiming they are ultra-processed and can cause inflammation which can be damaging to cardiovascular health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;But, there isn't evidence to back this up. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;In fact, these oils contain a low amount - 5-10% -  of unhealthy saturated fats and are high in healthier mono- and polyunsaturated fats. Polyunsaturated fats (including omega-3 and omega-6) are essential for brain and heart health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Forouhi says that these oils are "absolutely good for us".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;She explains that they can offer a reduction in disease risk "when saturated fats [which can raise bad cholesterol] like butter, lard or ghee are replaced with these oils".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;At around £2 per litre in most supermarkets it's also a more budget friendly option  for cooking at home.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 bPbmDW"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 fsBZby"&gt;2. Margarine can help reduce bad cholesterol&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jHorPx"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 ilsLtA"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20250919-090805-05e5ba0164-web-2.30.1-2/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 hagXkB hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/204f/live/dcc67a60-9ef0-11f0-928c-71dbb8619e94.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/204f/live/dcc67a60-9ef0-11f0-928c-71dbb8619e94.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/204f/live/dcc67a60-9ef0-11f0-928c-71dbb8619e94.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/204f/live/dcc67a60-9ef0-11f0-928c-71dbb8619e94.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/204f/live/dcc67a60-9ef0-11f0-928c-71dbb8619e94.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/204f/live/dcc67a60-9ef0-11f0-928c-71dbb8619e94.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/204f/live/dcc67a60-9ef0-11f0-928c-71dbb8619e94.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/204f/live/dcc67a60-9ef0-11f0-928c-71dbb8619e94.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Getty Images Stock photo shows a close up image of a knife running through margarine with a spot of sunlight pouring in." class="sc-5340b511-0 bGQwLJ"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 lha-dta"&gt;Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 etSgSK"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 jFVvLh"&gt;Modern day margarines have close to zero amounts of trans fats in&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Margarine has had a bad reputation for years and many of us believe we should steer clear of it. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;That's because it used to contain harmful trans fats which are strongly linked with cardiovascular disease but modern day margarines "have close to zero amounts of trans fats" according to Forouhi. "So it can actually be part of a healthy diet and reduce the bad cholesterols."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Butter also isn't off the menu entirely. "If you love butter, for instance on your toast, by all means have it," says Forouhi. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;You can use both margarine and butter for cooking, but Forouhi recommends sometimes swapping them out for oil instead which has less saturated fat in. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;UK health guidelines advise to keep your saturated fat intake below 10% of calories and this is easier to do if you're using oil to cook with instead of butter.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 bPbmDW"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 fsBZby"&gt;3. Olive oil isn't suitable for deep frying &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jHorPx"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 ilsLtA"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20250919-090805-05e5ba0164-web-2.30.1-2/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 hagXkB hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/4198/live/01c15600-9ef1-11f0-92db-77261a15b9d2.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/4198/live/01c15600-9ef1-11f0-92db-77261a15b9d2.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/4198/live/01c15600-9ef1-11f0-92db-77261a15b9d2.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/4198/live/01c15600-9ef1-11f0-92db-77261a15b9d2.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/4198/live/01c15600-9ef1-11f0-92db-77261a15b9d2.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/4198/live/01c15600-9ef1-11f0-92db-77261a15b9d2.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/4198/live/01c15600-9ef1-11f0-92db-77261a15b9d2.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/4198/live/01c15600-9ef1-11f0-92db-77261a15b9d2.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Getty Images A stock photo shows a woman pouring a big bottle of sunflower oil into a deep wok pan on an electric hob with cooking ingredients all around her and her kitchen cabinets and oven in the background." class="sc-5340b511-0 bGQwLJ"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 lha-dta"&gt;Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 etSgSK"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 jFVvLh"&gt;Use sunflower or vegetable oil if you're deep frying food &lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Oils behave differently when heated which makes some of them unsuitable for frying.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Extra virgin olive oil, for example, is packed with antioxidants and beneficial compounds but its low smoke point means it is better for salad dressings or drizzling over food rather than deep frying.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;A smoke point is the point at which the fats in the oil start to break down and nasty compounds are released which can make the oil taste bitter, burnt or unpleasant. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Restaurateur Tim Hayward says for shallow frying he uses a basic olive oil.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;But for deep frying something like chips or battered fish, vegetable or sunflower oil is best as they withstand higher temperatures without breaking down. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Some studies have also shown that oils heated to above their smoke point release toxic chemical by-products. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;But Professor Forouhi says that type of cooking in the home is not very common and that long-term health studies still show that vegetable oils "without exception are related with better outcomes for chronic diseases."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 bPbmDW"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 fsBZby"&gt;Which oils should I be using? &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;If you're looking for a simple kitchen strategy:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class="sc-6f869981-0 bYhyhr"&gt;&lt;li class="sc-734a601e-0 NnDUj"&gt;For everyday cooking: Sunflower or rapeseed oil are affordable, healthy, and versatile. You could also use a basic olive oil&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul class="sc-6f869981-0 bYhyhr"&gt;&lt;li class="sc-734a601e-0 NnDUj"&gt;For salads and finishing dishes: Extra virgin olive oil adds flavour and health benefits&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul class="sc-6f869981-0 bYhyhr"&gt;&lt;li class="sc-734a601e-0 NnDUj"&gt;For deep frying: Stick with a high smoke point oil like vegetable or sunflower&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul class="sc-6f869981-0 bYhyhr"&gt;&lt;li class="sc-734a601e-0 NnDUj"&gt;For flavour variety: While they may not have the same health benefits as olive oil, you could use sesame, coconut or avocado oils for cold dishes if you like the flavour&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Overall, Professor Forouhi says it is better to look at your whole diet rather than obsess over which bottle to buy. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"I would recommend going with what taste and cost considerations you have and experiment with different types of oil that will bring you some health benefits," she explains. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;&lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.bbc.co.uk/newsletters/zyxfdnb" class="sc-f9178328-0 jZoZnB"&gt;Sign up here&lt;/a&gt; to receive our weekly newsletter highlighting uplifting stories and remarkable people from around the world.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BBC</author><pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 23:06:27 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiWkFVX3lxTE5tVHI1Rmhkbzk3V0JYem5PM01rMVBBZnNsc2F2LXNNZ01jOVlkZ204Um9wZVBMYkhwUUlkczJzbU1pdUJ5U2lHWmZXSE52aXdLa0w0UnpQeWk2Zw</guid></item></channel></rss>