<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>GNews Health</title><link>https://news.google.com/</link><description></description><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>专家说，这19种日常习惯正在无声地破坏您的健康- BuzzFeed</title><link>https://www.buzzfeed.com/kristatorres/quiet-habits-that-wreck-health</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="subbuzz buzz-width--standard__subbuzz buzz-type--list__subbuzz subbuzz-text
  subbuzz-index-1
  
  
  
  
  " data-keywords="cleaning" data-module="subbuzz-text"&gt;
  
  &lt;p id="139816362" class="subbuzz-anchor"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;h2 class="subbuzz__header subbuzz__header--standard subbuzz__title  "&gt;
    
      &lt;span class="subbuzz__number"&gt;1.&lt;/span&gt;
    

    
      &lt;span class="js-subbuzz__title-text"&gt;"Having an 'all or nothing' mentality when it comes to habits. Five minutes of exercise is always better than 0, one serving of fruits or vegetables is better than 0, etc. It doesn’t have to be big to be impactful."&lt;/span&gt;
    
  &lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;—&lt;a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/Unhappy-Ad9177/" target="_blank"&gt;u/Unhappy-Ad9177&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"My favorite take on this perspective: Anything worth doing is worth half assing. Trying and failing at something, doing the bare minimum, or getting less done than you wanted to will almost never leave you in a worse position than if you didn't do it at all.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For the sake of clarity, this does not apply to anything where half assing it will likely injure yourself or someone else. Don't half ass electrical work, good lifting form, raising children, or hostage negotiations."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;—&lt;a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/SKIKS/" target="_blank"&gt;u/SKIKS&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I tell people this all the time. A half-clean room is better than not cleaning. A halfway maintained diet is better than no diet. Any improvement over what you're doing is better than none, and you have no one to impress but yourself."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;—&lt;a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/Nol3s4ever/" target="_blank"&gt;u/Nol3s4ever&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BuzzFeed</author><pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 02:16:04 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMid0FVX3lxTE1ubWstT2ZrMkc3bWdXVGJRSC1jRzl5RFI5T2s2ZDBzRWVULWluaGloQlN1NkprdG9OenRmS1Z0V2xPOHoxbDRiSW53NG9JM2Fydzg4bG1NeVJHMWh5Q1daVVFUblVlZW5RbXZOWEdJUWhHNTdSMEhB</guid></item><item><title>NICOLE LYNN ALLENBAUGH的讣告- Jamieson和Yannucci殡仪馆</title><link>https://www.jamiesonandyannucci.com/obituary/NICOLE-ALLENBAUGH</link><description>&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;
&lt;center&gt;&lt;h1&gt;403 Forbidden&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;/center&gt;
&lt;/body&gt;
</description><author>Jamieson &amp; Yannucci Funeral Home</author><pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 01:55:25 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMib0FVX3lxTE82WFVpMU5DZDVIRl9JN3hmMVd2TzZIc2oteEtTbWx1V0YyeGRlaFFFZ3Z2Y0lBM0E0dHdkTWhaMzhvQ253UEVyZF9mLVZrZ2xVSllWbmI1QlpGSy10aG1vZ29mLVVOX2MyeE9RRUpBdw</guid></item><item><title>专家们恳求人们在2025年摆脱这14种“健康”趋势- BuzzFeed</title><link>https://www.buzzfeed.com/ashleybroadwater1/unhealthy-health-trends-2025</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="subbuzz buzz-width--standard__subbuzz buzz-type--long__subbuzz subbuzz-text
  subbuzz-index-19
  
  
  
  
  " data-keywords="fast fashion" data-module="subbuzz-text"&gt;
  
  &lt;p id="139815927" class="subbuzz-anchor"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Apple watches, Garmin watches, Fitbit watches, the Strava app … there are endless ways to track miles walked, calories burned, and steps taken. Not only that, but there’s been a big push to track those measures every time — and it may be hurting your health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The obsession with self-tracking of health metrics with wearables can increase anxiety and cause you to ignore what your body is telling you,” said &lt;a href="https://baptisthealth.net/doctors/michael-swartzon/869766" target="_blank" data-skimlinks-tracking="7994495" data-affiliate="true"&gt;Dr. Michael Swartzon&lt;/a&gt;, a sports medicine physician at Baptist Health Orthopedic Care. “The raw data can lead to emotional stress when your body is just going through normal biological variations, probably the opposite of your goal.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For &lt;a href="https://freespira.com/leadership_team/robert-cuyler-ph-d/" target="_blank" data-skimlinks-tracking="7994495" data-affiliate="true"&gt;Robert Cuyler&lt;/a&gt;, a behavioral health expert, whether health tracking is “healthy” is about when and how much you do it. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The availability of tech-mediated health data is interesting and useful for those who use these tools (smartwatches, rings, etc.) in moderation and for specific purposes, with some guidance by evidence,” he said. “However, health tracking ... can become excessive, fueling bodily hypervigilance and anxiety.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Instead, Swartzon encouraged people to focus on the basics: fitting some physical exercise into their day, eating a wide variety of foods, maintaining a regular sleep schedule and listening to their body. All that other data isn’t necessary.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BuzzFeed</author><pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 01:16:02 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMie0FVX3lxTFBoQkRsaFhlcmVpcXQ1b1MwWndRRDBXZmhrZFplUWhOcXJkdlA0VEhWME9oakljTVZjbEhvRE1EMjdVTEw4VHBZbGRzWEdDS3oyM3JtNlB4aUYzanpfODVHcThIZHd0ZlVxemloeWVMWl95UmNkNDVXTERFNA</guid></item><item><title>9岁的女孩，在从流感中恢复期间接受了罕见的诊断。现在，她的妈妈警告父母“可怕”的并发症-雅虎英国新闻</title><link>https://uk.news.yahoo.com/girl-9-receives-rare-diagnosis-011116089.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="" data-article-body="true"&gt;&lt;h3 class="mb-4 text-lg font-bold"&gt;NEED TO KNOW&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul class="mb-4"&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;A 9-year-old Michigan girl received a rare diagnosis while recovering from the flu&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Now, her mom is warning other parents about the "scary and very unexpected complication"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“This completely caught me off guard," the mom said of her daughter's diagnosis&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;A Michigan mom thought her daughter was "turning a corner" amid her bout with the flu — but then she was suddenly unable to walk, leading to a rare diagnosis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Ashley Geuther’s 9-year-old daughter, Tori, became ill with the flu and at first experienced symptoms typical of the virus, including a high fever, chills and fatigue, per &lt;a href="https://www.newsweek.com/girl-symptom-after-flu-shock-diagnosis-11150191" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Newsweek;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;&lt;em&gt;Newsweek&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. Ashley, 35, told the outlet she made sure Tori got plenty of rest and continued to monitor her.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;When Tori's fever broke after a few days, Ashley believed she was on the mend. "Then suddenly, she started complaining of intense pain in both legs," the mom recalled.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The pain began in Tori's thighs before moving down to her calves. As she was still recovering from the flu, Ashley assumed the leg pain was "just normal soreness" from the virus.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="relative mb-4"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="relative text-sm mt-1 pr-2.5"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;getty&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; Mother taking a child's temperature (stock image)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;But soon, the pain became so intense that Tori complained of being unable to stand, saying "her legs felt too weak to support her," Ashley told &lt;em&gt;Newsweek&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;She took Tori to a walk-in clinic, but doctors “didn’t seem concerned" and advised Ashley to take her daughter home and allow her to continue to rest and drink plenty of fluids.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The next morning, however, Tori attempted to get out of bed and "took one step and dropped straight to the ground because the pain was so unbearable when she put pressure on her feet," her mom said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;"That was the moment I knew this was something serious,” Ashley recalled.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="relative mb-4"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="relative text-sm mt-1 pr-2.5"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;getty&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; Child in hospital (stock image)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Ashley took Tori to the emergency room, where she underwent testing, including bloodwork and a urinalysis. Tori was then diagnosed with benign acute childhood myositis (BACM), a rare disease that is "characterized by localized muscular pain (especially in the calves) that typically follows a viral upper respiratory tract infection," according to the &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC12454055/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:National Institutes of Health;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;National Institutes of Health&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;"The illness typically lasts for a brief period of time, usually up to 1 week," the &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC6250949/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:NIH;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;NIH&lt;/a&gt; said, noting, "Since many clinicians are unfamiliar with BACM, it is often misdiagnosed and interpreted as a more severe and complex disease."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;In Tori's case, the 9-year-old fully recovered — and was able to walk normally again — after a week in the hospital, where she was closely monitored and administered IV fluids and pain medication.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;But her mom told &lt;em&gt;Newsweek&lt;/em&gt; that her daughter's BACM diagnosis came as a shock.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“This completely caught me off guard," she said. "I had never even heard of this kind of complication from the flu before. It was scary and very unexpected.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Now, Ashley is warning other parents about the rare complication. In a now-viral &lt;a href="https://www.tiktok.com/@ashleygeuther/video/7556258488939253047" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:video;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;video&lt;/a&gt; posted on her TikTok account, she shared a clip of Tori walking on her toes around her hospital room while holding onto a wheeled cart.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;"As flu season begins, please remember to listen to your kids and watch closely for complications," she wrote in the caption.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Never miss a story — sign up for&lt;a href="https://people.com/people-news-daily-newsletter-sign-up-8692701" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:PEOPLE's free daily newsletter;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt; PEOPLE's free daily newsletter&lt;/a&gt; to stay up-to-date on the best of what PEOPLE has to offer​​, from celebrity news to compelling human interest stories.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Ashley then detailed what led to Tori's diagnosis and hospital stay, before concluding: "Thankfully, after a week, she made a full recovery and was able to walk again. I'm sharing our story so other parents can know what to watch for."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Speaking with &lt;em&gt;Newsweek&lt;/em&gt;, Ashley added, “Listen to your kids when they say something hurts, even if it seems unusual. Trust your gut — you know your child better than anyone."&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Read the original article on &lt;a href="https://people.com/girl-9-receives-rare-diagnosis-after-being-sick-with-the-flu-11863834" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:People;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;People&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Yahoo News UK</author><pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 01:11:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMie0FVX3lxTE1LNWdhRFA4ZUI2OTlHSlgwaWRIRGRiWnhGTUlDeThTS28tZFRrdjQtQkhiRHc3clRObWpLSm44SE5xWFRQRDIwWEp3RWgwMnhDdExWbXV4c1U1b1ZPOG95UWxoNG1QZVM3dDJrU0xpZTAyRURjNWtuWWJKbw</guid></item><item><title>带通拉曼光谱如何让您在不刺痛手指的情况下监测血糖-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/how-band-pass-raman-spectroscopy-lets-you-monitor-blood-sugar-without-pricking-your-finger/articleshow/125820063.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you regularly monitor your blood sugar, you are likely familiar with the repeated discomfort and inconvenience of finger-prick tests. These traditional methods, although widely used, can cause minor pain, skin irritation, or bruising, and their frequency can reduce adherence. Advances in optical sensing technologies are now offering alternatives that allow you to monitor glucose continuously without breaking the skin. One particularly promising technique is band-pass Raman spectroscopy, which captures the unique vibrational signatures of glucose molecules in the skin and underlying tissue. By translating these molecular fingerprints into continuous readings, this approach could improve accuracy, reduce discomfort, and offer detailed insights into daily glucose fluctuations, allowing you to manage your health more precisely. The method also has the potential to integrate into compact, wearable devices, offering convenience while maintaining clinical reliability and patient safety.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="6"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="7"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;How band-pass Raman spectroscopy detects glucose in your body&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="8"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Band-pass Raman spectroscopy relies on the interaction of light with molecules to identify glucose in the skin and tissue. When a focused laser beam illuminates the skin, most photons scatter without change, but a small fraction interacts with molecules, causing a shift in energy that produces a Raman spectrum. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Each type of molecule has a distinctive spectral signature, and glucose produces identifiable peaks that can be isolated from signals of proteins, lipids, and other biomolecules. Band-pass optical filters allow the device to focus on the spectral range where glucose signals are strongest, reducing background interference. These signals are then analysed by advanced computational algorithms, which convert the spectral information into glucose concentrations continuously. Because the technique is non-invasive, it allows repeated measurements without puncturing the skin, providing consistent monitoring throughout the day. The approach also lends itself to compact, portable designs, making it suitable for wearable devices that integrate seamlessly into your lifestyle while providing clinically relevant data.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="15"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="lOvcW vdo_embedd"&gt;&lt;div class="k7lcu"&gt;&lt;p class="efT4r"&gt;Diabetes Management Made Simple: 5 Yoga Asanas That Work&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="17"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="18"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;What research says about painless, continuous glucose tracking&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="19"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;A &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://pubs.acs.org/doi/10.1021/acs.analchem.5c01146" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;study published in Analytical Chemistry&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; explores the feasibility of using band-pass Raman spectroscopy for continuous glucose monitoring with a compact, point-of-care device. Researchers demonstrated that the system could reliably detect glucose concentrations with accuracy comparable to standard finger-prick methods. The study highlighted the importance of device calibration, signal processing, and precise optical alignment to ensure reliable readings. The compact design was particularly suitable for use both in clinical settings and in home environments, enabling continuous monitoring without the discomfort of repeated blood sampling. Findings indicated that non-invasive monitoring could reduce both the physical and psychological burden of conventional methods while providing a more comprehensive understanding of glucose dynamics. Continuous monitoring allows identification of trends that might otherwise be missed with intermittent sampling, enabling timely interventions and potentially improving long-term health outcomes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="28"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="29"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;The benefits of tracking blood sugar without needles&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="30"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Non-invasive glucose monitoring offers clear advantages compared with traditional sampling. Eliminating repeated skin punctures reduces pain, bruising, and the risk of infection. Continuous data provide a dynamic view of glucose fluctuations, allowing you to respond quickly to rising or falling levels. Integration with wearable devices enables real-time data transmission to smartphones or healthcare providers, supporting remote monitoring and personalised care. Because measurements are automated, the method reduces errors associated with sample handling, timing, or technique, improving overall reliability. The approach also allows for long-term tracking, giving both patients and clinicians a richer dataset for informed decision-making regarding diet, medication, and lifestyle adjustments.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="37"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Key advantages include:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="39"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="40"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="41"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="42"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Removal of finger-prick testing and associated discomfort or skin irritation&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Real-time continuous monitoring of glucose fluctuations throughout the day&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Reduced risk of skin infections or minor injuries&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Integration with wearable technology for remote data collection and monitoring&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Improved adherence due to convenience and ease of use&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Reduced errors from manual sampling and handling&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Potential for automated alerts and personalised intervention strategies&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Enhanced long-term tracking for more informed healthcare decisions&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="43"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="44"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;What challenges still stands in the way of needle-free glucose monitoring&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="45"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Despite its promise, band-pass Raman spectroscopy faces several challenges before it can be widely implemented. Variations in skin pigmentation, tissue composition, and ambient environmental conditions can affect the Raman signal, necessitating careful calibration for each individual user. Signal processing must effectively separate glucose peaks from background noise, requiring sophisticated algorithms and extensive validation. Device design also needs to balance compactness, comfort, battery life, and reliable wireless connectivity for continuous wear. Researchers are exploring hybrid systems that combine Raman spectroscopy with complementary sensing methods to improve accuracy and robustness. Ensuring consistent performance across different environments and user conditions remains a critical step. Overcoming these challenges is essential to translating laboratory prototypes into practical, everyday tools suitable for clinical use and long-term patient monitoring.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="50"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Main challenges include:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="52"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="53"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="54"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="55"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Variability in skin tone, tissue composition, and optical properties&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Interference from ambient light, background fluorescence, or environmental factors&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Requirement for individual calibration to maintain accurate readings&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Complex signal processing to isolate glucose signals reliably&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Device ergonomics and comfort for continuous wear&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ensuring consistent performance across different conditions&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Integration with secure wireless transmission and long-lasting battery solutions&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Development of hybrid systems to improve accuracy and robustness&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="56"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="em" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Disclaimer: This article is for general informational purposes only and is not a substitute for professional medical advice, diagnosis, or treatment. Always seek the guidance of a qualified healthcare provider regarding any medical condition or lifestyle change.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="58"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="59"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="60"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Also Read | &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/can-spending-more-time-in-the-sun-extend-your-life-know-what-researchers-found/articleshow/125819111.cms" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;Can spending more time in the sun extend your life; know what researchers found&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 23:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimgJBVV95cUxNVk9kWXBjQXEyS0kwT3FRemxQSTVTcWdnYUVvbUUzaG1jbkx1Zkx2SGhRQmVMNFBUNy1ONXlEZmxxTWNrM1FzYndRb25GNzZhUTEtWVk5VUI5b0FxRnRqMmpQN2JxUDZSTFlqbnVoTXlWenNnWW5QdWhBTTdEaU5VNlF5TUlrUTZHYV9iOFNuSkk0OGNYckhCZTRaUzZ0dWRIeFZUdGt3cTltQkhuSWN6TnZtaGVPWXZwdGliVWVxbXpLZFFlRi1fRTZHcDFhZzl5MTh2WGwtUGk4d244dVFRYTlwM1FCVFB0T1dhazl4SU9YOEpWeVU4eDZnSkhwUjZkeDU5TmVuU3EzU2ZuVHI0cjBPTWVGUl9HSlE</guid></item><item><title>在新墨西哥州徒步郊狼和狂犬病- KOB.com</title><link>https://www.kob.com/news/top-news/hiker-bit-by-coyote-with-rabies-in-new-mexico/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="storyContent"&gt;
								
								&lt;p&gt;SANTA FE, N.M. — A hiker in the Gila National Forest was bitten by a coyote that tested positive for rabies, according to the New Mexico Department of Health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The hiker didn’t require hospitalization. However, they are receiving “routine treatment” to prevent a rabies infection.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;NMDOH conducted testing that confirmed the diagnosis. They stated they have seen three other cases of rabid animals in southwest New Mexico this year — a bobcat in Sierra County, a coyote in Catron County and a dog in Grant Country. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Rabies is preventable, but only if we take it seriously,” said Dr. Erin Phipps, state public health veterinarian for NMDOH. “The best way to protect your family — including your pets — is to make sure your animals are vaccinated.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;NMDOH recommends the following to stay safe from rabies: &lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class="wp-block-list"&gt;&lt;li&gt;Keep your pets up to date on vaccinations and ensure they wear current license tags.  &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;If your cat or dog has been bitten or scratched by a wild animal, call your veterinarian for a rabies booster, even if the wound is superficial.    &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;If an animal bites you, wash the area immediately and thoroughly with soap and water and seek medical attention promptly.     &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Vaccinate horses and other household pets, even if they remain exclusively on your property. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Report any exposure or bite to your local animal control and call the NMDOH Helpline at 1-833-SWNURSE (1-833 796-8773).&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
								&lt;nav aria-label="breadcrumb"&gt;&lt;ol class="breadcrumb"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;For Related Stories:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.kob.com/tag/new-mexico-department-of-health/" rel="tag"&gt;New Mexico Department of Health&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;/nav&gt;
								
										&lt;p id="spm-container"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

										
								
        
        &lt;p id="rc-widget-d60515" data-rc-widget data-widget-host="habitat" data-endpoint="//trends.revcontent.com" data-widget-id="248039"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        
        								
							&lt;/div&gt;

						&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>KOB.com</author><pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 22:51:38 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihwFBVV95cUxNUFJtN3pjVnM5Y2Jtd3poTFhCaXk3MjcxWUVjUFBNR2M4VnBEQzd6b1ZrR1gzXzFLV1dMTkRqVEtmNzRyeE9HUDQxR0lLYUpEVzloQzBXY3MtWXl6NTE2bHBrRzVGUlJsYlBHQmNxN0NUaWcyWDlDc2FNMGxrdDIyX3U2ZVo4dlk</guid></item><item><title>减肥吸毒者被告知要减肥或冒着老化10年的风险-泰晤士报</title><link>https://www.thetimes.com/uk/healthcare/article/weight-loss-drug-users-told-to-do-weights-or-risk-aging-10-years-8klcb50s8</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div data-testid="article-content-body" class="responsive__ArticleContent-sc-15gvuj2-8 kuowVf"&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;People taking weight-loss drugs have been urged to do strength training to stave off potential muscle wasting equivalent to “ten years of ageing.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;Research shows that people taking the new range of weight-loss treatments such as Mounjaro and Wegovy can lose significant amounts of lean muscle alongside fat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;The resulting reduction in strength can be especially significant for older people, putting them at risk of frailty and falls. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;• &lt;a href="https://www.thetimes.com/culture/film/article/kate-winslet-interview-avatar-goodbye-june-parents-5jhpc26wm" class="link__RespLink-sc-1ocvixa-0 csWvlP"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Kate Winslet: ‘Young women have no concept of what being beautiful is’&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;Fitness experts said that more needed to be done to back up advice that those taking the medications do so alongside exercises designed to maintain their strength.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;With an estimated 2.5 million people in the UK on the drugs, Dr Matthew Wade, a researcher&lt;span class="paywall-EAB47CFD"&gt; at UKActive, a fitness non-profit that represents UK gyms, said that doctors should be clear that patients will benefit from boosting muscle mass.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="paywall-EAB47CFD"&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;“The rapid rollout of GLP-1 has shown dramatic results for patients but in order to avoid weakening the body, there are simple and effective strength exercises which are essential for sustainable results,” Wade said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;“The health and fitness sector can support people taking weight loss medications, but we want to see the government go further by working with the fitness, nutrition and pharmaceutical industries to deliver the critical wraparound support patients need.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;An evidence &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/38687506/" class="link__RespLink-sc-1ocvixa-0 csWvlP"&gt;review&lt;/a&gt; published last year found that use of the drugs caused a “rapid and significant loss of lean mass,” averaging about 6kg per person — more than might be expected in a decade. The study also highlighted that this can potentially be avoided with resistance training.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;This tallies with official NHS advice. The National Institute for Health and Care Excellence advises that those using the drugs must not receive them as standalone treatments, and instead take them alongside fitness and dietary interventions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;• &lt;a href="https://www.thetimes.com/uk/healthcare/article/the-children-taking-wegovy-to-turn-their-lives-around-gdvb5h9fp" class="link__RespLink-sc-1ocvixa-0 csWvlP"&gt;&lt;b&gt;The children taking Wegovy to turn their lives around&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;A report by &lt;a href="https://www.ukactive.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/GLP-1-medications-and-muscle-mass-preservation.-Implications-and-recommendations.pdf" class="link__RespLink-sc-1ocvixa-0 csWvlP"&gt;UKActive&lt;/a&gt; called for gyms to work with the government to tailor programs to those taking the medications, known as GLP-1 agonists.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;Bryce Hastings, head of research at Les Mills, a fitness company that worked on the report, said that exercise also helped to lessen weight gain once people stopped taking the drugs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="last-paragraph" class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;“More research is needed to deeper understand the relationship between weight loss medications and strength training, but the evidence and recommendations in our report are the start of the journey and offer practical next steps to better support the growing number of people taking weight loss medication,” he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p id="paywall-portal-article-footer"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Times</author><pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 21:45:41 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMivgFBVV95cUxOTlBTQS0wY3FmN2o4d0c1YmVPTENDb01LSGt1QUQycjhkNlVQb0VYTm5lbWJNTmRIZTVLcDl2SngtNWZwcFZ0ZG42azJGUWZjdlVtZnBvOTE3SUlLUnVGNy1RWVBSNWR2Q0dWVXpnVmpIMDhOMU5iNFdNai1TM3o0TnpMSDJ4bWJHdzRVUEN5eFVtMUhjcGVTRGNETEMxcmxrdE9pa1hTMGFyWElEek1KRVpPUTB2LVJJVGIzQThn</guid></item><item><title>你真的可以通过“一个奇怪的把戏”来获得更健康的面包消费吗？ - Boing Boing</title><link>https://boingboing.net/2025/12/07/can-you-really-one-weird-trick-your-way-to-healthier-bread-consumption.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Boing Boing</author><pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 19:31:58 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMirgFBVV95cUxOY1EtNVpsOXVzaHlyS3JST2JUTDJjdHhZWnNSZzFxb01YWDBzS2oyM2tBMFpITGJieXV6cld0Zjd6SDM1WGF2Qm1QaUJWM1I2RUk3a1RwVnNLZjJXcEVMVzJLRHRaNWtQRjJheHY1Ym9PZFVxUTRlcWpQZ2hUSEdQRHQyN2xDSlA5cDlXUzZoWXJ2ZEpzVlpQaGNiXzNBQjNibzJrNGI2bS03SDMxd2fSAbMBQVVfeXFMTnY1MFJDdWI2dHFJcW5NUHA3YW1GNE1yRVlNY2ZUVFR2c2F2aE9ja3dqUFVSalJxS1o4Z195bkwxY1J5LTY2eFlCRFBLRjl5dG1rVkk3U2ZYU0RHNlliTk0zdHB4LWVZQlpjcDE1QWlhcFZfVFJCQVBUejVuLUowbGhNRU44d1ZRbDlmS0tfV2FWSFB2YURxdHU0dzI2TEZNTFJTMnJmT2tIVnR0SmQzWm1qMjA</guid></item><item><title>新研究将青少年认知脱离综合征与多动症区分开来- PsyPost</title><link>https://www.psypost.org/new-research-differentiates-cognitive-disengagement-syndrome-from-adhd-in-youth/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="content-inner "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Recent investigations into child psychology have provided evidence that a specific cluster of behavioral symptoms is separate and distinct from attention-deficit/hyperactivity disorder. The research indicates that this condition, known as cognitive disengagement syndrome, presents a unique set of challenges that shift as children mature into adolescents. These findings were published in the &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1177/10870547251344719" target="_blank"&gt;Journal of Attention Disorders&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cognitive disengagement syndrome is a condition characterized by a specific pattern of mental functioning. Individuals with this syndrome often exhibit excessive daydreaming, frequent mental confusion, and a general slowing of thinking or behavior. These behaviors were historically described as “sluggish cognitive tempo” in older medical literature.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Psychologists and researchers have debated how to best categorize these symptoms for years. The primary question has been whether these behaviors represent a subset of attention-deficit/hyperactivity disorder or if they constitute a standalone clinical syndrome. Clarifying this distinction is necessary for ensuring that children receive accurate diagnoses and appropriate support.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Past research has largely focused on validating the list of fifteen symptoms associated with cognitive disengagement syndrome. Studies conducted in countries such as Brazil, South Korea, and the United States have supported the idea that these symptoms are structurally different from the inattention associated with attention deficits. Structural validity indicates that the symptoms group together reliably and are mathematically distinct from other attention problems.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers behind the current study aimed to take this understanding a step further by examining clinical categories. They sought to determine if they could identify groups of youth who met the criteria for cognitive disengagement syndrome but did not meet the criteria for attention-deficit/hyperactivity disorder. They also investigated whether the emotional and social difficulties associated with these conditions change between childhood and adolescence.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study was conducted by a team of international experts in child psychopathology. G. Leonard Burns of Washington State University and Stephen P. Becker of Cincinnati Children’s Hospital Medical Center led the investigation. They collaborated with Juan José Montaño, Belén Sáez, and Mateu Servera from the University of the Balearic Islands in Spain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The investigators utilized a nationally representative sample of families residing in Spain to gather their data. They recruited participants through an online platform to ensure a broad demographic reach across the country’s various regions. The final sample consisted of parents reporting on 5,525 children and adolescents.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study participants ranged in age from 5 to 16 years. To analyze developmental differences, the researchers divided the youth into a childhood group (ages 5 to 10) and an adolescence group (ages 11 to 16). Parents completed the Child and Adolescent Behavior Inventory to rate the frequency of specific behaviors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This inventory assessed symptoms related to cognitive disengagement, inattention, and hyperactivity-impulsivity. It also measured functional impairments such as academic struggles, social difficulties, and sleep problems. The researchers used statistical thresholds to create specific clinical groups based on the parents’ ratings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They identified children who scored in the clinical range for cognitive disengagement syndrome only. They also identified those who scored in the clinical range for attention-deficit/hyperactivity disorder only. The latter group was further broken down into three presentations: predominantly inattentive, predominantly hyperactive-impulsive, and combined.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The first major finding concerned the independence of the two conditions. The data showed that a distinct group of youth exhibited high levels of cognitive disengagement without significant symptoms of attention-deficit/hyperactivity disorder. This independence was observed in both the childhood and adolescent age groups.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers found that approximately 2.5 percent of children and 1.5 percent of adolescents in the general population fit the “cognitive disengagement syndrome only” profile. This confirms that the syndrome can exist as a solo clinical entity. However, the study also provided detailed statistics on how often the conditions overlap.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the childhood group, about half of the youth with cognitive disengagement syndrome did not qualify for a diagnosis of attention-deficit/hyperactivity disorder. This rate of independence decreased slightly as the children got older. In the adolescent group, roughly one-third of those with cognitive disengagement syndrome did not have a co-occurring attention disorder.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study then examined how these groups differed in terms of emotional and behavioral problems. In the childhood group, those with cognitive disengagement syndrome displayed a significantly higher risk for internalizing disorders. They scored higher on measures of anxiety and depression compared to children with attention-deficit/hyperactivity disorder.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These children also exhibited higher rates of somatization. This refers to the expression of psychological distress through physical symptoms, such as headaches or stomachaches. This tendency toward physical complaints was more pronounced in the cognitive disengagement group than in any of the attention-deficit groups.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The pattern of findings shifted noticeably when the researchers analyzed the adolescent group. The gap in anxiety and depression scores between the conditions largely disappeared. Adolescents with attention-deficit/hyperactivity disorder reported levels of anxiety and depression that were similar to those with cognitive disengagement syndrome.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This convergence suggests different developmental pathways for these disorders. It is possible that depression in cognitive disengagement syndrome is a consistent feature that begins early. Conversely, depression in attention-deficit/hyperactivity disorder may develop later as a reaction to years of academic and social struggles.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sleep difficulties emerged as a strong and consistent differentiator between the groups. Across both childhood and adolescence, youth with cognitive disengagement syndrome experienced more daytime sleep-related impairment. They were more likely to appear drowsy, lethargic, or tired during the day than their peers with attention deficits.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nighttime sleep disturbances were also more common in the cognitive disengagement group. This includes trouble falling asleep or staying asleep. While this difference was clear in childhood, the distinction became less consistent in adolescence regarding comparisons with the hyperactive-impulsive group.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers also assessed social functioning, which revealed nuanced differences. In childhood, the cognitive disengagement group showed higher levels of social withdrawal. These children were more likely to isolate themselves from peer interactions compared to those with attention deficits.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, peer rejection presented a different dynamic. Children with the hyperactive-impulsive presentation of attention-deficit/hyperactivity disorder often experience active rejection by peers. The study found that while cognitive disengagement children withdraw, they do not necessarily face the same level of active rejection as hyperactive children.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;By adolescence, the differences in social impairment leveled off. The cognitive disengagement group and the attention-deficit groups showed similar levels of social difficulties. This indicates that while the specific nature of the social problems might differ, the overall impact on social life becomes comparable in the teenage years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Academic impairment provided one of the clearest distinctions between the conditions. In the adolescent sample, the attention-deficit groups showed significantly greater academic struggles. The combined presentation of attention-deficit/hyperactivity disorder was associated with the highest levels of school-related difficulty.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Adolescents with cognitive disengagement syndrome fared better academically than those with attention deficits. This suggests that the symptoms of daydreaming and mental confusion may be less detrimental to school grades than the symptoms of inattention and impulsivity. This finding aligns with previous research suggesting different functional outcomes for the two conditions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study also looked at oppositional defiant disorder, which involves a pattern of angry or argumentative behavior. In the adolescent group, those with attention-deficit/hyperactivity disorder showed significantly higher levels of oppositional behavior. The cognitive disengagement group had lower rates of these disruptive behaviors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This suggests that externalizing behaviors, such as defiance and aggression, are not central features of cognitive disengagement syndrome. The syndrome appears to be more closely improved with internal distress and withdrawal. Attention-deficit/hyperactivity disorder, particularly the combined and hyperactive types, is more strongly linked to outward behavioral conflict.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers noted several limitations to their study that context is required to interpret the results. The data relied solely on ratings provided by mothers and fathers. The study did not include information from teachers, who often see different behaviors in the classroom setting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Additionally, the study did not include self-reports from the adolescents themselves. Teenagers often have unique insights into their own internal emotional states, particularly regarding anxiety and depression. Future research would benefit from incorporating multiple perspectives to build a more complete picture.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study design was cross-sectional rather than longitudinal. This means the researchers looked at different children at different ages at a single point in time. They did not track the same individual children as they grew from age 5 to age 16.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Because of this design, the suggestions regarding developmental pathways are hypotheses rather than confirmed timelines. Longitudinal research is needed to verify whether children with attention deficits actually develop depression later in life as a result of their struggles. Tracking individuals over time would clarify the cause-and-effect relationships suggested by this data.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The authors also emphasized the need to replicate these findings in other cultural contexts. While this study confirms findings from the United States using a Spanish sample, further global research is necessary. Differences in school systems and cultural expectations could influence how these symptoms present and impact functioning.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Despite these caveats, the study provides strong evidence for the validity of cognitive disengagement syndrome. It reinforces the idea that clinicians should assess for these symptoms separately from attention deficits. Recognizing the unique profile of this syndrome could lead to more targeted and effective interventions for struggling youth.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study, “&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1177/10870547251344719" target="_blank"&gt;Cognitive Disengagement Syndrome is Clinically Distinct from ADHD Presentations within Childhood and Adolescence&lt;/a&gt;,” was authored by G. Leonard Burns, Stephen P. Becker, Juan José Montaño, Belén Sáez, and Mateu Servera.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>PsyPost</author><pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 19:07:09 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipwFBVV95cUxNVnlRNHdZUEl2Mk1oYkR2VDZvRTNDb01HTTkzLVNXbG1LeFlJNzBnamFNMGNucUhGNVF6aEJFdFJVYS11dHk4bXNVcm1BUmZKVGsxazRpMlNYMktKejRtS3pTcWN4WVJHei12b2lTSzlJcV9oQ0FRandpbjY1Mjd3ZUdZSm9Id0tMT3dybHowMGM0YUdtU0JZMnJGTzdXS3NETzVPRnpOaw</guid></item><item><title>这种日常咖啡习惯可能有助于减缓老化过程- SciTechDaily</title><link>https://scitechdaily.com/this-daily-coffee-habit-may-help-slow-the-aging-process/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>SciTechDaily</author><pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 19:06:19 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiAFBVV95cUxNMER1Ul9Sei10SUFpdkRyN3lkY3B2Y2dZZU5rZUsxNzE0dXNNbExSRjVQbFNWMGhfd3FKMDgwZUNqOVM2UF8wUHlWVGxlb2NVY081ZGZDMGc0S2J3VldRdWhDZE82RWVoTUJrMUs3aWFXc1F0SHBBYWR4Ry1DTUF0NXk3aWNNNTRs</guid></item><item><title>尖端技术捕捉人体心脏动脉内的图像，彻底改变医学科学- Earth.com</title><link>https://www.earth.com/news/cutting-edge-tech-captures-images-inside-human-heart-arteries-revolutionizing-medical-science/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="page_content__AwOj6"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Heart doctors are capturing images showing the inside of heart arteries, helping them watch plaque respond to powerful cholesterol drugs in real-time. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In these studies, PCSK9 inhibitors, drugs that block a cholesterol controlling protein, made plaques smaller and more stable within about one year of treatment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The pictures come from international trials that scanned the same artery segments in hundreds of patients before and after therapy. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Teams at major hospitals in Europe and North America combined their data to see how these drugs change arteries deep inside the body.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-huge-impact-of-artery-imaging"&gt;Huge impact of artery imaging&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;For many years, doctors tracked coronary &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/late-night-habits-raise-the-risk-of-coronary-artery-calcification/"&gt;atherosclerosis&lt;/a&gt;, a slow buildup of fatty plaque in heart &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/microplastics-linked-to-risk-of-stroke-and-heart-attack/"&gt;arteries&lt;/a&gt;, with angiograms that only outlined the vessel channel. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Those pictures showed where arteries narrowed but revealed almost nothing about the hidden material inside the vessel wall.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A recent &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/39150672/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;review&lt;/a&gt; pulled together studies that used invasive imaging to watch how PCSK9 based treatment changes coronary plaque in living patients. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The work was led by Massimiliano Ruscica, PharmD, PhD, at the &lt;a href="https://www.unimi.it/en" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;University of Milan&lt;/a&gt;, whose research centers on PCSK9, atherosclerosis, and lipid lowering therapies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-cholesterol-and-plaque"&gt;Cholesterol and plaque&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;For decades, treatment focused on lowering low density lipoprotein cholesterol, a blood fat that drives plaque growth, and counting &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/microplastics-linked-to-risk-of-stroke-and-heart-attack/"&gt;heart attacks&lt;/a&gt; and strokes. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Statins already reduced those events, yet many patients still had trouble even when their lab numbers looked fine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;PCSK9 inhibitors keep more LDL receptors active in the liver, so the body clears extra LDL particles from the bloodstream. As a result, they can push LDL cholesterol far below levels that most people reach with statins alone.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/28304224/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;FOURIER&lt;/a&gt; outcomes trial showed that adding evolocumab to statins dropped LDL to about 30 milligrams per deciliter and reduced major cardiovascular events in high risk patients. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That result raised a sharp question about whether the benefit came only from changing blood numbers or also from reshaping plaque inside the artery wall.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Answering that question meant looking directly at the plaques instead of guessing from cholesterol tests. New invasive imaging tools made it possible to watch plaque in the same artery segment change over time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-intravascular-cameras"&gt;Intravascular cameras&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;New tools such as intravascular ultrasound, a catheter based ultrasound that images artery walls from inside, let cardiologists measure plaque volume rather than just the open channel. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The same catheter run can be repeated months later, giving matching before and after pictures of the very same vessel segment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Light based optical coherence tomography, a high resolution imaging method using reflected light, can see the thin fibrous layer that covers the soft core of a plaque. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It can measure how thick that cap is, which matters because very thin caps are more likely to tear and release clot forming material.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Near-infrared spectroscopy (&lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/topics/food-science/near-infrared-spectroscopy" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;NIS&lt;/a&gt;) uses infrared light absorption patterns to map how much oily lipid sits inside plaque cores. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When combined with ultrasound or optical imaging, it helps identify plaques that are especially rich in lipid and therefore more dangerous.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Taken together, these invasive cameras give several complementary views of the same disease. One measures size, another shows structure, and a third highlights the chemical makeup inside the plaque.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-pcsk9-and-dangerous-plaques"&gt;PCSK9 and dangerous plaques&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/27846344/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;GLAGOV&lt;/a&gt; trial, nearly one thousand statin treated patients had coronary plaque measured from inside the artery using intravascular ultrasound. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Adding evolocumab produced a clear drop in the percentage of the artery wall filled with plaque, and more than half of the patients showed actual regression of plaque volume.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A later &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/35431172/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;study&lt;/a&gt; called HUYGENS used optical coherence tomography and ultrasound in patients who had a type of heart attack called non ST elevation myocardial infarction. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Evolocumab on top of statins made the protective cap thicker and reduced the arc of lipid inside plaques compared with placebo.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/35368058/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;PACMAN-AMI&lt;/a&gt; trial tested the PCSK9 blocker alirocumab in three hundred patients after an acute myocardial infarction, a sudden blockage of a heart artery that kills muscle. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Serial imaging showed that alirocumab plus high intensity statin therapy shrank plaque burden, reduced lipid rich core, and increased cap thickness in arteries that had not caused the original heart attack.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In people born with very high cholesterol, a condition called familial hypercholesterolemia, an inherited disorder that causes lifelong high LDL, the &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/37009731/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;ARCHITECT&lt;/a&gt; trial followed more than one hundred patients on alirocumab and strong statins. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Over roughly a year and a half, overall plaque burden in the coronary tree fell, and the unstable fibrofatty and necrotic core portion shrank while more stable fibrous and calcified tissue increased.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-why-the-plaque-changes-matter"&gt;Why the plaque changes matter&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cardiologists watch features such as a large lipid core, a very thin fibrous cap, a scar-like tissue layer over plaque, and high inflammation because they signal a plaque that can rupture. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These risky plaques may sit in &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/microplastics-linked-to-risk-of-stroke-and-heart-attack/"&gt;arteries&lt;/a&gt; that look only mildly narrowed on standard angiograms, yet they are often the ones that break and trigger clots.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Imaging trials now suggest that PCSK9 inhibitors shift plaques away from this high risk pattern toward a quieter, more stable state. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In these studies, plaques tended to become smaller, more fibrous, less packed with free cholesterol, and better covered by thicker caps that are less likely to split.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These shifts in plaque features match what doctors expect when LDL is driven very low for long periods. The imaging results link changes in &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/simple-blood-test-detects-cancer-before-symptoms-appear/"&gt;blood tests&lt;/a&gt; to physical changes in plaque, which makes the clinical benefits of intensive treatment easier to understand.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Because the imaging work follows the same patients over time, it connects LDL reductions with direct evidence of plaque healing in those arteries. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That picture helps explain why treating aggressively, sometimes within days after a heart attack, can change long term risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-lessons-from-artery-imaging"&gt;Lessons from artery imaging&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;These studies encourage a move from caring only about how narrow an artery looks to caring about what kind of plaque is present. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A modest narrowing made mostly of soft lipid with a thin cap can be more dangerous than a tighter narrowing built from tough fibrous and calcified tissue.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Researchers are testing whether noninvasive scans guided by plaque features, such as low density regions or changes in surrounding fat, can flag people who most need aggressive LDL lowering. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If that strategy proves reliable, doctors might one day tailor PCSK9 therapy not just to &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/just-one-handful-of-pecan-nuts-each-day-can-lower-cholesterol-heart-health/"&gt;cholesterol&lt;/a&gt; numbers, but also to the hidden biology of each patient’s plaque.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At the same time, PCSK9 inhibitors remain costly and are usually reserved for people at very high risk who do not reach LDL targets with other treatments. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Imaging could help make those decisions more precise by identifying patients whose plaque still looks dangerous despite apparently good standard therapy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ongoing trials are exploring how early and how intensively to use these drugs after a heart attack, and whether imaging endpoints should help steer future guidelines. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As more data emerge, artery cameras may play a growing role in showing when plaque has truly calmed and when more treatment is still needed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study is published in &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC11393034/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Current Atherosclerosis Reports&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;—–&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Like what you read? &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/subscribe/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Subscribe to our newsletter&lt;/a&gt; for engaging articles, exclusive content, and the latest updates.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Check us out on &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/earthsnap/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;EarthSnap&lt;/a&gt;, a free app brought to you by &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/author/eralls/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Eric Ralls&lt;/a&gt; and Earth.com.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;—–&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Earth.com</author><pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 19:06:01 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMivgFBVV95cUxNMTNMY3ExTnlBNFdiLWl6MTg0bXVXX0tzVWR5Ukk2YW51RHhFRWhOUndPaVE2c0FfcUs5WHZWc0RVbEZhQXBwVG45MWQzVEFZMmdBSkdGc0JfdlEtV3N1dE0zQ0lXTTF2VzJMWWJINDdkeG5nSXQ0V1A3VWdCQm9aMlJkR2F6R1BEVTVHd0ZzYi1DSFAxbFF0NVpMVDA5SkhUR004REo5elZnWFpqQ1VpNjRnaFRiVk1jUXZ3ZEFn</guid></item><item><title>“Scromiting”是一种与慢性大麻使用有关的奇怪疾病，正在上升- East Idaho News</title><link>https://www.eastidahonews.com/2025/12/scromiting-a-bizarre-condition-linked-to-chronic-marijuana-use-is-on-the-rise/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="articleText"&gt; &lt;p&gt;(CNN) — It was a pain worse than childbirth, said a TikTok mom as she described bouts of uncontrollable vomiting after marijuana use.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;“I was crying and screaming and I was like ‘I can’t take this anymore!’ I hate my life,” she said. “I’m just begging God, like please make it stop!”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Dubbed “scromiting” by social media due to the combination of screaming and loud vomiting, the medical name for the condition is cannabis hyperemesis syndrome, or CHS, which is on the rise in the United States. Habitual users of cannabis, including teenagers, are showing up in emergency rooms complaining of severe intestinal distress.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="mediumRec1Mobile" class="mobile-ad medium-rectangle centered"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;“They are writhing, holding their stomach, complaining of really bad abdominal pain and nausea,” said Dr. Sam Wang, a pediatric emergency medicine specialist and toxicologist at Children’s Hospital Colorado, who treats adolescents with the condition.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;“They vomit and then just continue to vomit whatever they have in their stomach, which can go on for hours,” Wang told CNN in a prior interview. “They often say they took a scalding hot shower before they came to the ER but it didn’t help.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="smallTile1Mobile" class="mobile-ad small-tile centered"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Immediate treatment consists of anti-nausea medications and IV fluids to combat dehydration from the vomiting. But patients also undergo a battery of tests to rule out other causes: blood and urine tests, expensive CT scans, unpleasant upper GI endoscopy and gastric emptying tests, to name a few.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;For some adolescents, those tests could be repeated again and again.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;“For some of our kids, this is their fifth ER visit in the past two months, with symptoms that they can’t control,” Wang said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="mediumRec2Mobile" class="mobile-ad medium-rectangle centered"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;And if they wait too long to come in, the condition can be life-threatening.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;“Regardless of whether it’s cannabis hyperemesis syndrome or another virus that makes you vomit a lot,” Wang said, “if you let it go too long, you can have electrolyte disturbances, go into shock and have organ failure. CHS is no different.”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A bizarre condition&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Cannabis hyperemesis syndrome burst upon the medical scene in 2004, when a group of Australian researchers wrote about 19 chronic marijuana users who had repeated episodes of abdominal pain and retching. The researchers followed nine of the patients over time and found symptoms went away when cannabis use was stopped but returned when it was restarted.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Oddly, over half of the 19 reported using extremely hot baths or showers to self-treat their symptoms. As more and more cases of CHS began to appear, hot bathing as a home treatment became a recurring theme.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;“It’s pretty universal for these patients to say they need a really, really hot shower, or a really hot bath, to improve their symptoms,” he said.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Why hot? “That’s not entirely clear,” said Wang, who is also an associate professor of pediatrics at the University of Colorado Anschutz Medical Campus in Aurora, Colorado.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Tetrahydrocannabinol, or THC, the main psychoactive compound in weed, has access to the body’s pain receptors, so one theory is that the distracting sensation of the extreme heat interrupts the pain cycle, thus easing symptoms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="mediumRec4Mobile" class="mobile-ad centered"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;To compound the strangeness of the disorder, THC and other cannabinoids in the marijuana plant have been used for pain relief — paradoxically relieving nausea and vomiting in cancer patients undergoing chemotherapy. However, despite the popularity of marijuana as a painkiller, study results on its effectiveness have been mixed.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Still, why would the same compound relieve and also cause pain? Among a myriad of possibilities: dosage levels. Wang points to the ever increasing potency of THC in today’s marijuana products.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;“It’s been well documented that the amount of THC that now comes in cannabis is increasing substantially,” Wang said. “In the ’90s the average was like 4% or 5%. Now in Colorado, it’s anywhere from 15% to 20%.”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Another mystery: Not all heavy users of weed are affected by CHS.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;“It’s not entirely clear who is predisposed to getting it,” Wang said. “Is it a certain frequency or duration of use? Is it a specific potency? Or is it a specific type of product? We don’t have that data.”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CHS is on the rise&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Data show CHS is a national problem. Between 2005 and 2014 when only medical marijuana was legal in most states, a 2020 study found nearly 1 in 5 people hospitalized for cyclical vomiting in the United States reported concurrent cannabis use.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;After Colorado legalized recreational marijuana in 2012, Wang and his colleagues found over 800,000 cases of reported vomiting due to cannabis in Colorado between 2013 and 2018. That’s about a 29% increase since legalization, Wang said. The study, published in September 2021, found the rate was highest in counties with no prior marijuana dispensaries.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;A newer study, published in July 2025, found emergency room visits for adolescents aged 13 to 21 years across the nation increased more than 10-fold between 2016 and 2023. Yet another November 2025 study found the rate of CHS among adults 18 to 35 rose sharply during the pandemic years of 2020 and 2021 and remained high.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;However, all of these studies have been limited by the lack of a medical diagnosis or insurance billing code to enable objective tracking of CHS. To do the studies, researchers had to compare medical records of vomiting with documented or self-reported cases of marijuana use — data that many people decline to provide.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;That’s changed. On October 1, 2025, a US federal committee created R11.16, an official medical diagnosis code for cannabis hyperemesis syndrome. The World Health Organization did the same, allowing researchers worldwide to better track the condition. Experts say future studies will be more accurate, allowing researchers to shed more light onto this unusual condition.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>East Idaho News</author><pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 18:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMitwFBVV95cUxNbzI4d2c2YUpQQnNtMzBGVUpfWlNVb0JHYXhYY2RTRXloM1FQcFBHMTBibTNuMFE0NE0zVU9PWVhHT1hPaDhKeGtKSFF2MWQ4VzRaa1p5aHNZTy1xWEZzTFJBTlBObFRUTDBDZlc4dUxQU2FwRmw0SHhjQy13djFCQXh4amR2TDBRMV9oSHBWenhiMEVjVGowSG43UHZrNkpHR0hPY3pVSndKTEhfQVFrMmRCZHVEc1E</guid></item><item><title>核辐射实际上对您的身体有什么影响？ - bgr.com</title><link>https://www.bgr.com/2040801/what-nuclear-radiation-does-body-explained/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="content" class="article"&gt;
            

            &lt;article class="news-post"&gt;
    
    
    
                &lt;p class="news-article"&gt;
                &lt;h1 class="title-gallery" data-post-id="2040801" id="title-gallery" data-has-pixel-tags="1" data-pixel-tag="bgr" data-author="Nicolae Bochis" data-category="science" data-content_type="Short Article" data-mod_date="2025-12-07" data-layout="Infinite" data-post_id="2040801" data-pub_date="2025-12-07" data-day="Sunday" data-dayhour="Sunday-1PM" data-pubhour="1PM" data-num_slides="3" data-num_words="700" data-pitcher="Joshua Hawkins" data-trello_board="News" data-intent="evergreen" data-ideation="paa-tools" data-importanttopic="True"&gt;What Does Nuclear Radiation Actually Do To Your Body?&lt;/h1&gt;
            &lt;/p&gt;

    
                &lt;div class="news-article"&gt;
                
                                
                                &lt;div class="slide-key image-holder gallery-image-holder credit-image-wrap lead-image-holder" data-post-url="https://www.bgr.com/2040801/what-nuclear-radiation-does-body-explained/" data-post-title="What Does Nuclear Radiation Actually Do To Your Body?" data-slide-num="0" data-post-id="2040801"&gt;
                                             &lt;picture id="pa050f7762a709e2aa10794165ca0acb5"&gt;
                                                    &lt;source media="(min-width: 429px)" srcset="https://www.bgr.com/img/gallery/what-does-nuclear-radiation-actually-do-to-your-body/intro-1764608555.webp" type="image/webp"&gt;
                            &lt;source media="(max-width: 428px)" srcset="https://www.bgr.com/img/gallery/what-does-nuclear-radiation-actually-do-to-your-body/intro-1764608555.sm.webp" type="image/webp"&gt;
                        &lt;img class="gallery-image " src="https://www.bgr.com/img/gallery/what-does-nuclear-radiation-actually-do-to-your-body/intro-1764608555.jpg" data-slide-url="https://www.bgr.com/2040801/what-nuclear-radiation-does-body-explained/" data-post-id="2040801" data-slide-num="0" data-slide-title="What Does Nuclear Radiation Actually Do To Your Body?: " alt="Radiation warning sign in the Chernobyl exclusion zone"&gt;
                    &lt;/source&gt;&lt;/source&gt;&lt;/picture&gt;
                    &lt;span class="gallery-image-credit"&gt;Jerry Vermanen/Shutterstock&lt;/span&gt;
                    &lt;/div&gt;
				            &lt;div class="columns-holder "&gt;
                
                
                &lt;p dir="ltr" id="docs-internal-guid-1a09ee40-7fff-9793-989e-9f884aca211b"&gt;Radiation can wreak havoc on the human body when it's exposed to high doses or for prolonged periods of time. The world understood this in horrifying detail after the Chernobyl and Fukushima Daiichi nuclear disasters. In each case, people were not simply exposed to radiation, the nuclear radiation rewrote what was happening in their bodies. Bone marrow was affected, thyroid glands absorbed radioactive iodine, and cells mutated quietly over the years after the exposure. Some victims collapsed in a matter of days, others suffered for decades. Scientists have even seen signs of &lt;a href="https://www.bgr.com/science/the-dogs-of-chernobyl-may-be-evolving-right-before-our-eyes/" target="_blank"&gt;dogs around Chernobyl mutating and evolving&lt;/a&gt; faster. Nuclear radiation doesn't necessarily announce itself with flames or a loud bang. It works silently and invisibly from within.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;Through years of hard work and experimentation, scientists learned a great deal about radiation. We now understand how it travels through food, which organs it attacks first, and why children can be more vulnerable. Although medicine has advanced, emergency systems have improved, and treatments have become smarter, we still don't know everything there is to know about how nuclear radiation affects human bodies. Nonetheless, here's what we do know so far.&lt;/p&gt;

            &lt;/div&gt;
            &lt;/div&gt;

            &lt;div class="news-article"&gt;
                
                &lt;h2 class=""&gt;How nuclear radiation damages the human body&lt;/h2&gt;
                                &lt;div class="slide-key image-holder gallery-image-holder credit-image-wrap " data-post-url="https://www.bgr.com/2040801/what-nuclear-radiation-does-body-explained/" data-post-title="What Does Nuclear Radiation Actually Do To Your Body?" data-slide-num="1" data-post-id="2040801"&gt;
                                             &lt;picture id="p354347d82e18e8d31c9a4346f168e346"&gt;
                                                    &lt;source media="(min-width: 429px)" srcset="https://www.bgr.com/img/gallery/what-does-nuclear-radiation-actually-do-to-your-body/how-nuclear-radiation-damages-the-human-body-1764608558.webp" type="image/webp"&gt;
                            &lt;source media="(max-width: 428px)" srcset="https://www.bgr.com/img/gallery/what-does-nuclear-radiation-actually-do-to-your-body/how-nuclear-radiation-damages-the-human-body-1764608558.sm.webp" type="image/webp"&gt;
                        &lt;img class="gallery-image " src="https://www.bgr.com/img/gallery/what-does-nuclear-radiation-actually-do-to-your-body/how-nuclear-radiation-damages-the-human-body-1764608558.jpg" data-slide-url="https://www.bgr.com/2040801/what-nuclear-radiation-does-body-explained/" data-post-id="2040801" data-slide-num="1" data-slide-title="What Does Nuclear Radiation Actually Do To Your Body?: How nuclear radiation damages the human body" alt="3D rendered closeup image of cancer cells"&gt;
                    &lt;/source&gt;&lt;/source&gt;&lt;/picture&gt;
                    &lt;span class="gallery-image-credit"&gt;Koto_feja/Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;
                    &lt;/div&gt;
				            &lt;div class="columns-holder "&gt;
                &lt;p dir="ltr" id="docs-internal-guid-58482616-7fff-f6c3-a210-5397eba16b19"&gt;Nuclear radiation tears through the human body at the molecular level. When radiation enters the body, it interacts with the cells violently. This process is known as ionization. It knocks electrons loose and destabilizes the chemistry of life. DNA strands can snap, proteins lose their shape, and healthy cells suddenly become broken factories.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;First to suffer are systems where cells divide fastest. Children are most affected because their growing bodies divide cells at faster rates than adults. Bone marrow may stop producing white cells, leading to infections, hemophilia, and excessive fatigue. The lining of the gut can peel away, causing to violent vomiting and dehydration. Skin exposed to high doses of radiation blisters and dies as if it were severely burned. Within weeks, the exposed person can lose their hair. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;Some radioactive particles don't just pass through our bodies. If radioactive dust is inhaled or swallowed, it often settles in the lungs, bones, or thyroid. Cesium, for example, mimics potassium and spreads through soft tissue. Strontium behaves like calcium and embeds itself in bones. Once inside, these particles can continue irradiating the human body for months and even years.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;High doses and sudden exposure can lead to the quick development of radiation poisoning. Confusion, nausea, weakness, and collapse are the first symptoms. Although lower exposure may seem harmless, if it's constant or over a prolonged period of time, it may cause cancer. That's why scientists are &lt;a href="https://www.bgr.com/science/scientific-breakthrough-could-make-x-ray-scans-safer-by-reducing-radiation/" target="_blank"&gt;working to make X-ray scans safer&lt;/a&gt; and reduce the amount of radiation we're exposed to over our lifetime.&lt;/p&gt;

            &lt;/div&gt;
            &lt;/div&gt;

            &lt;div class="news-article"&gt;
                
                &lt;h2 class=""&gt;What we know and what remains a mystery&lt;/h2&gt;
                                &lt;div class="slide-key image-holder gallery-image-holder credit-image-wrap " data-post-url="https://www.bgr.com/2040801/what-nuclear-radiation-does-body-explained/" data-post-title="What Does Nuclear Radiation Actually Do To Your Body?" data-slide-num="2" data-post-id="2040801"&gt;
                                             &lt;picture id="p5092cae4584c3c3dc99df9ae9ca9745c"&gt;
                                                    &lt;source media="(min-width: 429px)" srcset="https://www.bgr.com/img/gallery/what-does-nuclear-radiation-actually-do-to-your-body/what-we-know-and-what-remains-a-mystery-1764608560.webp" type="image/webp"&gt;
                            &lt;source media="(max-width: 428px)" srcset="https://www.bgr.com/img/gallery/what-does-nuclear-radiation-actually-do-to-your-body/what-we-know-and-what-remains-a-mystery-1764608560.sm.webp" type="image/webp"&gt;
                        &lt;img class="gallery-image " src="https://www.bgr.com/img/gallery/what-does-nuclear-radiation-actually-do-to-your-body/what-we-know-and-what-remains-a-mystery-1764608560.jpg" data-slide-url="https://www.bgr.com/2040801/what-nuclear-radiation-does-body-explained/" data-post-id="2040801" data-slide-num="2" data-slide-title="What Does Nuclear Radiation Actually Do To Your Body?: What we know and what remains a mystery" alt="3d rendered image of damaged DNA"&gt;
                    &lt;/source&gt;&lt;/source&gt;&lt;/picture&gt;
                    &lt;span class="gallery-image-credit"&gt;Alioui Mohammed Elamine/Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;
                    &lt;/div&gt;
				            &lt;div class="columns-holder "&gt;
                &lt;p dir="ltr" id="docs-internal-guid-61a3a90c-7fff-8bee-c76a-ed05174413e8"&gt;Major nuclear accidents have forced science to learn about radiation effects the hard way. Disasters like Chernobyl, Fukushima, Three Mile Island, and other &lt;a href="https://www.bgr.com/science/this-is-the-most-contaminated-nuclear-location-in-america/" target="_blank"&gt;contaminated nuclear locations&lt;/a&gt; taught the world that nuclear radiation doesn't behave in neat, predictable ways. Once it escapes into the environment, it's devastating. Radioactive iodine was found in milk days after Chernobyl. Ocean currents carried Fukushima contamination across the Pacific. Radiation doesn't fade like smoke. It lingers, seeps, and settles. It caused many towns to be erased from maps because the area remains unsafe for human life for decades.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;Medicine used these accidents to learn what the human body can survive, and what it cannot. Doctors now understand radiation burns, radiation sickness, and bone-marrow failure far better than before. The link between radiation and thyroid cancer became undeniable after thousands of cases appeared in exposed children in Ukraine. Since then, protective medicine such as potassium iodide became a standard.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And yet, despite everything we learned, some mysteries remain. Scientists still can't precisely predict who will develop cancer after low-level exposure and who will not. Two people can receive the same doses of radiation and face completely different futures. The effects of long-term exposure to small doses remain deeply uncertain. We know radiation damages DNA, but what we don't know is how often the repairs of damaged DNA fail. We also cannot predict when and if a damaged cell will turn into a cancerous one, because radiation alone is not the only mechanism behind tumors. Accidents such as Chernobyl give us data, but not nearly enough to completely understand the dangers of nuclear radiation to human bodies.&lt;/p&gt;

            &lt;/div&gt;
            &lt;/div&gt;

    
&lt;/article&gt;                        
            
                            
                           &lt;p id="div-ad-1x1a" class="google-ad-placeholder clear placeholder placeholder-1-1" data-ad-height="any" data-ad-width="any" data-ad-pos="1x1"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

        &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>bgr.com</author><pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 18:17:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMie0FVX3lxTE5aUF9LbmUxZmRzOEVfNGdzdjhfUkpEeEZ1eWNsRjJ6SldKU2pybGo2by1haVJ6VTBjeHhrUkl2ZzY1V1JOTWhDMkVOVkd6RVZYZzRBZTJuUEhlb1RnUkdTemdXYTJkU1ZOYi1LRi0zQ2lzYlZlSGVGeC1rYw</guid></item><item><title>朊病毒样脑损伤可能在没有传染性朊病毒的情况下发生，研究结果- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/prion-like-brain-damage-can-occur-without-infectious-prions-study-finds</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;We may have been overestimating the role of a pathological class of misfolded protein in neurodegenerative disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Called prions, these molecules are responsible for conditions such as &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/mysterious-form-of-mad-cow-disease-emerges-in-the-us"&gt;bovine spongiform encephalopathy&lt;/a&gt; or 'mad cow disease', &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/zombie-deer-disease-zoonotic-transfer-suspected-after-two-human-deaths"&gt;chronic wasting disease&lt;/a&gt; in deer, and &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/infectious-deadly-prions-in-people-s-eyes-could-be-a-biohazard-scientists-warn"&gt;Creutzfeldt-Jakob disease&lt;/a&gt; in humans.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A new study in mice has found that some of the hallmarks of prion disease in brain tissue – such as the appearance of sponge-like holes, scarring, and accumulation of &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/new-alzheimers-treatment-clears-plaques-from-brains-of-mice-within-hours"&gt;amyloid plaques&lt;/a&gt; – can develop even in the complete absence of prions in their infectious configuration.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Related: &lt;/b&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/misfolded-proteins-could-make-dementia-transmissible-scientists-suggest"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Misfolded Proteins Could Make Dementia Transmissible, Scientists Suggest&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Instead, the study found that non-infectious prion precursors in the presence of chronic inflammation driven by a bacterial endotoxin were enough to trigger prion-like neurodegeneration.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This finding suggests we have overlooked some of the mechanisms that contribute to prion diseases, and in some cases, even mistaken the underlying cause. It also has implications for prion-like conditions such as  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/go/IaO" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73015" data-postid="183897" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;Alzheimer's&lt;/a&gt;,  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/go/IYl" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73029" data-postid="183897" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;Parkinson's&lt;/a&gt;, and ALS, in which misfolded proteins are central to irreversible brain damage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_183907" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-183907" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/12/spongiform.jpg" alt="" class="size-full wp-image-183907" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/12/spongiform.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/12/spongiform-600x451.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-183907" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Spongiform encephalopathy under the microscope. (UCSF/Getty Images)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Prion diseases –  found in humans – are the terrifying result of a normal biological process going randomly awry.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Proteins consist of sequences of amino acids precisely folded to perform specific functions. They don't always work quite as intended, though; cells make wonky, misfolded, non-functional proteins &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1186/s40035-017-0077-5"&gt;all the time&lt;/a&gt;. Your body is also pretty good at unfolding or destroying the wonky proteins when this happens.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On extremely rare occasions, however, some types of misfolded protein can become a prion. Not only do they not function as they should, but these oddly-shaped proteins also force other proteins to adopt the same misfolded shape. Worse still, they resist the body's protease clean-up mechanisms, allowing them to accumulate and destroy cells.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Think of a cog with a bent tooth; every cog it interlocks with also ends up with a bent tooth, which it then passes on to its adjacent cogs, and so on. The result is an unstoppable spread of dysfunction. What makes it even more horrifying is that prions are, by definition, infectious; they can be spread between individuals, most commonly by consuming prion-contaminated meat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Proteins that can turn into prions are called prion proteins, or &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Major_prion_protein"&gt;PrP&lt;sup&gt;C&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. A misfolded PrP&lt;sup&gt;C&lt;/sup&gt; doesn't have to become a prion – that's a very specific, infectious type of misfolding – but recent evidence suggests that the other, non-infectious ways PrP&lt;sup&gt;C&lt;/sup&gt; can misfold may also trigger neurodegeneration.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Other emerging evidence suggests that a bacterial endotoxin called lipopolysaccharide (&lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Lipopolysaccharide"&gt;LPS&lt;/a&gt;), found on the outer membranes of some bacteria, can accelerate prion disease by inducing protease resistance in prion proteins. It also activates the host immune system's inflammatory response, further contributing to neurodegeneration.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Led by immunologist Burim Ametaj of the University of Alberta in Canada, a team of researchers used transgenic mice to determine the contribution of misfolded, non-infectious PrP and chronic inflammation to prion-like neurodegeneration.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/artificial-human-prion-created-in-a-lab-neurodegenerative-disease"&gt;artificially generated&lt;/a&gt; a misfolded form of a PrP that is toxic to neurons without being infectious.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Then, they divided their study mice into six groups.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The first group was given only saline – that was the control group. The second group was administered LPS, and the third group the toxic, misfolded, non-infectious PrP. The fourth group received both. The fifth group received actual infectious prions, and the sixth group received prions and LPS.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_183913" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-183913" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/12/prion-spread.jpg" alt="" class="size-full wp-image-183913" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/12/prion-spread.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/12/prion-spread-600x464.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-183913" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;This 2011 photomicrograph shows how prions, colored red, spread between mouse neural tissue cells. (&lt;a href="https://phil.cdc.gov/Details.aspx?pid=18131"&gt;NIAID&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Then, the researchers carefully monitored and tested their mice for up to 750 days, studying their brains for spongiform changes, protease resistance, a type of brain scarring called &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Astrogliosis"&gt;astrogliosis&lt;/a&gt;, and amyloid plaques – all of which are associated with prion disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The group that was given just the misfolded, non-infectious PrP alone developed the spongiform brain damage and scarring, but not the protease-resistant PrP that defines infectious prions. Meanwhile, the LPS-only group developed amyloid plaques, spongiform damage, and a high 40 percent mortality rate – but again, no protease resistance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Combining LPS with the non-infectious PrP misfold did not increase lethality, but holes in the brains of mice in this group did grow larger. Finally, combining the prion with LPS dramatically accelerated the course of the disease. All of the mice in this group died within 200 days.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"This fundamentally challenges the prevailing theory that these types of brain diseases are only about prions or similar misfolded proteins," &lt;a href="https://www.ualberta.ca/en/folio/2025/12/u-of-a-led-research-suggests-new-culprit-in-mad-cow-disease.html"&gt;Ametaj says&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The results suggest that, in at least some prion diseases, the host may first be weakened by inflammation before the protein misfolding that leads to prion formation – that prion disease may not actually start with prions, but with inflammation, or the non-infectious, misfolded PrP.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/newsletter?utm_source=promo_generic_health"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-642x273.jpg" alt="Subscribe to ScienceAlert's free fact-checked newsletter" class="alignnone wp-image-182810 size-medium" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-642x273.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-768x326.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-600x255.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final.jpg 850w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Alzheimer's-like presentation of the mice administered only with LPS has some interesting implications. It suggests that inflammation may play a key role in kicking off neurodegenerative, prion-like diseases – echoing other recent studies &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/brain-autopsies-reveal-a-potential-culprit-behind-alzheimers"&gt;that have found links&lt;/a&gt; between &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/gut-inflammation-linked-to-alzheimers-disease-yet-again"&gt;inflammation and Alzheimer's disease&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It opens up an entire anti-inflammatory medicine toolkit. Bacterial endotoxins &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1186/s13024-024-00722-y"&gt;have been found&lt;/a&gt; in the brains of Alzheimer's patients, so risk factors that reduce dementia – exercise, anti-inflammatory diets, gut health, metabolic health – might work partly by reducing endotoxin burden," &lt;a href="https://www.ualberta.ca/en/folio/2025/12/u-of-a-led-research-suggests-new-culprit-in-mad-cow-disease.html"&gt;Ametaj says&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"These diseases are complex, but if endotoxin exposure contributes to even 20 to 30 per cent of cases, controlling this modifiable risk factor could spare millions of people. We might prevent some neurodegenerative diseases the way we prevent heart disease, by managing inflammatory risk factors throughout life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"In a field where there's been little hope, that matters."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The research has been published in the &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.3390/ijms26136245"&gt;&lt;i&gt;International Journal of Molecular Sciences&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 18:03:41 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiogFBVV95cUxNUFc5TUNhdmJqaEU2LWVYOUg5NXJqV0RaVWZIRjBBNHpuNkRSeUgxejFBRnRhUmE1a09xZkVYd0NfenNCRkh2UWdUdC02MzBtMF9JaVRqVTRRMFdrY1lKWHB0dGhMbjJ4M3FfdzUyTWZiQTcySVp4VXZOVHljeGRvQjlkR1h5Qld6TWpnczd1UHJvNlFiT0NtNFkzWHhZQjMzMlE</guid></item><item><title>他的免赔额为$ 4,000。为了控制他的糖尿病，他不得不偷工减料。-《华盛顿邮报》</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/health/2025/12/07/high-deductible-plans-diabetes/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text subtype-from-the-source" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="GBRXOTQUCBGPZOM27VJFM5GFW4" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;David Garza sometimes feels as if he doesn’t have health insurance now that he pays so much to treat his Type 2 diabetes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="URI5MJ6R5RASFAXWF2QMY5VQBA" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;His monthly premium payment of $435 for family coverage is roughly the same as the insurance at his previous job. But the policy at his current job carries an annual deductible of $4,000, which he must pay out-of-pocket for his family’s care until he reaches that amount each year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 18:00:28 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihwFBVV95cUxPSS1uY2ZhMEp1bjRfVFFkcFJ1Sm05dnJWMnp6TGU3dVNjMzVVckFIUEtlT1NNNS04TEV3MXNkbGctYzVsanhINWdvc3JrdHNsVEFzY2x5RDY1RnhRVzRVSDRYTTNjNjBnbkd2WnEwY1FQLWdGckFrSHp0WFZ3QXF6Q0VlVEExR2M</guid></item><item><title>新的燃烧脂肪的糖尿病药丸保护肌肉和食欲- ScienceDaily</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/12/251207031345.htm</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p id="first" class="lead"&gt;Lowering blood sugar and increasing fat burning without reducing appetite or muscle mass is emerging as a promising possibility in the treatment of type 2 diabetes and obesity. These encouraging results come from a study published in &lt;em&gt;Cell&lt;/em&gt; by researchers at Karolinska Institutet and Stockholm University.&lt;/p&gt;

						&lt;div id="text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The treatment, which is taken as a tablet, works in a completely different way from well-known GLP-1-based medications such as Ozempic that are given through injections. GLP-1 drugs influence hunger by altering communication between the gut and the brain, and they can cause side effects that include appetite loss, decreased muscle mass, and gastrointestinal discomfort.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Targeting Muscle Metabolism Rather Than Appetite&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Instead of acting on hunger pathways, the new compound boosts metabolic activity directly within skeletal muscle. In animal studies, it improved blood sugar levels and body composition while avoiding the drawbacks commonly linked to today's GLP-1-based treatments.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A phase I clinical trial involving 48 healthy volunteers and 25 individuals with type 2 diabetes indicates that the treatment is also well tolerated in humans.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Our results point to a future where we can improve metabolic health without losing muscle mass. Muscles are important in both type 2 diabetes and obesity, and muscle mass is also directly correlated with life expectancy," says Tore Bengtsson, professor at the Department of Molecular Bioscience, Wenner-Gren Institute, Stockholm University.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A New Type of β2 Agonist Designed for Safety&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The active substance is based on a laboratory-developed molecule, a form of β2 agonist. This molecule activates key signaling pathways in a novel manner that benefits muscle function while avoiding the heart overstimulation typically associated with β2 agonists.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="insertion_middle"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"This drug represents a completely new type of treatment and has the potential to be of great importance for patients with type 2 diabetes and obesity. Our substance appears to promote healthy weight loss and, in addition, patients do not have to take injections," says Shane C. Wright, assistant professor at the Department of Physiology and Pharmacology at Karolinska Institutet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Potential as a Stand-Alone or Combination Therapy&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Because this drug operates through a mechanism distinct from GLP-1 medications, it may be effective on its own or when paired with GLP-1 drugs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"This makes them valuable both as a stand-alone treatment and in combination with GLP-1 drugs," says Shane C. Wright.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Next Steps and Research Collaboration&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The next stage in development is a larger phase II clinical trial planned by Atrogi AB, the company leading the drug's advancement. This study will examine whether the positive effects observed in earlier research also appear in people living with type 2 diabetes or obesity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The work represents a collaboration involving Professor Volker M. Lauschke and teams from Karolinska Institutet, Stockholm University, Uppsala University, the University of Copenhagen, Monash University, and the University of Queensland. Funding came from the Swedish Research Council, the Swedish Society for Medical Research, the Novo Nordisk Foundation, and additional sources.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Several authors are employed by or hold shares in Atrogi AB, which financed the clinical trial. Tore Bengtsson is the founder and chief scientific officer of Atrogi AB, which is continuing to develop the drug candidate, and he and a co-author have applied for patents related to the substances examined in the study. Additional company affiliations are detailed in the full publication.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

					&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceDaily</author><pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 18:00:10 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMib0FVX3lxTFBsMklZR3h5VU5PU0NueUtIV1g4U1FCbDY4X2JjYTRKWDczbUlkYk9aOWhnN1Q4V0xmWWdVa1hBei1xS0g0c2NuX3hveVZaQWxuWnA4VmdFY1Y2ckhONjdlc2ZrdzVsTExMa2FJckJsMA</guid></item><item><title>犹他大学健康研究经费在2025年达到创纪录的5.31亿美元- KSL.com</title><link>https://www.ksl.com/article/51414035/university-of-utah-health-research-funding-reaches-record-531m-in-2025</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="articleContainer"&gt;&lt;p&gt;SALT LAKE CITY — University of Utah Health has amassed record research funding totals, surpassing the half-billion mark for 2025, reaching $531 million.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Securing competitive funding is essential to the University of Utah's mission of delivering exceptional societal impact. These investments fuel research, advance knowledge, improve health in Utah and worldwide and support the training of future scientific leaders," the U. said in a statement.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The National Institutes of Health was once again the largest source of funding support, providing $264.1 million.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That chunk comes despite the NIH &lt;a href="https://www.ksl.com/article/51250766" rel="follow" target="_blank"&gt;cutting billions of dollars&lt;/a&gt; in research projects under the Trump administration, a move U. President Taylor Randall described in February as an "imminent threat" to the university's mission as a research institution.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bob Carter, senior vice president for health sciences and CEO of University of Utah Health, said, "Research, innovation and advancing knowledge is an uncompromising part of who we are as an institution, a culture and a nation," when the cuts were announced.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Challenges to NIH's attempted cuts to funds known as "indirect costs" of medical research are currently making their way through the courts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Carter added that in Utah, National Institutes of Health funding supports over 45,000 jobs and nearly $785 million in economic activity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Still, the U. secured the bulk of its funding from the NIH, with industry partnerships making up the second-largest funding category at $99 million.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Other federal agencies like the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention, Environmental Protection Agency, and Department of Defense contributed $57.4 million, and additional contributions from the state, other universities and various foundations totaled $110.7 million.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr. Rachel Hess, system chief research officer for University of Utah Health, said faculty submitted $2.3 billion in research proposals in 2025 — a $500 million increase compared to the previous year and a testament to the perseverance of the research community.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Notably, research in the health sciences sector continued its rise, growing 24% over the past five years and more than doubling since 2014.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This year, health sciences funding accounted for 68% of the university's &lt;a href="https://www.research.utah.edu/facts-and-figures/" rel="nofollow" target="_blank"&gt;total research portfolio&lt;/a&gt; that totaled $782 million, the university said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="kt_disclaimer"&gt;
                                    The Key Takeaways for this article were generated with the assistance of large language models and reviewed by our editorial team. The article, itself, is solely human-written.
                                &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>KSL.com</author><pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 17:03:11 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiqwFBVV95cUxPT25BMkt5YUp1M2JZU3YzLUVaYmRZcXV6d0g5N2NzUnpIelFCSVVyYUppS3NvWDF1T1BxTFpRNllsNVA5N0lfUUtGSWFwVHBOXzdNenNaekY1LU9fWTVrQ0x1cEd3NnVDcU9uQmg1bE1xM3BiMlFYaF84YjRZSjNKY08zRHlvbHhCdm1WX1JSNFQ2ZnFRNVhpbTA5WWZOdzZzUmE4QmZCM1NJVDQ</guid></item><item><title>这个5分钟的晚间锻炼程序比50岁后的早晨锻炼更好地锻炼肌肉-吃这个不是那个</title><link>https://www.eatthis.com/5-minute-evening-routine-build-muscle-after-50/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="content single-post-content"&gt;
																			&lt;p class="tagline"&gt;End your day strong with a 5-minute evening routine that builds muscle after 50.&lt;/p&gt;
												
																			
																		
						
						
						&lt;p&gt;You’ve likely heard that the best time to build muscle is &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer external" href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC10198889/" target="_blank"&gt;first thing in the morning,&lt;/a&gt; before breakfast or work, and the day gets away from you. But while morning workouts are certainly beneficial, evening strength training can be just as helpful for older adults in building muscle.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What’s more, you don’t need sixty minute long intense gym sessions to benefit from &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://www.eatthis.com/10-minute-evening-routine-belly-overhang-after-40/" target="_blank"&gt;evening exercise&lt;/a&gt;. Even short routines (when done consistently) can prime your muscles, reinforce healthy movement patterns, and make regular training feel more achievable. That’s because &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer external" href="https://www.frontiersin.org/journals/aging/articles/10.3389/fragi.2025.1493827/full" target="_blank" data-citation="true" data-citation-type="ScholarlyArticle"&gt;studies&lt;/a&gt; show that after 50, staying consistent with your exercise becomes one of the most critical factors of healthy aging.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To learn more, we chatted with &lt;b&gt;Kris Herbert, CPT&lt;/b&gt;, a certified personal trainer and owner of &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer external" href="https://www.instagram.com/p/DGte-cNyzSn/" target="_blank"&gt;The Gym Venice&lt;/a&gt;, who shares a stellar five-minute evening routine to help you build muscle better than &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://www.eatthis.com/5-minute-bedtime-routine-builds-strength-after-50/" target="_blank"&gt;morning workouts after 50&lt;/a&gt;. However, Herbert explains that, “A five-minute routine will not replace full strength training, and it is not a magic shortcut. That said, short, consistent evening sessions can help &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://www.eatthis.com/seated-leg-exercises-reverse-muscle-loss-after-50/" target="_blank"&gt;keep muscles active&lt;/a&gt;, maintain joint mobility, and reinforce the habit of training.” In other words, even if you’re exhausted at the end of the day, those few minutes of exercise are still worth doing as they keep your body active and help keep you consistent.&lt;span aria-hidden="true"&gt;6254a4d1642c605c54bf1cab17d50f1e&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The following five-minute evening routine cycles between five movements for 30 seconds each, with 15 to 30 seconds between transitions for a total of five minutes. “As strength and confidence improve, gradually increasing challenge is what delivers meaningful gains in muscle, function, and healthy aging,” says Herbert.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="karma_unit karma_unit--distinct inline karma_unit--mobile hide-desktop karma_unit--sliding htlad-lazy-mob-square-fixed karma_unit--halfpage"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Read on to find out exactly how to do it. Then, when you’re finished, be sure to check out these &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://www.eatthis.com/7-quick-standing-exercises-better-than-hour-long-workouts-after-45/" target="_blank"&gt;7 Quick Standing Exercises That Deliver More Results Than Hour-Long Workouts After 45&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;h2 id="glute-bridge" class="o-slide-title" data-num="1"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Glute Bridge&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
	
&lt;p&gt;&lt;iframe title="YouTube video player" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/OUgsJ8-Vi0E?si=SXDpdLRvZPCovX0R" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"&gt;VIDEO&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The glute bridge kickstarts your glutes and hamstrings, which after a long day of sitting, often become underactive and can contribute to lower back pain, weak hips, and poor posture. Fortunately, doing just 30 seconds of controlled glute bridges regularly can help restore strength in these weakened muscles.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;How to do it:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lie on your back with your knees bent and your feet flat on the floor.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Press through your heels and lift your hips until your body forms a straight line from your shoulders to your knees.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hold  briefly at the top then lower with control.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Continue for the full 30 seconds.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Why it works:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Activates the largest lower body muscles&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Supports hip stability and reduces strain on your lower back&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prepares your body for more advanced strength training&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Progressions&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Pause for two to three seconds at the top&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lift your toes slightly to increase heel drive&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
	&lt;h2 id="bird-dog" class="o-slide-title" data-num="2"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Bird Dog&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
	
&lt;p&gt;&lt;iframe title="YouTube video player" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/-LRjkbEy-qU?si=TDkkn60SxXwo2ihv" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"&gt;VIDEO&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The bird dog is a unique core-stability exercise that’s widely recommended for reducing lower back pain by &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer external" href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC10305076/" target="_blank"&gt;boosting coordination between spinal stabilizers&lt;/a&gt;. Also, this exercise helps strengthen the deep core muscles that protect your spine and improve balance, which are crucial for &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer external" href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC12315335/" target="_blank"&gt;healthy aging and longevity&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;How to do it:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Get down on your hands and knees.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extend one arm forward and the opposite leg back.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hold briefly, then return to the starting position.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Switch sides and continue alternating for 30 seconds.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Why it works:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="karma_unit karma_unit--distinct inline karma_unit--mobile hide-desktop karma_unit--sliding htlad-lazy-mob-square-fixed"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strengthens deep core stabilizers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Improves balance and cross-body coordination&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Reduces compensations that strain your lower back&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Progressions&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hold each extension for two to three seconds&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

	&lt;h2 id="wall-sit" class="o-slide-title" data-num="3"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Wall Sit&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
	
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The wall sit is an isometric hold (where you hold a specific position without moving) that fires up your quads, glutes, and core without requiring movement that stresses sore or stiff joints. This exercise also builds muscle endurance, improves joint control, and reinforces proper alignment for everyday activities like squatting, climbing stairs, or standing up from a chair.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;How to do it:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Stand with your back against a wall and slide down until your knees are bent to a comfortable angle.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hold for 15 to 20 seconds.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Stand briefly to reset, then repeat until the 30-second window ends.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Why it works:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Builds strength in major leg muscles&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Improves core stability and posture&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Supports balance and knee control&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Progressions&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lower deeper into the sit&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hold the entire 30 seconds without standing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

	&lt;h2 id="wall-angels" class="o-slide-title" data-num="4"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Wall Angels&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
	
&lt;p&gt;&lt;iframe title="YouTube video player" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/-cdph8hv0O0?si=CPNZI2qPizgGQ0lr" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"&gt;VIDEO&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After hours of slouching, driving, and looking down at screens, shoulders and upper backs can stiffen like crazy. Fortunately, wall angels help counteract this stiffness by strengthening the upper-back muscles while enhancing shoulder mobility. Over time, this can reduce the rounded posture that becomes more common with age.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;How to do it:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Stand with your back against a wall, your elbows bent, and your arms raised to shoulder height.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Slide your arms up the wall as high as comfortable.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Return to the starting position.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Continue slowly for 30 seconds.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Why it works:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Increases shoulder mobility&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strengthens upper-back muscles&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Supports better posture and overhead movement&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Progressions&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Keep your wrists touching the wall throughout the entire movement.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p class="karma_unit karma_unit--distinct inline karma_unit--mobile hide-desktop karma_unit--sliding htlad-lazy-mob-square-fixed"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;h2 id="plank-shoulder-taps" class="o-slide-title" data-num="5"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Plank Shoulder Taps&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
	
&lt;p&gt;&lt;iframe title="YouTube video player" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/gKA5LBy7WAI?si=T0ja1FjgnV9TfhvO&amp;amp;start=9" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"&gt;VIDEO&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Plank shoulder taps are a full-body stability drill that improve core strength, balance, and stability, which are crucial skills that help protect the spine and carry over to daily movements that involve lifting and carrying.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;How to do it:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Start in a plank position on your hands (either on the floor or elevated).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Widen your feet slightly for better balance.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tap one hand to the opposite shoulder.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Switch sides and continue alternating for 30 seconds.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Why it works:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strengthens deep core stabilizers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Enhances shoulder stability&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Builds anti-rotation control&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Progressions&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Move to a lower surface or the floor&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

																		
																	&lt;/div&gt;
										&lt;div class="c-article-short-bio"&gt;
	&lt;p class="c-article-short-bio__name"&gt;Adam Meyer, RHN&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;div class="c-article-short-bio__bio"&gt;&lt;p&gt;
		Adam is a health writer, certified holistic nutritionist, and 100% plant-based athlete.					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a class="c-article-short-bio__more" href="https://www.eatthis.com/author/adam-meyer/"&gt;Read more about Adam &lt;/a&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
					&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Eat This Not That</author><pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 17:02:30 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMie0FVX3lxTE1QUnRoUWg2aEJhM3AyRjE0TVBHY0x0V1pQMFI3MS0wUXU1b19laDBnby1WOVBBVWd6ZWNyRU9oaHZoMl95c1FKWTM5QXFaUDVyd0w0VVJNR1h4Z2lzZmdVakxRdXRKbzh6emxQUVkxZ19ac0hKQU9qcGN5bw</guid></item><item><title>成绩单：斯科特·戈特利布在“与玛格丽特·布伦南面对国家” ， 2025年12月7日-哥伦比亚广播公司新闻</title><link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/scott-gottlieb-face-the-nation-transcript-12-07-2025/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;section class="content__body"&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;The following is the transcript of the interview with former FDA commissioner Scott Gottlieb, who now serves on the boards of Pfizer and United Healthcare, that aired on "Face the Nation with Margaret Brennan" on Dec. 7, 2025.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;MARGARET BRENNAN: For a look at some recent changes to U.S. public health policy. We're joined now by former FDA commissioner Dr Scott Gottlieb. He also serves on the boards of Pfizer and United Healthcare. Welcome back. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;DR. SCOTT GOTTLIEB: Thank you. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;MARGARET BRENNAN: You know there was some pretty big news on Friday, and the American Academy of Pediatrics said they are deeply alarmed that the CDC vaccine advisory panel, ACIP voted in this 8-3 decision to change this 30 year long policy regarding Hepatitis B and newborns. They are now recommending delaying the dose until a child is two months old, instead of within 24 hours of birth. What does this decision mean for families of newborns?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;DR. SCOTT GOTTLIEB: Yeah. Well, look, I think we first need to understand why we give that birth dose of the vaccine, because the idea of giving a vaccine to a newborn, to a lot of parents, sounds discomforting, that the first thing a child is going to face when they're born is going to be a vaccine within the first 24 hours. For a child over the age of five, if they develop Hepatitis B infection, if they're exposed to it, they're going to have a 95% chance of clearing that infection, and they'll go on to develop lifelong immunity. For children between the ages of one and five, they only have about a 25 to 50% chance of clearing the infection, so about 25 to 50% of kids will develop chronic infection, and about a quarter of them will go on to die from hepatitis B if they're between the ages of one and five. So children are more vulnerable to this virus and can't clear the infection. But when you're talking about a newborn, an infant, 90% of newborns who become infected, and they'll become infected during delivery, will go on to develop chronic infection, they won't be able to clear the hepatitis B, and about 25% of them will die from sequelae of that infection, either from liver disease, cirrhosis or from liver cancer. So we have this unique opportunity by giving this birth dose and the subsequent inoculations to virtually eliminate the chance that a newborn can contract Hepatitis B and go on to develop chronic infection, it's almost 99% effective at preventing that chronic infection. And the refrain is.&lt;/p&gt;

    
    &lt;p id="mpu-plus-outstream-middle" data-ad="mpu-plus-outstream-middle" class="ad-mpu-plus-outstream-middle ad-wrapper " data-ad-unit='"mpu-plus-outstream-middle"'&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;MARGARET BRENNAN: And– &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;DR. SCOTT GOTTLIEB: And one final point, the refrain is, oh, sorry, please.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;MARGARET BRENNAN: No, no. And this decision now is to wait two months before giving that dose.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;DR. SCOTT GOTTLIEB: Right.&lt;/p&gt;

    
    
    &lt;p id="mpu-flex-inc3" data-ad="mpu-flex-inc" class="ad-mpu-flex-inc ad-wrapper " data-ad-unit='["mpu-flex-inc",3]'&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;MARGARET BRENNAN: The President of the United States came out and said, this was very good, because Hep B is only transmitted sexually or through dirty needles.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;DR. SCOTT GOTTLIEB: Yeah, look, that's the problem. That's simply not true. The fact is, there's a refrain that if you just test the moms during, while they're pregnant, you can detect whether they have hepatitis B, and if they have hepatitis B, you continue to give that birth dose. But the reality is, many moms don't get tested, even though they intend to, many times, those test results aren't checked, and the tests themselves have a false negative rate, meaning they're going to say you don't have hepatitis B, when in fact, you do, of about 2 percent. That may not sound like a lot, but that 2% is going to translate into at least 1000 babies being born and getting infected with hepatitis B. There was one modeling estimate that estimated in the first year of this new guidance, there's going to be 1,400 children, infants contracting hepatitis B, and again, 25% of them will die from that infection.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;MARGARET BRENNAN: Well, we look at this because there is this broader scrutiny of vaccines right now by the Trump administration and in this board decision, which the public could listen into. It was publicly broadcast. The board was hand picked by RFK Jr, who is a skeptic here of vaccines, from those who voted against the decision to delay. One of them who you heard at the top of the show said the CDC is doing harm. Another said, "No rational science has been presented, and the committee must accept responsibility when harm is caused." Those are pretty extraordinary statements. If the group making a decision that has such high consequences for the most vulnerable Americans isn't basing it on science, no rational science, what does that indicate about what comes next?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;DR. SCOTT GOTTLIEB: Well, look, this is the ACIP by and large, except for a handful of members, are anti-vax activists who were put there to carry out a specific agenda. And look, the Secretary, to his credit, has been very honest about what his intentions are here. He's the most prominent anti-vaxer in the country prior to coming into this position, and he stated that his goal is to eliminate childhood immunization, or many of these childhood immunizations, and I think they're going to take a methodical approach and slowly chip away at this. This is a big unforced error insofar as ACIP was a esteemed body that a lot of states tie their own decision making to, and what we're seeing right now is as a group, it's being degraded, and I don't think it will ever be restored. I don't think you can just flip the switch and restore this where people are going to suddenly respect its decisions again. There's about 600 state laws that were tied to decisions ACIP made. About 17 states have already passed new legislation saying they will no longer respect the decisions of ACIP. The insurers came out and said they're going to tie their own coverage decisions to the professional bodies like the American Academy of Pediatrics and not ACIP. So I think in time, ACIP is going to be fully degraded as a decision making body, and it's going to be more symbolic. There will be certain states that- that adhere to it, but will be more symbolic.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;MARGARET BRENNAN: So you this week, we saw a big sell off in biotech stocks following these reports that the FDA, which you used to run the first part of the Trump administration, is now going to require one study to clinch approval of vaccines. You were one of the former commissioners who put out this really extraordinary editorial in the New England Journal of Medicine, arguing that the FDA and top vaccine regulator, Dr. Vinay Prasad, are changing policies in a way that's going to slow down new and better vaccines. What specifically is the problem you see? Because this isn't just hep B, this is the vaccines of the future. You're saying just won't be created?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;DR. SCOTT GOTTLIEB: Right. So Vinay Prasad, who is the head of the biologic center. Also oversees the vaccine Division. He also has been appointed the head of biostatistics, the Chief Medical Officer of the agency, and chief scientific officer. So he occupies a lot of positions. Put out a memo saying that they're going to do away with, or move away from, what they call immuno bridging studies. These are studies that allow you for well validated vaccines, like the flu vaccine, to be able to demonstrate each year that the vaccine, the new vaccine, that's formulated against the circulating strain, can elicit antibodies that are effective against that particular strain, and that could be the basis of approval, rather than requiring new outcome studies every year to prove that the vaccine actually reduces the incidence of influenza. For established vaccines, where we know that antibody production is a good correlate for immunity, this has been a long standing practice. It's, we do it for flu vaccine, we do it in covid Certainly, we do it for things like pneumococcal vaccine, the vaccine for pneumococcal disease, where we look at serotypes circulating bacterial serotypes. This allows us to update vaccines as these viral and bacterial strains change, and as the composition of the strains change in time to provide protection for the Fall respiratory season. If they move away from this, which is what he said, they plan to do, we're just not going to be able to update vaccines each season, as we've done historically, to accommodate whatever the circulating strain is.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;MARGARET BRENNAN: And 12 former FDA commissioners came out saying they're deeply concerned about what is happening. That memo that made clear the changes that are happening within the FDA from Dr. Prasad was obtained by CBS, and it claimed that career FDA staff are making changes in part because they found at least 10 children have died after and because of receiving the Covid vaccine, referred to it as a profound revelation, and said and asked, Did it kill more healthy kids than it saved? The administration, to date, has not backed up information to back up these claims, but, but, what questions do you have for the FDA commissioner, because they're arguing they're doing this to help people?&lt;/p&gt;

    
    
    &lt;p id="mpu-flex-inc4" data-ad="mpu-flex-inc" class="ad-mpu-flex-inc ad-wrapper " data-ad-unit='["mpu-flex-inc",4]'&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;DR. SCOTT GOTTLIEB: Yeah, look, well, first of all, one thing doesn't flow from the next. So the idea if, in fact, they found cases where the covid vaccine was linked to tragic deaths, it doesn't then follow that you make these policy changes. In fact, the policy changes wouldn't address what the concerns are related to the covid vaccine itself. These are- every case needs to be carefully adjudicated. It's tragic to see any suspected case that could be linked to a vaccine. And these were looked at previously by the FDA, and I don't believe that the new FDA had access to the case level data analysis of cases, individual cases that get filed with the agency where there is a death in proximity to vaccination, and some of these are filed by the manufacturers themselves are very subjective and require the goodwill the people involved in that. And so I think that they should make that analysis public so it could be scrutinized and people can get comfort in that they've already backed away from the 10 is reporting from endpoints that now they're saying it's eight or nine, so they're already backing away from it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;MARGARET BRENNAN: Okay. And HHS said they will eventually make that data public. We'll look for it when it comes out. Dr Gottlieb, thank you for your analysis today. We'll be back in a moment.&lt;/p&gt;

    

                    
        
  
    
  
  &lt;aside class="component list recirculation component--type-recirculation component--type-recirculation-collection"&gt;
                    
                                            
        &lt;div class="component__heading-wrapper recirc"&gt;
          &lt;h3 class="component__title"&gt;Face The Nation Transcripts
                          &lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/feature/face-the-nation-transcripts/?intcid=CNI-00-10aaa3a" class="component__view-more component__view-more--lg" data-invalid-url-rewritten-http=""&gt;
                More
                &lt;svg viewbox="0 0 32 32" class="icon__caret-right" aria-hidden="true"&gt;
                  &lt;use xlink:href="#icon-caret-down"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;
                &lt;/svg&gt;
              &lt;/a&gt;
                      &lt;/h3&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
                  &lt;div class="component__item-recirc-block"&gt;
            
    &lt;ul&gt;
                                                                                
            &lt;li id="inline-recirc-item--id-b53438d6-6dba-43ca-816e-02c4ad629fc3" class="card-recirc item"&gt;
                &lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/news/face-the-nation-full-transcript-12-07-2025/?intcid=CNI-00-10aaa3a" class="item__anchor" draggable="false" data-invalid-url-rewritten-http=""&gt;
                    &lt;article&gt;
                        &lt;svg&gt;
                            &lt;use xlink:href="#recirc-cbs-news"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;
                        &lt;/svg&gt;
                        &lt;h2&gt;Full transcript of "Face the Nation with Margaret Brennan," Dec. 7, 2025&lt;/h2&gt;
                    &lt;/article&gt;
                    
                &lt;/a&gt;
            &lt;/li&gt;
                                                                            
            &lt;li id="inline-recirc-item--id-efc3e268-2996-4179-84b6-bee9c59e4e9e" class="card-recirc item"&gt;
                &lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/news/scott-bessent-treasury-secretary-face-the-nation-transcript-12-07-2025/?intcid=CNI-00-10aaa3a" class="item__anchor" draggable="false" data-invalid-url-rewritten-http=""&gt;
                    &lt;article&gt;
                        &lt;svg&gt;
                            &lt;use xlink:href="#recirc-cbs-news"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;
                        &lt;/svg&gt;
                        &lt;h2&gt;Transcript: Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent on "Face the Nation with Margaret Brennan," Dec. 7, 2025&lt;/h2&gt;
                    &lt;/article&gt;
                    
                &lt;/a&gt;
            &lt;/li&gt;
                                                                            
            &lt;li id="inline-recirc-item--id-753905f8-8fe7-43b6-85d2-999edb6eb94c" class="card-recirc item"&gt;
                &lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/news/ilhan-omar-minnesota-democrat-face-the-nation-transcript-12-07-2025/?intcid=CNI-00-10aaa3a" class="item__anchor" draggable="false" data-invalid-url-rewritten-http=""&gt;
                    &lt;article&gt;
                        &lt;svg&gt;
                            &lt;use xlink:href="#recirc-cbs-news"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;
                        &lt;/svg&gt;
                        &lt;h2&gt;Transcript: Rep. Ilhan Omar on "Face the Nation with Margaret Brennan," Dec. 7, 2025&lt;/h2&gt;
                    &lt;/article&gt;
                    
                &lt;/a&gt;
            &lt;/li&gt;
                                                                            
            &lt;li id="inline-recirc-item--id-70be51bd-e072-4ec1-97e0-22704cc3ab4f" class="card-recirc item"&gt;
                &lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/news/scott-gottlieb-face-the-nation-transcript-12-07-2025/?intcid=CNI-00-10aaa3a" class="item__anchor" draggable="false" data-invalid-url-rewritten-http=""&gt;
                    &lt;article&gt;
                        &lt;svg&gt;
                            &lt;use xlink:href="#recirc-cbs-news"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;
                        &lt;/svg&gt;
                        &lt;h2&gt;Transcript: Scott Gottlieb on "Face the Nation with Margaret Brennan," Dec. 7, 2025&lt;/h2&gt;
                    &lt;/article&gt;
                    
                &lt;/a&gt;
            &lt;/li&gt;
                                                                            
            &lt;li id="inline-recirc-item--id-1b74ae6c-9388-4317-88c5-4d2f0d866fe0" class="card-recirc item"&gt;
                &lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/news/jim-himes-connecticut-democrat-face-the-nation-transcript-12-07-2025/?intcid=CNI-00-10aaa3a" class="item__anchor" draggable="false" data-invalid-url-rewritten-http=""&gt;
                    &lt;article&gt;
                        &lt;svg&gt;
                            &lt;use xlink:href="#recirc-cbs-news"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;
                        &lt;/svg&gt;
                        &lt;h2&gt;Transcript: Rep. Jim Himes on "Face the Nation with Margaret Brennan," Dec. 7, 2025&lt;/h2&gt;
                    &lt;/article&gt;
                    
                &lt;/a&gt;
            &lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;/ul&gt;
          &lt;/div&gt;
                            &lt;/aside&gt;



  
    
    
  &lt;/section&gt;

  

  
    
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>CBS News</author><pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 16:49:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiigFBVV95cUxPMkZuRWw3ZDNfMkZWQVBOTmtnLXU4aGFwT1FRc3JoLVBQbVdabzBUaHVyS2Y0ZnByd1RTd1lLbURqZVQwQVdnd1BiSzBiNUxMdEpucjNQMklwZDUwNGRsbVdSaTJiWHZyWFNQd0xScGhJOGxvRU5GcC11Qk1vTUtYamhETElnVTJlcGfSAY8BQVVfeXFMT2I1alRlZmN4YmI1c2x0V1MxajNmY1JTZGx4VDQwd1U2QklTdVFIMEVvMFNHNmVpNzZXd3NOYmloaHJfc3pUYnp1VF9mQ3hFaWdtRHU0UXdMdzVrc0FldWRXYU41ZVplamFXWEZDYzgzQUdIYm9xNDZCbkZneXJ4TDlrcG12ZUlTYmI1WGRiaXM</guid></item><item><title>增强免疫力和健康的10种最佳天然维生素C来源-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/diet/10-best-natural-sources-of-vitamin-c-to-boost-immunity-and-health/photostory/125819021.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="COQxt" data-ua-type="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Vitamin C, also known as ascorbic acid, is one of the most essential nutrients for human health. Unlike some vitamins, the body cannot produce it on its own, making dietary intake crucial. This water-soluble vitamin is renowned for its role in boosting the immune system, promoting collagen production, and acting as a powerful antioxidant that protects cells from oxidative damage. &lt;br&gt;Beyond immunity and skin health, vitamin C also enhances iron absorption from plant-based foods, supporting overall metabolic and cardiovascular well-being. &lt;br&gt;Here are the ten best natural sources of vitamin C: &lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Times of India</author><pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 16:45:30 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi7gFBVV95cUxPTnZLOEtIbUlaa0tnb183eGdPbGozQjk4WVVzQWJzSTBpYVk5QmZacS1VUnZhbGZMYnBGMEFSR0JGM3lxS0lJVC1IMWNfNjl2dUJid2FDNWx6eFBEcFF6MzNENVZ6cXl4YUZlSG9OdzRIWV9iQnM0ODBWdUNuMVp5b2RrV3E2a0dKQzMzdXRKWkd5MGZPUWRCVnM3NFRkbXd0Y1Bxd1puT2tiRTMxdUwxNkFOSm1WdjNmVXZITFNROVJjQlRKZGJZUnBBWWg4aHV2UWNIQnRBTEhubU85QWpoa3owdmxyZ2lOaUZ2bnpB0gH2AUFVX3lxTFBlaTkxdGZTRHhDS0R6Slk5RHU5THVXY2Z4eUlDLTY3dFhPTXNEeU9oc0txQWlldFR2V3JNSFBVSWI4LUZueWUyM1o3WWZDekdKMDVzNzZtQXB6TkI3OFI0V3RMUE0xd2N2cnlvZVA5ZC03bkUzVzJJSzlhblJSYmFVZTNjT19ScUNGcko4X0w4OVJUTUIyRWpveFBQbE5GbFVYa0xvUTZoeXpTa3lQVzBvU2xsQS04dFUzQWhNb2UyejNIMVR5Mi1qSHJ1T21xb1lLWkk5czl6OVVrQVoweVdwZ0NFZEdxNkNOLURGRk85Z2ozUWVuZw</guid></item><item><title>神经病学家警告年轻的印度人有患帕金森病的风险，揭示了4个早期迹象： “呼吸困难的声音……” |健康-印度斯坦时报</title><link>https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/neurologist-warns-young-indians-are-at-risk-of-parkinsons-disease-reveals-4-early-signs-breathier-voice-101765117030994.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="detail " dataid="/lifestyle/health/neurologist-warns-young-indians-are-at-risk-of-parkinsons-disease-reveals-4-early-signs-breathier-voice-101765117030994.html"&gt; &lt;div class="storyParagraphFigure"&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/is-exercise-the-perfect-antidote-to-parkinsons-disease-neurologist-explains-shares-workout-routine-to-follow-101746198675428.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="Parkinson's disease"&gt;Parkinson's disease&lt;/a&gt; is often considered an illness of old age, but now early signs are seen even in young adults, in their 20s, 30s, and 40s. Before the condition fully develops, it gives off subtle clues that many overlook or dismiss as stress or &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/high-performers-at-workplace-suffer-fatigue-too-experts-describe-high-functioning-burnout-and-how-to-prevent-a-meltdown-101753868886055.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="burnout"&gt;burnout&lt;/a&gt;. These early symptoms are actually vital red flags and, when brought to medical attention on time, can make a vital difference in diagnosis and management.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;figure class=""&gt; &lt;span class=""&gt; &lt;picture&gt; &lt;source media="(max-width:767px)" srcset="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/12/07/550x309/27685_1765121326361_1765121333987.jpg" alt="Sudden soft or low voice is one of the signs seen in young adults. (Picture credit: Freepik)" title="Sudden soft or low voice is one of the signs seen in young adults. (Picture credit: Freepik)"&gt;&lt;/source&gt; &lt;img src="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/12/07/550x309/27685_1765121326361_1765121333987.jpg" alt="Sudden soft or low voice is one of the signs seen in young adults. (Picture credit: Freepik)" title="Sudden soft or low voice is one of the signs seen in young adults. (Picture credit: Freepik)"&gt; &lt;/picture&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;figcaption&gt;Sudden soft or low voice is one of the signs seen in young adults. (Picture credit: Freepik)&lt;/figcaption&gt; &lt;/figure&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;p id="readMoreFTUser"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="highlight"&gt;ALSO READ: &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/neurologist-shares-the-3s-that-silently-increase-your-stroke-risk-101761204984302.html#google_vignette" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="Neurologist shares the 3S that silently increase your stroke risk"&gt;Neurologist shares the 3S that silently increase your stroke risk&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="mt-10 mb-10 htEchoRecirculationWidget"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="mt10 mb10 htEchoArticlePromo"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="predictorShow mb20" data-vars-predictor="true" data-vars-quiz="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="quizShow mb20" data-vars-minimized="false" data-vars-predictor="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="highlight"&gt;To understand the early signs, HT Lifestyle reached out to Dr Sanjay Pandey, Professor and Head, Department of Neurology and Stroke Medicine at Amrita Hospital, Faridabad.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The condition is appearing in younger people alarmingly, and there's also a steady rise in cases. &lt;span class="highlight"&gt;Dr Pandey said, “India is projected to have the highest absolute number of Parkinson’s cases globally, and nearly 40 to 45 per cent of Indian patients develop motor symptoms between the ages of 22 and 49.&lt;/span&gt; This makes early-onset Parkinson’s Disease (EOPD) far more common than most people realise.”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;4 signs of early Parkinson's disease&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr Panday revealed that the early symptoms can be underestimated because they may overlap with the aftereffects of the stress. He also shared an example from his practice where the patient ignored all the early signs.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;“Interestingly, I recently treated a 38-year-old male who had all these symptoms. He brushed them off as routine stress, only to learn that he had young-onset Parkinson’s triggered by a genetic factor,” he said.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The neurologist listed out the 4 early signs seen in young adults:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. Small handwriting: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;A sudden and unexplained shrinking of handwriting size, known as micrographia, is one of the earliest red flags. People often blame stress or exhaustion, but it reflects reduced control of hand movement.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2. Trouble moving or walking: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;Slower walking, stiffness, dragging of one foot, or difficulty turning while walking are classic symptoms. These appear gradually and are often confused with muscle fatigue or lack of exercise.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;figure class="inlineIMG"&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;img data-src="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/12/07/original/1920_1765121533465.jpg" class="lazy" src="https://images.hindustantimes.com/default/550x309.jpg" alt="Stiffness in leg is one of the signs. (Picture credit: Freepik)" title="Stiffness in leg is one of the signs. (Picture credit: Freepik)"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;figcaption&gt;Stiffness in leg is one of the signs. (Picture credit: Freepik)&lt;/figcaption&gt; &lt;/figure&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3. A soft or low voice: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;A voice that becomes softer, breathier, or less expressive can be an early neurological sign. Most people think it is due to throat strain, but Parkinson’s can affect the muscles involved in speech.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;4. Tremor: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;A slight shaking in the hand or fingers at rest is a well-known symptom, yet many ignore it if it is mild or intermittent. Early tremor is often subtle but clinically significant.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;What you can do&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The neurologist emphasised acting promptly and getting regular check-ups, as ignoring subtle signs may lead to complications. He advised, “&lt;span&gt;I highly recommend regular neurological screenings, paying attention to persistent symptoms, maintaining physical activity, and seeking evaluation if you have a family history. This can help immensely with early detection. If you notice any of these signs, consult a doctor promptly rather than waiting for them to worsen.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Note to readers: This article is for informational purposes only and not a substitute for professional medical advice. Always seek the advice of your doctor with any questions about a medical condition.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Hindustan Times</author><pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 15:41:41 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiggJBVV95cUxPb3cyYnEtSkZidno4VlVNVjZqd2hKSHBoNk5hSG1PVzEyR2tVRDlRcWVoQXZxbGhWMUZjOFNTUElqZE9GR1llTHNCR2t1WUFfdkxyX243TXRnVDZqRXBzQmFEdGZWcjRwUjFwb1JOMlFhV3J5a2VkZEJaSnBDRm94T096RWtLOWdLQkxCLV9DMEpqMEFVQ3VJSTNFMF9QRU9sRmNfQVBMVW42b2FlNjVKdlJWMlpkSi1XdXkyRXVwR0NVWE5zVWduMW9yenp6NmQyWHlhRGpzZnRWd0JNMVI1dExnemU0dGRNMTNzamRmdkNKdjRSaDhkY2luZUQ0UDNnS0HSAYcCQVVfeXFMTm1Mb1p6ZzY2V0RhNmNrWTlVaGotalVQUHAySnVQWjY3TlJEeWphVE9aMjhuTERJbGFzR0VOUk9Gd2VFbVF0dWdSLTU4TUJISTZUU3dkSlV5LWl3bGlsY1BwZ1pWbHhDZUdwZXh6MW5pV09Dd1hZSXpoVHVHYU9zSUVUMHdXanp6cDdGcFdxYU4zN2VzR0l2cUxuVlNXV1NJbVdxWjhnQVJySnFZNDBpazQ1V04tTzNrVXJsei1HeXBQMXZ3RTlabDNVWXNKYnA0MnNtNU9rNHFQeFFjVXRJYnhVaGVGVEUxcVczX3ZRMEN2VmdEeldOaHdHeUZZOHRtLXNlOEhMdnM</guid></item><item><title>我们请3位营养学家说出最好的谷物品牌--他们都选择了同一个--非常简单</title><link>https://www.realsimple.com/nutritionists-name-healthiest-cereal-brand-11863168</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="realsimple-sc-page_1-0" class="comp realsimple-sc-page mntl-sc-page mntl-block structured-content" data-sc-sticky-offset="90" data-sc-ad-label-height="24" data-sc-ad-track-spacing="100" data-sc-min-track-height="250" data-sc-max-track-height="600" data-sc-breakpoint="50em" data-sc-load-immediate="4" data-sc-content-positions="[1, 1250, 1550, 1950, 2350, 2750, 3150, 3550, 3950]" data-bind-scroll-on-start="true"&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-block_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block realsimple-sc-block-callout--summary realsimple-sc-block-callout mntl-sc-block-universal-callout theme-summary" data-tracking-id="mntl-sc-block-callout" data-tracking-container="true"&gt; &lt;h3 class="mntl-sc-block-universal-callout__heading"&gt;Key Takeaways&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;div class="mntl-sc-block-universal-callout__body"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Most traditional cereals aren’t great for blood sugar or long-term health. Many popular cereals are ultra-processed, low in protein and fiber, and high in added sugars—leading to energy crashes, cravings, and increased risk of metabolic conditions like diabetes and heart disease.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Healthy cereals share specific nutrition criteria. Dietitians recommend choosing cereals with ≤5g added sugar, 5–8g protein, 3–5g fiber, whole-food ingredients, and minimal processing—plus healthy fats from nuts or seeds and whole grains listed first.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;All three nutritionists agree: Seven Sundays is the best healthy cereal brand. The brand stands out for real, nutrient-dense ingredients, balanced macros, low sugar, and satisfying flavors. Recommended varieties include Oat Protein Cereal, Blueberry Almond Real Food Cereal, and Classic Bircher Apple Cinnamon Muesli.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_2-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; If eating cereal brings you back to the simpler times of childhood, you’re not alone. The breakfast staple is nostalgic, delicious, and most of all—fun! However, if you want to get the most out of cereal, it’s worth being mindful of conventional versions.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_3-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_4-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; The reason? “Traditional cereals are often ultra-processed, low in &lt;a href="https://www.realsimple.com/best-sources-of-protein-8775868" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;protein&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.realsimple.com/dietitians-favorite-high-fiber-foods-11819806" link-destination-recommendation="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;fiber&lt;/a&gt;, and rely heavily on refined grains and added sugars,” explains registered dietitian Samantha Peterson, MS, RD. This combo can spike your blood sugar first thing in the morning (assuming you’re eating the cereal for breakfast), setting you up for an energy crash and more cravings later in the day, she notes.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_5-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_6-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Over time, the rapid rise and fall of blood sugar levels can lead to fatigue and hunger soon after meals, shares registered dietitian Seema Shah, MPH, MS, RD. They can also contribute to long-term health consequences, including prediabetes, type 2 diabetes, heart disease, and other cardiometabolic issues, Shah points out. Plus, “some traditional cereals contain artificial ingredients and additives, along with &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.realsimple.com/healthy-foods-high-in-sodium-7564072" link-destination-recommendation="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;surprisingly high sodium amounts&lt;/a&gt;, which are not great for our health,” Shah explains.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_7-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_8-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Now, there’s nothing wrong with occasionally enjoying your favorite “fun” cereal. But if you’d like to prioritize nutrition, you may want to eat healthier varieties more often. What do those cereals look like, exactly, and is there a brand that experts recommend? To find out, we asked dietitians to share the top features of a better-for-you cereal, along with their go-to brand.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_9-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="mntl-sc-block_10-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block realsimple-sc-block-callout--meetourexpert mntl-sc-block-universal-callout--meetourexpert mntl-sc-block-universal-callout theme-meetourexpert callout--bordered" data-text="Meet the Expert" data-tracking-id="mntl-sc-block-callout" data-tracking-container="true"&gt;
&lt;div class="mntl-sc-block-universal-callout__body"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://elladavar.com/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1" rel="nofollow"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ella Davar&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, RD, is a longevity dietitian and founder of the Gut-Brain Method&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://simplywellnessllc.com/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="2" rel="nofollow"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Samantha Peterson&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, MS, RD, is a registered dietitian and the founder of Simply Wellness&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://seemashahrd.com/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="3" rel="nofollow"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Seema Shah&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, MPH, MS, RD, is a registered dietitian and the owner of SeemaShahRD Whole Nutrition&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-what-to-look-for-when-buying-cereal"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_11-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block realsimple-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; What to Look for When Buying Cereal &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_12-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; When shopping for cereal with nutrition in mind, here’s what experts recommend looking for:
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_13-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_14-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block realsimple-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Added Sugar &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_15-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; This is a big one. Whereas traditional cereals tend to be higher in the added sugar department, healthier varieties are usually lower. Aim for a cereal with 5 grams (or less) of added sugar per serving, suggests longevity dietitian Ella Davar, RD. That’s because high sugar intake is the biggest driver of energy crashes, cravings, and poor metabolic health, Davar notes.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_16-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_17-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block realsimple-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Protein &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_18-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; “Choose cereals with at least 5 to 8 grams of &lt;a href="https://www.realsimple.com/how-much-protein-for-breakfast-8303189" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;protein&lt;/a&gt; [per serving] to help balance your morning and extend fullness,” Davar says.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_19-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_20-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block realsimple-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Fiber &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_21-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Look for a cereal with 3 to 5 grams of &lt;a href="https://www.realsimple.com/how-much-fiber-do-you-need-a-day-7564730" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;fiber&lt;/a&gt; per serving, suggests Davar. “Fiber supports gut health, satiety, and stable blood sugar,” she explains. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_22-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_23-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block realsimple-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Healthy Fats &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_24-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; If possible, Davar recommends picking a cereal with &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.realsimple.com/healthiest-nuts-to-eat-11686130" link-destination-recommendation="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;nuts&lt;/a&gt;, seeds, or coconut. These ingredients contain &lt;a href="https://www.realsimple.com/healthy-fats-8740244" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;healthy fats&lt;/a&gt;, which contribute to satiety and manage inflammation.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_25-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_26-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block realsimple-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Whole Ingredients &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_27-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; “Prioritize whole-food, minimally processed ingredients. Avoid artificial sweeteners, dyes, and preservatives,” Davar says. According to Shah, whole grains should be the first ingredient on the label.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_28-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_29-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block realsimple-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Serving Size &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_30-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; “The serving size listed on the &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.realsimple.com/red-flags-on-food-labels-8781749" link-destination-recommendation="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;nutrition label&lt;/a&gt; can sometimes be smaller than what you consume,” Shah says. Thus, she suggests converting the nutritional facts to the amount that you’re actually eating.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_31-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_32-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Finally, if you have a GI condition, look for a &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.realsimple.com/food-recipes/recipe-collections-favorites/desserts/gluten-free-desserts-0" link-destination-recommendation="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;gluten-free&lt;/a&gt; or grain-free variety. “Many people with digestive issues do better with oat-, nut-, or seed-based blends,” explains Davar.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_33-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_35-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_37-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-what-is-the-healthiest-cereal-brand"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_38-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block realsimple-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; What Is the Healthiest Cereal Brand? &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_39-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; The next time you shop for cereal, consider the factors listed above. Alternatively, if you’d rather get an expert recommendation, you’re in luck: When asked to name their favorite healthy cereal brands, all three dietitians called out &lt;strong&gt;Seven Sundays&lt;/strong&gt;.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_40-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_41-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; “Seven Sundays stands out because it focuses on real, nutrient-dense ingredients rather than the ultra-processed grains and additives common in traditional breakfast cereals,” Davar explains. “Seven Sundays is much closer to a functional food than a conventional boxed cereal,” she adds.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_42-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure id="mntl-sc-block_43-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block realsimple-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image--no-theme no-theme figure-square figure-high-res"&gt; 
&lt;figcaption id="mntl-figure-caption_1-0" class="comp mntl-figure-caption text-utility-100 figure-article-caption"&gt; &lt;span class="figure-article-caption-owner"&gt;Credit: &lt;p&gt;Seven Sundays&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_44-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; More specifically, the brand does an excellent job balancing protein, healthy fats, and fiber, something you rarely see in the cereal aisle, Peterson notes. This combo is “genuinely supportive of &lt;a href="https://www.realsimple.com/habits-for-healthy-metabolism-11799741" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;metabolism&lt;/a&gt;, hormone health, and &lt;a href="https://www.realsimple.com/most-satiating-foods-8424198" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;lasting fullness&lt;/a&gt; in a way that fits real life,” Peterson adds. Plus, Seven Sundays products are not only nutritious and well-balanced, but delicious too, per Shah.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_45-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_46-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; If you’re new to Seven Sundays, here’s a specific recommendation from each dietitian:
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_47-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_48-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Seven Sundays Oat Protein Cereal:&lt;/strong&gt; “This cereal uses &lt;a href="https://www.realsimple.com/health/nutrition-diet/benefits-of-oatmeal" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;oats&lt;/a&gt; as the star ingredient, delivering a naturally high-fiber, whole-grain base with added oat protein to make it more filling than traditional cereals,” explains Peterson. Plus, unlike most cereals, it has a short recognizable ingredient list, low added sugar, and balanced macros that keep you satisfied, Peterson adds.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Seven Sundays Blueberry Almond Real Food Cereal: &lt;/strong&gt;Featuring whole almonds, &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.realsimple.com/food-recipes/recipe-collections-favorites/popular-ingredients/benefits-of-blueberries" link-destination-recommendation="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;blueberries&lt;/a&gt;, and oat clusters, this cereal is high in fiber and naturally sweetened, according to Davar. It also offers a great balance of carbs, fat, and protein, a combo that can keep blood sugar stable, she adds.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Seven Sundays Classic Bircher Apple Cinnamon Muesli:&lt;/strong&gt; With gluten-free oats listed as the first ingredient, this cereal is appropriate for gluten-free diets. It’s also high in fiber and protein and low in total sugars. This makes it a “nourishing and tasty option for breakfast that will give you sustained energy and balanced blood sugar levels throughout the morning,” explains Shah.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_49-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_50-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Remember: You don’t need to give up your favorite childhood cereals to be healthy. Instead, enjoy them as the occasional treat, and focus on healthier versions (like those from Seven Sundays) for your daily bowl.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Real Simple</author><pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 15:01:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihAFBVV95cUxQZ1ZVVk9hUjRweE51UGFjVG5hblFOcW80VWdCZDg4VWFXeDJmT3N5UFYxMmd4UXJfSE01bEcwZjlTMkN5STRsZEE2Z0hRYlpha1loWWExYTNXaGUzWEZVc1ZIdDJ6ZDFZN3N4cjk5dHpLVEhMOXg4OU9yODFOS29raDBEd2g</guid></item><item><title>​结直肠外科医生分享了她避免降低结肠癌风险的5件事-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/colorectal-surgeon-shares-5-things-she-avoids-to-lower-colon-cancer-risk/photostory/125817504.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="COQxt" data-ua-type="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Ultra processed foods” refers to industrially manufactured foods that go far beyond traditional cooking. These typically contain many ingredients,  preservatives, emulsifiers, flavorings, artificial additives etc. They are often ready-to-eat or ready-to-heat, highly processed, and low in dietary fiber. As per Dr. Karen, even baked goods and snacks are dangerous. &lt;br&gt;A 2025 &lt;a href="https://www.massgeneralbrigham.org/en/about/newsroom/press-releases/ultra-processed-foods-early-onset-colorectal-cancer-study"&gt;study &lt;/a&gt;of nearly 30,000 women under age 50  found that participants with the highest intake of Ultraprocessed foods had around  45% higher risk of developing adenomas, compared with those with the lowest intake. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Times of India</author><pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 13:57:56 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigAJBVV95cUxPZ281eV9WX21IWlUyOURIb2JBXzJKTXhIMFN3bEpqSzNGVHNQaWNrR3dsN2NMdmhXcy1YbTNVZ1hZSmJKZUpSWUFrOXJzREF5NjNlTlZJZ3dOay05bmRES3RYMy1jMlcyX3pJb0UwZ3pZMGFCX2JURHRHZVl0Z3E0YWptcUZPaHpBdWh3RDNPUjBiYTlJVHVoQ1ZpaFl6bXdPOTg0SFdFRjVBRi1zWVJkY1hlSHAzLWFpRXFUcFNLQk5DdEhxZ3VrX3o3UkhTNWtFUlc5MENiV09IQ1QtUG5mR3FDOTJnZ0hoOW9pajV1SUdsWXN2clYyc082WWhSTkQx0gGIAkFVX3lxTE5WdG45UzhWVlBQTjk4cXVvSzRBcXNUS2FIemFqelItTVVlT0s0ZjhNZXhIOE5OallIMndQakFKWDBDMVAweVRpRmtSbFl4ai1rRGpvOW9ISGtCVjBWbGdwdTdtWUJnVmJTTUZlOGRLMEJRSUFIT2ZGanZlZVhncWRwbHhnY3R5SU90Y1BSM3JOZnJlLURKeGh3ZzhNOEpLRFhBeHIyTU44bU0zTVBrV2x4cHQ5a0paczFkOHJDMS1RM1Z2aWlfcGtSUklqMk44OXlsd0w2MS1INDJHdVkwUE9ScFlvb3h5cjU1dkxodUJwT1pQc0NfaEdJWEt1MXhFZVlBc1E3akpTSA</guid></item><item><title>减肥刺拳可能会使身体老化十年，并增加虚弱和跌倒的风险-每日邮报在线</title><link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-15361247/Weight-loss-jabs-age-body-decade-increase-risk-frailty-falls.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;
    &lt;div class="message-box"&gt;
        &lt;h2&gt;Associated Newspapers Ltd&lt;/h2&gt;
        &lt;h3&gt;Access Restricted&lt;/h3&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;
Thank you for your interest. Unauthorised access is prohibited. 
To access this content, you must have prior permission and a valid contract. 
Please contact our team at 
&lt;a href="mailto:partnerships@dmgmedia.co.uk"&gt;partnerships@dmgmedia.co.uk&lt;/a&gt; 
 to discuss licensing options.
 &lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; If you are a registered user, please contact &lt;a href="mailto:websupport@dmgmedia.co.uk"&gt;websupport@dmgmedia.co.uk&lt;/a&gt; , quoting the reference code on this page.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Reference ID: 0.ad423917.1765117855.676996d4&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/body&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Daily Mail Online</author><pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 13:28:39 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMitgFBVV95cUxNNWVmZDlVWXEycVMyaG1EXzFQSUtOdEx6bHVmTGoxTjhZT19Nb0otZFBLZkUzSDhaSllVSlFadTQ5c0VodHAzZ0tPS2IwRERZVmV3bDN4REhMTXJsYm13bXBLMVg0VDd3WFlWU2VkdkQyallqbUdzelYtWk9iWFdXUW5EWkgycWgtRzJRUkRMbXAxcUhGc0FhVW9KNkg1YTdHXzZLMHZhbWZJODV6WmtPQW5jTUpEQdIBuwFBVV95cUxObDdrWHd4VEVHTmNXQ2lfZjMwR2xpVlc5U29kcm5fbjZPX1VqSE9xTmVDYS1PcUFKX05BNFoyODJOUEVQcW1EN2l0dlNkNGdtc24xZno0bEpKREZYMmp0NUFVM3RfVExYNnROeEsxT1NYVk5NdGZZa195Vy00dmluX1dvNFBmVDhtVkJTRG5rSTZoTFJlbWdiNDZWUGFOcjBLdDU4TUdnYVY4dEluX0o0UVozam5OU1JJWFpz</guid></item><item><title>美味食物如何降低血压-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/hypertension-foods-can-lower-high-blood-pressure/articleshow/125816095.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;div class="MwN2O"&gt;&lt;div class="vdo_embedd"&gt; &lt;div class="T22zO"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nearly half of Americans have hypertension, according to the US FDA’s data from 2024. This means more than &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.fda.gov/drugs/special-features/high-blood-pressure-understanding-silent-killer" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;119 million US adults&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; are struggling with high blood pressure, according to the US Food &amp;amp; Drug Administration. What’s more shocking is that only one in four of them has this condition under control. Far worse, many are even unaware that they have hypertension, which is exactly why it is called a silent killer. Hypertension can &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.who.int/health-topics/hypertension#tab=tab_1" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;increase the risk of heart,&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; brain, kidney, and other chronic diseases, according to the WHO. This is why keeping blood pressure in check is crucial.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="8"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; What if you could lower blood pressure naturally? How? By eating the right foods. A recent study from the University of Surrey, published in the &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="em" data-ua-type="1"&gt;European Journal of Preventive Cardiology&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;, found that &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://academic.oup.com/eurjpc/article-abstract/32/14/1322/8092214?redirectedFrom=fulltext" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;foods rich in flavan-3-ols&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; can significantly lower blood pressure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="16"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="lOvcW vdo_embedd"&gt;&lt;div class="k7lcu"&gt;&lt;p class="efT4r"&gt;5 Basic yoga poses that bring down BP naturally&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="18"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="20"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;How flavan-3-ols help to lower blood pressure&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; You may have a new reason to enjoy your daily cup of tea or a small piece of dark chocolate. A new study found that naturally occurring compounds called flavan-3-ols, found in cocoa, tea, apples, and grapes, may improve blood pressure and the health of your blood vessels.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="22"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; The researchers analysed data from 145 randomised controlled studies to understand the impact of flavan-3-ols on blood pressure. They found that consumption of foods rich in these specific flavanols can lead to a reduction in blood pressure readings, especially in people with elevated or high blood pressure. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In fact, in some cases, the researchers even observed that the average blood pressure-lowering effects were comparable to those seen with some medications.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="26"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; These flavan-3-ols improved the function of the endothelium, the inner lining of blood vessels, which is crucial for overall cardiovascular health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="28"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="30"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;How to eat your way to normal blood pressure&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; For people who are struggling with high blood pressure, incorporating flavanol-rich foods into the diet, along with medications, can significantly improve the condition. “The findings are encouraging for those looking for accessible ways to manage their blood pressure and support their heart health through enjoyable dietary changes. Incorporating small amounts of commonly consumed foods like tea, apples, dark chocolate, or cocoa powder into a daily balanced diet could provide beneficial amounts of flavan-3-ols,” Professor Christian Heiss, lead author of the study and Professor of Cardiovascular Medicine at the University of Surrey, said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="35"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; “While not a replacement for prescribed medications or medical advice, including more flavan-3-ol-rich foods in a daily routine could be a valuable addition to a healthy lifestyle, especially for those with higher blood pressure. These are findings that, although promising, require ongoing investigation,” Heiss added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="37"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong em" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Note:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="em" data-ua-type="1"&gt; The information provided in this article is for educational purposes only and is not intended as medical advice. Always consult a qualified healthcare professional before starting any new medication or treatment, or before changing your diet or supplement regimen&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="40"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 12:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi4gFBVV95cUxOSllFMjhoclp4Y2Y3OEQ4V0NaZXVoLUF0RVZBNDB0UGZRYjg2Z3VTS0tHUHhHN0dLZzAzQTZ0b0RReFlxVGFsMm0yRG91aE5zSkFCWUl0cHNwV2FHZDVZYjJBRzh6b2VCTHc5QnFZXzdEQlpmVDVOeUU1R3cxSDZsTDBUaExGY1NlRmNGekxIWTBoU0RiOXNoQ200SmZLeEdua1pNd0xINzVOeHB2eWhOdVd5Ty1NaXFlaVRtcEM0dWdpa2FYaUZ5NVNXeFVuWnJwQ3UyaFNwWnNVRHJhd3JUQVl3</guid></item><item><title>原料amla vs amla果汁：哪种更健康-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/diet/raw-amla-vs-amla-juice-which-is-healthier/photostory/125816694.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="COQxt" data-ua-type="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Both raw amla and amla juice deliver valuable health benefits, but raw amla emerges as the healthier choice for regular, long-term consumption. Eating amla in its whole form preserves its full nutrient profile, including dietary fibre, which supports digestion, gut health, and better metabolic control. The fibre-rich structure of raw amla allows for the gradual release of vitamin C and antioxidants, potentially offering more sustained protection against oxidative stress and metabolic disturbances.&lt;br&gt;So, from an evidence-based nutrition perspective, raw amla offers greater nutrient stability and long-term advantages, while amla juice works best as an occasional or supplementary option. &lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Times of India</author><pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 12:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMizgFBVV95cUxQS2pLaGNpemQ5UU5WWVZCMFpZY1gzeURVNWkwek5aVlZYR25oTlhJRk5qQUFsOXdIbTBjYk53V0NZa2FzbUY1eXNCYnpmWm8tZFY5RElDaGhTRE1RdENtMjBmbTF3OFhPTlZ6dHhuQXNIOHYzb1FWZWpQV3pfYm9GdlEwRVUwaG5jcndhdTJjZ1BHUXJUeDZkSzBMeml2SjdzeWhyMW5FVHpnemJtU2xWWE53MjZyZlUzQ2tJY2ZtbWVFNG9VQWo4bmFSMUN5Z9IB1gFBVV95cUxNTXM3d3ltS0ZOYmF4dmFOTm1MNERvSWQtTGRVOUppTHRtd0R0RFgxTjk5Ym1hRWZnTU9Xejh2ejlwLXdaZTdtVjBSN2dqYUJhdDFqU2RuUU8zNEN0djJ2Q1dLc0p3OFFlbDdWTWlvSWF4d09aZ1hlOUlDNDBGLTE1R3RjMnk1ODRLc2NTclVUbU9BTWNUZkdOaGtqbVQ5Rm1PX2RLcld4ZDhHTlFkVG5NTEttaVpLSTl5YzhRMWJzbF9iS0owVjVybEMzZ0pSM051LWNCWlBn</guid></item><item><title>还在每天早上整理床铺吗？你可能应该停止……这是一个可能会适得其反的习惯--《银河日报》</title><link>https://dailygalaxy.com/2025/12/daily-bed-making-habit-linked-to-allergies-and-asthma/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content dynamic-entry-content" itemprop="text"&gt;
			
&lt;p&gt;Every morning, it happens without question. Duvets are pulled tight. Pillows are fluffed. &lt;strong&gt;The bed&lt;/strong&gt;, now perfect, marks the transition from rest to productivity. For generations, this ritual has been seen as a cornerstone of discipline—an act of daily order in an otherwise unpredictable world.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Across cultures, “&lt;strong&gt;making the bed&lt;/strong&gt;” is promoted not just as a chore, but as a small win, a psychological anchor. Military routines, parenting blogs, and productivity books all hail it as a symbol of self-control and success. But what if this common act is masking an overlooked problem—one that’s quietly affecting millions?&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;div class="wp-block-image"&gt;
&lt;figure class="aligncenter size-full"&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" decoding="async" src="https://dailygalaxy.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Unmade-bed-in-morning-light-with-rumpled-sheets-and-open-window-in-a-sunlit-bedroom.jpg.webp" alt="Unmade bed in morning light with rumpled sheets and open window in a sunlit bedroom" class="wp-image-112241" srcset="https://dailygalaxy.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Unmade-bed-in-morning-light-with-rumpled-sheets-and-open-window-in-a-sunlit-bedroom.jpg.webp 1000w,https://dailygalaxy.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Unmade-bed-in-morning-light-with-rumpled-sheets-and-open-window-in-a-sunlit-bedroom-420x280.jpg.webp 420w,https://dailygalaxy.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Unmade-bed-in-morning-light-with-rumpled-sheets-and-open-window-in-a-sunlit-bedroom-520x347.jpg.webp 520w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="wp-element-caption"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Leaving your bed unmade for a few hours allows moisture to evaporate, disrupting the dust mites’ ideal environment&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;. Credit: Shutterstock&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;


&lt;p&gt;In recent years, indoor air quality and respiratory health have become urgent public concerns. Conditions like &lt;strong&gt;asthma&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;allergic rhinitis&lt;/strong&gt;, and &lt;strong&gt;chronic sinusitis&lt;/strong&gt; are now closely linked to the quality of the air inside homes—especially bedrooms. And that’s where the story of the made bed takes a surprising turn.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;The Unseen Consequences of a Tidy Bed&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;In a landmark study from &lt;em&gt;Kingston University&lt;/em&gt; in the UK, researchers found that &lt;strong&gt;leaving your bed unmade during the day could reduce the population of dust mites living in your bedding&lt;/strong&gt;. Led by environmental building scientist &lt;strong&gt;Dr. Stephen Pretlove&lt;/strong&gt;, the team investigated how these microscopic organisms respond to changes in heat and humidity trapped inside the bed.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The conclusion was striking. A made bed traps &lt;strong&gt;moisture and warmth&lt;/strong&gt; from the night’s sleep—conditions that &lt;strong&gt;dust mites&lt;/strong&gt;, which feed on dead skin cells, need to thrive. When the bed is left open and exposed to circulating air, those conditions evaporate. This &lt;strong&gt;disrupts the mites’ habitat&lt;/strong&gt;, making it harder for them to survive.&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;div class="wp-block-image"&gt;
&lt;figure class="aligncenter size-full"&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" decoding="async" src="https://dailygalaxy.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Magnified-microscopic-view-of-dust-mites-on-fabric-fibers.jpg.webp" alt="Dust,mite,under,the,light,microscope,view." class="wp-image-112243" srcset="https://dailygalaxy.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Magnified-microscopic-view-of-dust-mites-on-fabric-fibers.jpg.webp 1000w,https://dailygalaxy.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Magnified-microscopic-view-of-dust-mites-on-fabric-fibers-420x280.jpg.webp 420w,https://dailygalaxy.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Magnified-microscopic-view-of-dust-mites-on-fabric-fibers-520x347.jpg.webp 520w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="wp-element-caption"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Up to 1.5 million dust mites can live in a single bed, feeding on dead skin and thriving in warm, humid conditions. Credit: Shutterstock&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;


&lt;p&gt;“Something as simple as leaving a bed unmade during the day can remove moisture from the sheets and mattress,” Dr. Pretlove explained in &lt;a href="https://www.kingston.ac.uk/about/news/messy-bedroom-could-spell-end-for-creepy-crawlies" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Kingston University’s release&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Why does this matter? Dust mites are one of the most common sources of &lt;strong&gt;indoor allergens&lt;/strong&gt; worldwide. Their waste particles can trigger a range of reactions, from mild sneezing and nasal irritation to more serious respiratory problems like &lt;strong&gt;asthma&lt;/strong&gt;. The &lt;em&gt;American Lung Association&lt;/em&gt; highlights &lt;strong&gt;bedding and pillows&lt;/strong&gt; as the most concentrated reservoirs of dust mite allergens in the home.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;An estimated &lt;strong&gt;1.5 million mites&lt;/strong&gt; can live in the average bed. Their presence is invisible—but the effects often aren’t. By simply giving your bed time to dry out naturally, you may be taking a meaningful step toward &lt;strong&gt;reducing allergy triggers&lt;/strong&gt; in your home.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;A Warmer Bed, a Bigger Problem&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Most people associate a tidy bed with cleanliness, but in reality, &lt;strong&gt;a freshly made bed may seal in moisture&lt;/strong&gt; from overnight perspiration. The typical adult loses about a liter of fluid each night through sweat and respiration. Combine that with thick comforters, insulated bedrooms, and limited morning ventilation, and the bed becomes a microclimate tailor-made for mite colonies.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Colder months make things worse. Heating systems dry out the ambient air while homeowners keep windows closed, limiting natural airflow. In this environment, &lt;strong&gt;moisture trapped in bedding has nowhere to escape&lt;/strong&gt;, allowing mites to feed, reproduce, and expand their reach.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Health agencies including the &lt;em&gt;Centers for Disease Control and Prevention (CDC)&lt;/em&gt; recommend reducing indoor humidity and increasing airflow to help control allergen levels. Yet few guidelines consider how something as basic as bed-making affects these dynamics.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;For households with children, seniors, or anyone with &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://dailygalaxy.com/2024/11/yellow-stains-pillows-alarming-signs-their-hidden-meanings-bed/" target="_blank" data-type="post" data-id="72006" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;allergic asthma&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;, reconsidering how—and when—you make the bed could be a low-cost way to improve &lt;strong&gt;bedroom air quality&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Airing It Out&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Rather than abandoning the idea of a &lt;strong&gt;clean bed&lt;/strong&gt;, researchers suggest a &lt;strong&gt;strategic delay&lt;/strong&gt;. Instead of making the bed right after waking up, allow the bedding to remain open for several hours to promote &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://dailygalaxy.com/2025/11/an-event-so-extreme-it-erased-a-sea-new-evidence-reveals-what-happened-6-2-million-years-ago/" target="_blank" data-type="post" data-id="109281" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;evaporation&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;. Pull back the duvet. Crack a window. Let the mattress and sheets breathe.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;This doesn’t replace good hygiene. Washing bedding every one to two weeks in hot water, vacuuming the mattress, and using &lt;strong&gt;dust-mite-proof pillow covers&lt;/strong&gt; are still essential. But making the bed later in the day—or even just airing it out first—can tip the balance against an invisible indoor threat.&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;div class="wp-block-image"&gt;
&lt;figure class="aligncenter size-full"&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" decoding="async" src="https://dailygalaxy.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Well-ventilated-bedroom-with-open-windows-and-sunlight-over-loosely-arranged-bedding.jpg.webp" alt="Breeze,blowing,through,open,window,in,cozy,bedroom" class="wp-image-112244" srcset="https://dailygalaxy.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Well-ventilated-bedroom-with-open-windows-and-sunlight-over-loosely-arranged-bedding.jpg.webp 1000w,https://dailygalaxy.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Well-ventilated-bedroom-with-open-windows-and-sunlight-over-loosely-arranged-bedding-420x280.jpg.webp 420w,https://dailygalaxy.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Well-ventilated-bedroom-with-open-windows-and-sunlight-over-loosely-arranged-bedding-520x347.jpg.webp 520w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="wp-element-caption"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Simple ventilation—like pulling back the covers and opening a window—can significantly reduce indoor allergens. Credit: Shutterstock&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;


&lt;p&gt;These changes are especially relevant for allergy sufferers. Data from the &lt;em&gt;National Institute of Allergy and Infectious Diseases&lt;/em&gt; indicates that &lt;strong&gt;10–20% of the population&lt;/strong&gt; is sensitive to dust mite allergens, and symptoms often peak after prolonged exposure in poorly ventilated bedrooms.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;In homes where people now work, rest, and sleep in the same room more than ever before, these small shifts matter. They’re not about rejecting routine—but about adapting it to reflect what we now know about the spaces we inhabit.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;

				&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Daily Galaxy</author><pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 12:15:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijwFBVV95cUxQaGlqRmF6LS1LRTNfaWFpel9CLUpUeE5XSXJzN3FqaTl5Ym45Y3NDWjFGcjc1NFdEbmZOTTdBOEMzWFpobjg3YVJmaGxCM2s2V0ZKaXQ3RHliQUtpelNCYlZXRWpTVW5sOHJRN1M2NXNLT0haSFFNSGVxZl9sR3pGTGxwNlF1MFIwSnR2cDhTTQ</guid></item><item><title>潜伏在污水中的未来抗菌素耐药性的严峻信号- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/grim-signals-of-future-antimicrobial-resistance-found-lurking-in-sewage</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Dangerous bacteria and other disease-causing microbes are rapidly evolving ways to defy our best antibiotic medications, a phenomenon known as antimicrobial resistance. Humans are inadvertently contributing by overexposing pathogens to our limited defenses.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;With drug-resistant bacteria already killing &lt;a href="https://www.thelancet.com/journals/lancet/article/PIIS0140-6736(24)01867-1/fulltext"&gt;more than 1 million people a year&lt;/a&gt;, researchers are seeking clues about the future of these superbugs by examining the world's wastewater.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A new study by an international team of researchers has found that latent antimicrobial resistance is more common than we realised.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/study-reveals-alarming-rise-of-superbugs-in-newborn-babies"&gt;Study Reveals 'Alarming' Rise of Superbugs in Newborn Babies&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The scientists hunted for clues in wastewater from around the world, sifting through 1,240 sewage samples from 351 cities across 111 countries in search of the &lt;a href="https://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/jobm.202100201"&gt;antimicrobial resistance genes&lt;/a&gt; (ARGs) that grant microbes protection against our life-saving medications.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aside from known ARGs, the researchers used a process known as functional metagenomics to scour their samples for latent genes, or genetic variations that exist within an organism's DNA but are not actively expressed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Latent genes can become active under certain circumstances, which means latent ARGs might play important roles in the poorly understood evolution of drug-resistant 'superbugs.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_184430" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-184430" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/12/redpills_antibiotics_superbugs_642.jpg" alt="antibiotics" class="wp-image-184430 size-full" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/12/redpills_antibiotics_superbugs_642.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/12/redpills_antibiotics_superbugs_642-600x421.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-184430" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Latent genes in the environment may give infecting bacteria a way to resist antibiotic treatment. (&lt;a href="https://www.canva.com/photos/MAD0CUkOF5I/"&gt;Olesya22/Getty Images/Canva&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;The new study suggests latent ARGs are &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/antibiotic-resistance-can-emerge-in-your-gut-even-without-antibiotics-use"&gt;abundant nearly everywhere&lt;/a&gt;, forming a &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/antibiotic-resistance-genes-can-travel-through-the-air-and-we-re-slightly-terrified"&gt;hidden global library&lt;/a&gt; of latent antimicrobial resistance. This latent resistance is apparently even more prevalent than the known resistance conferred by already active, or acquired, genes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The research shows that we have a latent reservoir of antimicrobial resistance that is far more widespread around the world than we had expected," &lt;a href="https://www.eurekalert.org/news-releases/1107666"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; first author Hannah-Marie Martiny, a bioinformatician at the Technical University of Denmark (DTU). &lt;span&gt;This may be because selection and competition seem to play a larger role in the development of these resistance genes than dispersal, the researchers found.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One noteworthy takeaway from this discovery is the need for more proactive wastewater surveillance, says co-first author Patrick Munk, an associate professor with the DTU National Food Institute.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"To curb future antimicrobial resistance, we believe that routine surveillance of antimicrobial resistance in wastewater, in addition to including already acquired resistance genes, should also encompass latent resistance genes, in order to account for tomorrow's problems as well," Munk &lt;a href="https://www.eurekalert.org/news-releases/1107666"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Researchers often focus on ARGs that can be transferred among species of microbes, since these acquired ARGs already pose a threat to public health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/newsletter?utm_source=promo_generic_health"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-642x273.jpg" alt="Subscribe to ScienceAlert's free fact-checked newsletter" class="alignnone wp-image-182810 size-medium" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-642x273.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-768x326.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-600x255.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final.jpg 850w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If we broaden our surveillance of sewage, however, we might learn valuable secrets from latent ARGs, possibly helping researchers demystify the origins of antimicrobial resistance (AMR) or &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/researchers-trace-the-genes-for-antibiotic-resistance-back-to-their-source"&gt;map the ecology of the genes&lt;/a&gt; involved.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"By tracking both acquired and latent antimicrobial resistance genes, we can gain a broad overview of how they develop, change hosts, and spread in our environment, and thereby better target efforts against antimicrobial resistance," Martiny &lt;a href="https://www.eurekalert.org/news-releases/1107666"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Wastewater is a practical and ethical way to monitor AMR," she &lt;a href="https://www.eurekalert.org/news-releases/1107666"&gt;adds&lt;/a&gt;, "because it aggregates waste from humans, animals, and the immediate surroundings."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most of these genes may not endanger public health right now, the researchers note, but some of them probably will in the future.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"In general, I don't think we need to be too worried about most latent antimicrobial resistance genes, but I do believe that some of them will eventually cause problems, and we would like to know which ones," Martiny &lt;a href="https://www.eurekalert.org/news-releases/1107666"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That kind of knowledge could help us predict which microbes in the future might be vulnerable to which antimicrobial treatments.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"When new antibiotics are developed – a process that takes many years – bacteria may already have invented new 'scissors' capable of destroying them," Munk &lt;a href="https://www.eurekalert.org/news-releases/1107666"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"If we can study both types of genes over time," he &lt;a href="https://www.eurekalert.org/news-releases/1107666"&gt;adds&lt;/a&gt;, "we may be able to find out which of the latent genes become problematic resistance genes, how they arise, and how they spread across geography and bacteria, and in that way lessen the burden of antimicrobial resistance."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study was published in &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41467-025-66070-7"&gt;Nature Communications&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 12:02:18 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiogFBVV95cUxOMGh6alYwRF9QSzdHR3kwaXlUTVFEcGZpUGhkQmthMFg3Nm1jOGt3Zk54WUNQT0wyeTNnVjJOZno4dlhKRGNIdlM3MV81bzFiZEhmR09VMzVKUXNIV2pYZXdCTHdrSWNVT2F5ZVVqMVNtenViMkhKM1F4eUxMUDdWNm1yV3l4akhKWDBkTG10U1VmV210TllQN21GQS1Jc0hzeEE</guid></item><item><title>行业和官员表示，乙型肝炎疫苗的保险范围不会改变- CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2025/12/07/health/hepatitis-b-vaccine-insurance-coverage</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article__content" data-editable="content" itemprop="articleBody" data-reorderable="content"&gt;
                
    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmit92yov0002356nzsrwf9e8@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Parents will still be able to get the &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/health/live-news/cdc-vaccine-meeting-hepatitis-b-12-05-25"&gt;hepatitis B vaccine&lt;/a&gt; for their children at no cost even though the US Centers for Disease and Control Prevention’s vaccine advisers recommended a major change to the immunization practice.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmit91wid0000356nplwgs1i8@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The CDC’s Advisory Committee on Immunization Practices, whose members were chosen by US Health and Human Services Secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr., voted Friday to end universal hepatitis B vaccination recommendations for newborns.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmit9a4l8000f356nv7rcbzrv@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The revised recommendation calls for mothers who test negative for the virus to consult with a doctor or other health care provider before having their babies vaccinated. This could create confusion and place additional hurdles in front of parents and result in fewer children being immunized.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmit9ctxj000l356nh6f67o8v@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The advisers also voted in favor of recommending that babies who don’t receive a dose at birth should wait at least two months before being immunized.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmit92yov0003356nqh0tg1ue@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Two major health insurance industry groups, the Blue Cross Blue Shield Association and AHIP, reiterated Thursday that they will continue to cover all vaccines recommended by the committee as of earlier this year, with no cost-sharing, through 2026.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmit92yov0004356n84bc98b3@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            BCBS companies will cover all immunizations recommended by ACIP as of January 1, 2025, while operating within federal and state laws and meeting program and customer requirements, a spokesperson told CNN. AHIP members will do so for all vaccines recommended by ACIP as of September 1, 2025, a spokesperson said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmit92yov0005356nc3b10dfl@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Both groups released these &lt;a href="https://nam11.safelinks.protection.outlook.com/?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.cnn.com%2F2025%2F10%2F07%2Fhealth%2Fcovid-19-vaccine-free-health-insurance&amp;amp;data=05%7C02%7CTami.Luhby%40cnn.com%7C1d2d2b3566ab4484afce08de336a415f%7C0eb48825e8714459bc72d0ecd68f1f39%7C0%7C0%7C639004728613843954%7CUnknown%7CTWFpbGZsb3d8eyJFbXB0eU1hcGkiOnRydWUsIlYiOiIwLjAuMDAwMCIsIlAiOiJXaW4zMiIsIkFOIjoiTWFpbCIsIldUIjoyfQ%3D%3D%7C0%7C%7C%7C&amp;amp;sdata=21uN25sTPL2BFJ%2FiUDoZJgkPO3Z8CcjCIWpoL7E8Kag%3D&amp;amp;reserved=0" target="_blank"&gt;statements&lt;/a&gt; earlier in the fall, before ACIP announced changes to recommendations for the &lt;a href="https://nam11.safelinks.protection.outlook.com/?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.cnn.com%2F2025%2F09%2F19%2Fhealth%2Fcdc-acip-hepatitis-mmrv-covid-vaccine&amp;amp;data=05%7C02%7CTami.Luhby%40cnn.com%7C1d2d2b3566ab4484afce08de336a415f%7C0eb48825e8714459bc72d0ecd68f1f39%7C0%7C0%7C639004728613861325%7CUnknown%7CTWFpbGZsb3d8eyJFbXB0eU1hcGkiOnRydWUsIlYiOiIwLjAuMDAwMCIsIlAiOiJXaW4zMiIsIkFOIjoiTWFpbCIsIldUIjoyfQ%3D%3D%7C0%7C%7C%7C&amp;amp;sdata=%2FxcYYsHhqNUbtxFMI0O%2B7ESjWOEIFdVhJweXv%2BLf%2BCM%3D&amp;amp;reserved=0" target="_blank"&gt;Covid-19 vaccine&lt;/a&gt; and the &lt;a href="https://nam11.safelinks.protection.outlook.com/?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.cnn.com%2F2025%2F09%2F18%2Fhealth%2Fcdc-vaccine-panel-acip-mmrv-hepatitis&amp;amp;data=05%7C02%7CTami.Luhby%40cnn.com%7C1d2d2b3566ab4484afce08de336a415f%7C0eb48825e8714459bc72d0ecd68f1f39%7C0%7C0%7C639004728613877970%7CUnknown%7CTWFpbGZsb3d8eyJFbXB0eU1hcGkiOnRydWUsIlYiOiIwLjAuMDAwMCIsIlAiOiJXaW4zMiIsIkFOIjoiTWFpbCIsIldUIjoyfQ%3D%3D%7C0%7C%7C%7C&amp;amp;sdata=rrk2E7p3mms5A6xC%2FYIxUVhRPHlUyGMnLvaLHPz%2BQ6k%3D&amp;amp;reserved=0" target="_blank"&gt;combined measles, mumps, rubella and varicella (MMRV) vaccine&lt;/a&gt;.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmit9ct09000i356n0zwbq2so@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The CDC committee members recommended in September that patients consult with a health care provider for a Covid-19 vaccine, a process known as shared clinical decision-making, but do not need to have a prescription. And the members voted to recommend against using the combined MMRV vaccine for young children.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmita5j5w0015356nt0nt35dg@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The change to requiring a consultation with a doctor has raised concerns that insurers would no longer be required to cover the full cost of the immunization. The Affordable Care Act mandates that most private insurers cover vaccines recommended by ACIP at no cost, and Medicaid’s no-cost coverage of vaccines is tied to the committee’s recommendations.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmita8jnm001c356ng05pizbz@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The shift to shared clinical decision-making will not affect the ACA’s mandate for insurers, said Jen Kates, senior vice president of global and public health policy for KFF, an independent health policy research organization.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmitbsj2y001p356naml2bowi@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “The change today will have an impact, but not on insurance coverage,” Kates said Friday.&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;Rather, she said&lt;strong&gt;,&lt;/strong&gt; the effect will be that fewer newborns will receive the vaccine.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmit92yov0006356n6c84vpuc@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            ACIP also voted to &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/health/live-news/cdc-vaccine-meeting-hepatitis-b-12-05-25?post-id=cmit1w40t000u2e6fwghwjhf7"&gt;recommend&lt;/a&gt; shared clinical decision-making on the hepatitis B shot for parents who get free vaccines through the federal Vaccines for Children program. The program provides a variety of immunizations at no cost to children who are eligible for Medicaid, are uninsured or are underinsured.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmitd3at600043b6qv8xrr0op@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Dr. Georgina Peacock, director of the CDC’s Immunization Services Division, said Thursday that if that recommendation was approved, those immunizations would be covered by Vaccines for Children.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmit92yov0007356nqc8r0nsl@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Also Thursday, a Centers for Medicare and Medicaid Services official said the inclusion of individual-based decision-making language would not affect coverage of the vaccine without any cost-sharing.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmit9ctxj000m356nrloe2tg8@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The CDC makes the final decision on vaccine recommendations&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;but typically aligns with the advisory panel’s vote.
    &lt;/p&gt;

              &lt;/div&gt;
                  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>CNN</author><pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 12:00:59 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiggFBVV95cUxQMkdKaWNQVFQ5alhnTnV2ZUNpZjVEVlN0NFFhclR6S3NjYUVISXVJRlJtbUdaUDhwOTg3em1yQjNHM3Rud3ZweHI3WkZwUjFEeTZ6c0JMRldxSVRjSXVKYWtWdlNpNmNYUUNvVnRZZXhTdzhPdmRBdFpMbDZ1RHY3TVRn</guid></item><item><title>香蕉的成熟度实际上对您的健康很重要—方法如下- HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffpost.com/entry/banana-ripeness-and-health-g_l_6931b101e4b08d8fed00c74f</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;section class="entry__content-list js-entry-content js-cet-subunit"&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Here’s something you may not have thought about: For some foods (in this case we’re talking about bananas), the nutritional effects on your health can vary depending on the ripeness level when you eat it.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;As a banana ripens, its nutritional content — the amount of sugar, starch and vitamins — changes. Meaning, if you &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/entry/are-carbs-and-sugar-bad_l_670fcbbce4b072cc9eb529a1" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-internal-link" data-vars-item-name="need more sugar before a workout" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="6931b101e4b08d8fed00c74f" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="670fcbbce4b072cc9eb529a1" data-vars-target-content-type="buzz" data-vars-type="web_internal_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="0"&gt;&lt;span&gt;need more sugar before a workout&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;, or less sugar because of diabetes, you may want to eat your banana at a certain ripeness level.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Ahead, registered dietitians share the various ripeness levels, what a banana looks like at each stage, and the health conditions or goals that are best addressed at each level of ripeness.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Underripe&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="cli cli-image js-no-inject"&gt;&lt;p class="cli-image__spacer"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="cli-image__source-wrapper"&gt;&lt;div class="cli-image__credit" aria-label="Image Credit: Dorin Musat / 500px via Getty Images"&gt;&lt;p class="credit-container"&gt;&lt;span class="credit"&gt;Dorin Musat / 500px via Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption class="cli-image__caption caption-cli"&gt;An underripe banana can help you feel full longer.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bananas at this stage look green; they’re firm and difficult to peel. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“This stage has the highest resistant starch and low sugar content,” said &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.mycrohnsandcolitisteam.com/writers/683f0deb46c7aa1e0f3349e2" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Avery Zenker" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="6931b101e4b08d8fed00c74f" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.mycrohnsandcolitisteam.com/writers/683f0deb46c7aa1e0f3349e2" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="1"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Avery Zenker&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;span&gt;a registered dietitian at MyCrohnsAndColitisTeam.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The benefits of resistant starch are many, including helping to feed healthy gut bacteria that &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.huffingtonpost.co.uk/entry/im-a-nutritionist-follow-these-steps-to-reduce-chronic-inflammation_uk_65b24b41e4b074981636f0e7" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-internal-link" data-vars-item-name="reduce inflammation" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="6931b101e4b08d8fed00c74f" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="65b24b41e4b074981636f0e7" data-vars-target-content-type="buzz" data-vars-type="web_internal_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="2"&gt;&lt;span&gt;reduce inflammation&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; and keeping blood sugar levels stable, according to Zenker. It’s also digested more slowly, which can keep you full for longer.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“Resistant starch acts very similarly to fiber, which means it’s fermented in the gut (so it fuels your good gut bacteria) and it can be helpful for blood sugar control,” added registered dietitian &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.csulb.edu/media/page/amanda-sauceda" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Amanda Sauceda" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="6931b101e4b08d8fed00c74f" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.csulb.edu/media/page/amanda-sauceda" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="3"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Amanda Sauceda&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;span&gt;a nutrition lecturer at California State University, Long Beach.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;While good gut bacteria and blood sugar management are generally important for your health, they may apply to some individuals more than others. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“This level of ripeness is ideal for people who are trying to control blood glucose levels, such as those with insulin resistance as seen with prediabetes, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/entry/meal-times-type-2-diabetes-prevention_l_64c1269ce4b053a700938ca7" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-internal-link" data-vars-item-name="Type 2 diabetes" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="6931b101e4b08d8fed00c74f" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="64c1269ce4b053a700938ca7" data-vars-target-content-type="buzz" data-vars-type="web_internal_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="4"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Type 2 diabetes&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; and other metabolic conditions,” Zenker said. “Unripe bananas can also be beneficial for anyone looking to improve &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/entry/gut-health-experts_l_61c0b9eae4b0bb04a627fe69" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-internal-link" data-vars-item-name="gut health" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="6931b101e4b08d8fed00c74f" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="61c0b9eae4b0bb04a627fe69" data-vars-target-content-type="buzz" data-vars-type="web_internal_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="5"&gt;&lt;span&gt;gut health&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; by improving microbiome balance.” The latter may be especially important for people who are trying to manage digestive issues like &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/entry/issues-irritable-bowl-syndrome_l_62587134e4b0be72bff476af" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-internal-link" data-vars-item-name="irritable bowel syndrome" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="6931b101e4b08d8fed00c74f" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="62587134e4b0be72bff476af" data-vars-target-content-type="buzz" data-vars-type="web_internal_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="6"&gt;&lt;span&gt;irritable bowel syndrome&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“If you want to up the health benefits of your green banana, consider pairing it with some peanut butter,” Sauceda added. “You get a little protein and healthy fats, which help for a better blood sugar response and are good for the gut.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Some people may want to avoid an underripe banana, however. Zenker said athletes may fall into that category since slow digestion can cause stomach heaviness. People who are sensitive to resistant starch and experience gastrointestinal discomfort after may want a different ripeness level, too.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Barely Ripe&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="cli cli-image js-no-inject"&gt;&lt;p class="cli-image__spacer"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="cli-image__source-wrapper"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="cli-image__caption caption-cli"&gt;Barely ripe bananas still have a little green near the ends.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bananas at this stage are mostly yellow with some green at the ends. While slightly softer, they’re still firm. This ripeness level suggests the banana is still high in fiber and low in sugar, but not to the same extent as underripe bananas. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“The resistant starches have started converting into simple sugars,” Zenker said. “Their mineral levels remain stable, particularly potassium and &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/entry/magnesium-has-definite-uses-but-isnt-the-cure-all-social-media-says-goog_l_685d64f9e4b0dc2d3f533c53" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-internal-link" data-vars-item-name="magnesium" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="6931b101e4b08d8fed00c74f" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="685d64f9e4b0dc2d3f533c53" data-vars-target-content-type="buzz" data-vars-type="web_internal_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="7"&gt;&lt;span&gt;magnesium&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;.” &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;She recommended a barely ripe banana to people who want the digestive benefits of an underripe banana without that chalky taste, as well as those who need steady energy throughout the day without major effects on their blood sugar. That means, similar to underripe bananas, barely ripe ones are great for people with insulin resistance, prediabetes, diabetes, metabolic syndrome or digestive conditions. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“They can also be ideal for peri- or post-menopausal women due to the resistant starch content that helps combat the effects of insulin resistance and supports gut health as hormonal changes occur,” Zenker added.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ripe&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="cli cli-image js-no-inject"&gt;&lt;p class="cli-image__spacer"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="cli-image__source-wrapper"&gt;&lt;div class="cli-image__credit" aria-label="Image Credit: Yaorusheng via Getty Images"&gt;&lt;p class="credit-container"&gt;&lt;span class="credit"&gt;Yaorusheng via Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption class="cli-image__caption caption-cli"&gt;A fully ripe banana has no green showing on the ends.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bananas at this stage are fully yellow and soft, but not mushy. They’re easy to peel and have a sweet smell.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;While ripe bananas are listed separately from barely ripe ones here, it’s important to note that not all experts find the differences noteworthy. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Nutrition-wise, these types of bananas are pretty much the same,” Sauceda said. “In fact, the &lt;a href="https://fdc.nal.usda.gov/food-details/1105314/nutrients" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="USDA nutrient database categorizes these two types of bananas together" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="6931b101e4b08d8fed00c74f" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://fdc.nal.usda.gov/food-details/1105314/nutrients" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="8"&gt;USDA nutrient database categorizes these two types of bananas together&lt;/a&gt;.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;With that said, if we’re going to make distinctions, Zenker shared what they are: In ripe bananas, starches have mostly converted into natural sugars, &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/entry/signs-not-enough-fiber-digestions_l_66ba37afe4b0eabd2393b96d" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-internal-link" data-vars-item-name="fiber" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="6931b101e4b08d8fed00c74f" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="66ba37afe4b0eabd2393b96d" data-vars-target-content-type="buzz" data-vars-type="web_internal_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="9"&gt;fiber&lt;/a&gt; decreases, and sugar and antioxidant content increase. Vitamins and minerals hit their peak.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sauceda added more noteworthy benefits. “One banana has 8% of your daily value for potassium, which is a mineral many people don’t get enough of,” she said. “This mineral is important for blood pressure and muscle contraction. It also meets 8% of your daily value for magnesium, which is important for &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/entry/the-best-types-of-milk-to-drink-for-bone-health-including-non-dairy-options_l_6564b70be4b05f498ba14f45" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-internal-link" data-vars-item-name="bone health" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="6931b101e4b08d8fed00c74f" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="6564b70be4b05f498ba14f45" data-vars-target-content-type="buzz" data-vars-type="web_internal_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="10"&gt;bone health&lt;/a&gt;.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Zenker encouraged a ripe banana for people who are about to work out, want quick and convenient whole-food energy, or are looking to increase potassium intake (perhaps to manage high blood pressure or other cardiovascular issues), as well as for kids who want an easy-to-eat, sugary food. Ripe bananas are also a good in-between for people who want fiber without the digestion-related concerns.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Very Ripe&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="cli cli-image js-no-inject"&gt;&lt;p class="cli-image__spacer"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="cli-image__source-wrapper"&gt;&lt;div class="cli-image__credit" aria-label="Image Credit: Stefania Pelfini la Waziya via Getty Images"&gt;&lt;p class="credit-container"&gt;&lt;span class="credit"&gt;Stefania Pelfini la Waziya via Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption class="cli-image__caption caption-cli"&gt;Two very ripe bananas, indicated by brown spots on the peel.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bananas at this stage are soft, have brown spots and emit a strong aroma.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“Sugar content is near its peak, and fiber continues to decrease,” Zenker said. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;That’s great for people who need quick energy, have sensitive digestive symptoms, have low appetite or want a sweet treat, Zenker said. Individuals who are trying to manage their blood sugar may want to avoid very ripe bananas, however, since they’re higher in sugar.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Overripe&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="cli cli-image js-no-inject"&gt;&lt;p class="cli-image__spacer"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="cli-image__source-wrapper"&gt;&lt;div class="cli-image__credit" aria-label="Image Credit: Karl Tapales via Getty Images"&gt;&lt;p class="credit-container"&gt;&lt;span class="credit"&gt;Karl Tapales via Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption class="cli-image__caption caption-cli"&gt;An overripe banana looks brown or black and is usually mushy.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bananas at this stage look brown or black and are soft, even mushy. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;They’re highest in sugar and antioxidants, lowest in fiber, losing their vitamin C content and maintaining their potassium content, according to Zenker. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;As far as other vitamins go, some are increasing while others are decreasing. “For example, a &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://fdc.nal.usda.gov/food-details/1105314/nutrients" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="ripe banana has 14 milligrams of vitamin C" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="6931b101e4b08d8fed00c74f" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://fdc.nal.usda.gov/food-details/1105314/nutrients" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="11"&gt;&lt;span&gt;ripe banana has 14 milligrams of vitamin C&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; but an &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://fdc.nal.usda.gov/food-details/1105073/nutrients" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="overripe one has 10 milligrams" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="6931b101e4b08d8fed00c74f" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://fdc.nal.usda.gov/food-details/1105073/nutrients" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="12"&gt;&lt;span&gt;overripe one has 10 milligrams&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;,” Sauceda said. “Interestingly, overripe bananas have a bit more folate than ripe bananas.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;So again, there are pros and cons, and certain populations and situations for which it’s best suited. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“This stage is best for baking and freezing (banana bread, cookies, smoothies) rather than as a raw snack,” Zenker said. “It’s gentle on digestion and good for anyone needing fast calories, such as athletes, [but] not as ideal for people with diabetes or those seeking fiber or nutrient density.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Sauceda is a fan of the smoothie option. “You don’t need to add as much banana when you use an overripe one for your smoothie, which can mean less added sugars,” she said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;As evidenced here, the banana to pick at the grocery store isn’t necessarily &lt;/span&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span&gt;just&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;span&gt; the one you like the taste or color of. Yes, we know this concept is a bit bananas, literally — &lt;/span&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span&gt;and&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;span&gt; it’s true.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;At the same time, we can’t blame you for going by the taste metric. Plus, bananas are nutritious whenever you eat them. “Overall, bananas are a great fruit whether you eat them green or ripe,” Sauceda said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>HuffPost</author><pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 12:00:18 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijwFBVV95cUxNenBwbHI2dGl2RVJxYXRsZ0xMV25WVlNmYWJVeVhOYS1DQ09UTk8yMFFPU0NXc2t1M3cyejVhVmN2aHdBbS1IX2hGSlNVR0RaQ0xDd1RlbHlTdUZiamxkcDFZSGJXX1dFcUc1LUtjdGxZWGwxNm10WDN6dzZUQkZmUUpQSlZ1ck1jZkJLQzBzc9IBlAFBVV95cUxPaVFfTGs1RGRRNzBfNDJ3NWNWRVN6YU1mMVFZLXdtYmdJYUNtc25yaV9EVkxmUlpqV1pxaDJUUDZTUHIwT2pJVFB0M0ZReDVkX043RW9XQUZuSndaSE5vTndHc3pMeGJFOFpyUHAybmFsSzBtcFRMbGlPSG1HRjZyVUVBTXRFUFZSVkxydW1ydm05dEI0</guid></item><item><title>带状疱疹疫苗可能会减缓，防止痴呆进展，研究发现-今日美国</title><link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/graphics/2025/12/07/shingles-vaccine-slow-prevent-dementia-study/87606825007/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_dt"&gt;Updated Dec. 7, 2025, 11:10 a.m. ET&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="gnt_ar_b"&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;A new &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41586-025-08800-x" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" data-t-l=":b|z|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;study&lt;/a&gt; suggests the &lt;a href="/story/life/health-wellness/2025/03/24/how-long-does-shingles-last/82634260007" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" data-t-l=":b|e|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;shingles&lt;/a&gt; vaccine may lower the likelihood of developing dementia as well as slow its progression in people who have already been diagnosed with the disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;Researchers are finding more evidence that certain herpes viruses, such as shingles, which can infect the nervous system, might play a role in causing dementia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;An initial study published in &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41380-021-01138-6" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" data-t-l=":b|z|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;Nature&lt;/a&gt; and a follow-up study conducted by &lt;a href="https://med.stanford.edu/" data-t-l=":b|z|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;Stanford Medicine&lt;/a&gt;, published in the journal &lt;a href="http://linkinghub.elsevier.com/retrieve/pii/S0092867425012565" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" data-t-l=":b|z|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;Cell&lt;/a&gt; on Dec. 2, show the shingles vaccination may also have therapeutic benefits against dementia by reducing the disease's progression and lowering the chance of dying from it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;For those battling dementia, these findings are promising. Dementia cases have been predicted to increase in the coming years, according to a &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41591-024-03340-9.epdf?sharing_token=rnJZ3-p0kX4lowC-Bt-PZ9RgN0jAjWel9jnR3ZoTv0MVutFf8dmYDbw6diQeD5ESeQi4_Zi5WoMqvnLv8j67SeaLJo1TjACSb9yKKx4AwC_iAdWBIDfJ40ornjGdxmiLTnVLuT6dUNYY2YtjrXKeceIH6e5jENTgtkHdPsSYgI6GHyMXllcVUIxrhsnLYz5FGk4ZEeVfqe5qNp-7Zak-6IJOS7XZGEGWiDZlU7o4OYo%3D&amp;amp;tracking_referrer=www.scientificamerican.com" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" data-t-l=":b|z|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;study&lt;/a&gt; released in 2024, which states the lifetime risk of dementia could rise to 42% after age 55 − a much faster rate than anticipated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Unable to view our graphics? &lt;a href="/story/graphics/2025/12/07/shingles-vaccine-slow-prevent-dementia-study/87606825007/" data-t-l=":b|e|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;Click here to see them.&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;“We see an effect on your probability of dying from dementia among those who already have dementia,” Dr. Pascal Geldsetzer, assistant professor of medicine at &lt;a href="https://profiles.stanford.edu/pascal-geldsetzer" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" data-t-l=":b|z|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;Stanford University&lt;/a&gt; and senior author of the most recent study, said of the potential effects of the shingles vaccine in a recent interview with &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2025/12/02/health/shingles-vaccine-dementia-progression-study-wellness" data-t-l=":b|z|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;CNN&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;“That means that the vaccine doesn’t just have a preventive potential, but actually a therapeutic potential as a treatment, because we see some benefits already among those who have dementia,” he said. “To me, this was really exciting to see and unexpected.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="gnt_ar_b_h2"&gt;The link: Shingles and dementia&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;The varicella-zoster virus is a type of herpes virus that causes both chickenpox and shingles. The virus stays dormant in the body after a person has fully recovered from chickenpox. The &lt;a href="/story/life/health-wellness/2025/03/24/elizabeth-banks-shingles-vaccines-aging-parenting/82633098007/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" data-t-l=":b|e|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;shingles virus&lt;/a&gt; often doesn't cause any more issues, but it can reappear years later and cause shingles, a painful rash, according to the &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/shingles/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" data-t-l=":b|z|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;Centers for Disease Control and Prevention&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;The CDC estimates that about 1 in every 3 people in the United States will develop shingles in their lifetime. Shingles can be prevented by getting the two-dose vaccine, which is about &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/shingles/vaccines/index.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" data-t-l=":b|z|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;90% effective&lt;/a&gt; in preventing shingles in the elderly. The CDC recommends getting the vaccine when you turn 50.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;The study results support the growing theory that viruses affecting the brain's function may raise the risk of dementia. Dementia affects over 55 million people worldwide, according to &lt;a href="https://www.alzint.org/about/dementia-facts-figures/dementia-statistics/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" data-t-l=":b|z|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;Alzheimer's Disease International&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;Scientists suspect that the shingles vaccination may help by preventing the reactivation of dormant viruses like varicella zoster and herpes simplex, which are thought to contribute to brain inflammation and the accumulation of dangerous proteins linked to dementia. How that works is still unknown.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;Another theory is that the vaccine may strengthen the immune system more broadly, preventing immunological deterioration as people age, according to &lt;a href="https://www.cardiff.ac.uk/news/view/2985389-shingles-vaccine-may-help-prevent-and-slow-dementia,-study-finds" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" data-t-l=":b|z|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;Cardiff University&lt;/a&gt; in Wales.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;The scientists note that more research is necessary to confirm the results and gain a deeper understanding of how the vaccine affects brain health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_s gnt_ar_s0"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_s gnt_ar_s25"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_s gnt_ar_s50"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_s gnt_ar_s75"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_s gnt_ar_s100"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>USA Today</author><pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:26:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMirAFBVV95cUxOZDhVYjg1bUhuWW5fczQ2ZHQ2em9yTFp2QV9oLVM2RFhkZEVhMVUxdFJpYUVCc0s5d0RhRjFzNkZ6T1Fycy1ad1RSYmIxb2ltTUJrc29rb1VoWFFPWE5iR0VobGdNQ01KaExqSHRwRk9DMlRfRUNxRmlPMzRvVS1BcWpHNWJwZy1LemtmRkt1SV84Sk1oMlU3NUltSzAyeEhPcGFJREMtcmtUNUlo</guid></item><item><title>您是不是睡得太多了？新的研究揭示了成年人真正需要多少小时来维持大脑健康-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/are-you-sleeping-too-much-new-research-reveals-how-many-hours-adults-really-need-for-brain-health/articleshow/125814858.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;div class="MwN2O"&gt;&lt;div class="vdo_embedd"&gt; &lt;div class="T22zO"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most of us worry about not sleeping enough, the bleary mornings, the heavy eyelids, the sense of running on fumes. What almost no one considers is the opposite problem: the idea that getting too much sleep might quietly work against your brain. It sounds counterintuitive. It even borders on unfair. But researchers in Washington, US, found that the range of sleep linked to better brain health may be smaller than expected, with both short and long nights tied to decline, a finding that contradicts years of official guidance and could make even good sleepers pause.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="3"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;And yes, it’s unsettling. Most of us have had nights where eight or nine hours felt like a luxury; few imagine it could put them in the same risk bracket as someone sleeping far too little. But that’s exactly what one new study suggests.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="8"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="lOvcW vdo_embedd"&gt;&lt;div class="k7lcu"&gt;&lt;p class="efT4r"&gt;Fix Your Sleep Naturally! Sadhguru’s 5-Step Routine for Deep Rest&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="10"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="11"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What the Washington researchers found&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="12"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; Their &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://academic.oup.com/brain/article/144/9/2852/6401973" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="_blank" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;study &lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;looked at a group of older adults whose sleep varied widely but whose sleep quality was consistently poor. The striking finding was that people sleeping less than 4.5 hours a night, and those sleeping more than 6.5 hours, showed greater risk of cognitive decline over time. The pattern, they noted, resembled the kind of deterioration associated with ageing ,one of the strongest predictors for conditions such as Alzheimer’s.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="17"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; They even suggested an ideal zone: between 4.5 and 6.5 hours of sleep, at least for the specific population they studied. It’s a narrow band, and the conclusion is the kind that makes both the public and the sleep-science community sit up a little straighter.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="19"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="20"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why this challenges what health bodies say&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="22"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; Writing in &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/sleeping-longer-than-6-5-hours-a-night-associated-with-cognitive-decline-according-to-research-whats-really-going-on-here-170989" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="_blank" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;The Conversation&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class="em" data-ua-type="1"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;, senior psychology lecturer Greg Elder acknowledged that the results run counter to what major health bodies teach. He explained that, “The study showed that sleeping longer than 6.5 hours was associated with cognitive decline over time, this is low when we consider that older adults are recommended to get between seven and eight hours of sleep every night.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="28"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Elder notes that neither the &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.nhs.uk/every-mind-matters/mental-health-issues/sleep/#:~:text=a%20great%20night.-,How%20many%20hours%20of%20sleep%20do%20I%20need?,between%208%20to%2016%20hours." rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="_blank" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;NHS &lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;nor the&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/sleep/about/index.html" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="_blank" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt; US Centres for Disease Control (CDC)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; currently suggest that sleeping more than 6.5 hours is harmful. But he emphasises that the Washington study measured sleep quality as well, and that all participants who slept very little or a lot were also sleeping badly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="34"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="35"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Why might sleep duration affect the brain?&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="36"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; He also notes that researchers still don’t fully understand why lack of sleep is linked to cognitive decline. “One theory is that sleep helps our brain flush out harmful proteins that build up during the day,” he writes. “So interfering with sleep might interfere with our brain’s ability to get rid of these. Experimental evidence even supports this, showing that even just one night of sleep deprivation temporarily increases beta-amyloid levels in the brain of healthy people.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="41"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; Beta-amyloid is one of the proteins associated with Alzheimer's disease. The theory is not a certainty, but Elder points to it because it illustrates how sensitive the brain may be to disrupted sleep.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="44"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="45"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;So is it too much sleep, or something else entirely?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="47"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;At the same time, he is careful about what the study cannot claim. All participants, regardless of how long they slept, struggled with poor sleep quality. That detail matters.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="49"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Elder suggests that the real story may be less about the clock and more about what happens while you’re asleep. “It could be the case that it isn’t necessarily the length of the sleep that matters, but the quality of that sleep when it comes to risk of developing dementia,” he says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="52"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Although the study found a correlation between sleeping more than 6.5 hours and cognitive decline, Elder stresses an important point: the people sleeping the most may have had underlying issues that weren’t detected in the tests.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="54"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;“For example, this could include poor health, socioeconomic status or physical activity levels. All of these factors together may explain why longer sleep was linked to cognitive decline.” In other words, long sleep may be a marker of something else, not a cause in itself. It’s a reminder that correlation and causation rarely hold hands as neatly as we’d like.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="58"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="59"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Another study says sleep duration may be genetic &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="60"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;While the Washington findings challenge conventional assumptions, another group of researchers on the opposite side of the US is offering an even more complicated picture. A separate &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.ucsf.edu/news/2022/03/422416/when-it-comes-sleep-its-quality-over-quantity" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="_blank" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;study from San Francisco&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; centred on Familial Natural Short Sleep (FNSS), a genetic trait in which people naturally function fully on four to six hours of sleep. These individuals aren’t sleep-deprived; they simply don’t need the traditional eight-hour benchmark.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="66"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Neurologist Louis Ptacek, lead author of the study, said: &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="em" data-ua-type="1"&gt;“There’s a dogma in the field that everyone needs eight hours of sleep, but our work to date confirms that the amount of sleep people need differs based on genetics. Think of it as analogous to height; there’s no perfect amount of height, each person is different. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="em" data-ua-type="1"&gt;We’ve shown that the case is similar for sleep.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="71"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; Ptacek and his team have spent over a decade studying these short sleepers, though he warns that understanding the genetics will take time. Mapping the sleep genes, he says, is like solving&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="em" data-ua-type="1"&gt; “a thousand piece jigsaw puzzle.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; What they can say for certain is that some people are built for shorter nights, and that treating them as chronically underslept would be a mistake.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="76"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; The San Francisco researchers also point out how often sleep patterns intersect with neurological disease&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="em" data-ua-type="1"&gt;. “Sleep problems are common in all diseases of the brain,”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; they write, explaining that sleep relies on many parts of the brain functioning together. When any of these areas are damaged, disrupted or degenerating, sleep disturbances often follow.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="80"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="81"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What all of this actually means for sleepers&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="83"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; Taken together, the two studies paint a picture that is more nuanced than any single recommendation can capture. On one hand, sleeping significantly less than 4.5 hours or more than 6.5 hours &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="em" data-ua-type="1"&gt;in a population already experiencing poor sleep quality&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; was associated with cognitive decline. On the other, the San Francisco team reminds us that some people are genetically wired to do perfectly well on short nights, and that sleep quantity is far from the whole story.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="88"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; For readers, it’s tempting to interpret the Washington findings as a directive, a new rule to replace the old one. But neither Elder nor the researchers themselves suggest rewriting national guidelines based on a study of 100 people. Instead, Elder leans toward a simpler, more intuitive takeaway: focus less on the number of hours you’re asleep, and more on &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="em" data-ua-type="1"&gt;how well&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; your sleep restores you.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="92"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; If anything, the emerging research nudges us toward a more personalised understanding of sleep. The idea that everyone needs eight hours may have been a convenient shorthand, but the science, and the people studying it, are telling a more complex story. Sleep is individual. Sleep is layered. And sometimes, sleep is too much of a good thing, not because of the number on the clock, but because of what the brain is struggling with while you’re in it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="94"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:25:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiowJBVV95cUxPczhVbHZfY05SQlEzWEhrSmh5czNyRVZBOVdmcnNfOWpWRjNPckFNUFVid2FPbm0wc050MUJnekVINmUxZnpxam5za2ZrbDNMRGlqTXRscEFKZDdpT09GMENRQkMxM1pobXpPOEtzOHpFU3Jib1NZTEJSbUdwaFdOOFh5YXQ4eGJHbjNxSzh4Ny1EWnI0bGxfYmY3NVZiQTZRWHVmcW1ScTV5TTFjZHRKYW5STkw3dlROb0pzT3BHbkwwa3hkdTV2WWVkaWNsOHRyTVcxUFFPekZEU1AzeFNzQk5CX1AzeEo1U2JQRnREYTE0bThVUWxod1djaE82SXFFZVpQZjJaTHpWSFdVN0VqV3pfcDZHYUNvWVI5aUhlbnJGQUk</guid></item><item><title>专家表示，肯尼迪疫苗顾问“扭转了局面” -路透社</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/kennedy-vaccine-advisers-turned-back-clock-disease-prevention-experts-say-2025-12-07/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Reuters</author><pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:08:42 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi3gFBVV95cUxPQ0tleU1rU2xSdTl1SG1jNXkzeWZNNTNyU1hVZXRpeEZuaXhVaWo0dmRrR0RvNmtyckNxUzB2NVY1MkdvdmJ3U2ZvTjhBeFRxODRHbndxS2ZjSlBFZ0Q3TDU4MW9hR1o2ZmFfNDVIaHJPOVR3cXpWbmhZa08yVHd1OHdFSzkxRERLX1RXcUdBbVBMNmxFNnM4LVJUcHE2WVppY2ZwcWprT0VrN2JaY2U0Q1BTTkxRRXFuX0ZHY2dDU2pYQ01wbTU1QlhCN2tkNnM4c3czQXdydzVoY0hWaXc</guid></item><item><title>女性在亲戚几乎不知道被要求借钱后处于尴尬的境地，发短信“连续多次” - Yahoo Life UK</title><link>https://uk.style.yahoo.com/woman-awkward-position-relative-she-110000702.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="" data-article-body="true"&gt;&lt;h3 class="mb-4 text-lg font-bold"&gt;NEED TO KNOW&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul class="mb-4"&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;A woman said that a relative recently texted and requested to “borrow” money for an “urgent” reason&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;She said she has only met the relative twice in her life&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The woman shared her story on a community forum and asked others what they thought she should do&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;A woman says that a relative who she barely knows recently asked to &lt;a href="https://people.com/husband-refuses-to-lend-sister-in-law-money-after-borrowing-8k-now-hes-being-called-controlling-11858009" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:borrow money,;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;borrow money,&lt;/a&gt; and she’s not sure what to do about it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The woman shared her story on the &lt;a href="https://www.mumsnet.com/talk/am_i_being_unreasonable/5452330-relative-asking-for-money" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:“Am I Being Unreasonable?”;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;“Am I Being Unreasonable?”&lt;/a&gt; forum on the U.K-based community site Mumsnet.com, a place where people can go to seek input on a variety of interpersonal topics.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;In her post, the original poster (OP) shared that she and her parents recently came back from visiting family abroad. She said that shortly after returning home, one of her relatives texted and asked to “borrow money.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“Bear in mind, I've met her twice — the last time being 12 days ago and before that about 10 years ago when she was a child,” the OP explained.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="relative mb-4"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="relative text-sm mt-1 pr-2.5"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Getty Stock Images&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; Woman worriedly checking her phone (stock image)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“She said she would pay it back in a few months and that it was 'urgent' — to the point where she was texting multiple times in a row,” she added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The woman said that she is not only shocked by the unexpected request, but she &lt;a href="https://people.com/woman-annoyed-after-her-neighbor-lets-their-kids-run-amok-on-her-property-11852667" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:is also “annoyed”;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;is also “annoyed” &lt;/a&gt;due to the fact that the relative didn’t ask for a specific amount, but rather “asked me 'how much I'd be willing to give.’ ”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Never miss a story — sign up for&lt;a href="https://people.com/people-news-daily-newsletter-sign-up-8692701" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:PEOPLE's free daily newsletter;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt; PEOPLE's free daily newsletter&lt;/a&gt; to stay up-to-date on the best of what PEOPLE has to offer​​, from celebrity news to compelling human interest stories.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The OP said that she has since told her parents about the request and they are “also baffled.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="relative mb-4"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="relative text-sm mt-1 pr-2.5"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Getty Stock Images&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; Hand holding cash (stock image)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“AIBU [am I being unreasonable] to say 'no' outright, despite [the relative] knowing we obviously have some money to travel (having just seen them all)?” she asked at the end of her post.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;In a follow-up comment, the OP clarified that the relative in question lives in a &lt;a href="https://people.com/health/ranchers-struggle-with-access-to-mental-health-services-as-covid-puts-stress-on-rural-communities/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:small rural area;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;small rural area&lt;/a&gt;, and that her family gave their family cash on their recent visit as is the “custom” in that area of the world.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Commenters unanimously agreed that the OP should not lend her relative the money.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“Sounds like there may be a family or &lt;a href="https://people.com/woman-wants-to-buck-tradition-and-not-name-firstborn-son-after-father-in-law-11682823" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:cultural tradition;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;cultural tradition&lt;/a&gt; where your parents have sent money to relatives back home? And now the younger generation have been brought up with this and are expecting money from you,” one person said, before adding, “Families are complicated and if you don’t want to do this then don’t. You might need to block the relative though as it doesn’t sound like they’ll stop asking.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;a href="https://people.com/people-puzzler-8620185" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:The PEOPLE Puzzler crossword is here! How quickly can you solve it? Play now!;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The PEOPLE Puzzler crossword is here! How quickly can you solve it? Play now!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“They are being very cheeky. I would respond sorry I’m broke not sure how I’ll make it to payday myself,” said some else.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Someone else suggested a simpler route and advised the OP to “say no and stick to it,” then &lt;a href="https://people.com/woman-finds-out-friends-girlfriend-blocked-her-reddit-11827020" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:“block and ignore”;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;“block and ignore”&lt;/a&gt; if needed.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Read the original article on &lt;a href="https://people.com/woman-in-awkward-position-after-relative-she-barely-knows-asked-to-borrow-money-11860028" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:People;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;People&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Yahoo Life UK</author><pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigwFBVV95cUxNVnZFcTRNUWlmX20takxKZ1N2ekpsWHNabUxGZ2NyVllPRW5mRkpDUUh6bU5oeW1WR1pUdTlfSWFtdklxbjR2WkR2amx1aDd5WEs5NWQ0VTg4a0dJRU1GM0llemR3YldSTVlBenVRbFZ6QVpxcXVvd1VMcFNBYjQ4R0lhTQ</guid></item><item><title>泰勒·斯威夫特（ Taylor Swift ）确保永远不会做这1件事。Neuroscience Says She's Right - Inc.com</title><link>https://www.inc.com/minda-zetlin/taylor-swift-makes-sure-never-to-do-this-1-thing-neuroscience-says-shes-right/91274508</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Inc.com</author><pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 10:37:44 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiuwFBVV95cUxOWHFGazlKcDVwWVQ1NmlRVjNQMFlmRXB3QkFDN0pyWTB0VDRvdnlGRWg2QWYxYy01TEVXaXI0SkpTbW5tb1N6eW9jcmdSbXFOVXlEU2tJY1U5WEtabFZUWXhpNWcxT3A5bHRUTG9vbkdZOEd5d2M0MUdrbzZLaXBnendpYXBiZDVXMXlHSTByTmJOVzkwOExORTRSeEF0dWoyMFdCNVg1NmtJcHgtM1d1ZkxmRHdZUU9GTWlv</guid></item><item><title>随着疫苗指南被颠覆，父母的困惑和焦虑-《纽约时报》</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/12/07/us/vaccines-chlldren-hepatitis-guidelines.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The New York Times</author><pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 10:02:36 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiAFBVV95cUxNSGZ2Sy1aVXgzb3hWZjdkMENJYVNSWHl2QkJpLWI2TzZPZ3FDYk1HX0xrZ3NtRTlzZUhBQ3JqMXk5aTdzcnZuYWc5dnM5aDBFUktVSWxqY0VkaVBMYmJDd1VSWWpVenJEY2YtZ0FObXFQbWlEdFhVRW5WbEZqeFE1amlxYUZhRWxX</guid></item><item><title>德里肿瘤学家诺伊达警告“持续咳嗽不正常” ；分享您不应忽视的肺癌早期迹象|健康-印度斯坦时报</title><link>https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/noida-delhi-oncologist-warns-persistent-cough-is-not-normal-shares-early-signs-of-lung-cancer-you-should-not-ignore-101765098880586.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="detail " dataid="/lifestyle/health/noida-delhi-oncologist-warns-persistent-cough-is-not-normal-shares-early-signs-of-lung-cancer-you-should-not-ignore-101765098880586.html"&gt; &lt;div class="storyParagraphFigure"&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="highlight"&gt;A cough that continues for weeks despite rest, routine medication, and familiar home remedies is often the body’s way of indicating that something deeper may be happening inside the lungs.&lt;/span&gt; A persistent cough is rarely just a leftover &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/topic/infection" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="infection"&gt;infection&lt;/a&gt; or a seasonal reaction, and when it lingers without a clear reason, it becomes a clinical sign that deserves attention.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;figure class=""&gt; &lt;span class=""&gt; &lt;picture&gt; &lt;source media="(max-width:767px)" srcset="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/12/07/550x309/105361_1763808507134_1765099562312.jpg" alt="Lung cancer symptoms often overlap with common ailments, leading to delays in diagnosis.(Freepik)" title="Lung cancer symptoms often overlap with common ailments, leading to delays in diagnosis.(Freepik)"&gt;&lt;/source&gt; &lt;img src="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/12/07/550x309/105361_1763808507134_1765099562312.jpg" alt="Lung cancer symptoms often overlap with common ailments, leading to delays in diagnosis.(Freepik)" title="Lung cancer symptoms often overlap with common ailments, leading to delays in diagnosis.(Freepik)"&gt; &lt;/picture&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;figcaption&gt;Lung cancer symptoms often overlap with common ailments, leading to delays in diagnosis.(Freepik)&lt;/figcaption&gt; &lt;/figure&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;p id="readMoreFTUser"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;In many early-stage &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/topic/lung-cancer" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="lung cancer"&gt;lung cancer&lt;/a&gt; cases, this cough appears long before any noticeable pain or breathlessness, which is why people tend to brush it aside. &lt;span class="highlight"&gt;In an interview with HT Lifestyle, Dr Manish Sahni, surgical oncologist and robotic surgeon, Kailash Hospital, Noida and Delhi, shares why a persistent cough is never “normal” and lists the early signs of lung cancer to watch for.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt; (Also read: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/fitness-coach-shares-3-simple-tips-to-lose-1-kg-per-week-before-new-year-2026-exact-plan-for-quick-results-weight-loss-101765083736736.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="Fitness coach shares 3 simple tips to lose 1 kg per week before New Year 2026: 'Exact mini-cut I use for quick results'"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fitness coach shares 3 simple tips to lose 1 kg per week before New Year 2026: 'Exact mini-cut I use for quick results' &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="mt-10 mb-10 htEchoRecirculationWidget"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="mt10 mb10 htEchoArticlePromo"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="predictorShow mb20" data-vars-predictor="true" data-vars-quiz="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="quizShow mb20" data-vars-minimized="false" data-vars-predictor="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;What lung-cancer coughs look like&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sharing key symptoms, Dr Sahni says, “A cough linked to lung cancer behaves differently from one that follows a cold or a &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/cities/mumbai-news/hosps-see-sharp-spike-in-heat-exhaustion-viral-illness-cases-amid-soaring-temperatures-101744140408533.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="viral illness"&gt;viral illness&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;span class="highlight"&gt;It often carries on for more than three weeks, does not respond to usual symptomatic treatment, and may slowly become deeper or more forceful as the tumour irritates the airway lining.&lt;/span&gt; Some individuals notice blood tinges in the mucus or a change in their voice. &lt;span class="highlight"&gt;These shifts occur because an early tumour can alter the airflow pathways or create subtle pressure inside the lungs, triggering irritation that results in a steady cough.&lt;/span&gt;”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;Pollution is changing who gets diagnosed&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to Dr Sahni, smoking still remains a major contributor, but it’s no longer the only one. “There is also a visible change in the profile of patients being diagnosed today. &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/topic/smoking" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="Smoking"&gt;Smoking&lt;/a&gt; remains a major risk factor, yet a growing number of cases are now being detected in individuals with no history of tobacco use. Long-term exposure to polluted air is emerging as an important contributor.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;figure class="inlineIMG"&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;img data-src="https://images.hindustantimes.com/img/2024/08/09/550x309/shutterstock2401940947_1723203498457_1723203516451.jpg" class="lazy" src="https://images.hindustantimes.com/default/550x309.jpg" alt="Many significant factors contribute to lung cancer risks that are frequently overlooked((Shutterstock))" title="Many significant factors contribute to lung cancer risks that are frequently overlooked((Shutterstock))"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;figcaption&gt;Many significant factors contribute to lung cancer risks that are frequently overlooked((Shutterstock))&lt;/figcaption&gt; &lt;/figure&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="highlight"&gt;He adds, “Fine particulate matter and toxic gases can travel deep into the lung tissue, causing persistent inflammation that, over time, may alter the genetic behaviour of lung cells.&lt;/span&gt; This helps explain why people living in severely polluted cities are reporting symptoms earlier, even without traditional risk factors.”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;The subtle signals most people overlook&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="highlight"&gt;He also highlights that lung cancer symptoms are often mistaken for everyday fatigue or minor infections: “The early phase of lung cancer often blends into everyday life.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="highlight"&gt;Unexplained tiredness, a sense of heaviness in the chest, mild breathlessness during routine tasks, frequent throat irritation or a sudden drop in appetite are frequently mistaken for minor health fluctuations.&lt;/span&gt;”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;“Tuberculosis is a major public health challenge in India, and its symptoms mimic early signs of lung cancer, making it one of the important factors for delayed &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/topic/diagnosis" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="diagnosis"&gt;diagnosis&lt;/a&gt;. Some individuals also experience recurrent chest infections because tumour-related obstruction can prevent air from moving freely in the affected area,” says Sahni.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Ending with a reminder, Dr Sahni emphasises, “Lung cancer tends to progress quietly, which is why delays in seeking care remain common. Any cough that persists beyond a few weeks, particularly in high-pollution environments or in people with a family predisposition, should be evaluated. With timely diagnosis supported by advanced imaging and precise treatment options, outcomes can improve considerably. Recognising the earliest signs and responding without delay can make a meaningful difference.”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Note to readers: This article is for informational purposes only and not a substitute for professional medical advice. Always seek the advice of your doctor with any questions about a medical condition.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Hindustan Times</author><pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 09:41:51 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikgJBVV95cUxOYnhGM1hQY05INnI5TXBYM3dhSF9DejFiLWMySlFSRU9GUG1XTWo2TndkQjJLc0FFSDg1MnZlamRqSTBpclQzaDFrVFNtNGp1ZWdSSU5qRUd2c0RILXZYN1piQXk5OGZUTTlqRWcwZ1o5QlZ2bjBxN2ZnM0FMbU5ZbU83QVJOR2RlTzZZeC04bEVfUURMaENUNFh6MWZRWmQtbHJEb05wdGxrLWJhVEFBYk5XbVNaT21XUURuU29hOV9xUUNOdE9NVkszOVRSdDFHUHE5bWYyZ1BlQlJpUmZoalJjdnpuRGRhNG95ZklEb28ycGRUbC1zLU9xM0l6dnlqazdVQ3FxWTl5TURTMkc4VEtR0gGXAkFVX3lxTE1HTjkwQ0I4NHp4NkNJM1VEQl9ScHBVbjlpR0NORUVSd3A4Z1pzeUpXVm1VTFdlVnA2NjFuTEJPWUVqaWVaVVlsNGNNX1NScGxwblM5RGpZR3RsYldxbzRablFzbl9WemlMdXplNUhnVHp3WmJLMVB6RUpkZ215YjNaOU9IRXFISjY2clFGaEJ5UUowVVRPbm5DSUlCMmE4b2Z4V2NZUmJVN2U1WW5nMkpKMmxyNWRFa1FIWlZPdjJGYnFEMmhUa2w3MWtaUS1VQzJiQzkwSURmM3IyRnRIVG40M0JyXzlNdDR4dDJNRll2YlJ3ZFJPY1g4ZlZuakpfR3lobWY5al81LUxBeEZ2NUtGVkZsUnU0TQ</guid></item><item><title>健身教练分享了他全年保持苗条的简单饮食计划： “尝试这种方法至少1个月” |健康-印度斯坦时报</title><link>https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/fitness-trainer-shares-simple-diet-plan-he-uses-to-stay-lean-all-around-the-year-try-this-method-for-at-least-1-month-101765095820904.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="detail " dataid="/lifestyle/health/fitness-trainer-shares-simple-diet-plan-he-uses-to-stay-lean-all-around-the-year-try-this-method-for-at-least-1-month-101765095820904.html"&gt; &lt;div class="storyParagraphFigure"&gt; &lt;p&gt;Is it possible to maintain a lean physique without obsessively &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/mom-of-2-with-no-time-for-gym-calorie-tracking-shares-her-top-8-fitness-secrets-no-strict-diet-or-meals-after-6pm-101762147489882.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="tracking every calorie"&gt;tracking every calorie&lt;/a&gt;? Zach Kieran, a fitness coach, thinks so. &lt;span class="highlight"&gt;In a November 20 Instagram post, he revealed his personalised diet approach, which he called 'building your own personal menu' – a method he said was 'fun, effective, and enjoyable enough to be able to stick with'.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Also read | &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/fitness-coach-shares-3-simple-tips-to-lose-1-kg-per-week-before-new-year-2026-exact-plan-for-quick-results-weight-loss-101765083736736.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="Fitness coach shares 3 simple tips to lose 1 kg per week before New Year 2026"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fitness coach shares 3 simple tips to lose 1 kg per week before New Year 2026&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;figure class=""&gt; &lt;span class=""&gt; &lt;picture&gt; &lt;source media="(max-width:767px)" srcset="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/12/07/550x309/Screenshot_2025-12-07_135718_1765096063653_1765096082238.png" alt="Zach Kieran has shared a diet plan for a year-round lean physique. (Representative picture: Freepik)" title="Zach Kieran has shared a diet plan for a year-round lean physique. (Representative picture: Freepik)"&gt;&lt;/source&gt; &lt;img src="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/12/07/550x309/Screenshot_2025-12-07_135718_1765096063653_1765096082238.png" alt="Zach Kieran has shared a diet plan for a year-round lean physique. (Representative picture: Freepik)" title="Zach Kieran has shared a diet plan for a year-round lean physique. (Representative picture: Freepik)"&gt; &lt;/picture&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;figcaption&gt;Zach Kieran has shared a diet plan for a year-round lean physique. (Representative picture: Freepik)&lt;/figcaption&gt; &lt;/figure&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;p id="readMoreFTUser"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Zach, who said he hasn't strictly tracked calories for years, outlined a three-step process designed to foster calorie awareness and long-term consistency. Here it is:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="mt-10 mb-10 htEchoRecirculationWidget"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="mt10 mb10 htEchoArticlePromo"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="predictorShow mb20" data-vars-predictor="true" data-vars-quiz="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="quizShow mb20" data-vars-minimized="false" data-vars-predictor="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;The 'personal menu' blueprint&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The first step, according to Zach, was to establish a &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/fitness/how-many-calories-to-burn-and-eat-for-weight-loss-here-s-the-right-answer/story-HsdXNOxBfD6C9O1ZQsTRnI.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="daily calorie target"&gt;daily calorie target&lt;/a&gt; needed for fat loss by using any online calorie calculator. “They will ask you to enter your weight, height, age, and gender,” he explained.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Next, his Instagram followers were instructed to distribute the calculated total consistently across two to four daily meals. As a sample plan, the online fitness coach suggested a total of 1,800 calories split into four consistent time slots:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;⦿ Breakfast: 500 calories&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;⦿ Lunch: 500 calories&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;⦿ Dinner: 500 calories&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;⦿ Evening snack: 300 calories&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The third, and most crucial, step involved carefully curating the menu itself. Zach advised selecting two to three low-calorie, &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/goa-fitness-coach-shares-9-high-protein-muscle-building-meals-for-vegetarians-dosa-rice-soya-egg-chicken-non-vegetarians-101762934292307.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="high-protein meal"&gt;high-protein meal &lt;/a&gt;alternatives for each time slot (breakfast, lunch, dinner, and snack). &lt;span class="highlight"&gt;He said that these selections must be enjoyable and should include at least one 'very simple and effective' go-to option that can be prepared ahead of time for days when fatigue hits.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="highlight"&gt;“You want to ensure that at least one of these meals is very simple and effective, one that you can turn to when you are tired,” he said, adding, “Your food is meant to be simple and enjoyable.&lt;/span&gt; Otherwise, you won't be able to stick to it.”&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Flexibility is key&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Zach stressed that the process was not meant to be restrictive. The method encouraged flexibility by combining meal budgets for higher-calorie choices, he explained. &lt;span class="highlight"&gt;For instance, if someone desired a high-calorie meal, such as a takeaway, they should combine the calories from dinner and a snack — aiming for 800 to 900 calories — to fit the choice within their daily budget.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Finally, Zach highlighted the importance of consistency over perfection. “&lt;span class="highlight"&gt;Whenever you notice yourself falling off track or having a weekend bender, the only thing that I want you to do is place your focus into getting back on the plan,” he advised.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="highlight"&gt;He concluded: “The longer you can stay consistent on this plan and stay within your calories, the quicker and more consistently you're going to be able to reach your goals...&lt;/span&gt; you will reach a position where you are &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/topic/weight-loss" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="losing weight"&gt;losing weight&lt;/a&gt;, leaning out, and keeping it for the long term.”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="highlight"&gt;In his caption, Zach urged his followers to 'save this and try this method for at least a month', noting that the structure helped individuals become 'more aware of your calories, without becoming completely obsessed with them'.&lt;/span&gt; He wrote in his caption, “The dieting structure that I have used for years. To get lean and stay lean year round. It’s simple, and effective. And it stops me from having to obsessively track every meal with a food tracking app. This will help you become more AWARE of your calories. Without becoming completely obsessed with them. Save this and try this method for at least a month. Whenever you fall off, gently place your attention back onto the process.”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Note to readers: This report is based on user-generated content from social media. HT.com has not independently verified the claims and does not endorse them.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;This article is for informational purposes only and not a substitute for professional medical advice.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Hindustan Times</author><pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 08:59:37 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilAJBVV95cUxQTG80MzJPbS1KeDFydVlNSmhacnhieHJxMVljSWJ4TGZlWmNPSWwzOWtVRDk3WURoSW1aaEdPTTR1VWgyTkpGODJNYTk3c1ZxMVpxYmtMaU9xWFdHbEo3QXF3bE9FUTd2MXVTWFhiQzBIRkQwdnJGZU1EZ1E2NWRvUGFaUVIzbjJXOHRzQmhVa0RUTU1MSFpUN0pUa1VWZEJuaGU2OFM4RHZqU2FTVUg4NlNyZlUtdUgwUVNoTHY4dG1rbFFhd2Rxd3ByZVlRX1M5ekE2RjlFaFFBcmJIdV93MmRuWDBOUkNfOFhWRGtPWG91VjYyVFdtZnRyNmUyNnlWOUtxQTFQU1RDRzA4aHBOOXJ3V0PSAZoCQVVfeXFMT1RBWnNQdklWTVZXZ1ZGaXpUU3BWTDhMVmJreFdtNnR5R0hjRnJIeHFOZFlKUXRiMXNiR3dLZ1NiMFhtRnBDQ1dZdzgzWFVxazE1U1BzaW4zaGFQQ05vYXVPdGRkcjdlUzdrUlZqWVh0c2ZwbzM1RGoxT05pTnZ1VWZjYkxWTWdJT1AzZUxuTmFNb0RfRjhKRmdqcGk0NXktZmRlQ1pDdjBUbmVxUHFObDAxU2ZpVlhVVDFLZ2hZSm5zSmN2M2pWeGpfclh0Smd1WW9oUUVuNGtlclI2Sko5NUtiSF8yOTZQT2U0Qnl0cjBBM3h2SjN1OTFxbEs2WVExLW5VRUoycjBCRGhWeVk2SXFsel9MYThYVnV3</guid></item></channel></rss>