<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>Screen Slate</title><link>https://www.screenslate.com</link><description></description><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>Edges of Ailey</title><link>https://whitney.org/exhibitions/edges-of-ailey</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
            

            &lt;div class="mb-m"&gt;
              &lt;p class="large"&gt;
                &lt;strong&gt;Open: Sept 25, 2024–Feb 9, 2025&lt;/strong&gt;
              &lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;/div&gt;

          &lt;p class="large"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Edges of Ailey,&lt;/em&gt; opening at the Whitney Museum of American Art on September 25, is the first large-scale museum exhibition to celebrate the life, dances, influences, and enduring legacy of visionary artist and choreographer &lt;a href="/artists/t6396"&gt;Alvin Ailey&lt;/a&gt; (b. 1931, Rogers, Texas; d. 1989, New York, New York). This dynamic showcase—described as an “extravaganza” by curator Adrienne Edwards—brings together visual art, live performance, music, a range of archival materials, and a multi-screen video installation drawn from recordings of Alvin Ailey American Dance Theater (AAADT) repertory to explore the full range of Ailey’s personal and creative life.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="large"&gt;Presented at the Museum in two parts, &lt;em&gt;Edges of Ailey&lt;/em&gt; consists of an immersive exhibition in the Museum’s 18,000 square-foot fifth-floor galleries—featuring works by more than eighty artists and revelatory archival material—and an ambitious suite of performances in the Museum’s third-floor theater, including AILEY in residence for one week each month during the exhibition. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="large"&gt;Sweeping holdings of rarely seen archives, including performance footage, recorded interviews, notebooks, letters, poems, short stories, choreographic notes, drawings, and performance programs and posters gathered from Ailey’s archives and others forge a vital throughline in the gallery. Selections from the Alvin Ailey Archival Papers—courtesy of the Allan Gray Family Foundation and held at the Black Archives of Mid America in Kansas City, Missouri—and the Alvin Ailey Dance Foundation Archives Collection held at the Library of Congress are of singular importance, specially digitized and exhibited for this show’s occasion. A dynamic montage of Ailey’s life and dances will play on loop across an 18-channel video installation created by filmmakers Josh Begley and Kya Lou, with curator Adrienne Edwards.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="large"&gt;Ailey’s presence, felt through the video surround and his encased personal effects, envelops a scenic installation of artworks by over eighty artists. These works are arranged by themes that shaped Ailey’s life and dances. Sections span an expanded Black southern imaginary that enfolds histories of the American South with those of the Caribbean, Brazil, and West Africa; the enduring practices of Black spirituality; the profound conditions and effects of Black migration; the resilience for and necessity of an intersectional Black liberation; the prominence of Black women in Ailey’s life; and the robust histories and experiments of Black music; along with the myriad representations of Blackness in dance and meditations on dance after Ailey.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="large"&gt;Artists exhibited among Ailey include &lt;a href="/artists/69"&gt;Jean-Michel Basquiat&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="/artists/80"&gt;Romare Bearden&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="/artists/14995"&gt;Faith Ringgold&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="/artists/1326"&gt;Alma Thomas&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="/artists/759"&gt;Jacob Lawrence&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="/artists/8851"&gt;Rashid Johnson&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="/artists/15056"&gt;Kevin Beasley&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="/artists/4563"&gt;Kara Walker&lt;/a&gt;, and many others. A recent acquisition of Eldren Bailey and new works by Karon Davis, &lt;a href="/artists/18966"&gt;Jennifer Packer&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="/artists/11868"&gt;Mickalene Thomas&lt;/a&gt;, and Lynette Yiadom-Boakye will be presented for the first time in honor of this landmark exhibition.   &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="large"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Edges of Ailey&lt;/em&gt; also offers a rare opportunity for visitors to watch intimate live performances by Alvin Ailey American Dance Theater in the Museum’s third-floor theater. As part of the exhibition's robust live &lt;a href="/exhibitions/edges-of-ailey/performances"&gt;performance program&lt;/a&gt;, AILEY is in residence at the Whitney for one week each month, for a total of five weeks and over ninety performances. This gives visitors the opportunity to experience the full scope of Ailey's world and legacy, including performances of classic and contemporary works by the two repertory companies—Alvin Ailey American Dance Theater and Ailey II—as well as showcases by students from The Ailey School, workshops and education programs from Ailey Arts In Education, and classes from Ailey Extension. During the weeks AILEY is not in residence at the Museum, a series of dance commissions by leading choreographers and their collaborators, including Ronald K. Brown, Trajal Harrell, Bill T. Jones, Ralph Lemon, with interdisciplinary artist &lt;a href="/artists/15056"&gt;Kevin Beasley&lt;/a&gt;, Sarah Michelson, &lt;a href="/artists/18870"&gt;Okwui Okpokwasili&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="/artists/18882"&gt;Peter Born&lt;/a&gt;, Will Rawls, Matthew Rushing, Yusha-Marie Sorzano, and Jawole Willa Jo Zollar will be showcased.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="large"&gt;&lt;a href="/exhibitions/edges-of-ailey/performances"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Program tickets&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt; are now on sale. Tickets are limited and must be booked in advance. Visitors with program tickets that include Museum admission are welcome to visit the exhibition on the same day within regular museum hours. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="large"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Visitors can also see Alvin Ailey American Dance Theater during the company's &lt;a href="https://ailey.org/series/ailey-new-york-city-center"&gt;annual engagement at New York City Center&lt;/a&gt; from December 4 to January 5. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-pm-slice="1 1 []" class="large"&gt;Edges of Ailey is organized by the Whitney Museum of American Art in collaboration with the Alvin Ailey Dance Foundation. Special acknowledgment to the Allan Gray Family Foundation and the Black Archives of Mid-America in Kansas City for access to archival materials. The exhibition is curated by Adrienne Edwards, Engell Speyer Family Senior Curator and Associate Director of Curatorial Programs, with Joshua Lubin-Levy, Curatorial Research Associate, and CJ Salapare, Curatorial Assistant, with thanks to Katie Fong, Curatorial Assistant, for research support. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-pm-slice="1 1 []"&gt;Review &lt;a href="/exhibitions/edges-of-ailey/accessibility-information"&gt;accessibility information&lt;/a&gt; before visiting Edges of Ailey.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The lead sponsor for &lt;em&gt;Edges of Ailey &lt;/em&gt;is the Jerome L. Greene Foundation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://whitneymedia.org/assets/image/829205/gf02_H_logotype_purple_final.jpg"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This exhibition is also sponsored by&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://whitneymedia.org/assets/image/824959/bofa_lo1_rgb_Digital.png"&gt;  &lt;br&gt;&lt;img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://whitneymedia.org/assets/image/824938/Delta_c_r__2_.jpg"&gt;      &lt;img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Leadership support is provided by the Ford Foundation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://whitneymedia.org/assets/image/830693/large_Ford-single-black.jpg"&gt;      &lt;img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Generous support is provided by Judy Hart Angelo and the Arnhold Family | Arnhold Foundation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Major support is provided by the Barbara Haskell American Fellows Legacy Fund; the Horace W. Goldsmith Foundation; The KHR McNeely Family Fund | Kevin, Rosemary, and Hannah Rose McNeely; Anne-Cecilie Engell Speyer and Rob Speyer; the Whitney’s National Committee; and Clara Wu Tsai.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Significant support is provided by The Holly Peterson Foundation, The Keith Haring Foundation Exhibition Fund, the National Endowment for the Arts, and Denise Littlefield Sobel.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Additional support is provided by A4 Arts Charitable Trust, the Adam D. Weinberg Artists First Fund, Candace and Rick Beinecke, Jeanne Donovan Fisher, Kevin Gan and Benjamin Blad, The Harkness Foundation for Dance, Nancy Magoon, Jeanne Greenberg Rohatyn and Nicolas Rohatyn, and an anonymous donor.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Curatorial research and travel for this exhibition were funded by an endowment established by Rosina Lee Yue and Bert A. Lies, Jr., MD.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Support is also provided by the Marshall Weinberg Fund for Performance, endowed in honor of his parents Anna and Harold Weinberg who taught him the meaning of giving.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://whitneymedia.org/assets/image/830765/large_2018-LogoBW-Horizontal.jpg"&gt;      &lt;img&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Generous support for the catalogue is provided by the Mellon Foundation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://whitneymedia.org/assets/image/827959/Mellon_Logomark_Lockup_Black_copy.png"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;FCB New York is the exclusive marketing agency sponsor.&lt;em&gt; New York&lt;/em&gt; magazine is the exclusive media sponsor.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>&lt;a href="/venues/whitney-museum" hreflang="en"&gt;Whitney Museum&lt;/a&gt;</author><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 13:02:06 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">65445</guid></item><item><title>9999</title><link>https://queensmuseum.org/exhibition/cameron-a-granger-9999/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="description forma-body rich-text spaced mb-16 max-default mx-auto"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;In &lt;/span&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span&gt;9999&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;span&gt;, Cameron A. Granger uses the framework of video games and magic to imagine an alternative method of liberation for Black communities from the compounding effects of racist urban planning. In early role playing video games, due to low computer processing capacity, 9,999 was the numerical damage limit done to a character that could be registered on screen. Yet sometimes, additional damage continued to accrue off-screen – incapacitating, yet unseen. Granger takes this concept of the concealed yet relentless harm, and applies it to the cumulative corrosion of segregative design, environmental racism, and gentrification.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;To make sense of the convoluted legacies of systemic injustice, Granger visualizes the wounds left by structural violence through “black holes” that rip the city’s fabric. His films, prints, and sculptures create a video game-like narrative that provides puzzles, tips, and charms that aid in deciphering these black holes. In diagnosing the root cause of the issue, Granger proposes that the black holes are the result of a spell cast by nefarious, hidden forces. To break the curse, he speculates what might be possible if the black holes could be used as portals to share knowledge.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Seeking answers, Granger turns to stage magicians, root workers, and conjurers. His work references Black magicians such as Henry “Box” Brown (1815-1897) whose performances alluded to his 1849 self-emancipation via mail, and Benjamin Rucker aka Black Herman (1892-1934) whose magic acts and conjuring remedies built a massive following in the 1920s among Black communities. Granger also draws on the practice of conjuring, invoking remedies for locating harm’s source, protecting, and healing. Additionally, he calls upon the Haitian folklore of zombies, originally mythologized as the spirits of enslaved laborers trapped to haunt plantations in their afterlife. Granger reconceptualizes their spirits as a unified force reemerging from the grave to aid in liberation.  &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Sourcing wisdom from Black forebears whose knowledge helped their communities self-emancipate, heal, and thrive, Granger offers a collective vision of empowered futurity. In a dimly lit gallery that mimics the digital landscape of a video game, Granger creates a narrative where memories of and knowledge from Black ancestors provide clues, methods, and tools that once pieced together, may reveal the key to break free. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;em&gt;Cameron A. Granger: 9999&lt;/em&gt; is curated by Sarah Cho, Assistant Curator.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;


&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Cameron A. Granger &lt;/b&gt;&lt;span&gt;(b. Cleveland, OH, 1993) is an &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://queensmuseum.org/2022/11/11/announcing-recipients-of-in-situ-artist-fellowship-and-qm-jerome-foundation-fellowship-for-emerging-artists/"&gt;&lt;span&gt;In Situ Artist Fellow at the Queens Museum&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;. He attended Euclid, OH public schools and Skowhegan School of Painting &amp;amp; Sculpture. Granger has exhibited his work in solo exhibitions at No Place Gallery, Columbus, OH (2022); Ortega y Gasset Projects, Brooklyn, NY (2019), and Vox Populi, Philadelphia, PA (2018), among others. He has shown in group exhibitions at MoMA PS1, Long Island City, NY (2022), Jack Shainman The School, Kinderhook, NY (2022), and The Bemis Center for the Arts, Omaha, NE (2021), among others. Granger was an artist-in-residence at the Studio Museum in Harlem, NY (2022). His film, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span&gt;Before I Let Go&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;span&gt;, was awarded Best Experimental Film and the Audience Award at the 2023 BlackStar Film Festival. Granger’s work can be found in the collection of the Columbus Museum of Art, Columbus, OH. He is a member of MINT Collective &amp;amp; ACRE Residency. Granger lives and works between Columbus, OH and Queens, NY. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
          
                  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>&lt;a href="/venues/queens-museum" hreflang="en"&gt;Queens Museum&lt;/a&gt;</author><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 13:02:06 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">72927</guid></item><item><title>Basic Cable</title><link>https://www.amant.org/exhibitions/94-jenna-bliss-basic-cable</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="text-image-module__content markdown"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jenna Bliss’s photomontages, ready-mades, and Super 8mm films evoke the sensations of the &lt;em&gt;agent observateur&lt;/em&gt;. Recorded on regular walks through New York, Jenna’s imagery of the cityscape and architectural environment is montaged with brand and advertising signage. Installed in an antechamber at 306 Maujer, &lt;em&gt;Basic Cable&lt;/em&gt; brings together light boxes that exist within a constellation of film recorded in Manhattan’s Financial District. These superimposed images allude to the infrastructures that surround us and the matrix that runs below the city, signaling an analogical pairing that New Yorkers come across daily. These works are presented alongside the artist’s most recent film work, &lt;em&gt;True Entertainment&lt;/em&gt; (2023), which follows the fictional artist Lola Van Haas and her gallery at a prestigious art fair in the lead up to the 2008 economic crisis and the US presidential elections.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;
&lt;a name="image-jenna-bliss-conspiracy-2021-super-8mm-film-transferred-to-hd-video-and-animation-1-46-minutes-courtesy-of-the-artist-felix-gaudlitz-vienna-and-ulrik-new-york"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Image: Jenna Bliss, &lt;em&gt;Conspiracy&lt;/em&gt;, 2021. Super 8mm film transferred to HD video and animation,1:46 minutes. Courtesy of the artist; Felix Gaudlitz, Vienna; and Ulrik, New York.&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>&lt;a href="/venues/amant" hreflang="en"&gt;Amant&lt;/a&gt;</author><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 13:02:06 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">77328</guid></item><item><title>A Coin from Thin Air</title><link>https://www.amant.org/exhibitions/95-loretta-fahrenholz-a-coin-from-thin-air</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="text-image-module__column"&gt;
      &lt;p class="text-image-module__content markdown"&gt;Loretta Fahrenholz is a filmmaker and visual artist based in Berlin. Fahrenholz’s work has been shown internationally, including solo exhibitions at Bergen Kunsthall (2023); Kölnischer Kunstverein, Cologne (2022); n.b.k. – Neuer Berliner Kunstverein (2021); mumok – Museum of Modern Art Ludwig Foundation, Vienna (2018); Fridericianum, Kassel (2016); Stedelijk Museum, Amsterdam (2016), and Kunsthalle Zürich (2015), as well as film screenings at CPH:DOX, Copenhagen (2024), Ann Arbor Film Festival (2019, 2020, 2021), and Kurzfilmtage Oberhausen (2014, 2020), among others.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>&lt;a href="/venues/amant" hreflang="en"&gt;Amant&lt;/a&gt;</author><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 13:02:06 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">77329</guid></item><item><title>Robert Frank&amp;#039;s Scrapbook Footage</title><link>https://www.moma.org/calendar/exhibitions/5735</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>&lt;a href="/venues/museum-modern-art" hreflang="en"&gt;Museum of Modern Art&lt;/a&gt;</author><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 13:02:06 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">77521</guid></item><item><title>Mother</title><link>https://www.momaps1.org/programs/460-sohrab-hura</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="col-md-6 markdown program-description-module__main"&gt;
            &lt;div class="economy-i18n economy-i18n--en"&gt;
          &lt;p&gt;The first US survey of artist Sohrab Hura (Indian, b. 1981) showcases more than fifty works from the last two decades of his experimental practice. &lt;em&gt;Sohrab Hura: Mother&lt;/em&gt; weaves together bodies of work across photography, film, sound, drawing, painting, and text that have never before been shown together. Renowned for capturing remarkable everyday moments that give form to systemic political forces, Hura brings into focus colonially imposed borders, the trauma of partition, and the changing ecosystem of the Indian subcontinent. This survey includes a selection of key works such as &lt;em&gt;Pati&lt;/em&gt; (2010), a film that explores the rural Indian region of Madhya Pradesh and its role in the movement to pass the 2005 National Rural Employment Guarantee Act; &lt;em&gt;The Coast&lt;/em&gt; (2019), a book project, series of photographs, and film that use India’s coastline as a lens to examine the nation’s changing politics; and a selection of pastel drawings and gouache paintings from &lt;em&gt;Things Felt But Not Quite Expressed&lt;/em&gt; (2022–ongoing) and &lt;em&gt;Ghosts in My Sleep&lt;/em&gt; (2023–ongoing), his new series depicting familial memories both experienced and imagined. Through cathartic strategies of personal and political introspection, the exhibition traces Hura’s shifting existential concerns around the ethics of image-making as a documentary act.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sohrab Hura&lt;/strong&gt; is a photographer and filmmaker who lives and works in New Delhi, India. Recent solo and group exhibitions have been presented at Huis Marseille Museum for Photography, Amsterdam; Liverpool Biennial 2021; Kunstmuseum Bonn; The Museum of Modern Art, New York; Kettle’s Yard, Cambridge; and the Cincinnati Art Museum. His films have been shown in film festivals such as the Berlin International Film Festival and the 66th International Short Film Festival Oberhausen. Hura has self-published five books under the imprint Ugly Dog. His work is in the permanent collections of The Museum of Modern Art, New York; Ishara Art Foundation, Dubai; and the Cincinnati Art Museum, among others. &lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;  
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>&lt;a href="/venues/moma-ps1" hreflang="en"&gt;MoMA PS1&lt;/a&gt;</author><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 13:02:06 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">77524</guid></item><item><title>Offerings for Escalante</title><link>https://www.momaps1.org/programs/461-enzo-camacho-ami-lien</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="col-md-6 markdown program-description-module__main"&gt;
            &lt;div class="economy-i18n economy-i18n--en"&gt;
          &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Offerings for Escalante&lt;/em&gt; marks the first major US museum exhibition of artist duo Enzo Camacho (Filipino, b. 1985) and Ami Lien (American, b. 1987). For over a decade, Camacho &amp;amp; Lien’s multidisciplinary practice has addressed geopolitical relations by attending to localized forms of dispossession, survival, and resistance, particularly in the context of the Philippines. Through moving-image works, a light-based installation, as well as a suite of handmade paper compositions, &lt;em&gt;Offerings for Escalante&lt;/em&gt; centers the Philippine island of Negros, known for its sugar plantations. A newly commissioned long-form film, &lt;em&gt;Langit Lupa&lt;/em&gt;, draws upon survivor testimonials to narrate the story of the 1985 Escalante Massacre, a tragic incident of state violence against a mass protest in Negros under the Ferdinand Marcos dictatorship. Laying bare the brutality of plantation societies, &lt;em&gt;Offerings for Escalante&lt;/em&gt; emphasizes remembrance and mourning within ongoing struggles for land justice, food sovereignty, and anti-imperialist resistance. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Enzo Camacho &amp;amp; Ami Lien&lt;/strong&gt; are based between New York, Manila, and Berlin. Solo exhibitions of their work have been held at the Glasgow Gallery of Modern Art; Center for Contemporary Art Berlin; Para Site, Hong Kong; Kunstverein Freiburg; 47 Canal, New York; and Green Papaya Art Projects, Quezon City, Philippines. They have been included in group exhibitions at Tai Kwun Contemporary, Hong Kong; the Asia Pacific Triennial, Queensland Art Gallery, Brisbane; the New Museum Triennial, New York; the EVA International, Limerick; Manifesta 13, Marseille; the Drawing Center, New York; the Kuandu Museum of Fine Arts, Taipei; the Brunei Gallery, SOAS University of London; the NTU Center for Contemporary Art, Singapore; UCCA Center for Contemporary Art, Beijing; Jim Thompson Art Center, Bangkok; and Green Papaya Art Projects, Manila. They are currently Senior Fellows at the Lunder Institute of American Art at Colby College.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;  
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>&lt;a href="/venues/moma-ps1" hreflang="en"&gt;MoMA PS1&lt;/a&gt;</author><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 13:02:06 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">77525</guid></item><item><title>Ceremonies Out of the Air</title><link>https://www.momaps1.org/programs/377-ceremonies-out-of-the-air-ralph-lemon</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="col-md-6 markdown program-description-module__main"&gt;
            &lt;div class="economy-i18n economy-i18n--en"&gt;
          &lt;p&gt;This major exhibition of artist Ralph Lemon (b. 1952, Cincinnati) features more than sixty artworks made over the last decade across disciplines and marks the debut of several collaborative performances. One of the most significant figures to emerge from New York’s downtown scene, Lemon has expanded the capacity for storytelling across contexts and traditions. &lt;em&gt;Ceremonies Out of the Air: Ralph Lemon&lt;/em&gt; comprises dance, drawings, photographs, sculpture, paintings, and video throughout the museum’s expansive third-floor galleries, alongside a synchronous program of live works staged in a dedicated performance space. The centerpiece of the exhibition is &lt;em&gt;Rant redux&lt;/em&gt; (2020–24), a major four-channel video and sound installation realized with Kevin Beasley and based on the live performance &lt;em&gt;Rant&lt;/em&gt; (2019–ongoing). The performance program includes the US debut of &lt;em&gt;In Proximity&lt;/em&gt; (2022) and the New York premiere of &lt;em&gt;Tell it anyway&lt;/em&gt; (2024), and invites a series of special guests to respond to Lemon’s drawings from &lt;em&gt;Untitled (The greatest [Black] art history story ever told. Unfinished)&lt;/em&gt; (2015–present). Lemon’s work takes the body as an archive of raw emotion, physical labor, and received histories to challenge the ways we have been taught to see the world.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ralph Lemon&lt;/strong&gt; is a choreographer, writer, and visual artist based in Brooklyn and Philadelphia. His work has been the subject of exhibitions at The Kitchen (2007/2015), Contemporary Art Center, New Orleans (2008), Studio Museum in Harlem (2012)  and the Walker Art Center (2006, 2014, 2024). At MoMA, he performed in the Museum’s Donald B. and Catherine C. Marron Atrium for &lt;em&gt;On Line: Drawing Through the Twentieth Century&lt;/em&gt; (2010); he organized the performance series &lt;em&gt;Some sweet day&lt;/em&gt; (2012); and he led the discursive project &lt;em&gt;Value Talks&lt;/em&gt; as an Annenberg Fellow (2013–14). MoMA published the first monograph on his oeuvre, &lt;em&gt;Ralph Lemon&lt;/em&gt; (2016) in the Modern Dance series. Lemon is a recipient of three Bessie Awards (1986, 2005, 2016), two Foundation for Contemporary Art Awards (1986, 2012), a 2009 Guggenheim Fellowship and Doris Duke Performing Artist Award (2012). In 2015, he received a National Medal of Arts from President Barack Obama. He is the recipient of a 2018 Heinz Family Foundation Award and a 2020 John D. and Catherine T. MacArthur Foundation Fellowship. Lemon won the Bucksbaum Award for his contribution to the 2022 Whitney Biennial. His works are in the permanent collections of institutions including the Walker Art Center, the Studio Museum in Harlem, the Whitney Museum of American Art, and the Museum of Modern Art.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;  
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>&lt;a href="/venues/moma-ps1" hreflang="en"&gt;MoMA PS1&lt;/a&gt;</author><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 13:02:06 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">77526</guid></item><item><title>Recording the Ride: The Rise of Street-Style Skate Videos</title><link>https://movingimage.org/event/recording-the-ride/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="fl-rich-text"&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-contrast="none"&gt;In the late 1980s and 1990s, skateboard teams harnessed inexpensive, widely accessible video equipment to record and share limit-pushing tricks. Featuring skaters traversing stairs, benches, and other skate-able elements of public architecture, such videos assembled grainy footage of bodies in flight into music-driven montages.  &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-ccp-props='{"134233117":false,"134233118":false,"201341983":0,"335551550":1,"335551620":1,"335557856":16777215,"335559738":0,"335559739":160,"335559740":279}'&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-contrast="none"&gt;These high-energy VHS-format videos, shot with limited budgets on consumer-accessible cameras equipped with genre-defining fish-eye lenses, were circulated among skaters and sold in skate shops. They served as inspiration and instruction, a form of proto social media that bound together an avid, expanding skater community. Soon, skating and the way it was captured on video became inextricably linked, complementary forms of artistic expression.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-ccp-props='{"201341983":1,"335557856":16777215,"335559739":160,"335559740":300}'&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Recording the Ride&lt;/em&gt;&lt;span data-contrast="none"&gt; features videos and artifacts from skate culture’s formative years, with a focus on releases by H-Street, Plan B, World Industries, Girl, Zoo York, 411, Birdhouse, and others that manifest the structure and style that defined the modern skate video genre. Highlights include artifacts from the production of &lt;/span&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Bones Brigade Video Show&lt;/em&gt; &lt;span data-contrast="none"&gt;(1984)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span data-contrast="none"&gt;; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;span data-contrast="none"&gt;a focus on Mike Ternasky and the brand Plan B, with vintage production and post-production artifacts used in the making of their seminal releases &lt;/span&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Questionable Video&lt;/em&gt;&lt;span data-contrast="none"&gt; (1992) and &lt;/span&gt;&lt;em&gt;Virtual Reality&lt;/em&gt;&lt;span data-contrast="none"&gt; (1993); and behind-the-scenes images, including photos shot by Spike Jonze—whose filmmaking career began with the production of skate videos—on the set of &lt;/span&gt;&lt;em&gt;Video Days&lt;/em&gt; &lt;span data-contrast="none"&gt;(1991). Period skateboard decks link the spirit and aesthetic established in these videos to the emergence of 1990s skater-owned brands.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-ccp-props='{"134233117":false,"134233118":false,"201341983":0,"335551550":1,"335551620":1,"335557856":16777215,"335559738":0,"335559739":0,"335559740":279}'&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-contrast="none"&gt;Organized by guest curators Jacob Rosenberg and Michaela Ternasky-Holland, Deputy Director for Curatorial Affairs Barbara Miller, and Director of Exhibition Management and Design Dánae Colomer.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Exhibition Sponsor:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="alignnone wp-image-49094" src="https://movingimage.org/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/thumbnail_image001.png" alt="" srcset="https://movingimage.org/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/thumbnail_image001.png 862w, https://movingimage.org/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/thumbnail_image001-300x200.png 300w, https://movingimage.org/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/thumbnail_image001-768x511.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 159px) 100vw, 159px"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Museum gratefully acknowledges the generous participation of Deckaid, The Secret Tape, and Look Back Library.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About the guest curators:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jacob Rosenberg came of age making the seminal Plan B skateboard videos in the early ’ 90s under the mentorship of Mike Ternasky. Rosenberg is a director/filmmaker who has made documentaries and commercials for such brands as Nike, Ford, Verizon, MLB, and NBA. His debut documentary, &lt;em&gt;Waiting for Lightning&lt;/em&gt; premiered at SXSW in 2012.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Michaela A. Ternasky-Holland is a Peabody-nominated and Emmy award-winning director who specializes in creating impactful stories using immersive and interactive technology. She is one of the first directors to create and premiere a short film utilizing Open AI’s SORA platform, which screened at Tribeca Festival 2024. As a nominee for the Producers Guild of America’s Innovation Award, she is also a consultant, speaker, and thought leader, who has been recognized as one of the 100 Original Voices of XR and listed as one of Blooloop’s 50 Immersive Influencers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Pictured: Keenan Milton and Aaron Meza. Los Angeles, 1998. Photo: blabacphoto.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="et_bloom_bottom_trigger"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>&lt;a href="/venues/museum-moving-image" hreflang="en"&gt;Museum of the Moving Image&lt;/a&gt;</author><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 13:02:06 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">77527</guid></item><item><title>Shareen Lightfoot</title><link>https://80wse.org/exhibitions/shu-lea-cheang</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="block block--text padding"&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;
&lt;i&gt;Shareen Lightfoot&lt;/i&gt;, 2024, is a commissioned installation by Shu Lea Cheang at Washington Square Windows coinciding with the &lt;span&gt;30th anniversary of her groundbreaking film, &lt;i&gt;Fresh Kill, &lt;/i&gt;1994. &lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The experimental film &lt;i&gt;Fresh Kill &lt;/i&gt;speculates a post-apocalyptic New York City in which main character lesbian protagonists navigate existential eco horror, consumer society, urban class drama, and technological dystopia.  Described as an "eco cyber noia" and "avant-anarcho ecosatire", the film features a screenplay by Jessica Hagedorn and music by Vernon Reid.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The new street level installation &lt;i&gt;Shareen Lightfoot &lt;/i&gt;spotlights an iconic neon sign from the film that alternates between the words "Kiss Kiss" and "Kill Kill" and a sprawling assemblage of televisions showing static noise.  The image of film character Shareen Lightfoot (played by Sarita Choudhury) leaping over a techno junkyard wreckage looms in the background.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;Organized by Howie Chen &lt;/small&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;Gini Yu Pei Lee, Curatorial Assistant. Produced by Jon Huron, 80WSE. &lt;/small&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;The exhibition’s presentation is made possible by Teiger Foundation.  
 &lt;/small&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Special thanks for the support of the Asian/Pacific/American Institute at NYU, CHENZO.STUDIO, and Fales Library and Special Collections. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
&lt;span&gt;Equipment provided in part by Lower East Side Ecology Center. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>&lt;a href="/venues/80wse" hreflang="en"&gt;80WSE&lt;/a&gt;</author><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 13:02:06 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">80331</guid></item><item><title>Three Films by Ana Mendieta</title><link>https://www.moma.org/calendar/galleries/5778</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>&lt;a href="/venues/museum-modern-art" hreflang="en"&gt;Museum of Modern Art&lt;/a&gt;</author><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 13:02:06 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">81718</guid></item><item><title>The Clock</title><link>https://www.moma.org/calendar/exhibitions/5746</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>&lt;a href="/venues/museum-modern-art" hreflang="en"&gt;Museum of Modern Art&lt;/a&gt;</author><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 13:02:06 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">81742</guid></item><item><title>Looking At Andy Looking</title><link>https://www.museumofsex.com/exhibitions/looking-at-andy-looking/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="exhibition__content"&gt;
                                    &lt;p&gt;Filmmaking is a mechanical art, but it can capture real people on the surface and below. Andy Warhol (1928-1987) lived much of his life “on the surface.” He embraced mechanical techniques like screen-printing, photography, and film, but Andy himself was not a machine. Behind the cool, detached persona was the highly personal—and above all queer—perspective of an inveterate experimenter.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This exhibition will explore themes of intimacy and voyeurism, including the depiction of homosexual desire, in Warhol’s early years of filmmaking. In films and footage from 1963-64, we witness the artist beginning to figure out what he could do and say with his newest plaything: the 16mm camera.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;More than anything else, Warhol loved repetition: “My fascination with letting images repeat and repeat—or in film’s case “run out”—manifests my belief that we spend much of our lives seeing without observing.” To remedy this, Warhol liked to “lengthen” his reels by projecting the film at a slower speed. Nowhere is this preoccupation with looking and long duration more evident than in his first major work &lt;em&gt;Sleep&lt;/em&gt;, a 5-hour 21-minute bedside portrait of Warhol’s lover at the time, John Giorno.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In contrast to the handheld camera work and lingering intimacy of &lt;em&gt;Sleep &lt;/em&gt;(1963), are instances in which Warhol trained a tripod-mounted camera on pretty, young men and let the film roll run out. This preference for prolonged observation could signal the artist’s affection for a person. It could also blur the line between desire and exploitation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Preservation of Warhol’s film work is a joint undertaking by The Andy Warhol Museum, Pittsburgh, and The Museum of Modern Art, New York. The original film material digitized for this exhibition is courtesy of their ongoing collaboration. Presented alongside &lt;em&gt;Sleep&lt;/em&gt; (1963), &lt;em&gt;Blow Job&lt;/em&gt; (1964), and &lt;em&gt;Couch&lt;/em&gt; (1964), half the titles featured here have never been shown. Unlike the more “produced” later work, all were filmed by Andy Warhol himself.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Warhol once said, “I just want to watch.” This exhibition invites us to take time to look where his gaze lingered.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This exhibition is organized by the Museum of Sex in partnership with The Andy Warhol Museum, one of the four Carnegie Museums of Pittsburgh.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Andy Warhol, &lt;em&gt;Couch&lt;/em&gt;, 1964. 16mm film, black-and-white, silent, 58 minutes at 16 frames per second. © The Andy Warhol Museum, Pittsburgh, PA, a museum of Carnegie Institute. All rights reserved. Film still courtesy The Andy Warhol Museum.&lt;/p&gt;
                                &lt;/div&gt;
                            &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>&lt;a href="/venues/museum-sex" hreflang="en"&gt;Museum of Sex&lt;/a&gt;</author><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 13:02:06 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">82219</guid></item><item><title>3 Songs from the River</title><link>https://www.gladstonegallery.com/exhibition/13694/3-songs-from-the-liver/installation-views</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="grid-x grid-padding-x StayBlack"&gt;&lt;p class="cell"&gt;November 21, 2024 – February 15, 2025&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>&lt;a href="/venues/gladstone-21st-street" hreflang="en"&gt;Gladstone (21st Street)&lt;/a&gt;</author><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 13:02:06 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">82626</guid></item><item><title>A Non-Coincidental Mirror</title><link>https://www.smackmellon.org/exhibition/carmen-amengual-a-non-coincidental-mirror/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content center-column simple-links"&gt;
			
&lt;blockquote class="wp-block-quote is-layout-flow wp-block-quote-is-layout-flow"&gt;
&lt;blockquote class="wp-block-quote is-layout-flow wp-block-quote-is-layout-flow"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;



&lt;blockquote class="wp-block-quote is-layout-flow wp-block-quote-is-layout-flow"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Please note that the galleries will be closed December 24 through January 1, reopening on January 2, 2025.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Smack Mellon and the Vera List Center for Art and Politics at The New School are pleased to announce &lt;em&gt;A Non-Coincidental Mirror&lt;/em&gt;, an exhibition by 2022–2024 VLC Fellow Carmen Amengual.  &lt;em&gt;A Non-Coincidental Mirror is &lt;/em&gt;a film installation by the Los Angeles-based Argentine artist and her first solo institutional exhibition in the US. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The exhibition results from ongoing research that Amengual started in 2022 about a little explored event in the cultural history of Global South solidarities: the First Third World Filmmakers Meeting in Algiers in 1973 and its second iteration in Buenos Aires in 1974. The event served as a hub where self-identified “third-world” filmmakers discussed the role of filmmaking in anti-colonial struggles, made agreements, and strategized about how to produce and distribute films under dire political conditions.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Based on an archive Amengual inherited from her mother—who collaborated with the organizers of the meeting in Algiers—the artist embarked on a field investigation that took her to Algiers, Buenos Aires, and Rome to follow the thread of this forgotten event and film in these locations as she looked to reimagine a failed documentary project that the organizers, together with the artist’s mother, attempted to make as part of the follow up meeting in Argentina.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The exhibition consists of a film installation that creates a kaleidoscopic reconstruction of this experience. Using architecture as an entry point to the utopian horizons of the past, and to the ruinification of these in the present, the multichannel film installation intertwines three storylines: an inquiry on political cinema and its methodologies, as they manifested in the Filmmakers’ Meetings; a question about the role of architecture and the decolonial project—reflecting on some of the architectural projects in Algiers and the student-led efforts to decolonize architecture education at the University of Buenos Aires; and a question about the present, as it emerges from the filmic portraits of buildings and urban infrastructure that the artist conducted during her research trips.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;As part of the film installation, Amengual designed a series of functional, sculptural objects and exhibition display structures that further underscore the cross-continental entanglement of localized, anti-Imperialist pedagogy and cultural expression. They offer a space for attentive viewership, communal reflection, and study while showcasing the artist’s ongoing project research, documents, facsimiles, and other printed material. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Told in the present, &lt;em&gt;A Non-Coincidental Mirror&lt;/em&gt; speaks of Global South solidarities and reclaims for the current moment a concrete experience of transnational, self-organized collaboration while foregrounding the social and historical conditions that made it possible. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The exhibition is accompanied by a publication featuring an essay by curators Eriola Pira and Rachel Vera Steinberg, a conversation between the artist and independent curator and writer Natasha Marie Llorens, and an essay by film historian Mariano Mestman. Designed by Jacob Lindgren, the publication features extensive images from the research and film installation. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;hr class="wp-block-separator has-alpha-channel-opacity"&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Carmen Amengual&lt;/strong&gt; is an interdisciplinary artist, independent researcher, and filmmaker from Argentina, now based in Los Angeles. Her work explores the emergence of collective imaginaries, identity formations, and conceptions of time and history that shape political imagination. She has presented her projects in various formats both nationally and internationally, with exhibitions at Artist Space (New York), Human Resources and 2220 Art &amp;amp; Archives (Los Angeles), Table (Chicago), Biquini Wax EPS (Mexico City), and Museo Centenario (Buenos Aires). Her work has also been featured in conferences such as Film Undone: Elements for a Latent Cinema (Silent Green / Kino Arsenal, Berlin) and Film Act: Third Cinema and Its Legacies (American University in Cairo), and in screenings across the US and abroad.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;A Non-Coincidental Mirror &lt;/em&gt;is her first solo institutional exhibition in the US. Amengual graduated in Comparative Literature from the University of Buenos Aires and holds an MFA in Visual Arts from the California Institute of the Arts. She is a 2021–2022 Whitney Museum of American Art Independent Study Studio Program fellow, a 2022–2024 Vera List Center for Art and Politics Fellow, a 2023 and 2024 Graham Foundation grantee, and a 2024 Creative Capital awardee.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://amengualcarmen.com"&gt;https://amengualcarmen.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;hr class="wp-block-separator has-alpha-channel-opacity"&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Carmen Amengual:  A Non-Coincidental Mirror&lt;/em&gt; is co-presented with the Vera List Center for Art and Politics at The New School. It is a Vera List Center Fellowship-commissioned project and is supported by research assistance, production grants, and curatorial support by the Vera List Center for Art and Politics as part of its &lt;em&gt;Correction*&lt;/em&gt;  Focus Theme. Additionally, it is supported by the Graham Foundation for Advanced Studies in the Fine Arts, the Creative Capital Foundation, and a Foundation for Contemporary Arts Emergency Grant.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Carmen Amengual:  A Non-Coincidental Mirror&lt;/em&gt; is curated by Eriola Pira, Curator and Director of Programs, Vera List Center for Art and Politics, and Rachel Vera Steinberg, Curator &amp;amp; Director of Exhibitions, Smack Mellon.  &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;hr class="wp-block-separator has-alpha-channel-opacity"&gt;



&lt;p&gt;This exhibition is supported, in part, by public funds from the New York City Department of Cultural Affairs in partnership with the City Council, New York City Council Member Lincoln Restler, and the New York State Council on the Arts with the support of Governor Kathy Hochul and the New York State Legislature, and with generous support from The Andy Warhol Foundation for the Visual Arts, Robert Lehman Foundation, Select Equity Group Foundation, many individuals and Smack Mellon’s Members. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Smack Mellon’s programs are also made possible with public funds from the National Endowment for the Arts and with generous support from The Edward and Sally Van Lier Fund of The New York Community Trust, Jerome Foundation, Ruth Foundation for the Arts, Lily Auchincloss Foundation, Wolf Kahn Foundation, Cornelia T. Bailey Foundation, Milton and Sally Avery Arts Foundation Inc, The Roy and Niuta Titus Foundation, and an Anonymous Donor.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;In-kind donations and services are provided by Materials for the Arts, NYC Department of Cultural Affairs/NYC Department of Sanitation/NYC Department of Education and Sage and Coombe Architects. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Space for Smack Mellon’s programs is generously provided by the Walentas family and Two Trees Management.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Vera List Center programs are made possible by major support from The Andy Warhol Foundation for the Visual Arts, The Boris Lurie Art Foundation, Dayton Foundation, Mellon Foundation, Native Arts and Cultures Foundation, the New York State Council on the Arts with the support of the Office of the Governor and the New York State Legislature, Terra Foundation for American Art, and The New School, as well as members of the Vera List Center Board, members of our giving circles Vera’s List, the VLC Producers Council, and The New Society, and other individuals.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;hr class="wp-block-separator has-alpha-channel-opacity"&gt;



&lt;figure class="wp-block-image size-full"&gt;&lt;img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" src="http://www.smackmellon.org/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/VLC-logo-1-scaled.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-19891" srcset="https://www.smackmellon.org/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/VLC-logo-1-scaled.jpg 2560w, https://www.smackmellon.org/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/VLC-logo-1-680x97.jpg 680w, https://www.smackmellon.org/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/VLC-logo-1-1500x215.jpg 1500w, https://www.smackmellon.org/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/VLC-logo-1-600x86.jpg 600w, https://www.smackmellon.org/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/VLC-logo-1-768x110.jpg 768w, https://www.smackmellon.org/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/VLC-logo-1-1536x220.jpg 1536w, https://www.smackmellon.org/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/VLC-logo-1-2048x294.jpg 2048w, https://www.smackmellon.org/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/VLC-logo-1-300x43.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 2560px) 100vw, 2560px"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The Vera List Center for Art and Politics is an artist-focused research center and public forum for art, culture, and politics. It was established at The New School in 1992—a time of rousing debates about freedom of speech, identity politics, and society’s investment in the arts. A leader in the field, the center is a nonprofit that catalyzes and supports politically engaged art, public scholarship, and research worldwide. For over thirty years, the VLC has championed the arts as expressions of the political moments from which they emerge and considers the intersection between art and politics the space where new forms of civic engagement must be developed. Through public programs and the VLC Seminars, the Jane Lombard Prize, and artist and student fellowships, publications, and exhibitions that probe some of the pressing issues of our time, the center curates and supports new roles for the arts and artists in advancing social justice. &lt;a href="http://veralistcenter.org"&gt;veralistcenter.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;hr class="wp-block-separator has-alpha-channel-opacity"&gt;



&lt;figure class="wp-block-image size-full"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="http://www.smackmellon.org/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Ex-funders-2024_CA.png" alt="" class="wp-image-19885" srcset="https://www.smackmellon.org/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Ex-funders-2024_CA.png 1080w, https://www.smackmellon.org/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Ex-funders-2024_CA-680x756.png 680w, https://www.smackmellon.org/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Ex-funders-2024_CA-360x400.png 360w, https://www.smackmellon.org/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Ex-funders-2024_CA-768x853.png 768w, https://www.smackmellon.org/wp-content/uploads/2024/12/Ex-funders-2024_CA-300x333.png 300w" sizes="(max-width: 1080px) 100vw, 1080px"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
		
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>&lt;a href="/venues/smack-mellon" hreflang="en"&gt;Smack Mellon&lt;/a&gt;</author><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 13:02:06 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">82629</guid></item><item><title>To trace the line where your body cut the air</title><link>https://www.smackmellon.org/exhibition/to-trace-the-line-where-your-body-cut-the-air/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content center-column simple-links"&gt;
			
&lt;blockquote class="wp-block-quote is-layout-flow wp-block-quote-is-layout-flow"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Please note that the galleries will be closed December 24 through January 1, reopening on January 2, 2025.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Artists: Noor Abed &amp;amp; Mark Lofty, Christopher Gregory-Rivera, Utsa Hazarika, Cici Wu &amp;amp; Yuan Yuan&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Curated in collaboration with Carmen Amengual&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Curated in conjunction with Carmen Amengual’s installation in the adjoining gallery, &lt;em&gt;To trace the line where your body cut the air&lt;/em&gt; explores the ways information can alternatively be recovered or obscured via memory, personal encounters, architecture, and historical record. Across multiple media including found and staged video, photography, text, sound, and sculpture, the artworks on display embody an ethos of collaboration and collective experience, each following distinct threads present in Amengual’s work. The title takes from a line in Carmen Amengual’s film, &lt;em&gt;A Non-Coincidental Mirror,&lt;/em&gt; wherein the artist tried to physically follow in her late mother’s footsteps in order to unearth details of the first Third World Filmmakers Meeting in Algiers.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The connective pathways of migratory diaspora are central to this exhibition, reverberating amidst the backdrop of the current moment’s ongoing wars. As such, these works are limited by their respective repositories, leaning on the roles of various storage media as the vessels for communication. The artists challenge and uncover the inherent loss—and at times forced entropy—of recordkeeping. Their works explore the intersections between official histories in their idealized form and the messy incompleteness of lived experience, all in relation to various increasingly autocratic infrastructures. Through encounters with strangers, state archives, shared video diaries, and scholarship, the resultant language that circulates appears as fragments, tactics, abstraction, poetics, and warnings against patterns of suppression. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Included in this exhibition are excerpts from Christopher Gregory Rivera’s ongoing project &lt;em&gt;Las Carpetas&lt;/em&gt; (2014- ), which reimagines political memory in Puerto Rico by rescuing, photographing, and appropriating archives from a secret police division dedicated to political persecution in the US Territory. He is also showing for the first time raw footage from a leaked police video of protests in 2017, highlighting how the practice of political persecution is not only alive and well but increasingly relevant in understanding the current cultures of digital policing. Noor Abed and Mark Lofty’s &lt;em&gt;One Night Stand&lt;/em&gt; (2019) is an experimental documentary based on a real encounter with an unknown European anti-ISIS fighter that was secretly recorded on a cell phone. Through a re-staged simulation of this conversation, the filmmakers probe questions of ideological loyalties to the concept of freedom, distinctions between citizens and soldiers, and the potentials of representation through the documentary form. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Utsa Hazarika’s installation picks up on the investigation in Amengual’s A Non-Coincidental Mirror that examines the potential for architecture to leave impressions on bodies and on memories. In Twilight, Two Lights (2024), Hazarika appropriates text fragments from postcolonial scholarship, protest chants, news reports, and archival audio from artists and activists from the British Commonwealth and South Asia. These words are refracted through a translucent neon lattice work frame in the form of a disrupted and glitched South Asian jaali–an ornamental patterned architectural screen–as well as available as audio. The combination of the contrasting viewpoints of the text, image, and audio produces a hybrid space where new identities emerge. Departing from the softness of the gesture, Cici Wu’s work uses the techniques and forms of cinema to uncover aspects of archives and microhistories. The film Belonging and Distance is a long-distance collaborative endeavor with Beijing-based queer photographer Yuan Yuan that unfolded from 2022 to 2023. The work weaves together 16mm film fragments with DV video, tracing the indexicality of notions such as “diasporic” and “migratory.” Traversing through scenes from East Broadway Mall in New York’s Chinatown during the pandemic and Beijing in lockdown, family, a memorial site of the June Fourth Incident, Chang’An avenue, Dongdan park, and underground queer parties, the film ends with footage from the cross-harbor tunnel in Hong Kong, which references the siege of Hong Kong Polytechnic University, suggesting a migratory aesthetics as an experimental means of repair. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The contributing artists each speak from different geopolitical contexts and experiences, and yet their work is bound by the implicit solidarity with one another’s histories and continued existence. Together these works gesture towards the stated goals of Amengual’s primary research subject, the first and second Third World Filmmakers Meetings: to share strategies that run counter to top-down hegemonic rule and norms. The methods employed here do not simply offer solutions to these issues, but claim space to document stories and perspectives, attesting to the soft power of witness. The sentiment marks an attempt to capture the intangible–or at least that which modern methods of documentation cannot hold. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;hr class="wp-block-separator has-alpha-channel-opacity"&gt;



&lt;p&gt;This exhibition is part of the &lt;em&gt;Close Readings&lt;/em&gt; exhibition series and is curated in conjunction with Carmen Amengual, &lt;em&gt;A Non-Coincidental Mirror&lt;/em&gt;, co-presented with the Vera List Center for Art and Politics at The New School. &lt;em&gt;Close Readings&lt;/em&gt; presents a new commission by one under-recognized, early, or mid-career artist in Gallery One, along with an accompanying exhibition in Gallery Two that uses the central commission as a curatorial framework. This program extends our support for interdisciplinary artists by building conversations around their practices in addition to facilitating the realization of ambitious, site-specific projects. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;hr class="wp-block-separator has-alpha-channel-opacity"&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bios:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Noor Abed&lt;/strong&gt; is an interdisciplinary artist and filmmaker. Her practice examines notions of choreography and the imaginary relationship of individuals, creating situations for alternative social and representational models in Palestine. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mark Lofty&lt;/strong&gt; is an Alexandrian artist, filmmaker and producer. His work explores the boundaries between fiction, documentary, and new media art, and questions the everyday, contingent and the virtual. He co-founded with his fellows in 2005 the production space ‘Fig Leaf Studios’ with the mission of supporting independent filmmakers and artists in Egypt.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Utsa Hazarika&lt;/strong&gt; is an artist and writer based in New York. Her research-based practice ranges across video, sound, installation, sculpture and text, and explores how an interdisciplinary dialogue between art and social research can push us to think about power, memory and resistance. Her work has been exhibited internationally, including at Socrates Sculpture Park, Hessel Museum of Art, and Museum of the City of New York in the United States. She attended the Whitney Independent Study Program, and has been awarded residencies and fellowships in Asia and the United States, including Pioneer Works (US), Queens Museum (US), and Lijiang Studio (China), and Khoj International Artists’ Association (India). She holds an MFA in Fine Arts from The New School, where she was awarded the President’s Scholarship; and an MPhil in Social Anthropology from the University of Cambridge, where she was awarded Christ College’s Levy-Plumb Award for the Humanities. Her research has been published in Ethnos: Journal of Anthropology (UK), Trans Asia Photography Review (US) and The Caravan (India).&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Christopher Gregory Rivera&lt;/strong&gt; is a Puerto Rican artist living between New York City and Madrid, Spain.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;His work is particularly interested in rescuing, deconstructing and reconfiguring historic narratives through documentary, still life and archival research to promote a better understanding of the present.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;His work has been awarded by PhotoEspaña, Aperture/Paris Photo Book Prize, Rencontres Arles, the Magnum Foundation and exhibited at the Museum of Contemporary Art in Puerto Rico, Museum of Contemporary Photography in Chicago, Institute of Contemporary Art of Maine and the Abrons Arts Center in New York.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cici Wu&lt;/strong&gt; was born and raised in Beijing and Hong Kong, and currently lives and works in New York. Reducing filmmaking to its most humble and elemental components, she creates drawings, objects, videos, and installations which extend the imaginative and structural premises of cinematic language across a wide range of media. Often taking local microhistories or archives as a point of departure, Wu uses the cinematic frame as a means to negotiate and reflect on the ways in which transpersonal narratives of social, cultural and historical belonging structure our experiences of self.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Yuan Yuan&lt;/strong&gt;, formerly based in Beijing, currently living and studying in the Netherlands. With a background in literature and language, writing serves as the foundation of their artistic practice, often evolving with their image practice parallel. Their works explore the intersection of the collective unconscious and the cosmos, delving into themes of belonging and displacement, with an ongoing focus on minority groups.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;hr class="wp-block-separator has-alpha-channel-opacity"&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Image: Christopher Gregory Rivera, excerpt from &lt;em&gt;Las Carpetas&lt;/em&gt; (2014- ). Courtesy the Archivo General de Puerto Rico, San Juan.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;hr class="wp-block-separator has-alpha-channel-opacity"&gt;



&lt;p&gt;This exhibition is supported, in part, by public funds from the New York City Department of Cultural Affairs in partnership with the City Council, New York City Council Member Lincoln Restler, and the New York State Council on the Arts with the support of Governor Kathy Hochul and the New York State Legislature, and with generous support from The Andy Warhol Foundation for the Visual Arts, Robert Lehman Foundation, Select Equity Group Foundation, many individuals and Smack Mellon’s Members. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Smack Mellon’s programs are also made possible with public funds from the National Endowment for the Arts and with generous support from The Edward and Sally Van Lier Fund of The New York Community Trust, Jerome Foundation, Ruth Foundation for the Arts, Lily Auchincloss Foundation, Wolf Kahn Foundation, Cornelia T. Bailey Foundation, Milton and Sally Avery Arts Foundation Inc, The Roy and Niuta Titus Foundation, and an Anonymous Donor.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;In-kind donations and services are provided by Materials for the Arts, NYC Department of Cultural Affairs/NYC Department of Sanitation/NYC Department of Education and Sage and Coombe Architects. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Space for Smack Mellon’s programs is generously provided by the Walentas family and Two Trees Management.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;figure class="wp-block-image size-full"&gt;&lt;img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" src="http://www.smackmellon.org/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/Ex-funders-2024.png" alt="" class="wp-image-19483" srcset="https://www.smackmellon.org/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/Ex-funders-2024.png 1080w, https://www.smackmellon.org/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/Ex-funders-2024-680x756.png 680w, https://www.smackmellon.org/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/Ex-funders-2024-360x400.png 360w, https://www.smackmellon.org/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/Ex-funders-2024-768x853.png 768w, https://www.smackmellon.org/wp-content/uploads/2024/05/Ex-funders-2024-300x333.png 300w" sizes="(max-width: 1080px) 100vw, 1080px"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
		
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>&lt;a href="/venues/smack-mellon" hreflang="en"&gt;Smack Mellon&lt;/a&gt;</author><pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 13:02:06 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">82630</guid></item></channel></rss>